Fixed & Synced by bozxphd.Enjoy The Flick
Michelle,
please don't hang up.
Just talk to me, okay? I
can't believe you just left.
Michelle.
Come back.
Please say something.
Michelle, talk to me.
Look, we had an argument.
Couples fight.
That is no reason to just
leave everything behind.
Running away isn't gonna help it any.
Michelle, please...
More details on that.
Elsewhere today, power has
still not been restored
to many cities on
the Southern seaboard
in the wake of this afternoon's
widespread blackout.
While there had been some
inclement weather in the region,
the problem seems linked to
what authorities are calling
a catastrophic power surge that
has crippled traffic in the area.
No.
No!
Damn.
Okay. Okay, please.
Please.
Please don't hurt me.
Just let me go, okay?
I won't tell anybody.
I promise, okay? Please
just let me go. Please.
You need fluids.
You were in shock.
What are you going
to do to me?
I'm going to
keep you alive.
Work on getting handy
with these.
My boyfriend
was expecting me.
He'll send the cops looking.
I'm sorry.
But no one is looking
for you.
You've got some fight in you.
I can respect that.
But don't even think
about trying that again.
You're lucky
to be here at all.
And my generosity
only extends so far.
Eggs.
Toradol to help
with your pain.
Please.
Please, just let me go.
There is nowhere
to go, Michelle.
I looked through your wallet.
Given as how i saved your life,
i think that's acceptable.
You're lucky
to be here at all.
What do you mean?
I found you, and I saved your
life by bringing you here.
I don't understand. I...
There's been an attack.
What?
An attack. A big one.
I'm not sure yet
if it's chemical or nuclear,
but down here,
we're safe.
And where are we exactly?
Underneath my farmhouse.
Forty miles outside
of lake Charles.
I was driving north of here.
You were in an accident.
You were turned over
on the side of the road.
I was driving by
and I saw...
I saved your life,
Michelle.
I couldn't just
leave you there.
Okay.
Well,
thank you so much
for saving my life.
I guess I should go
to a hospital now.
You can't leave.
An attack means fallout.
Which contaminates
the air above ground.
That's how it works.
How long do we have to wait
until it's safe?
Depends on the proximity
of the closest blast.
One year, maybe two.
And that's if we're talking
about weapons that we know of.
Russians are developing
some nasty stuff.
And if the martians finally
figured out a way to get here,
their weapons will make the russkies'
look like sticks and stones.
Luckily,
I've prepared for this.
Right.
Well, I'll need to use
your phone then
to call my family and tell
them that I'm safe here
and make sure they're okay.
Michelle, they're not okay.
How do you know that?
Everyone outside of here
is dead.
But what about you?
Don't you have a family?
Who's that?
Excuse me.
What did you do?
You know what, Michelle? I'm
gonna tell you what I told him.
You need to eat,
you need to sleep,
and you need to start showing me
a little bit of appreciation.
My name is Howard,
by the way.
Oh, god! Oh, shit.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about that.
Uh, I didn't mean to
scare you.
Are you, um...
Here. You hungry?
So, how are you doing?
You okay?
What is this?
It's a bunker.
Your room's a little bit of a
fixer-upper, but at least you got a door.
A scary door,
but you still got a door.
How long have you
been down here?
Couple of days, I think.
You know, it's actually
kind of hard to tell
with no windows or
sunlight or anything.
I mean,
how do we get out of here?
Oh, he didn't tell you?
About...
Getting out of here is the
last thing you want to do.
Because the air up there,
it's contaminated.
I see
you've met Emmett.
What happened to him?
He did that to himself.
And his stumbling around
isn't helping anything.
What you heard earlier,
was him knocking over a shelf with
a whole week's worth of food,
which he's sorry for,
correct?
Totally.
Let's go. Bathroom time.
This is
the common area.
Good for r & r.
As you can see, I've
planned for a long stay.
The aquaponics system cleans
the air and keeps it fresh.
This is the living room.
Help yourself to any reading.
If you like to watch films, i have
some on DVD and vhs cassette.
Just make sure you put them back
in their sleeve when they're done.
The kitchen's
fully functional.
Has an electric stove,
refrigerator, freezer, silverware.
And that table's
a family heirloom,
which means
watch your glasses.
Always use coasters
and placemats.
Keep your hands
to yourself!
Understand?
No touching.
Take a seat.
This way.
This is my private space.
Off-limits, unless
i give express permission.
Go ahead.
I don't need to.
You will, though.
And I've got to pace these
things out, so please.
I need privacy.
You're welcome
to close the curtain.
I can't with you
standing there.
And I can't trust you
not to burn this place down.
This is for my own safety.
I'm not some pervert!
Just go.
Don't flush
unless you've gone!
We can't afford
wasted flushes.
Take a seat.
Are you hungry?
Those are Megan's.
She never went anywhere without
two or three of those things.
Who's Megan?
Megan's not with us anymore.
Don't worry.
Just the generator.
Maybe it's a car outside.
That's not possible.
I heard one earlier.
Above my room.
If you had heard a car, the
driver would be long dead by now.
Well, shouldn't we
at least try
to call the police or someone to
find out what actually happened?
There's no one left to call.
See that?
Nothing's coming through.
You think I sound crazy.
I mean, it's amazing.
You people...
You wear helmets
when you ride your bikes.
You have seat belts
in your cars.
You have alarm systems
to protect your homes.
But what do you do
when those alarms go off?
"Crazy" is building your ark after
the flood has already come!
I think maybe it's time
you met frank and Mildred.
Closest I could get
to an airlock.
See?
What happened to them?
They weren't
as lucky as you.
It's the air, Michelle.
That's what happens
when you get exposed.
I keep this door sealed
at all times.
No one comes in or out.
Met frank
and Mildred, huh?
It's funny, right?
The whole world ends
and the thing he's most upset
about is a pair of dead pigs?
You in need of some
reading material?
I took all the quizzes.
Sorry.
But I did learn
how to do a French braid, so,
you know, if you want me to do
that for you, just let me know.
What do you know about him?
He was in the Navy,
i know that.
I guess he did, uh,
some stuff with satellites.
What kind of stuff?
Satellite stuff.
Well, what brought him
out here?
I'm not sure.
He bought this property
a while back.
But I never paid
much attention
till he hired me to help him
get this place set up.
The work was entertaining,
though, that's for sure.
You know, Howard's like a black
belt in conspiracy theory.
Plus, you know, how often do
you get hired to help build
a doomsday bunker?
So, he didn't
kidnap you?
No!
What about your arm?
Weren't you trying to escape?
I was trying to get in.
I watched Howard build this
place, piece by piece, for years.
He was always talking about,
you know,
possible attacks from
al qaeda, Russia,
south Korea.
You mean north Korea.
Is that the crazy one?
So, yeah, that one.
And, uh, you know, poured all
his money into this place.
Took to it like his life
depended on it.
Which, you know,
that stays with you.
So...
He told you all this
while you're building
his bomb shelter.
And now he says that
the air is contaminated
and everybody's dead.
Yeah, I know what you're getting
at, but there's more to it.
Howard abducted me.
He drove me off the road
and he dragged me here.
So, whatever he's telling you
about the air, some big attack,
the purpose of this shelter,
is a lie.
No. No way.
The attack,
i saw it myself.
What do you mean?
I was on my way
home from work.
And it looked like a flash.
Bright red.
Like an explosion,
from way far off.
It wasn't like fireworks.
Naw, this was more like something
you'd read about in the Bible.
So, what, you saw, what,
a flash of light? Lightning?
A fire that flared up?
I'm not explaining it right.
This wasn't like anything
I'd ever seen.
And so, my first thought
was to come here.
And when I got here,
Howard was closing the door.
And I could see it,
right there on his face,
he knew something
was happening.
Something bad.
And so, I fought my way in.
I heard a car.
Right here. Above us.
You heard someone?
Right above us.
That isn't possible.
The air is...
What, contaminated?
How do you know that?
Because I told him.
Dinner's ready.
I see you two
are getting along.
Hmm.
How's that sauce?
It's fine.
As cooks go, I'm okay.
Not great, but okay.
Megan was a good cook.
You'll learn to love cooking.
Mmm...
Mmm.
It's delicious.
That's the best sauce
I've ever tasted.
Are you being funny?
No, I mean,
considering the alternative,
which is, you know,
getting burnt up in a
chemical attack, or nuclear,
I'd say being alive
and down here would
make a fried turd taste
pretty good, so...
Best damn sauce I ever had.
That's not a bad point.
And, please,
watch your language at table.
Right?
You know what I haven't been able to
get out of my head, for some reason?
Ever since
i got down here.
Tattoos.
Always wanted one.
But I never got any.
'Cause everybody always said,
"no, no, Emmett, you'll never get
a decent job if you do that."
Whatever.
Like that matters now,
right?
Tell you what, if I had
known this was coming,
I would've gotten, like,
50 of them. I swear, man.
I would look like a circus
freak, or something.
I'd just be covered
head to toe.
Tattoos all over my...
You know, everywhere. Face?
Sure. Right there.
Across my forehead.
Just my name. "Emmett."
Or, you know,
"thug life."
"Yolo."
I don't even know
what that means,
but, you know, I hear people
saying it all the time,
so, it must be cool.
Hey, what about you,
Howard?
Anything you wish
you'd done?
In all honesty, no.
No?
No crazy nights in Vegas?
Maybe, uh,
take a pilgrimage to waco?
Everything I wanted to do,
i did.
I focused on being prepared.
And I was.
And here we are.
Oh, my goodness.
Is that monopoly?
There we go!
Yeah, that's how
we kill the time.
What would you say, Howard,
we're gonna be down here,
what, like, a year?
Two? Maybe?
I bet you if we started
a game right now,
we might even get halfway
finished by the time...
Stop talking!
You don't need to make jokes about
how long we're going to be down here
when nobody knows
how long that's going to be.
Your humor is not funny.
I don't appreciate it
while I'm trying to eat,
and neither does Michelle.
Now, please shut up
and let us eat in peace.
Hmm.
Emmett?
Would you pass me a napkin?
Thank you.
I know what you're saying.
I never could finish monopoly.
That game really
does take forever, right?
For me, though,
it was, um...
Chutes and ladders,
uh...
Sorry!,
and trouble.
You know, the thing with the dice
and the thing that you pressed,
what was that called?
The...
Pop-o-matic bubble! Yeah.
Did you ever play that, um...
What was that, operation?
Loved operation!
I'm telling you, man,
I couldn't play that game.
It terrified me.
Why...
That noise that thing would make
when you hit that edge. I mean...
Good lord!
It was pretty scary.
Could you hand me the salt?
Please?
Ah, shoot! I'm sorry.
I'm gonna need
the pepper also.
What exactly do you think
you're doing?
I'm asking for pepper.
Like hell you were!
What was that?
I don't know what you're
talking about, Howard.
Are you trying to insult me?
Here, in the shelter that I
built that's keeping you alive?
You don't think I see
what you just did?
Is that how you thank me
for saving your life?
Howard, calm down.
Shut up!
Shut up and
stay in your seat!
Is it?
Now, let me tell you,
I know what a traitor
looks like.
Understand?
I have shown you nothing, but
generosity and hospitality.
I want you to apologize.
To tell me
you're going to behave.
I will.
You will what?
I'll behave.
And I'm so sorry.
Sit.
Ah...
Have to stay hydrated.
Hmm.
That's easy to forget
down here.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Where are my keys?
Michelle!
Michelle! Stop!
Give me those keys!
Come on.
No! Don't!
Stop!
No! No, don't! Don't!
Don't open that door!
There's a car!
There's a car! I see a car! No!
Here! Here! Here!
Michelle,
listen to me, don't do this!
Oh, god! Thank god!
- There's a woman.
- Open the door!
It's okay.
I just want to come inside.
She looks hurt.
She wants me to let her in.
Do not let her in!
Look at her face, Michelle!
No!
No, no, no!
Oh, my god, I'm fine.
I really am fine.
No, please, I'm okay.
There's...
It really only... It only
touched me a little. A little!
So, could you
open the door? Open it!
She's begging me.
You can't help her!
No one can!
Let me in. I'll be okay.
I'll be okay. It really
hardly touched me at all.
- Open the door!
- Don't listen to her!
God! Open the door,
you bitch!
Let me in!
Let me in! Let me in!
You!
You! You! You!
I know it's hard,
realizing they're all gone.
The ones you love.
I have something
to confess to you.
I crashed into your car.
Your accident
was my fault.
When I found out about
the incoming attack,
I got frantic.
I knew I needed to get back
here as soon as possible,
so I was driving
like a maniac.
I tried to pass you,
and
I'm the reason
you went off the road.
I mean, I know I seem
like a sensible guy,
but at the time,
i wasn't myself.
It was an accident,
but it was my fault.
I was afraid to tell you,
and,
I'm sorry.
Um...
You should shower.
Even the smallest
amount of air
that came through the hinges
could be toxic.
These were Megan's.
If you want.
I recognized
that woman's car.
Her name was Leslie,
i think.
You knew her?
She was a neighbor.
Emmett wasn't the only one
who knew about this place.
If any others somehow survived,
they could be coming here, too.
As of Friday, kindness and
generosity are antiquated customs.
I'm going to need
some stitches.
What? You want me to...
This is your doing,
isn't it?
I mean, I don't think
I'm really qualified.
I'll walk you through it.
Here.
Have a drink.
What is it?
Technically, it's vodka.
Ah! It's safe.
I distilled it myself.
I just said I distilled it,
I didn't say anything about it
actually tasting good.
Yeah, that's awful.
You want it on the rocks?
Little trick I taught myself
as a young man
stationed on a ship
with way too much free time.
Every now and again, if the C.O.
was working us too hard,
we'd freeze and snap
the knob off
the bathroom door
while he was still inside.
It usually took him an hour
or two to get out.
I'm good.
Suit yourself. Cheers.
Ah...
This is clean.
All you need to do
is stitch.
You're doing fine.
Some stuff
i grabbed from your car.
I didn't have time
to bring in the booze. Sadly.
What is all that?
I wanted to design clothes.
No wonder you were so good
with the stitches.
Megan wanted
to be an artist.
She was your daughter?
Yes.
She was smart.
Loved to read. The magazines
were just for fun.
She inhaled books.
Anything with Paris.
She liked their movies,
their culture, you know.
We used to
have this little joke.
Every once in a while
I'd ask her,
"what do you want to be
when you grow up?"
You know what she'd say?
"French."
Anyway, her mother
turned her against me.
Took her off to Chicago.
People are strange creatures.
You can't always convince them that
safety is in their own best interest.
You don't know they're gone.
Anyway, at least
i tried to help them.
Hey.
There was nothing you
could've done for that woman.
Even if you let her in,
she still would've died.
You asked earlier
about regrets?
Yeah, I've got
some of those.
Welcome to the club.
I mean, I lived my life
in a 40-mile radius.
And that was by design.
I made sure that happened.
I was so fast
in high school,
I even managed to outrun
my bad grades.
I was all-state track
three years in a row.
Caught a full ride to Louisiana
tech, up there in ruston.
I remember I spent the last
two weeks of that summer
showing off the bus ticket they sent
me to anybody who'd take a look at it.
And then came the night before
i was supposed to leave.
And I just got so worried
about how bad I was
gonna do up there
with all those smart kids.
So, I went out of my way
to get just piss-wasted
so bad
that I knew there was no chance
I was waking up in the morning.
So, I missed the bus.
And I didn't buy a ticket
for the next one.
Or the one after that.
Well, if you'd gone,
you might be dead now.
Yeah,
lucky me, right?
Lucky us.
A few years ago,
I was at a hardware store.
And there was this little girl
with her dad.
And he was in a hurry,
and she wasn't keeping up.
So, he kept
yanking on her arm.
But really hard, you know?
Too hard.
I know that feeling.
When my dad got that way,
my brother Colin was always
there to take the worst of it
for me.
And I thought,
seeing this little girl,
I thought maybe
i could do that
for her.
But I just kept watching.
And they're about to leave,
and I've done nothing.
And she slips.
And it throws him off-balance,
and he hits her.
And I wanted so badly
to do something
to help her, but...
I did what I always do
when things get hard.
I just panicked and ran.
Look, we're here.
We're alive.
And that means something.
It's gotta.
You've got to be kidding me.
What?
We're missing pieces here.
Look at this poor cat. He's been deformed.
He's got one eye.
He's about to go snorkeling
and everything, too.
What are you doing?
Ooh!
Cornering the market on
post-apocalyptic fashion, huh?
Mmm-hmm.
You need more
axes and chain saws.
For what?
She has a shotgun.
Yeah. But what if
up there it's like...
What? Lumberjacks?
Zombies.
Though even Howard doesn't
think that one's plausible.
But you should hear his theory
about mutant space worms.
What is that? Howard!
Stay calm. We're okay.
What was that?
Quiet.
That sounds like
helicopters.
Could be military.
But not ours.
How can you tell?
Fourteen years in the Navy.
What's happening up there?
My guess?
Those flashes that
kicked this all off?
That was phase one.
Take out your opponent's
population centers
with big hits,
all at once, fast.
And then for round two,
ground sweeps.
A satellite log showed an increase
in coded traffic recently.
Possibly
extraterrestrial signals.
I bet what we just heard
were airborne patrols
sent to hunt down
the remaining signs of life.
Like us.
Okay. Oh, boy.
That's bad.
And that's worse.
What's up there?
Air filtration system.
I can't...
Something blocking
the hatch.
If we can't get it back on, we're
gonna run out of breathable air fast.
You're the only one
small enough to reach it.
Reach what?
The filtration system. Through
there, the main duct.
Someone needs to get in there
and restart it.
Give me a hand.
Let me go. She's not gonna
know her way around the unit.
You won't fit. Plus your arm.
She'll be fine.
Now, to restart the unit,
you just swing the handle off,
then on, off, then on.
That should do it.
And neither of us will be able to go
in and help you if you get stuck.
Don't get stuck.
Michelle!
Everything okay up there?
It looks like a dead end.
That's the incline.
Climb up that and
you're almost there.
Ah, this sucks.
What's wrong?
Howard.
He lied,
he lied about Megan.
What do you mean?
I think he did
something horrible to her.
No, his family moved
to Chicago years ago.
What's this?
Is that blood?
Here, come with me.
Wait, that...
That's not Megan.
What do you mean?
Yeah. Her name is Brittany.
I remember her.
She went to high school
with my little sister.
She...
She went missing.
Two years back.
It was on the news
and everything.
Most people just thought
she skipped town.
There was a message
up there.
It said "help."
It was scratched
on the inside of the window.
And this earring...
This earring was with it.
Did she ever show back up
after she went missing?
He said to me... He said to my
face, that this was his daughter.
He said this was Megan.
He took her
and he killed her.
All right,
let's just think.
Maybe we take away
his gun.
Tie him up, get him to confess
to whatever it is he's done.
Confess to who?
The police?
Look, like I said, we can't
be the only survivors, right?
The woman, she was able
to get around, right?
At least a little.
Yeah, until she died.
Directly above us,
making choking noises.
Of all the people
to save us...
Now, that was
a great example of teamwork.
Very well done.
I feel like some music.
Problem solving always
puts me in a musical mood.
Michelle,
you should go shower,
just in case.
Sure.
I think I might
have an idea.
"Ten better ways
to style my bangs"?
No, not the article. This.
I think I can only make
one, but it's a start.
No kidding.
What are you doing up?
I didn't wake you up yet.
Well, I'm fixing
your breakfast.
One egg over medium.
Hey, Howard.
What is this? You re-watching
sixteen candles?
Pretty in pink.
It was one of Megan's favorite movies.
Can I help you with something?
No.
No, I'm just
grabbing some water.
Say, um...
You know, I was
just thinking...
Not that I'm trying to tell you how
to run this place or anything.
I'm just a little curious.
Michelle...
Say, how close do you think she
got to that air filtration unit?
You think she touched it?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
she touched it.
Well, I know she cleaned up
after and everything,
but I'm just thinking,
given that unit filters god knows
what through from outside,
if she tracked anything back in with
her, it'd be pretty concentrated.
And, I mean, it could be all
over the shower and the sink
in your bathroom,
right now.
Anyway, it's just a thought.
Not bad so far,
partner.
If Howard finds this,
he's gonna kill us.
All right, so, we get
the gun away from him.
All right. We tie him up, make
sure he isn't going anywhere.
And then one of us just
goes out and looks for help.
Um...
First word.
Uh...
Tiny.
Small. Pygmy. Um...
Little.
Yep! Mmm-hmm.
All right, uh,
second word.
Ooh! Michelle is a...
A girl.
A girl. A child. Um...
No, she's older,
see, so she is a...
"Little Princess"?
Um... no, it was woman.
Um, little women.
Wow. Little woman.
Next time, try being
a little more specific.
Let's see here.
I'm always watching.
Always.
Um...
God.
I go wherever I want.
Uh...
I mean...
Well, I don't know.
I know what you're doing.
I see what you're doing.
Um...
I know what you're up to.
Look, Howard, I don't know
what you're getting at, but...
I see you
when you're sleeping.
I know what you're doing,
and I'm always watching.
Always watching!
I'm always watching!
Santa claus!
You're Santa claus.
Yeah, Michelle,
that's great.
Except it was
Emmett's turn.
Sorry, I just got
a little excited.
Yeah, well,
I'm keeping that point.
Totally. You earned it.
Emmett?
Hey.
I need your help
with something.
Sure.
You.
On deck.
What is this?
The barrel.
What's in it?
Move it into the bathroom.
This is
perchloric acid.
Do either of you know
what that is?
It's usually produced as a
precursor to ammonium perchlorate,
a fuel
used for launching
naval satellites into orbit.
It's highly corrosive.
Dissolves most biological
material on contact.
With humans,
right down to the bone.
Hey, Howard, uh, what are
you showing this to us for?
You think I'm an idiot?
Uh...
Howard, please,
you're gonna have to tell us
what it is that
you're talking about.
I'm talking about
getting rid of some waste.
Tell me what you two
were doing with these.
You tell me what you two
were planning, right now!
Howard, listen, just take it easy.
Take it easy.
Howard, come on, please.
No. I'm giving you
one chance.
Hey.
Howard, just calm down.
One chance to answer with some
dignity, or I swear to god,
you're going into this barrel
while you're alive to feel it.
It was me.
All right? Not her.
It's just me.
No, no, no, we... Stay
out of this, all right?
She doesn't have a clue
what you're talking about.
I wanted your gun.
And so, I was thinking
about making a weapon
to get it from you.
I want her to respect me
the way that she respects you.
I'm not saying
that I was right, okay?
And I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
I'm sorry.
I accept your apology.
Listen to me. You heard him.
You heard him.
He was making a weapon.
He was gonna hurt us.
He was gonna hurt you.
And it's okay.
This was the way it was
always supposed to be.
You're safe.
Now it's just you and me.
It's okay, you know.
You should
go to your room now.
This next part isn't something
you need to see.
Okay.
Go on.
Michelle?
Hey.
I thought we'd change
things up tonight
and have dessert
before dinner.
After all, we can do
whatever we want now.
Would you like a cone
or a bowl?
Megan always wanted
hers in a bowl.
She said the cones
were too messy.
I know that this isn't
the life you'd prefer,
that it isn't easy for you
living down here,
but I want us
to be a happy family.
You and me.
The mess is
all taken care of.
So, just hang loose and
I'll go get dinner started.
Michelle?
Everything all right?
Yeah, I was just about
to do some reading.
Hmm.
It's time to set the table.
Supper's ready.
Yeah.
Okay.
It keeps doing that.
I don't know why.
Michelle, why is this loose?
Get up.
Why?
Get off the mattress now!
Oh, shit!
Michelle!
Stop! Goddamn it,
get back here!
You gonna
walk out on me?
After I saved you and kept you
safe, this is how you repay me.
No.
This is.
Michelle!
Stop!
You don't know
what's out there.
You can't run from them!
Stay with me!
Let me go!
Oh, come on.
Keys, keys, keys.
Come on, damn it!
Come on. Come on.
Help! I'm out here! Help!
Oh, god.
Oh, fuck.
The military has taken back
the Southern seaboard.
If you are hearing this
and aren't in a safe zone,
head north of Baton Rouge.
But if you have any medical
training or combat experience,
we need help.
There are people
in Houston.
There are survivors
at mercy hospital.
Please help.
Repeat. There are people in
Houston who need our help.
Come join us.
We've taken back
the Southern seaboard.
And we're winning.
But if you have any medical
training or combat experience,
there are survivors...