HAPPINESS
I'M LONELY.
MOOK
MISS PINN, A CRIPPLINGLY LONELY GIRL
IN NEED OF A MAN. AN UGLY FACE
IS ALL RIGHT IF YOU'RE RICH.
MOOK, YOU WEIRDO OF A FRIEND.
I HOPE YOU GET DUMPED IN CHIANG RAI.
MY MISERY WOULD LOVE SOME COMPANY.
WATCH YOUR MOUTH, PINN.
I'LL BITCHSLAP YOU.
AND BEWARE OF THAT HAG COMING
FOR THE RENT. FROM MOOK.
SHE WAS BANGING ON MY DOOR.
ENJOY YOUR TRIP ON MY BEHALF.
FINDING JOBS ONLINE
ACCOUNTANT
I'D LIKE TO KNOW YOU. FROM +66870447331
SO MEAN, I JUST WANTED TO TALK.
DO WE KNOW EACH OTHER?
NO, BUT WE'RE GETTING THERE.
ARE YOU A MALE OR FEMALE?
MALE.
CALLING
The number you have dialed
is not available at this moment.
Please try again.
HI.
NO NEW MESSAGES
HI, WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
JUST ENJOYING THE VIEW. YOU?
JUST LYING DOWN. I'M SO LONELY.
DO YOU HAVE AN EMAIL ADDRESS FOR MSN?
I DON'T HAVE A COMPUTER.
I HAVE A REALLY SMALL SPACE.
PITY. IF YOU GET BORED WITH TEXTING,
I'LL MISS OUT ON TALKING TO YOU.
I CAN TALK TO YOU ALL NIGHT.
YOU WON'T BORE ME. YOU?
ME TOO. I'VE BEEN SHUT IN.
HAVEN'T TALKED TO ANYONE FOR SO LONG.
ME NEITHER. I'VE BEEN ALONE
FOR 100 DAYS NOW.
ARE YOU ILL?
WORST OF LUCK. MY TAXI FLIPPED OVER,
ALMOST KILLING ME.
I'VE BEEN IN A CAST FOR OVER THREE
MONTHS NOW.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD ABOUT SILVER LININGS
AFTER A STORM?
ARE YOU ASLEEP?
NO, I'M NOT SLEEPY YET.
CAN I ASK FOR A PHOTO?
LET'S EXCHANGE. MY PHOTO FOR YOURS. DEAL?
DEAL. YOURS FIRST.
I'M PROBABLY NOT AS PRETTY AS YOU'D HOPED.
PROBABLY NOT AS HOT AS YOU EXPECTED.
NO CHEATING. THAT'S THE PHOTO I SENT.
LOOK CLOSER. I'M IN THE PHOTO WITH YOU.
SEARCH FOR PHONE NUMBER
CALLING
The number you have dialed
is not available at this moment.
I WENT TO A 100TH DAY MEMORIAL SERVICE.
THE DECEASED KILLED HIMSELF.
THEY PUT THEIR SON'S CELL PHONE IN
HIS COFFIN
IN CASE HE EVER GETS LONELY
OR WANTS TO COMMUNICATE.
I'VE BEEN ALONE FOR 100 DAYS NOW.
ARE YOU ILL?
WHAT ARE YOU SO AFRAID OF?
DON'T TURN OFF THE PHONE,
I DON'T LIKE THAT.
I'LL BE PASSING BY WHERE YOU LIVE.
CAN I COME AND SEE YOU?
NO, MY BOYFRIEND WON'T LIKE THAT.
YOU'RE ALONE. I'M WATCHING YOU.
I'M OUTSIDE THE BUILDING.
I'M HEADING UPSTAIRS.
I'M IN YOUR ROOM NOW.
AO: LET'S JUST SPLIT UP.
I'M SEEING SOMEONE ELSE.
Hey, Undertaker.
Aren't you going to say hi, huh?
Diew, I said it before,
just give me this once.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
-Start the car.
-Ngid, get the fuck over here.
-Not so fast.
You've gone too far.
Huh? What did you say?
Don't you think what you did was too much?
What was too much? What do you mean?
What you did--
Please...
don't hurt me.
I...
I have to go...
I have to go see my dad at the hospital.
See your fucking dad?
You think you're so fucking cool
now that you got us expelled?
I really didn't know.
I...
I just wanted my notebook back.
Fucking prick.
You got the guts to make excuses?
Opening people's bags without permission,
that's stealing.
You wanted your notebook,
you could've just taken it.
You didn't have to go to the teacher
because you saw the fucking weed.
But I really didn't know...
there was a teacher behind me.
Oh, yeah, right.
You didn't fucking know.
Enough. Please. Enough.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
I think it's best
you go drop out tomorrow.
And don't ever show up
with your rotten face again.
Do you understand?
Hey, Undertaker.
You're fucking trash.
Do you know what they do with trash?
Undertaker.
They either bury it or burn it.
But the likes of you,
should just be burned.
Hey.
Disappear.
Transfer schools if you like.
If you don't want to be burned alive,
don't ever show your face again.
Do you hear me?
Hey.
Get up. Take a look at your bike.
What a shame.
There goes your bike. Go and get it.
How about we just let him fall for real?
Dude, he could actually fucking fall.
If he does, he'll be mashed to shit.
Hey.
Shit.
Fuck, that was close.
Fuck.
TIT FOR TAT
Don't hold your breath,
because I have the nine.
I'm on fire.
My hand sucks.
You want my shirt, too?
-Your shirt?
-Just take it.
Keep your shirt on. Calm down.
Did you mark the cards?
If I didn't, I wouldn't have won.
Hey, what the fuck's this?
Oh, that's the Joker.
I forgot to take it out. Sorry.
Diew.
If anything happens to Ngid,
I hope your dad can save our asses.
Hell, Pink.
Watch your fucking mouth.
I think he's just fine.
He's probably dropped out by now.
You guys, too.
Go easy on the weed.
My dad already chewed me out.
If Ngid didn't find it,
we wouldn't be in such a hot mess.
It'd be great if he fucking died.
Speaking of him,
I saw his bike parked here yesterday.
Yesterday afternoon,
I was just going home...
...and his bike was here.
But I didn't see where he was.
Fucking shit.
What's your fucking problem, Undertaker?
You want to fucking go?
You didn't have enough last time, huh?
Enough.
He could actually die.
Stay out of this, Pink.
Scum like you...
should all just die.
Yo, don't get up.
Yo.
What the fuck are you laughing at?
-No.
-Yo.
Not me. No. Get out!
Fuck, get out!
Not me. Fuck, not me!
-What?
-What happened?
It's a person!
-Diew, what do we do?
-What should we do?
-Diew, what do we do.
-Diew.
-Get out of here. Come on, go.
Let's go, hurry up.
Leave the stuff. Just run. Go.
Get in your class.
What the fuck do we do?
-Go.
-We have to get to the hospital.
-Start the car.
-Which one is the closest?
-There's a clinic under my flat.
-Yo.
That one's the closest.
-Let's go.
-Okay, let's go.
Yo.
-This one?
-Yo.
-No, the next street.
-Here, turn here.
-Yo.
Okay.
No. Yo.
Yo.
-She's dead.
-Toot, get down. Quick.
-Yo.
-Get out of the car.
Yo!
What do I even tell her parents?
I think we should go to the police.
There's a fucking body down there.
That body was your friend.
-What the fuck...
-If it gets...
What the fuck just happened?
I think something's not right.
Did you see Yoghurt's face
when she read the book?
And then...
Ngid's shock just before he fell down.
I have something to tell you...
I saw...
What did you see?
I saw him doing it.
What did he do?
What if someone sees us?
Good, spice things up.
What if it's a teacher?
Good, that's even more exciting.
Hey, whose voice is that? Listen.
You can keep listening.
Stop. Listen.
Who's chanting what in here?
Let's just stop, Ball.
I'm not in the mood anymore.
Who the fuck?
Whoever looks you in the eye,
take them all.
Don't tell me that...
Ngid is into black magic?
Could it be that
he was trying to get back at us?
His father's an undertaker.
So it's not that far-fetched.
Maybe it was...
It was what, Ace?
A death sigil.
You take a picture of someone
who dies with their eyes open,
and perform a cursing ritual.
Whoever looks the dead in the eye is...
doomed to die on the spot.
I remember there was something
written on it, like...
What the fuck is this?
"I see you now", or something.
"I see you now"?
What the fuck are you looking at?
Fuck.
Shit!
Watch out.
I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry.
So this is what you call
being burned alive.
All right.
I mean, what you told us, I find it...
hard to believe.
Okay?
You're saying your friends died
because of this book?
Anyway, my men
called your parents for you.
They should be here soon.
You just sit tight in here.
Don't go anywhere.
Okay? We'll be right back.
Oh.
And...
do you want something to eat?
Hey.
Pink.
Look up here.
We're a gang, aren't we?
Right.
We're friends, aren't we, Pink?
Pink, we're waiting for you.
Don't leave us, Pink.
Hold out your hand, Pink.
Come with us.
Don't you like me anymore?
It's your turn now.
No.
I have nothing to do with this.
A death sigil.
You take a picture of someone who dies
with their eyes open, and perform a curse.
I've never done anything to you.
I had no part in it.
No.
You just stood there and watched.
And right now,
this is what I want you to see.
No.
Look at it.
I won't look.
I never did anything to you.
I had nothing to do with it.
You'll never get out unscathed!
Just look!
You'll die anyway!
Die here and end it all!
Look!
Calling all units,
an officer was shot in the toilet.
We need immediate backup.
Stop him, get in front of him, now.
Careful, he's armed.
Young lady, stay in here, don't be...
You don't have to worry about me.
He can't touch me now.
You can never take me.
I SEE YOU NOW
Hey, are you guys asleep?
What the fuck is it now?
Have you heard the story about
why you shouldn't sleep outside
when you're staying in the woods?
Why?
Tia told me a story once.
He went into the woods,
and fell asleep outside.
Late that night,
he heard footsteps, like someone
was walking towards them.
Crunch.
Then he felt there was someone
scratching his leg.
So he jolted up.
What he saw was...
a woman.
A female ghost?
Sitting at his feet.
Was she pretty?
She was, but more in a way that...
Fuck, no.
I haven't finished.
Don't drag me off topic.
I don't know.
He told me only that
it was a woman with long hair
covering her face,
and she was pale.
-Sitting at his feet.
-And...
what did he do next?
Well, what could he have done?
He squeezed his eyes shut
and waited until dawn.
When the sun came up,
he went and asked a ranger nearby.
He said that,
there was a woman
who drowned in the area.
Shit.
And the spot Tia slept at,
is the same spot you are
right at now, Shin. Right here.
-Tough luck, man.
-It's giving me goosebumps.
Don't pull that prank.
We're in the middle of the woods.
-Let's just go to bed.
-Hey, wait a minute.
Aren't you ever curious
why it's always a ghost of a woman
-with long hair, covering her face?
-Yeah.
I've seen it in countless movies,
it's all the same.
-Have you seen Shutter?
-Asshole.
I haven't seen it.
Don't fucking talk about it.
You've never seen Shutter?
Come here.
The ghost was sitting
on the protagonist's shoulders.
Fuck. Are you fucking nuts?
-Really. That's why his neck hurt--
-Enough.
I don't think ghosts are real.
Back in the day,
I used to take people out rafting here.
I'd stay in the woods by myself,
and I've never seen any ghosts.
Right.
-You're just paranoid, Shin.
-Idiot.
I don't know if they're real,
I just know I'm scared.
Oh, well.
Say, what if...
anyone amongst the four of us
ends up dead because of it?
Would you be scared?
I'm not scared of any of you dying.
I'm more scared of myself dying.
Fucking prick.
But seriously,
I think...
amongst the four of us,
if turdbag Shin died,
he'd make a frightening ghost.
Why is that?
Just look at his face.
He isn't even dead,
yet I'm already spooked.
Yeah, right, you fucking Prince Charming.
Why are you getting up?
-Yeah.
-Ter. Phueak.
Move over. I'm getting in the middle.
What's wrong with you?
Are you that much of a pussy?
-If you're not, just sleep outside.
-I'm not.
I'm... too lazy to move.
Ter.
You're not scared,
so switch places with me.
I mean I wouldn't be scared of you guys,
but I'm scared of ghosts in general.
-Just let me sleep in the middle. Please.
-What is wrong with you?
-Shoo. Dam it.
-Hey, hey, come on.
Stop fucking arguing.
Let's just go to bed. I'm so tired.
-See? He's tired. Just get to bed.
-Yeah.
And If I die,
I'm going to come back
and haunt the one in the middle first.
Well, well.
So may it be.
I hope you die, as you wish.
Did you even brush your teeth
before bed? You smell bad already.
IN THE MIDDLE
Just keep heading in this direction.
By the time we reach
the camping spot, it'll be evening.
Shin.
Why do you even have to read the compass?
The river just flows in one direction.
Yeah, were you expecting us
to make a turn somewhere?
Well...
I don't want it to go to waste.
Well, there's no need. Pocket it.
Hey, Phueak.
You too, asshole. Why are you shouting?
I'm Jack Dawson. Haven't you seen Titanic?
He stands at the bow of the ship.
Well--
Phueak, son of a bitch.
You want the boat to sink or what?
No. I just want to be Jack.
Hey, Shin.
Don't tell me you didn't know
that the Titanic sank.
Well, I haven't seen it.
You haven't seen Titanic?
You know, at the end,
Rose was on Jack's shoulders?
Shutter ripped that off.
-For real?
-For real.
Titanic did that like a decade before.
Well, fuck.
Sodding Thai movies.
Man, don't you have movie rentals
where you live?
Look.
It's party time!
Here we go.
Let's hit it harder!
Shin, help with the paddling!
Let's go!
Hey, Phueak.
Phueak, don't get up!
Phueak, don't get up. Get down.
You'll flip us over!
Phueak!
Phueak, don't stand!
Phueak, get down! Phueak!
Ter.
Help me!
Shin.
Phueak!
Shin, Phueak, are you all right?
I'm okay, you?
Where's Ter?
Fuck, you're right.
-Ter!
Ter, you bastard!
Ter!
-Shit, and he can't swim that well.
-Damn it.
Where is he?
-Ter.
-There.
-Fucking hell. Ter!
-Ter!
-Help!
-There's Ter!
Ter!
Aey, quick!
Help!
Ter.
-Help.
-Ter, hang on.
Help me.
Ter.
-Ter, don't pull me!
-Help.
-Hey.
Don't pull me.
Help!
-Help!
-Ter!
Aey, watch out!
Shit.
Fuck, no.
Where are they?
Aey!
Ter!
Shit! Where are you?
Aey!
Ter!
Hey, Ter.
Careful.
It's all right. You're okay now. Sit down.
How are you?
Are you okay?
Where's Aey?
-Aey.
-Damn it.
Aey!
-Where's that bastard?
-Aey!
Aey!
Aey, where are you?
Aey?
Fucking shit. Aey!
-Aey!
-Aey.
Aey!
Where are you?
Hey, Aey!
Do you think he'll be all right?
I think he'll be fine.
Don't overthink it.
You're the one overthinking.
Why are you fucking crying?
Aey isn't fucking dead yet.
When you know he's dead, then you can cry.
But we've been looking everywhere.
Let's not mull over it too much.
We'll be out of the woods tomorrow, right?
We can get the rangers
to come look for him again.
Let's just call it a night.
Trust me.
We've got a long way to go tomorrow.
I'm going to bed.
Ter.
Let's call it a night.
Hey.
What's wrong with you now, Ter?
Why aren't you sleeping in the same spot?
What spot are you talking about?
Well, I slept next to Aey last night.
So I should get to sleep on the end.
Hell, just sleep wherever is convenient.
It's fucking late.
Ter.
Don't tell me that
you're thinking
of what he said last night.
What the fuck did he say?
About that...
if he dies,
he's coming back
to haunt the one in the middle.
Dead, my ass.
Aey isn't fucking dead yet.
Stop talking nonsense.
We'll find him tomorrow. Let's go to bed.
If you're not scared,
then move over to the middle.
Shit.
Shin, man.
Your feet fucking stink.
No, they don't.
It's right up my nostrils.
Keep your fucking feet out of my face.
Why are you even smelling it then?
Hey, shh.
Do you hear something?
What?
What is that sound?
It sounds like...
someone's walking towards us.
Who's that?
Aey, is that you?
Aey.
What the fuck?
-Fuck, man.
-Shit.
Tough fucker, we thought you were dead.
Hey, Aey, how are you feeling?
Shin.
-Get him a towel, dry him up.
-Okay.
Are you okay, man?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Hey, and...
how did you make it back?
I'm cold.
Dry him up. There.
And go change your clothes.
You'll get sick.
We were looking for you.
It's good that you're back.
Damn, there's not a scratch on you, huh?
Fuck, that's awesome.
You're so damn lucky.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm going for a smoke.
Yeah, I'm coming along.
Hey.
Where's your smoke?
Come on.
Stingy douchebag.
Don't you think it's a bit strange?
-What's strange?
-Shit.
Keep it down.
-What?
-I mean about Aey.
What about him?
What kind of fucking person
can go under water for minutes on end
and come out just fine?
What?
And isn't it good that he's fine?
Don't jinx it, come on.
Aey.
Are you all right?
Aey?
Are you okay?
Aey.
What's wrong?
You?
What are you doing out here?
You don't even smoke.
Well, I'm going to start smoking today.
Take it easy.
Man.
Starting your rebellious phase
at this age?
Ter.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
What the fuck is wrong with you two?
Phueak.
What if Aey is already dead?
Dead, my fucking ass.
Then who's that in the tent?
Fuck, man.
Haven't you seen The Sixth Sense?
What of it?
The guy doesn't know that he's dead.
Really?
You son of a bitch.
Why did you have to tell me that?
I haven't seen it.
You had it coming.
My turn, bitch.
Maybe Aey is back for you, Ter.
You're the one who caused him to drown.
Fuck you.
Watch your fucking mouth.
I think he's back because you...
jinxed him to die.
What?
Didn't you say he isn't dead?
I'm just joking.
Shitheads.
Seriously, you think he's actually dead?
I don't know.
Maybe I'm just paranoid.
Yeah. I'd say you're paranoid.
Fine. I'll go take a piss.
And do it far away from the tent.
It's enough that I have to put up with
Shin's fucking feet.
Wait for me.
Hey, Ter.
Take Aey with you.
You're...
sweating a hell of a lot.
Are you okay?
Are you feeling warmer?
Yeah.
It's good that you're okay.
Fuck.
A snake.
I'm so fucked. I'm fucked.
What's wrong with you, Ter? What is it?
Aey is dead.
-Huh?
-What?
Aey is fucking dead.
-What are you talking about?
-Shit.
Here he comes.
He's walking right towards us.
Shit.
What's wrong, Ter?
Aey is fucking dead.
I just saw his body.
Are you playing a joke on us?
-It's not funny.
-Yeah.
Joke, my fucking foot.
I just saw his body floating in the river.
No way.
-Shit.
Ter, don't let it go, man.
-Man, what is wrong with you?
-But it's Aey.
-Hell, man.
-It's Aey.
Phueak, don't...
-Don't prank him like that.
-Phueak.
-It's Aey, Phueak.
-It's cold outside. Bullshit.
Shit, why didn't you stop me?
Fucking hell.
Is this a good idea?
I mean, he's our friend, after all.
But he's dead, dude.
I don't count ghosts as friends.
Aey.
Leave us alone.
You're dead, do you hear me?
Aey.
Is he gone?
Phueak, you go and check.
But why me?
Yeah, you go, Phueak.
Fuck.
I think he's gone.
Shit.
Where are they?
Hey.
Is Aey gone?
Maybe.
Fuck me.
How are we going to get down there?
Shit.
How did you get up here?
No.
No, this way.
Fuck, where are they?
Shit.
Who's there?
Fucker, tell me who you are?
Hey, it's me.
Phueak.
Shit, fuck you.
You scared me.
What are you afraid of?
Use your eyes, man.
Here.
Fuck me.
You should've given them to me
in the first place.
Fuck.
Ter, mate.
Shin. Phueak.
Come on, quick.
-Shit.
It's Aey's body.
Fuck, man.
What do we do?
I think we should go.
Then tomorrow,
we'll get the rangers to recover the body.
You're not taking him with us, are you?
Let's go.
Fuck, Aey, I'm sorry.
Wait.
What the fuck is it now?
Let's just get out of here.
-Aey.
-Shit.
Why are you calling him?
-Aey.
-No.
-Why are you calling him?
-So he can come and see his body.
I want him to know he's dead.
So he'll leave us alone.
Aey.
Come out, man.
Shit.
Aey, you're dead, man.
Now leave us alone.
Here's your body.
Look at it.
Shit.
Ter.
Look at it.
Shit!
So are we ghosts or humans?
-Phueak.
-Shit.
Fuck.
This is like The Others twist ending shit.
Fuck you.
You spoiled the ending again.
Why do you even fucking care?
We're all fucking dead!
I tried to tell you.
But you kept being pussies.
So I had to let you see for yourself.
Fuck.
A snake.
So?
Am I still your friend?
You are.
-Yes?
-Hello? Pim?
You just woke up? Can we talk?
Are you with your boyfriend?
No, I can talk, Miss.
And when are you going to introduce us
to your billionaire boyfriend?
You've been keeping him to yourself
and you just fell off the radar.
Can I help you with something?
Well, Pim,
there's a special flight tomorrow.
They want the same cabin crew on it.
Do you remember Prince Albert
and that Princess who booked the whole
plane for their honeymoon this year?
They're coming back,
landing in Phuket, like before.
I remember.
LAST FRIGHT
Yeah, I'm baffled, too.
I don't know why they asked
for the same crew
when only the Princess is coming.
But there's a rumor that she got beat up.
She's about to get dumped.
The Prince has a mistress.
Really? But...
I have a schedule conflict tomorrow.
Can you find someone else?
No, Pim, it's the higher-ups' request.
We really can't change that now.
You're the only one
who has flown with her.
I just called Tui up a moment ago.
All right, Miss.
Understood.
Oh. And where's Tui, Miss?
Why isn't she here yet?
Well, Pim, it looks like you'll have to
fly solo now.
What? Why is that?
Well, Ter, Tui's brother drowned in
Chiang Mai last night.
I really can't find someone
to replace her.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Aren't you a fucking lot to handle?
Your Highness.
Captain.
We're about to land,
would you like anything?
I'm good, thank you.
All right.
PHUKET AIRPORT 22 HOURS LATER
Last night, Princess Sophia
of the Republic of Vanistan
died in Phuket
at 9 p.m. local time
in her hotel room.
She was 34 years old.
As of now, the doctors have yet
to determine the cause of death.
The Bureau of the Royal Household has
requested for her body to be transported
back to her country within 15 hours.
A special flight will be arranged
accordingly by Golden Star Airline.
Miss Pim.
They've asked us to transport
her body back within 15 hours.
We can't transport her
under the plane in cargo...
as she's royalty.
So we have to arrange a seat for her
on the plane, just as on her way here.
Miss Pim.
You're responsible for the body.
Those without authorization
cannot get on board.
Yes, Captain.
You're aware that after this flight,
you'll be interrogated, right?
I am.
-Captain.
-What is it, Miss Pim?
Can you please come out here?
What's going on?
Uh.
Well...
Miss Pim, just state your business.
Nothing, Captain.
All right, Miss Pim,
we're in a storm zone.
I'm sorry.
Your meal, Captain.
Thank you.
-What is it now, Miss Pim?
-Captain.
What the hell are you playing now?
Where did you put her body?
What the heck are you talking about?
You've already violated
a lot of our regulations.
Pull yourself together.
Where did you put the Princess's body?
If you keep talking nonsense,
-I'm not going to pick up anymore.
-Captain.
Captain.
Land the plane now.
Do you hear me? Captain?
I told you to land it. Captain.
Open it.
I'm telling you to open it now.
Open the door now. Open.
Open it now.
-Pim.
-Let me go. Let go.
What the hell's wrong with you?
What the hell?
Take a look at the bitch's body yourself!
That's enough! I don't want to hear
any more of this nonsense!
Let me go. Let go.
Let me go!
Let go!
I'm not going. Let me go now!
Let me go!
Pim, you're going to be interrogated!
Captain, please let me go.
I've had enough. I'm scared.
Please let me go. I'm so scared.
I won't do it anymore!
No. I'm scared!
I won't touch him ever again.
Please let me go.
Subtitle translation by
Mingchut Anuwatnonthaket