FIVE STAR PRODUCTION PRESENTS
I'm sure everyone realizes
the present economic situation.
For the past year,
the executive board and I
have been trying everything we could
to maintain the situation of the company.
However, the day has come
that we have to face the fact.
I had to make a tough decision
which I didn't want to do.
Draw a number from
the Chi Chi Sticks and pass it on.
Come on, shake it and pass it on!
Yes, sir.
Three persons from each department
will be laid off today.
You all know that the company
treats everyone as a family member.
Like brothers, like sisters.
You all are like my relatives.
I can't bring myself to say
who should go or who should stay.
I just couldn't do that.
So I thought this is the fairest way.
NINE
Put it on the table, please.
Won't you draw a number too?
No, I won't.
I'm the boss.
The following three numbers
are the people to be laid off.
Seven.
Three.
No! How can that be?
This isn't fair.
How will I feed my family?
I still have mortgage to pay.
Nine.
Ms. Toom, allow me to help you.
Waiting for the elevator?
Yes.
You might have to wait for a few days.
Why?
OUT OF ORDER
You're on the third floor, right?
Room 6?
How do you know that?
May I help?
Are you afraid that I'll hit on you?
No, I'm not.
Do you often get people
knocking on the wrong door?
Sometimes.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
Oh, that's all right.
No. Please wash it off. It'll be harder
to get it off when it's dry.
Thanks.
Go ahead. Don't bother.
The sink is over there.
Do you like soft rock?
I prefer hip-hop.
That's just the radio.
Do you live here?
No. My friend does.
What kind of bird is this?
It's a gift from a friend.
Which bank do you work for?
A finance company.
Finance?
Wow, you're lucky to still be employed.
All my friends in finance got laid off.
Yeah. Lucky me.
Thank you.
Thank you, Miss…
Toom.
Thank you, Ms. Toom.
That'll be 548.50 baht, ma'am.
Five hundred baht for this?
It's not 500. It's 548.50 baht, ma'am.
-I'll put these back.
-Don't worry, ma'am.
Leave them to our staff.
No, I'll put them back.
But do you know where…
Hello?
Have you ever had sex?
How big are your breasts?
I'll tell you something.
I talk to these aliens
more often than my own wife.
I have a doctoral degree in physics.
I'm working with…
MAMA MINCED PORK FLAVOR
INSTANT NOODLES
Hello?
Jim,
what would you do if you wake up
and find a box filled with a million baht,
sitting in front of your room?
Do I really have to answer this?
Yes, you do.
I'd just leave it alone.
Wouldn't you want it?
Over a million baht inside?
Has someone really left a box of money
in front of your room?
No, I mean it's hypothetical.
Wouldn't you want it?
If it's just a 500-baht note,
I certainly would take it.
But a box with a million baht
placed in front of your room…
is a bit fishy, don't you think?
Okay, that's all.
You called just to ask me this?
Yeah, I've got to go.
Hey, wait--
Can I help you?
Pardon me, madam…
Have you seen a "WAI WAI" brand
instant noodle box somewhere around here?
It's "MAMA" brand…
a minced pork flavor MAMA box.
WAI WAI!
MAMA!
Who told you?
We always use MAMA boxes to deliver stuff.
All right. It's MAMA then.
A minced pork flavor MAMA box.
Have you seen it?
No… I haven't.
Answer again!
I'll ask the question again.
Now this time,
you listen carefully, all right?
Have you seen
a minced pork flavor MAMA box
in front of your apartment?
No, I haven't.
Something is telling me that
you're not telling the truth.
But, if you say you haven't seen it,
I guess you haven't seen it.
Please pardon us…
for the inconvenience.
This is just an overture, young lady.
If I find the box in here,
someone will end up dead.
KANCHIT THAI BOXING
-Noi! Check the cabinet.
-Yes, sir.
Sure thing.
Hey, Noi!
Did you see something under the bed?
It's minced pork flavor.
It's here!
Be careful. We're here for the money only.
…to have enough potential and knowledge
so they don't end up selling their bodies.
Hey! What the hell is going on?
Stop wasting natural resources.
Strop ruining your residential areas.
Stop cutting down trees…
Do you want to fight me? Don't you dare!
You're so dead.
Hello?
Kanchit, this is Tong speaking.
What happened?
What do you mean?
You haven't gotten the money yet?
I haven't seen even a shadow of it.
But my boys brought it to you
this morning.
Are you sure they followed
the instructions correctly?
They followed what you told me,
to place the box in front of Room 9,
knock three times, and leave.
Same as usual, isn't it?
Are your boys in need of some cash?
Are you suggesting that
my boys stole the money?
I'm not suggesting anything.
But, it isn't impossible, correct?
That's very unlikely.
Especially Berm.
His family has been
with us for generations.
Since his grandfather, father--
The history of you and your underlings
is of minor interest to me.
What interests me is
where the fuck the money went!
I've been waiting since this morning.
I just don't understand
why you want the money
to be put in front of the room.
Why not in the room--
Mr. Kanchit!
Have I ever interfered
with how you do your business?
I don't care how you fix your fights.
Likewise, this is my business.
And I have my own way of doing things.
If your boys followed the instructions,
things shouldn't go sideways.
I'll tell you what,
I'lI give you until 10 p.m. tonight.
I expect the money to be here.
It'll be better if you bring it yourself.
I have some errands to run.
If the money isn't here by 10,
you don't want to know what will happen.
-Wiroj.
-Yes, sir.
Get me Some-arng and Suparp.
Yes, sir.
Quick!
Some-arng!
Some-arng! Boss wants to see you.
The deaf one too!
HEY DEAF, BOSS WANTS TO SEE US.
MAYBE HE WANTS TO GIVE US SOME MONEY.
You want some "Sugus"?
It's called "So-gas", Boss.
"So-gas" my ass.
Hey, Some-arng.
Suppose I want you to deliver
one million baht from a fixed fight
to a friend of mine,
would you dare steal it?
Come on, Boss!
I'd be just as bad
as a motherfucker to do that.
You're not answering the question.
The question is whether
you'll "dare" to steal the money.
Of course, not… I dare not, Boss.
What about you, Suparp?
What did he say?
He said he would be tempted.
What about Berm and Noi?
Do you think they would steal from me?
KANCHIT THAI-BOXING
Hello? This is 191.
Hello, this is 191.
Mister! We've been going around
in circles for hours.
You're wrong. Admit it!
No, I'm not. I had the right of way.
Not wrong? You drove like an asshole.
No wonder your face got injured.
-Please calm down, miss.
-I drove on the right side.
I can't calm down.
We've been going around in circles
and there's still no conclusion!
You wouldn't give any ticket
and we don't know who's responsible.
I can't go to the garage.
I can't go to work.
-And it's late already!
-I'm hurt. I'm really hurt.
Serves you right! Driving like an asshole.
-You saw him cut in front of me.
-My vehicle is smaller.
He hit my car so he's wrong!
If I hit his car,
I would admit it's my fault.
Is it true, what she said?
You deserve to look like this.
Please, Miss.
I have too many cases already.
Please calm down.
-Sir, I've been wasting my time for ages.
-Yes.
-You know he hit my car.
-All right.
Why don't you just fine him?
Can we take the injured man
to the hospital first?
And what about the case?
What about my car?
I need to get it fixed.
All right. Draw me a diagram of
the accident to make sure--
I drew a diagram four times already!
It changes every time!
How can I make a judgment?
Of course! It's from different angles.
Take a look from that many angles
so you can make your call.
-I'm sorry.
-That's okay.
Toom!
What are you doing here?
Hey! I think I changed my mind.
About what?
The money.
If a box of money was left
in front of my room,
I think I'll take it.
However, once I take it,
I have to disappear.
Go to some remote provinces…
or even better, go abroad!
That way, no one can track me down.
And who knows?
I might find a foreign husband.
Mister! No giblets, please.
Just give me some blood.
Lots of blood, please.
Speaking about a husband,
have you met my new boyfriend?
Not yet.
Oh! He is so gorgeous. He's just my type.
Tor! Come here.
Toom, this is Tor. Tor, this is Toom.
Hi.
Isn't he gorgeous?
You know, my store survives
to this day because of him.
Teenage floozies like to come to my shop
and flirt with him.
They pretend to be shopping.
And while they're looking around,
they flirt with him.
And you know, Tor is so shy and polite.
Those horny sluts just go crazy.
Lots of them?
Lots of what?
Horny teenagers.
Lots and lots!
The worse the economy is,
the hornier people get, you know?
Don't you think, Tor?
-When are you two getting married?
-Married?
No way! Who would do that these days?
If a couple is in love,
then they're in love, okay?
If they're no longer in love,
how can a piece of paper
glue them together?
Every fortune teller I've been to
all agree on one thing.
That we are true soulmates.
And not only in this life.
One even said that even the power
of Godzilla couldn't separate us.
Here you go.
Make sure there's enough sauce.
How much?
It's 160 baht.
I have to go now, Toom.
If there's a box of money
in front of your room,
don't forget to call me.
Maybe we can go abroad together. Bye now.
See you.
Hurry.
I don't think
they'll last more than two months.
What did you say?
I don't think he'll last
more than two months. He's a playboy.
He changes women
like he changes his underwear.
Check, please.
That'll be 40 baht.
Is that you, Oy?
It's Toom.
Your friend, Toom.
No. I'm calling long distance
from Bangkok.
I have something to ask you.
Do you remember
the place where we went together
to get your fake passport
before you went abroad?
Where is it?
That's right, it was a Thai-style house.
Soi Annop.
Alley… okay, at the end of the alley
Yeah…
No, not for me.
It's for a relative of mine.
She got laid off.
So she wants to give it a try abroad.
Soon probably…
You want something from here?
MAMA noodles?
Sure. I'll bring some.
How's life?
Well, I'm sort of okay here.
A bit bored.
I have to go now.
I'll call again soon.
Thanks. Good luck. Bye.
Dear Mother,
don't be too surprised with this money.
"I just got a job abroad."
"I don't think I'll have
time to go and say goodbye
to you and the others in person."
"The company wants me
to start in a few days."
"I may even have to travel tonight."
"I can't really tell you
what kind of job it is at the moment,
but I can assure you that
it's not the type of job
that made Thai girls famous in the world."
"Mother, this is the money
the company paid me
three months in advance.
"It should be enough to take care
of Father and the rest for a while."
I love and respect you always.
Toom.
TAKE THE STAIRS
FOR A ONE-FLOOR TRIP
KANCHIT THAI BOXING
I think Noi and Berm
are still here somewhere.
That's their bike.
Yes?
Do you live here, young man?
Yeah, I do.
Did you happen to see two guys
dressed somewhat like us
around here this morning?
Yeah, I did.
"Kanchit Thai Boxing" sweatsuits
exactly like these.
They went into that apartment.
Whose apartment is it?
I don't know.
A woman. Pretty one as well.
Hey!
Can I ask you a question?
Are you guys here to set up a boxing gym,
or are you undercover cops?
Hey!
Son of a bitch!
It's a dirty phone call.
Why the hell did you give it to me?
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW? I'M DEAF.
YOU'RE DEAF, SO WHY DID YOU PICK IT UP?
IT CAUGHT ME BY SURPRISE.
ONE DAY, YOU'LL BE SURPRISED ENOUGH
TO SHOOT ME DEAD.
DON'T WORRY.
A BAD PERSON LIKE YOU WON'T DIE EASILY.
I'M JUST AS BAD AS YOUR FATHER.
WHAT HAS MY FATHER GOT TO DO
WITH A DIRTY PHONE CALL?
What the hell are you nodding for?
Can you hear it?
Whoa! Fuck!
I wouldn't be the least bit surprised
if Berm's body suddenly appears
out of nowhere…
Shit!
It must be that fucking Tong for sure.
Boss, I found Berm and Noi.
What do they have to say?
Nothing. They're fucking dead, Boss.
Tong, you bastard.
That's exactly what I thought too, Boss.
I found them dead in a girl's apartment.
What girl?
I don't know, Boss.
Good-looking too.
You know how Berm and Noi are.
They always flirt around.
I'm sure Tong had this girl
seduce them into her room and kill them,
then took off with the money.
Are you sure?
I'm 1,000-percent sure, Boss.
I'm hardly wrong with this sort of thing.
I think the next person on his list
is "you," Boss.
That's why Tong told you
to bring the money yourself tonight.
Okay. First thing, you two come back here.
And bring me as much information
about the girl as possible.
About tonight, let me figure out
how to deal with that bastard.
And don't let anyone see you
when you come out, all right?
Yes, Boss.
You want some Sugas?
Sorry, madam.
It's a bit of a hectic day for me.
Okay, so when do you want it?
Can I have it by today?
Wow, it seems that
you're in a great hurry.
Is it possible?
A relative of mine suddenly got ill.
Of course, it's possible.
But it means we have
to jump the queue for you.
And that would cost a bit more.
How much?
Let's say 50,000 baht.
You can have it by 10 tonight.
You pay half of the fee now,
and the rest, when you come
and get the document tonight.
How's that, 50,000 baht?
Okay.
But how can I be sure that--
That I won't play you?
You can't be sure of anything.
If you want to be absolutely certain,
I suggest you go to the Ministry of
Foreign Affairs for your passport.
Then get your real visa at the embassy.
That way, it's legal.
And it costs much less than mine.
But I guarantee that
you won't be traveling tonight for sure.
It'll take you a week or two
at the very least, madam.
And even if you do that,
how can you be sure that
you'll get a visa from the embassy?
Thai passport holders
are targeted in many countries,
particularly pretty young ladies
such as yourself.
Because those countries,
they still believe that there are
only two occupations in Thailand.
Please pardon my vulgarity,
women are all prostitutes
and men are drug dealers.
I told you not to move!
I'm not moving.
You cocksucker!
Who are you calling a "cocksucker"?
You're a cocksucker!
Excuse me.
Ma'am?
I completely reject all laws,
simply because they're stupid.
The only thing that the outlaws
like myself,
respect and honor is our "word."
Politicians only keep the laws,
but not their words.
If you're okay with the deal,
may I ask you to go
and have your photo taken?
Please do as the photographer tells you.
I think he's a bit moody today.
Are you sure you don't want any Sugas?
What are you looking at, Wiroj?
Here, have some Sugas.
How tall?
Fifty centimeters.
I mean how tall are you?
Me? I'm 168 centimeters.
Do you have anything bigger?
This is the biggest.
Are you going to put someone inside?
Just some old books.
Do you have a delivery service?
Of course, we deliver.
How much?
Four thousand baht.
That's already with a discount.
What the…
I'll help you get it inside.
That's all right. I can manage.
But it's heavy.
-I can manage. Thank you very much.
-Okay.
Don't be alarmed.
I can explain.
There's a gang of teenagers
doing drugs in the room next to yours.
I've been observing for a while.
Today, I think that
there's a celebrity among them.
So I thought I'd break in
through their balcony for a surprise.
To do so, I need to go out
through your balcony.
Miss… may I?
What will you do to me?
No, nothing at all.
I'm just asking for your permission
to climb out your balcony. That's all.
-Go ahead.
-Great.
What's your name again?
What's your name, Miss?
Why? What have I done wrong?
Nothing. Just so I can mention your name
in the interview.
Interview?
Of course.
I'll make the front page tomorrow.
Thank you so much.
Put your hands behind your head!
Lie face down on the bed! Now!
Lie face down!
Fuck!
Hi, missy.
Do you happen to have some fish sauce?
My name is Pen.
I live downstairs.
-Yes, I do.
-Can I ask you for some?
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm making some papaya salad
with my friends.
But I ran out of fish sauce.
So I've been knocking on every door.
But no one is home. They're all at work.
You're the first one who answered.
Can I bring it down to you in a minute?
Oh, no! Don't bother.
I can come in and get it myself,
and I'll return it in a few minutes.
Please don't come in.
My room is in a mess at the moment.
That's okay.
I understand a single lady's lifestyle.
I feel uncomfortable having you in.
Are you with your boyfriend?
Oh, dear! I didn't know.
I'm so sorry to interrupt. Take your time.
I'll wait downstairs.
Room 6, right under yours, okay?
There's no need to rush.
Here's the fish sauce.
Thank you, darling.
Please come inside.
I'd love to, but I'm in a hurry.
We're making some papaya salad.
Come on, you're really not joining us?
Thank you but I'll take a rain check.
You should go.
Don't keep him waiting.
AUNTY SRI'S
Where the hell is he?
Sompan!
Fuck!
Hello, Boss?
I think there's something fishy
about the money from the fixed fight.
What do you mean?
I think this Kanchit guy
is up to something.
He got the police involved in this.
And the cop killed Sompan.
I think the situation
doesn't look too good.
Where is he now?
Who, Boss?
The fucking cop
who shot your pal, you idiot!
Oh, I got him already.
He wasn't bad, this cop.
But I was a bit faster.
Got him right between the eyes.
It was quite a fight, Boss.
You had a gunfight with the cop?
Yes, it was spectacular.
Whatever.
I'll do anything for you, Boss.
Come back here right away.
I want to know the details.
The bastard Kanchit doesn't know
who he's fucking with.
You're damn right, Boss.
Oh, my…
He sent this bitch to check us out,
pretending to come for the passport.
I thought she looked
rather suspicious this morning.
Don't you think, Wiroj?
You're right, Boss.
I noticed she was avoiding eye contact.
You two go and find out who this bitch is.
If she just came to check things out,
she wouldn't come back
for the passport tonight.
But you never know what kind of trick
Tong has up his sleeve.
He might send her back, who knows.
If she comes back, Wiroj…
Yes, Boss?
Take her immediately to the apartment
where I'll meet Tong.
-Yes, Boss.
-I also want to know
how he will explain this to me.
-Uncle Yen, it's your turn.
-I know.
Ms. Toom is behaving rather strange today.
She goes in and out of the apartment.
How come she's not at work?
Stop snooping into people's business.
You motherfucker!
Watch your mouth.
I'm older than your father.
Old people don't snoop?
In your case, it's "snooping,"
but in my case, it's "concerning," got it?
-Is it my turn yet?
-Yes.
That's it! Checkmate!
You wish your chess skills
were half as good as your mouth.
Now find out how to solve this.
You cheated!
Do you want this foot
in your mouth, you bastard?
Oh, what good timing!
I went to your room
to return the fish sauce,
but you weren't there.
What? Are you moving out?
Oh, no. They're for my books.
Wow, you read a lot!
Yeah, some.
You know, I always envy people who read.
They're smart.
I don't read at all.
I like watching TV.
Here, let me give you a hand.
Oh, no. You don't have to. Don't bother.
Not a bother at all. Let me help.
You can go now. I'll help her.
Come on. Let's go.
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
Oh, it's so dark.
How can you stay here like this?
Here you go.
See how much better it is?
How can you stay in the dark like that?
You must like this kind of box, don't you?
You have so many of them.
They're good for storing unused stuff.
The room is kind of small.
You know what? I don't like it.
Whenever I see this kind of box,
it always reminds me
of something horrifying.
What do you mean?
Back in my hometown in Ayuthaya,
when I was a little girl,
there was this lunatic
who killed people in the village,
then he put the bodies
into boxes like these
and threw them in the water.
Into the river?
No, it wasn't a river.
It was a pond. A pond in Bangsai.
And the water in that pond
was so dark and muddy
because of the waste.
Boxes like these that sink into that pond
will never ever be found.
And the smell, my gosh.
Have you ever been near such a pond?
No, I haven't.
Oh! The smell is so bad.
No matter how badly the corpses decayed,
no one could smell it.
Was the murderer caught?
I don't think so.
By the time the bodies were found,
he was long gone.
Or maybe he turned himself in.
It was a long time ago. I'm not sure.
Can I use your bathroom?
I had to go since I met you
in front of the elevator.
Is your boyfriend still here?
Oh! Why didn't you tell me?
Then I'd better leave you alone.
Thank you very much.
It's all right, dear.
-See you.
-Bye.
Really?
Quiet.
Or she'll notice.
Are you all right, Pen?
What's wrong? Pen!
Hey, are you okay?
I'm sure they had done it more than once
for him to look half-dead like that.
I guess so.
Now I know why he got tired
so easily lately.
Unlike before.
We used to do it all the time.
Morning, noon, and night.
Sometimes, we even set
the alarm clock for this!
Wow! What a lucky girl you are.
In my opinion,
The bastard deserved
to get it chopped off!
-Chop what off?
-Well…
his dick, of course!
You should just chop his dick off.
If a dick turns a decent man
into a bad one,
why not just get rid of it?
I think it's only reasonable.
You're damn right!
Great idea, Pen.
Sorry.
All booked.
They're all booked.
The soonest would be on the 27th.
I can't wait that long.
I really need to go tonight.
-My relative is very ill over there.
-Tonight?
You just came in here two minutes ago
and you want to fly tonight?
This is an airline, madam, not a bus.
You need to have schedules and plans.
You can't just go to the next bus
when you miss this bus--
Isn't there any way at all?
Well, maybe I can take a look at it again.
There might be…
Well, you can't be so sure.
We must try harder, you know?
Somlak, Somjate, Sailom, Sawai…
Peter Lee…
-Roong!
-Yes.
How come this guy, Peter Lee,
hasn't confirmed his flight yet?
He's flying tonight but maybe…
maybe he's not.
I don't think he's going.
Peter Lee…
Well, he's not going.
You're going instead.
What a lucky girl you are.
Miracles do happen.
You cut it in one swift stroke!
After you cut it… put it in here.
Then you push this button.
While his banana is being minced,
that's when you explain to him
why he must part with his willy.
And to return the favor to that bitch
for her fish sauce,
you take the thoroughly minced pieces
of that flirtatious cop
and cook her a delicious dish
of spicy minced dick.
Here, let me do it.
The wastewater pond in Bangsai, remember?
No one will know.
Hello?
Yeah, Toom.
What do you want to borrow?
My pickup truck?
Why do you want to borrow it?
Donating books…
Why do you need the pickup truck?
Oh, lots of books.
What's wrong? Your voice is trembling.
Are you all right?
Yeah, come and take it.
I'll be here all day.
Okay. See you later.
Jim!
Oh, my god! Jim!
What happened?
It's that motherfucker, Tor!
You guys had a fight?
Not a fight. A breakup.
Can you imagine?
The prick didn't even have the guts
to tell me in person.
He called me on the phone.
I asked him who the bitch was.
He said she's one of the customers
who often come to the shop.
And they've been going out for a while.
I asked him to come over and have a talk.
He said he was busy.
I offered to go over to his place,
but he said that bitch was with him.
So I asked if they were sleeping together.
He was reluctant to answer.
He said yes. That totally blew me off!
That's what happened.
You said every fortune teller told you
that you were soulmates.
I lied. I said it myself!
Toom, can you stay with me?
I don't want to be by myself.
I have something to do.
Please, I beg you.
I just can't be alone tonight.
Well,
let me take care of my business,
then I'll be back when I'm done.
Donating those books?
But it's already late.
Are they still open?
I called them earlier to wait for me.
I'll go with you, then.
No, you can't.
You just got out of the hospital.
Just stay here.
I'm afraid I'll do
something stupid again if I'm alone.
Please let me go with you.
I promise I'll be quick.
What's the matter, Toom?
I'll just be sitting quietly
in the car, just like at home.
But at least I have you near me.
So I won't get too depressed
and do something stupid again.
You who have never been broken-hearted
probably don't know what it feels like.
You have no idea how much
I get in a muddle about it. I have no one.
Tor left me. If you leave me,
I have no one else anymore.
Please, Toom, let me come with you.
Please! Why can't I go with you?
You want to go?
Okay, if you want to go,
close the door, and let's go!
You're so good to me, Toom.
At least you love me.
Toom….
What's the matter?
What the hell is this place?
This place stinks!
Is the place you're donating the books to
somewhere around here?
Toom, what's wrong with you?
Have you gone mad?
These aren't books, are they?
What are they? Tell me!
Toom, what the hell happened?
These aren't books, are they?
What's happening?
Tell me what's going on.
If these aren't books,
then what's inside these boxes?
What's going on with you?
Tell me. I'm your friend!
What's inside the boxes?
Why do you have to do this?
What happened?
Get in the car, Jim!
Get in the car!
I said get in the car.
Jim… do you have a passport?
I do. Do you want it?
Do you want to go abroad with me?
Toom, what have you done?
Did you rob a bank?
Remember when I called you this morning?
And I asked you what would you do
if you woke up and found a boxful of cash
in front of your apartment?
Yeah, I do.
You mean there really was money
in front of your room?
Yes. A lot as well.
Just like in the movies.
Where's the money now?
Wait here. I'll go up there
to get my passport real quick.
Pardon me, ma'am.
My boss wants to see you now.
Here's the other half.
Cut the crap, lady.
My boss is waiting. Come on.
Toom. Whose house is this?
-Jim!
-Where do you think you're going?
-Let's go!
Jim!
Go!
Hurry!
Pull… pull over, please.
Are you all right?
Nothing. I said stop the car, please.
What's the matter?
I miss my mother.
This is her most favorite song.
The night she died,
she asked me to sing it to her.
She passed away
before I could even finish the song.
How did she die?
She got a brain infection…
from having too much manicure.
Manicure?
Right. The tools were dirty, perhaps.
So, the bacteria entered her brain
through her nails.
Which salon was this?
KANCHIT THAI BOXING
I couldn't help her.
I couldn't help her at all.
What are you doing, bitch?
Come in.
So, how's everything, Kanchit?
Do you have anything for me?
Of course!
A lot. Let's start with the first one.
Do you happen to know this girl?
Toom?
So you know her, right?
Then we should go to her room.
What does she have to do with this?
Did she steal the money?
I don't understand.
Come with me, if you don't understand.
Perhaps things will become
clearer for both of us. Come on.
Move!
Stop looking.
Where are we going?
You'll find out soon.
I'm fucked! Help me!
I tightened her veins for too long.
The tables have turned. Please help me!
She's dying. I…
Move it! Stop looking around.
Cut this crap already! It's getting late.
Where's my money, Kanchit?
Well, I think it's you
who should cut the crap.
You already took the money this morning
and had that girl kill my boys
right here in this room.
The girl in the photo?
She was just a secretary at my company.
How could she kill anybody?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Why would I kill them?
I wouldn't care if you killed
someone else.
But you killed two of my most trusted men.
Why did you kill them?
I told you, I didn't.
It's you who got the police involved.
The damn officer even killed
one of my men.
Listen to you.
What police?
Don't try to change the subject.
Just tell me what did Noi and Berm do?
Why did you kill them?
I said I didn't kill them.
If I did, where are the bodies?
Now just give me the money
and end this nonsense.
May I?
I thought you already quit.
I never said I quit.
I just stopped.
You bastard!
Mr. Tong,
I'll wait until I finish this cigarette.
After that,
each of my boys will put a bullet
into your skull.
One through your temple for Noi.
Another through your chin,
up to your brain, for Berm.
Mr. Tong, I have to kill you.
Otherwise, Noi and Berm's souls
won't find peace.
It's nothing personal.
I hope you understand.
Why are you smiling?
How can you smile
when you're about to die?
Isn't that delicious, my dear?
What's delicious?
My lord! Fuck!
Hey!
Drop the gun now.
Holy shit!
You slut! You fucking whore!
I want to make love to you.
Wait…
Thanks for your cooperation.
I'll call you again next time.
Mr. Suwat.
Attention please.
This is an announcement
for all passengers traveling
aboard Thai Airways
International Flight 306 bound for London
that the plane is now ready for boarding.
All passengers, please proceed to Gate 69.
WHEN GOD HANDS YOU A GIFT,
HE ALSO HANDS YOU A WHIP.
TRUMAN CAPOTE