I have planned an exercise session with Nuea
Ahhhhhhhh
- How come you haven’t changed your clothes yet? We’re going to the fitness gym downstairs, right?
- Huh!? Fitness gym?
I have a get-together gathering at the pub tomorrow
- Here you are
- Why are you giving me these?
We didn’t get to that stage yet last night
I think you should just go there so you can see with your own eyes
- Somebody is caught in the act
- Huh?
- Where?
You’re truly a legend today
Did you bring me here?
I’ll give a special training session
Trainer Nuea will offer you the intensive class
Starring
Billy – Patchanon Aounsa-ard as “Nuea Nimman”
Seng – Wichai Saefant as “Toh Thima”
Heng – Asavarid Pinitkanchanapan as “Sky”
Surprise – Pitikorn Siripornsawan as “Kaojao”
Opp – Weerapong Aodherng as “Intouch”
Nut – Witsarut Khakum as “Daisy”
Freen – Sarocha Chankimha as “Khongkwan”
Becky – Rebecca Patricia Armstrong as “Fon”
Dew – Nitikorn Pankram as “Tor”
Looknam – Orntara Poolsak as “Som”
Ging – Areeya Ponfutrakul as “Prao”
Punch – Tipanan Nilsiam
Paper – Peerada Namwong
Anda – Anunta Teavirat
Guest-starring
Saint – Suppapong Udomkaewkanjana as “Thep”
Pete Thongchua
Chanokwanun Rakcheep
Inthira Charoenpura
Siwadol Janthasaewee
Adapted from novel – “Stalker: The Secret Crush” by Darin
Directed by Thanamin Wongsakulpach
Secret Crush On You, The Series
[Erotic music tunes play]
Then
I’ll give a special training session
Trainer Nuea
will offer you the intensive class
[Sexy music plays]
But before we begin
we must prepare properly
[Sexy music continues]
[Nuea and Toh breathing sounds]
[“You’re the Magic in My Life” plays]
🎵 Ever since the day you came into my life 🎵
🎵 you have changed my life. You’ve brought meanings back to my life 🎵
🎵 Just by seeing you up close 🎵
🎵 is all that I can do. And I’m not hoping anything beyond that 🎵
🎵 I know who I am 🎵
🎵 It is more than enough as long as I can keep doing this 🎵
🎵 You’re the magic in my life. You’re the one that makes my heart 🎵
🎵 feel love since the day you walked in 🎵
🎵 You’re the one that changed my life. You make me realise 🎵
🎵 when I wake up the following day, I will spend all my time for you 🎵
[Romantic music tunes play]
What are you doing, my good boy
Well…I was just…hm... lost in my thoughts
Toh, what do you think 1 plus 1 is equal to?
Hm? It’s 2, of course
And do you think this answer can be changed at any point in time?
It’s a definite answer, so absolutely not
Then
I want you to believe me
in the same way you believe that the result of “1 + 1” is always 2
I love you, Toh
I love you the most
I love you too, Nuea. I love you very much
- Toh
- Hm?
I promise you that my feelings towards you will never change
[Soft and dramatic music tunes play]
Is he okay?
I don’t know. What’s wrong with him?
- He’s been staring into space for 2 days
- Yeah
- Thima has made his presence!
- Shushhh
- What’s up?
- No clue
Jao
What’s happening? You’ve been staring into nothing for the past 2 days
We’re worried about you, you know
Right right
Toh, shut up! Such a problematic one. Where have you been in these past 2 days!?
- I’ll pass you the microphone [to interrogate you] next
- Yeah
Jao, you might think we’re snooping on you
which is true
but we are also worried about you
Tell your friends what’s on your mind
All right
Well
You give in to Sky!
Argh! He just opens his heart
Jao, Sky is taking this very seriously. Why are you still paranoid, huh?
Som, think about it carefully
I don’t see how a person like Sky can be so serious about me
- What about it? What’s the problem of being you? Tell me. Why must it be a problem being a person like you?
- Aha
Jao
[Gentle music tunes play]
Listen to me
Try not to think too much about anything. Just let it be
And believe it the same way you believe that “1 + 1 = 2”
See, you don’t doubt in the slightest about the answer, right?
Try to put faith in Sky like that
- Hey
- Hm?
- His words sound kinda good
- Yeah
But why do they confuse me so much?
- Same
- Um
- Ah
[Lively and comedic music tunes play]
Jao
You like Sky. Sky likes you
- That’s it. The end
- True
Here it is! That’s the “1 + 1 = 2” I talk about
Urgh! Enough of that. Now it’s your turn. So, where were you the past 2 days? Tell us
Hurry up
I was exhausted
So, Nuea told me
to take some rest
- Woahhh, Toh!
- How was it? Give us the details
- That’s right. Spit it
Nah. It’s personal between me and my hub…oops
Hmph! I told you, didn’t I? It’s NueaToh, not TohNuea
Right. And since you have given yourself to him, cancel the rules of having a secret crush
Moreover, it’s time stop collecting the weird stuff
Huh!? Why!? No!
Then, let us put our heads together for a moment
Okay?
Come here
[Lively music tunes play]
- Hey
- What
- If Nuea sees what Toh has, he’ll be shocked
- Yeah. Then, what should we do?
- It’s impossible to make him stop this habit abruptly
- True
- He’ll suffer from excessive bloody flux
- How about this? He can collect one thing from each date
- Sounds good
- Just one thing
- Awesome
- Good
Here’s what we agree upon
For a person like you, it’s unlikely to make you go cold turkey. So…
the rule is changed to “One date, one thing”
[Entertaining music tunes play]
“One date, one thing”
For every date, you can keep only one thing. Do not cheat
And when you’re used to it
We’ll make you do it only once a week, once a month, and once a year
until you stop this habit
Yes. Fabulous
One date, one thing
Who will be able to do that? One date, one thing. That’s cruel. Jao, Som, Daisy!
Toh, what did you say?
Nuea. Well, we’re going to...
have a meal, go for a walk, watch a movie, and we’ll go back to the condo together
Could we count them as 4 separate dates?
[Fantasy music tunes play]
Toh, it’s 1 date, of course
Dang!
Huh?
Don’t you want to come with me?
Of course I do. Please don’t sulk, Nuea
Nuea, I want to
I want to go with you
Ah, Nuea
Nuea
Please don’t sulk, Nuea
Don’t be upset with me
[Romantic music tunes play]
Nuea, why are you such a tease?
That’s because you always act like you are waiting to be teased
Tonight
let me tease you some more
[SCOY Ost. plays in the background]
Let’s go
[Sassy music tunes play]
I’m meeting my friends tomorrow. I’d like you to come with me
Sky, you usually bring girls, but you bring this little one this time?
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
Secret Crush On You, The Series
Colla-AC, 1 tablet a day to reduce facial and body acne
[Soft and gentle music tunes play]
Are you tired yet?
No
I can still run
[Sky breathing out loudly and acting out of breath]
Are you okay, Sky?
I’m kind of short of breath
Take a rest first. Let’s sit down now
Yes
[Sounds of heavy breathing and panting]
Are you okay?
I think it’s been a while since I last exercised. I can’t keep up with my breathing
Here
For me?
Thank you, Sky
Didn’t you say you were exhausted?
Hoooo Hoooo!
[Sky’s fake heavy breathing and panting]
I am
I’m soooo exhausted
But if you let me lie down on your lap
I’ll recover in an instant
- If I could…
- No no no no. No way
- Just a little. Come on, Jao
- Don’t, Sky!
Sit there and behave
No
I’m angry now
Sit down
Can’t you see there are so many people around here?
Where? I don’t see anyone, Jao
There. Over there
[Rock music tunes play]
[Jao mouthing quietly and clicks his tongue]
Shoo! Tsk!
Jao, are you okay?
[Entertaining music tunes play]
[Jao fakes sneezing]
Are you not feeling well, Jao?
Er…
Grass flowers (i.e. Natal grass)
Erm…
I think it’s because of the grass flowers
Er…
Shall we run one more lap and head back?
Um
Well
Sky
[“You’re the Magic in My Life” music tunes play]
Hm?
I want to ask you something
What is it?
What do you think 1 + 1 equals?
2, of course
How could you say the answer without thinking?
Do I need to think about it?
There’s no need to over-complicate what’s easy to understand
It’s better to save our brain for other stuff
Ummm
I see
Or…
did you plan to do a pun? Like 1 + 1 equals “you and me”?
That’s not it
You nosey!
I don’t do such things. Bleh
Oh, are you free tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Um, yes
Does anything come up?
I’m meeting my friends tomorrow. I’d like you to come with me
Friends
Oh, Nuea and the squad?
No
They’re my high school buddies
Oh, I don’t know them then
But everyone is as nice as I am
You don’t have to be afraid…okay?
If you’re not coming with me, I won’t be able to eat anything
because I’ll keep thinking of you
Silly!
But Sky
I think I…
Whenever you feel like leaving, I’ll take you back. You have my word
Deal?
Er…it’s not like that, Sky
What I mean is…
if I don’t enjoy it, I can go home by myself. You don’t have to drive me back or anything
It’s better you stay back with your friends
What you’re saying is…
- so adorable
- Stop your track!
What are you doing?
Can I just hug you once?
- Na-uh
- Please
No way!
- Hmmm
- Ummmmm
I’m not talking to you anymore. I’m going now
Don’t let me catch you, then
Jao!
Hey, y’all
- Hey, buddy
- Hi
Thank you
This is Kaojao
Hello
Oh. Hello hello
Have a seat
Hey, what do you want?
- The crisp fried catfish
- Dig in
- Why did you even ask, then?
- Here, the chilli basil
- Don’t want it
- No, I’m just telling you it’s chilli basil
Arghhhh what the heck
- Hey
- I want Tomyum (Thai spicy and sour soup)
Here here here here. It’s your fav dish, shellfish
Let the cockles tilt. Don't tilt the cockles
(t/n Word play here. The word "cockle" in Thai is read as "hoi kraeng" which sounds close to the word "ta kaeng", which means "tilt and tilted")
- They’re clams
- Yeah
- Are they?
Jao, have this
What’s with you?
I think Jao should like this
Eat quickly or the food will be cold
Honey, can you pass me the crisp fried catfish?
- Crisp fried catfish
- Yeah, I like fluffy stuff
- Leave some for me. I only had one bite last time
- Sure
Pass me the tissue
Here goes
- Ah, I have changed my mind
- Hurry up and eat
Here, take it back
Is it good?
It is
- Excuse me, one more Padthai please
- Yes
- Sky
- Eat well
- Wait a minute
- Um
Sky
Seriously, I’m not used to this at all
You normally bring girls along
but you bring this young one this time?
Hippo, you’re exaggerating. I didn’t have company every time
All those you brought were hot though
- Ball, you ass
- You miss that, don’t you
Totally. I’m a gleaner. I pick up whatever remaining
Hey, stop digging up my past
I’m losing my points here
What points?
You’re talking as if you are after someone right now
Yeah. As if you are pursuing someone around here
Very suspicious
Hey hey hey. Are you flirting with me here?
Hey, we’re friends. We’re the same pole of the magnetic field. That won’t work
What? Why do you even need to ask?
I think I’m making things very clear here
Ah
Are you joking?
- He’s playing with us
- A joke for sure
It’s remotely funny
You’re asking for this, you jerk
Hey, you will hit him
What joke!? It’s not a joke
Let’s eat
Here, I’ll peel the shrimps for you
I’m good, Sky
I can do it myself
Are you refusing to share food with me?
So stingy
Ah, that’s not it
- I can peel…
- I’ll do it for you
You want one, Pop?
Yeah, peel it for me as well
Sky
- I’m asking you for real
- Aha
So, you really are going after him?
Yeah
[Gentle music tunes play]
I’m going after him right now
Shit. But you used to like…
That was the past. I only have him right now
Hmmm
Would you like some lime juice? It’ll be less greasy
Argh. What do you expect from him?
Whenever he wants someone, he’s always so courteous
- Absolutely
- Correct
He says the right thing today
- Right?
- Yeah
- True
That’s true. When I’m pursuing someone, I’m always like this
And right now
I want him so much
I want him as my lover for… another 10-20 years. May I, Jao?
Now that’s greasy!
How about this
If…you like him for real
confess to him right here for me
- Right
- Aha
- Yeah
Of course, I can do that
It’s just…
I’m afraid the kid around here will be embarrassed
Who’s embarrassed
Ouch, Jao. It hurts
Ouch, you’ve been hitting me so hard these days. Hmph
- Oh, don’t play weak
- Ouch…hurts
Urghhhh
Where did you vow [or pray]? Don’t forget to fulfil your vow
because a luck this good doesn’t come often
Bua, the one who must fulfil the vow is me
It hasn’t been easy to have him opened his heart for me
Wait!
So he lets you dangle around him already
So, do you like my friend?
Hippo
Do not pressure him
If he wants to say it, he will
Argh, don’t pretend to be cool. I know you wanna know
You like him?
Yeah, do you?
Hey, stop it. It’s true that I want to know, but I can wait. I’m not in any rush
Stop putting pressure on him
Eat
[Gentle music tunes resume]
Eat your food
Jao, listen to me
Try not to think too much about anything. Just let it be
And believe it the same way you believe that “1 + 1 = 2”
There’s no need to over-complicate what’s easy to understand
It’s better to save our brain for other stuff
Well…
I...
I like Sky
What did you say, Jao?
I said…
I like you, Sky
Jao!
Oh!
Did my friends pressure you to say this?
No, they didn’t
- Then…
- Stop!
You can’t
Can’t I?
We can’t date
You were saying you liked me a second ago
If you date me
you will be…
a laughing stock for your friends
Kaojao
Can you not pay attention to other people?
Let them think whatever they want
I’m focusing on you, only you
There’s only one reason that will stop me from dating you…that’s you don’t like me
Um
Thank you for giving a guy like me a chance
Though I’m less handsome than Nuea
and less clever than Tor
I love only you
Let’s go
Here, my treat
I’m leaving first
- See you later
- Hey!
- Let’s go, Jao
- He even treats us the meal
- Hurry
- Heh?
- Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Goodbye
- See ya. See ya
- Goodbye
- Best of luck, man
Secret Crush On You, The Series
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
Who is this, Nuea?
- This is my lov…
- I’m his junior at the university
Why did you say we were senior and junior?
Would it be all right, if I said we are lovers?
What’s so bad about it, Toh?
Erm…Nuea
Secret Crush On You, The Series
- The movie is about to start
- Yes
- Let’s hurry
[Romantic music tunes play]
Ah! Oh, look
Nuea, I want to take a look at that
The movie is starting soon, Toh. Come on
Ah, no, wait
Let me have a look please
Toh
We will miss the movie
Ah, no!
I don’t want to. I wanna look over there
Toh
I’m staying right here
Please. I really want to take a look
Toh, we will miss the movie
What are you talking about
We’ll make it
We will definitely make it in time
Toh
They won’t let us enter the cinema
I don’t care if they won’t
I will go there
I don’t care
Let me go there, please
Please, come on
I’m staying here, then
Hmph
I wanna see it
Come on
Not going
Fine. Let’s go check it out
Come. Hurry
- Hurry
- Yay
Let’s go
Just a moment
Here?
- Yes
- Quick quick
Let's go
Quick quick
Where? Where is it?
Here. Here it is
This picture has just arrived
Which one?
- This one?
- Yes
Oh!
Nuea
Are you here to watch a movie?
Yeah
Me too!
What a coincidence
And…who’s this?
- This is my lov…
- I’m his junior
[Soft dramatic music tunes play]
I’m his junior at the university. My name is Toh
My name is Fai
And here is Kratai
Ummm. Toh, is there a movie you can recommend to us?
Actually, the good one now is the horror one
But
I’m not really a fan of horror
So, I’m going to watch the animation one
- Oh! We also like the bright and cheerful animation
- Yeah
Shall we watch together?
The more, the merrier
Nuea, can we?
Let’s watch together, please?
Of course
Are you going to buy the tickets now?
[The girls are squealing]
All right
Take them then
I’m not watching anymore
Heh!?
- What’s the matter?
- Nuea
Nuea, what’s wrong?
Ah
Oh
Nuea
What’s happened
Those 2 were startled
I should be the one to ask. What’s wrong with you?
[Dramatic music continues to play]
Why did you say we were senior and junior?
Eh?
But
would it be all right, if I said we are lovers?
What’s so bad about it, Toh?
Well
I don’t want to trouble you
Troubling me?
Why do you have to be considerate?
We’re lovers already
Why did you tell others otherwise?
Or you…
have never taken this relationship seriously
You’re misunderstanding this, Nuea
It’s not like that
Umm
My bad, then
Say, if you want to watch the movie
you can go
call me when it’s over
I’ll come pick you up
Ah no no
I don’t want to do that, Nuea
I’m leaving, too
Please
Please get inside the car
[Soft music tunes play]
So you’re a jealous type
Huh?
What did you say?
Oh, nothing
But, well…
So, are you jealous or not?
Refusing to answer, I see
Then… I’ll go watch the movie
[Nuea mumbles]
Huh?
[Soft music tunes continue]
What did you say?
Yeah
Jealous
Ah, I can’t hear very well
Can you say that again?
Jealous
Too soft
Can you say that louder?
- I want it to be as loud as a thunder
- Jealous
That’s it
Satisfied now
I am
Then
I’ll go watch the movie
I’M JEALOUS
Oh?
You’re jealous?
Jealous Jealous Jealous Jealous Jealous Jealous
Ah!
Find your way back home yourself, then
No!
I’m leaving with you
Wait for me
Ah
Argh, wait for meeee
Nuea
I…
in fact
Ah. Eh?
Nuea
Argh
Geez
Toh, you jerk
What should I do now?
[Sexy music tunes play]
Aha
What would you like, Nuea?
[Sexy music tunes continue]
Would you like…
coffee
or me?
I’d like to have “you”, of course
A-choo!
Shit!
Ah!
Oh
Toh
Well
I’m so sorry
I really didn’t mean to break it
This pot
costs 4,000 bahts (120-130 USD)
If you are my junior
I will be scolding you harshly right now
But if you are my lover
I won’t say a word of complaint
So, what kind of relationship do you want to be in with me?
[“Like A Star (My Stellar)” music tunes play in the background]
I want to be
your lover
What did you say?
Hmmm
Muah
Nuea, please don’t be upset with me
I apologise
for what happened at the cinema
and about this pot
I’m really sorry
I won’t be anything else
apart from being your lover
Please?
Hm
Please
Coffee or Me?
[SCOY music tunes play]
Definitely you
Ahhhh
[Energetic music tunes play]
Khongkwan
- Hello
Dance. Let’s dance a bit
Come sit here
- Will it be okay?
- Are you sure it’s okay?
Quick quick
Hurry. Come over
Oops, here you are
[Toh mouths to Nuea] “You can do it”
Well well well
There’re like hundreds and millions of people around here
but they’re being lovey dovey in their world of two
Ooh
That’s true
Anyway…Toh
What did you pick up
from your date yesterday?
- Right
- True
- Yeah
Do you really wanna know?
[Lively music tunes play]
- The more you talk about, the more I want to know the detail
- Exactly
- Hurry up and say it
Spit it fast
Well
Button
(t/n The implication here is (Nuea's) buttons are ripped off during their "training" process. So, Toh collected the button that fell off)
Arghhhh
- What’s up?
- Nothing
- It’s nothing
- Nothing at all
- There’s nothing
I’m just warming up my vocal cords
I see
That’s right
Toh, why did you collect the button?
Jao
I’ll subscribe to an “Only Fans” content for you when we go back
(t/n Since Jao is clueless about the meaning behind the "button" story, Daisy suggests Jao watch porn so he knows the "other" meaning of "ripped button")
Hey
What
There’s no need for him to sign up for “Only Fans” content
He already has one
(t/n the word boyfriend or lover is read “faen” or “fan” in Thai)
He’ll learn about it soon
Woohoo
Som, enough already
Ooh, bashful
Big time
Another one
Daisy!
(t/n Daisy is imitating the act of holding a noodle-strainer, reminiscing her cooking with Touch. But, of course, this looks like the “other” action)
What the hell are you doing!?
That’s disgusting
Daisy
What
Is it a secret code you use with Touch?
Hm? What code?
Absolutely none!
Hey, you know
Your voice right now
is higher than your IQ
- Agreed
- Hmmm. Since you flirt each other so openly like this
if he wins
you’d better give him a reward. Don't you think?
- Woo!
- I agree
Piece of cake
for me
Hmmmm
Then, I challenge you
to kiss him if he wins
Hmph
Challenge accepted
If his team wins
- I will kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss Touch in front of you
- Hmmm
kiss kiss kiss kiss
kiss kiss kiss all over
You sure talk the talk
I’ll wait and see
What what
Hey, kids
- Yes?
- Let’s give our support to the Engineering team
- Sure!
- Quick
- Yes
- On your feet
- Okay okay
Left first. Start from the left
Three…Four!
Engineer Engineer Engineer Engineer
Keep going, Engineering!
[Energetic music tunes play]
- Whoo!
- Hey!
- Yay!
- Woah woah
- Woah woah woah
- Toh, your boyfriend is so fly
- Kill me now!
Ahhhhhh
Khongkwan
Argh
Dang
What the
[Referee blows the whistle to stop the game]
- Ah!
- Oh
- Ah
- Is he all right?
- Is it serious?
Argh
Oh my
Dear me. Is he okay?
- Still good
- Sit sit sit
Sit down
[Whistle blown again. The game resumes]
[Energetic music tunes resume]
Ahhhh
[SCOY Ost. music plays]
Nuea is coming this way
Ooh. Nuea
You were fantastic
Jao, sit down
Here
Thanks
My pleasure
Uh-oh
Nuea
Oh
Ermmm
Help me. Quick
That’s the final scene of the play. Please, please leave
Please, exit this way
- Here
- This way please
Do I look cool today?
Naturally
My lover is the coolest today
Hmmm
You sure know how to talk, huh
Hmph
Right, Toh
Yes?
I’ll drink with my friends at my place today
Sure. Then, be careful not to get too drunk
Why are you…
saying it like you won’t be coming?
Eh?
You’re gonna drink with your friends, right?
My friends
are the ones you already know
Come join me
All right?
Please come
Come on
[Fantasy music tunes play]
Say you’re coming
I’m going
Everybody, please come over
Erm
Are you inviting us as well?
Yes, I am. Let’s drink at my place
Oh
- Very well, then
- Also
Touch is going as well, Daisy
Oh. You know as well, Nuea?
- Awwww
- Nuea, come on
Hee hee
Then
Let’s meet at my condo
I’ll go get changed first
Yes, of course
I’ll see you soon
Yes
Take the towel
- Bye bye
- Bye. I’ll see you again in a bit
- See you soon
- Bye, Fon and Khongkwan
Jao
Hm?
Let’s go to Nuea’s condo today
Nuea’s condo?
Please. Let’s go together
Okie. Go go go go
Pack your stuff
- Packing
- Toh, your bag
Pick up your bags
I’m running out of gas
- It's steaming hot
- Yeah
Secret Crush On You, The series
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
Why?
You’re not taking good care of yourself
Take care of yourself
Sky
Secret Crush On You, The Series
- Come come come. Let’s clink our glasses
- Yeah, come on. Let’s do it
- Woohoo!
- Cheers!
Touch, you as well
Soda drinks party. Orange and green, so pure. Lovely and sweet
It’s like a couple party today, huh
[Joyful music tunes play]
How about we start with our couple, Som?
Oooohhhh
Som, since when have you had a thing with him?
Beauty privilege
Hmph
Are you perhaps…
pursuing me?
I think it’s pretty obvious
- Woah
- Tor
- Here we go. Go for it!
Hey, he’s good enough to teach me now
Let’s have some snacks
But I wanna have Fon more
Oops
Oohhhh
That’s slick
[in English] “Hey, you. You’re not meant to say that in front of other people. That’s just for us. Okay? Do you understand that?”
[in English]
- “Yeah”
- “Yep? Good girl”
[in English] “Do you understand that?”
[in English] “Yeah”
Am I good [at speaking English]?
Seriously?
You must be full by now, huh?
Ah-oh
Nuea, are those 2 lovers? Or, does one of them have muscle weakness?
Toh
Hey
Kaojao
Such a show off
Toh
Yes?
Should we do it here, then?
[Exciting music tunes play]
Woah!
Holy!
- Dear me
- Woah
Woah!
Enough playing around
Let’s play some games
Okayyyy
You all know how to play UNO, right? Right?
Do it faster
- Hey, take it easy
- Calm down
Now, come
[Entertaining music tunes play]
Oh, yeah. I have to do it first
Take it
Yeah, pass it to me
Touch
My turn now. I only have 2 cards left
- Doesn’t mean you’re gonna win
- Yeah, but then you have so many left in your hands
Loads
I look like a princess now with all these cards
Ah
- Not again
- Don’t I have a single normal card?
- Argh, Khongkwan
- Toh
- Toh, your turn
Here
- Not again, Toh!
- Oh
Hey
- Toh, you have to put down 2 cards each turn
- Eh?
And look at your cards as well
- Nuea
- Nuea, you cheat
Stop teasing him
- What a big bully you are
- Put down your cards
Arghhhh! What is this!?!
UNO
- Oh!
- Eh!
Here
Woahhhh
- We’re excellent
- I’m good, yeah?
Woah woah!
Look! Look!
- You should plan well next time, Kwan
- True
No. I’m not playing. There’s no next time
That’s totally fine. You don’t have to play in the future, but today you must have your punishment
Dance to “Chicken White Butt” song
(The Thai "Grilled chicken burnt" song)
Woohoo!
Live up to the Engineering standard. Come on!
Three…Four! Chicken white butt. Chicken white butt
When it’s hot, it’s so AH! When it’s hot, it’s so AH!
Turn to the left. Turn to the right
Very hot. Very hot. Very hot
Som, you can’t lose to me. Dance harder
Chicken white butt. Chicken white butt
When it’s hot, it’s so AH! When it’s hot, it’s so AH!
Turn to the left. Turn to the right
Burning hotttttt
Hey, are we done?
Khongkwan, don’t go down without a fight. Quick
[Soft and gentle music tunes play]
What are you doing?
Jao, what are you doing here?
You want some ice? I’ll bring it over
What were you doing?
Hm?
What are you hiding?
Nothing
So, you’re not telling me?
- Here
- Ouch!
I'm talking about this
Why didn’t you tell me?
Erm…
That’s all you can say, huh
Show it to me. Let me have a look
Sky
Please let me have a look
You’re not taking good care of yourself
See, there’s a bruise
It’s not too bad
Ouch!!!
Not too bad, you say?
Give me the ointment. I’ll put it on for you
Be more careful next time
Let me see
Does it hurt much?
Well, a bit
- Hmph!
- Argh!
Done
Take care of yourself
Understand?
Hm?
Thank you
I was in a bliss
Bliss?
- There
- Ouch!
Still in bliss?
- You want me to do that again?
- Ouch!
Here. Take this!
[Party music tunes play]
It hurts, doesn’t it?
Why are you still smiling?
If I look hurt
I won’t look cool, right?
You don’t look cool right now anyway
- Jao
- Ah!
[“You’re the Magic in My Life” music tunes play]
Sky
Hm?
We’re lovers now
It doesn’t matter if you look cool or not
I want to see every side of you
You don’t have to think too much
If not, what’s the point of being lovers
Right?
Then, if one day I no longer look cool, you mustn’t abandon me
Understood
Um!
Hmph!
Sky
Other people might see us!
- Ow ow ouch
- Ah!
Jao, it hurts. I can't stand up straight anymore. Owww
Ahhhh it’s painful
- It hurts so bad
- Enough already
- Jao, I can’t stand properly
- I said enough
- Ouch
- Sky
Ow, it hurts so bad
[Lively music tunes play]
You’re being naughty again, Thima
Why are you taking their photos?
Kaojao will be mad at you
Jao won’t be mad at me. He’s gonna love it
Plus, he took photos for me so many times
I must return the favour, right?
Took photos?
What photos?
Take the photos when I’m with you of course, Nuea
[SCOY music tunes play]
Oops!
What photos?
Photos
Photos when we went for the trip in the Northern region
(t/n “Nuea” also means “North”)
How about you, Nuea? What are you doing here?
Right
I want to ask you something
Are you free this Saturday?
Yes, I am
I can go anywhere with you
Um…but
where are we going?
My house
Let’s meet my father
Huh!?!
Secret Crush On You, The Series
Nuea asked me to go to his house tomorrow
- Woahhhh
- Shshhhh
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Ahhhhhh!
[Scream of chaos]
Dad!
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
Directed by Thanamin Wongsakulpach