This is almost ready.
Let's see.
All set.
Here you go.
"Partay," with ay? Really?
That's the way they say it.
Quit stalling and create the event.
How often is your mom out
on a Saturday night?
Who are all these people?
They are my friends.
You still haven't told me
where you know them from.
You're not the only one
making new friends.
If you're too chicken to do it,
-I will.
-What are you doing?
Let's see.
Event "partay," create...
-Created. Done.
-Give me my phone!
-OK.
-Idiot.
We'll have strangers in our house.
-You're irresponsible.
-That above all else.
But I know you, Samu.
You only care
about that fancy girl coming.
That's why you're organizing all this.
Idiot.
MARINA ACCEPTED THE INVITATION
Ander!
Ander.
Can you give me a minute
to explain myself?
Or will you keep ignoring me?
-I don't want you to end up--
-I know! I won't end up like your sister!
She was drugged and taken advantage of.
No one's gonna do that to me!
...to end up like my parents.
-What do your parents have to--
-My biological parents.
A week ago, I went to the agency.
I asked about them.
Apparently, I was ten years too late.
They both died of an overdose.
That shit ruins your life, man.
I can't let anything happen to you.
You're my friend.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because... we talk about other things.
We talk about cars, girls, parties,
but not that.
Maybe we should, right?
Yeah.
We could get kebabs and see a movie,
like the old days.
I'd like that, but I'm still grounded.
Because of you.
Your father listens to me.
I'll talk to him.
All right!
You were beaten
by someone who grew up in the desert.
It's as if you cared for Taliban girl.
-Who's saying I care for her?
-It looks that way.
I think you're gonna end up
like your sister.
Falling for the first person
from the slums who crosses your path.
-Fuck you, Lucrecia.
-That's what you were going to do.
Fuck her, to then expose her.
Because if I remember correctly,
that fundamentalist threatened you
in your own home.
When are you going
to cut her down to size?
-I'm gonna kill you, man.
-It wasn't me, I swear.
Why would I tell him anything?
He's had it in for me since day one.
Besides, I wouldn't tell on you.
You are my buddy.
In fact,
you're the only friend I have here!
-The wedding's off, then?
-Just postponed, OK?
It's going to happen.
It's the "weekend," man!
I end up learning the important words.
By the way, there's a party
at Samu's this weekend.
Lots of chicks.
Oh, and my buddy the dealer.
I'm not telling you anything,
but there you have it.
How come your parents
are letting you go to the party?
-Easy, I haven't told them.
-And your brother?
-No, it's better if he doesn't find out.
-Shit! What do I do with his invite?
I don't know.
-And your brother?
-He's the DJ.
You better like twerking.
-Love it.
-Oh, yeah?
Look.
OK, great, then.
As your lawyer, I advise you
to stop talking to the police.
-Unless you want to confess.
-I have nothing to confess.
You were covered in the victim's blood.
A victim you knew very well.
With whom you were seen
having an argument.
Look, Samuel,
maybe it's not what it looks like...
but I doubt any judge will believe you.
What if I saw someone leaving
when I got there?
Who?
Nano, someone is asking for you.
Great burger.
-You wrecked my house.
-No.
Not us.
We are not sent to break furniture.
We break bones.
Do you know how expensive wheelchairs are?
-If you pay now, you'd be saving money.
-I need more time.
People want what they don't have.
Look.
I'm working on getting the money,
but I'll need the weekend.
I can say I didn't find you today.
That you had left for the weekend.
But on Monday...
I will have run out of excuses.
And so will have you.
I swear, if I had the money,
I'd lend it to you.
I know.
What are you going to do?
Get the fucking documents.
I know the combination to the safe,
so I get them...
hand them over so they can get more dough
from the construction company owner
than I owe... and we all win.
If they catch you breaking
into that house, you don't win shit.
-You lose it all.
-Fancy girl's going to let me in.
-She's coming to the party.
-You'll try to hook up with her?
-Aren't she and your brother...?
-I know.
They're inseparable in class.
Don't get me wrong.
If I were a chick, I'd be all over you.
I'd fuck you dry.
Make you quadruplets, at least.
But there's no accounting for taste.
Maybe this chick isn't into good ham
and prefers bland turkey breast.
No way!
She's dumb enough to like me better.
For that, she deserves anything she gets.
-And your brother?
-What?
Does he deserve that blow?
He was due for a blow regardless.
The sooner the better.
Why don't we go on Monday?
Can Polo make it?
You ask him. He's not talking to me.
Wasn't it you who wasn't talking to him?
Same thing.
Same thing? Let me get this straight.
He brings that caveman
into your relationship,
then he freaks out, makes a scene,
and gives you the silent treatment?
He's gonna expect you to get
on your knees and beg for forgiveness.
And as usual, you'll do it.
Why are you mad at me too?
Because I can't stand it
when he walks all over you.
It's good to put your ovaries on the table
every now and then!
What do I say? "Marina, I like you, girl."
"Gurl" with a u.
Recite a sonnet or whatever.
No, don't do that.
Just make it clear that you like her.
-OK.
-This can be your night.
Is this a bad time to admit
I fear rejection?
How do I look?
You're shaking like a flan.
A very elegant flan, mind you.
OK, I'll go change.
Have a couple more pills?
What's that?
Have you expanded the business?
No surprise he has so many friends.
With yours, we still needed more.
I had to go through my contacts.
What are you doing?
Nothing. The usual, man.
-Relax, what's a couple of pills?
-Don't let Samu see.
-Is this sangria?
-No.
It's an alcohol-free punch.
But he put way too much sugar in it.
Better stick to beer.
OK.
Let's have a look.
Three...
two...
one!
Not bad, right?
Merry Christmas.
What's up?
-How are you?
-Good.
Hey, do they know who I am?
-They know who your dad is.
-I'm not like him.
You have his last name, right?
That must surely open
lots of doors for you in life.
If the price is getting the stink eye
from those two, that's still a good deal.
Wow, a reggaeton DJ and a philosopher!
Have fun.
Thanks.
Hey, Guzmán, what's up?
Thank you for talking to my dad.
In the end, he's lifted the punishment.
I'm not coming today.
I'm tired from training,
so I'll talk to you tomorrow, OK?
Bye.
Come on, Ander!
What are you doing here?
My father is in the back room.
Hello, by the way.
I'm a customer, Nadia. I'm here to buy...
this.
Asparagus?
You've come here to buy asparagus?
No.
I've actually come to ask you
where the skinny kid lives.
I know he's throwing a party.
Well...
If you don't have the address,
I guess you're not invited.
Listen, Nadia.
Marina is there
without my parents' permission.
You don't know her
or what she's capable of.
I just want to make sure she's all right.
Please, tell me where she is.
Nadia!
Nadia, please, tell me where it is!
Calm down, or I'm not going to tell you.
I close in half an hour.
There's a bar across the street.
Have a cup of tea while you wait,
and if you've calmed down,
maybe I'll go with you.
You're coming with me?
No.
You're coming with me.
I did get an invitation.
With me, they might even let you in.
Sir.
Your asparagus.
Put it on my tab.
What are you doing here?
Christian invited me.
I see he didn't tell you.
Never mind, don't worry.
I'll introduce you to everybody.
Come.
Omar.
This is my friend, Omar. Ander.
He's in my class, but fortunately,
he's not a leader of tomorrow.
-Can I take your jacket?
-Nice to meet you.
Likewise. You look familiar.
You don't. Andrés, was it?
-Ander.
-You're Román, right?
Thank you.
Andrés, really?
Samuel doesn't know about me.
Which part? That you're a dealer
or that you're a fag?
Neither. Does everybody know about you?
Which part? That I'm a stoner
or that I'm a fag?
That's why you won't answer my messages?
In case they catch you.
What is it?
Can't live without me, or what?
You know it! I'm here to buy.
It's your lucky day.
Come.
I've never tried these.
It's easy.
Put it in your mouth and swallow it.
If you're horny now, just wait
until that hits you. See you later...
Andrés.
Thank you.
Hey!
Who wants to play spin the bottle?
We're a little too old for that!
We are not children!
Know who's not afraid of being childish?
An adult. Who's in?
-I am.
-When he's right, he's right.
Kiss, dare, or truth?
Come on!
Do you like anybody here at the party?
It wasn't Nano.
I swear to God.
Why are you so sure?
Who did it, Christian?
Christian, who did it?
I only know Nano didn't do it.
I'm at the marchioness' house,
chilling on the sofa,
taking off our clothes...
and the guy shows up at the pool.
All that was missing was the popcorn.
I swear. But that's not all.
It turns out he had also been watching
at Marina's party.
He had a front row seat, for free.
-Polo is a voyeur?
-A fucking faggot is what he is!
-He got a hard-on and all.
-Like a pole.
Come on, it's not such a big deal.
-What's not a big deal?
-I mean...
If they wanted to do that,
they should have told you, but...
The fact that Polo likes guys,
if he does...
Who cares?
My cousin in Almería is a drag queen.
-Yes, Eligenio.
-Eligenio, total fag, man.
And he fucking rules.
I'll introduce you one day.
He's with me.
He just wants to talk to his sister.
Come on.
Let's show him that we do know
how to be good hosts.
Have you seen yourself?
Remember what happened
the last time we left you alone?
What did you take this time?
Pablo didn't drug me.
We smoked a little, that's all.
I slept with him because I wanted to.
I had bad luck.
Not bad luck.
You slept with the wrong person,
but you don't learn
and keep hanging out with those people.
You still believe
it's a disease of the poor, right?
Pablo liked rich girls, just like you.
How do you think he got infected?
It can happen to anybody.
It can happen to you too.
HIV doesn't give a fuck
about how big your house is,
how much money you make,
or how long your list of last names is.
It's not like you.
Did you bring him here?
-Your brother just worries about you.
-He doesn't need to.
You sure?
So, you're free to wear a veil,
but I can't take my clothes off?
How does that work?
I also have a sister.
I wish somebody had worried that much
about her.
-She wouldn't have ended up like she did.
-How did she end up?
-Lost.
-What are you doing here?
Nothing. She's come to save my soul.
But it's a bit late for that.
Do you have anything without alcohol?
There's punch over there,
but they put too much sugar in it.
Hey, fuckers, be quiet!
My brother and I have some poetry
for you. Is that OK?
If not, too bad, it's our house. Hit it!
Yeah, yeah
Say, say, say, say
Passions, brothers, and blood
I have plenty balls to bust this jail
If money doesn't count
If my accounts are erratic
The reason for my hopes
Is not to stop making mistakes
My life is an extreme
And you say no
How to ash my cigarette
Or throw away a banana peel
I don't want any money
I prefer a heart
The bills asphyxiating you
Are not my prison
I'm everything you're waiting for
I'm the one coming for you at night
To make you dream
I'm the starless sky
That can light you up, ah!
Brother, listen
You'll draw your dreams
On paper buildings
To make them understand
There's no triumph in the future
Without fighting in the present
Are you OK?
-Yes, and you?
-I'm great.
Best party of my life.
Why don't you introduce me
to your friends?
Those are not my friends.
They are not my friends--
I'm not good with people.
Or at life in general.
Then why throw this party?
Sorry!
-Are you OK?
-Sorry. I'm really sorry.
-It's OK, don't worry.
-I'm really sorry.
-No problem, Samuel.
-Shit.
Are you having a good time?
A better time than you, for sure.
You've had a sour face all night.
You've been watching me, huh?
Look...
I also like to play, but with my luck,
I'm sure I would never get a turn.
I'd rather do it without the bottle.
Want to?
Truth.
Why have you been looking at me all night?
Why do you think
I've been looking at you all night?
Kiss.
Dare.
Let's get out of here.
And go where?
Is there anybody at your place?
Give me another pill.
Another?
Not like this, like before.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
Ander!
-Why are you here?
-Guzmán.
You lied to me
and used me to get away...
but the worst part is you did it
to come to this party. Why?
Look who it is!
-It's the Ken doll!
-I'm talking to my friend.
He's my friend, too.
Actually, I invited him.
-You're crashing.
-Yeah, I was dying to come.
Let's see.
I think the chlorine from the pool
must have atrophied
that part of the brain
that takes hints.
We don't want you here.
Shall I say it in English
so you understand?
-Guzmán...
-What are you doing?
-What are you on?
-Nothing.
-You are high!
-I'm not!
You can't shut up!
-I didn't take anything!
-You!
-What did you give him?
-Nothing.
Don't go near him again,
not even with a cough drop.
Or your sister, mother, father,
and your whole family
will know what you do, OK?
Guzmán, I'm fine.
Stop lying to me, you retard. He told me!
OK?
If it's about joints, pills,
or cheap hair gel, I trust him.
Don't yell at him. He's so dumb,
he told me unintentionally.
Fuck off, Guzmán!
Fuck you, too! And fuck you!
You hear me? Fuck all of you!
Maybe I'll wind up having a good time
after all.
-Nadia, did you drink?
-Only punch.
That punch is loaded with sugar.
Samu! The cops!
The cops!
Polo, have you told your mothers
you are coming with us to Sardinia
for Easter?
I may have other plans.
I need to think. I don't know if I'll go.
Whatever Guzmán says, surely.
Excuse me?
Wow, you're talking to me.
-Carla, this is not the mom--
-Come now, kid.
After the fortune your mothers
have spent on speech therapists!
Please, don't tag the wall, OK?
Or what? They'll take away your hot tub?
You think I'm the typical rich girl
who's had nothing bad happen to her?
Actually, yes.
-There's something you should know.
-Oh, really?
OK, then.
Truth.
What should I know?
Where to now?
-I'm going home, and so are you.
-Why?
Because you all are bad
at looking down on people.
At least we do it discreetly.
I want to swim in your pool.
The two of us, swimming in my pool?
No.
Shall I tell the principal...
what I saw in the showers?
So swimming in my pool, huh?
Fantastic idea.
-Let's go?
-Let's go.
You're not going to talk?
OK, it's enough if you listen.
I really don't understand.
Why did you have to ruin it all
if we both liked it?
I panicked, OK?
What if you like him better than me?
Remember what you told me after the party?
"I love you more than ever."
I felt the same way.
I loved you more than ever
because you did what you wanted,
regardless of what people think.
Carla!
Fuck the world.
-What else do you want to do?
-You want to know?
Come on in.
-Shit. Please, they can't see you here.
-That wouldn't be good for me either.
Wait here for a moment, OK?
Hello.
What are you doing?
Nothing. You?
-You could have answered my calls.
-And you could leave me alone, right?
Omar.
-Have another pill?
-Stop it.
Guys. You deal?
Get lost.
-No.
-What are you doing? Let's go.
Stop.
I mean, do you sell pills or anything?
-Do we look like dealers?
-Ander, come, let's go.
You don't look like boy scouts.
-Man.
-Is he for real?
Ander!
Who do you think you are, rich boy? Look.
Hey, leave him alone.
Easy, man. Easy.
Please, stop.
Leave him alone.
Can't you see he's high?
Please.
Stop, please.
Let's go.
-Get out of here!
-Take your boyfriend, you fucking Muslim!
See? If you'd given me a fucking pill,
this wouldn't have happened.
Go fuck yourself, man.
And don't call me again.
Or write.
Why?
Why? Are you so high you don't remember?
Your friend threatened me.
-And if they find out about me...
-Which part?
If that gets out, you'll ruin my life.
It's best if...
we don't see each other again.
Best for both of us.
Nadia?
Are you getting in?
Are you OK?
I've never felt better.
You've been drugged, Nadia.
You're high.
Where are you going?
To get a towel and call a cab.
What happened?
What do you mean, what happened?
He hurt himself in your pool.
Ander?
Yes, Antonio, sorry.
I'm surprised.
I didn't know it was that bad.
-Good morning.
Yes, he'll have to wear it for two weeks.
You should be more careful.
It was my fault. I wasn't looking,
and he started goofing off.
It won't happen again.
I'll keep an eye on him.
All right, then.
What?
It means "I'm sorry."
I should have stayed out of your life.
How do you say "I'm still hungover"?
You remind me of May. My sister.
She used to smile all the time too.
Even if she felt sad on the inside.
Mainly, when she felt sad on the inside.
What did you mean the other day
when you said she was lost?
She drank.
She smoked.
Went out with boys.
She wanted to be like all Spanish girls.
She ended up doing what none of them do.
She left home at 18.
It's been two years...
without any news from her.
All I know...
is she left my family brokenhearted.
And the last thing I want
is to do the same.
-I think I'm also losing myself a little.
-Nadia.
We are 16 years old.
If we don't lose ourselves now, then when?
We have all our lives
to find ourselves again.
We have a witness
who saw you run bloodstained
out of the school.
A witness?
Of course. Some rich kid, probably.
Of course, because they never lie, right?
Our witness is Samuel.
Your brother.
Is he lying?
He knows perfectly well
I would never hurt Marina.
-Why?
-Because we were together.
Thank you.
What for?
For... not taking advantage
of the situation.
And for the cab.
-I'll pay you back.
-No problem. My treat.
Who would have thought.
You are a gentleman.
You surprised me too.
I did not see that business
with the pool coming.
Gentlemen don't mention those things.
Never. Ever. OK?
OK.
Can I give you some advice? As a friend.
-Are we friends?
-No.
But we are women.
And I don't like it when men toy with us.
-I don't know what you're talking about.
-Guzmán's only interested in you
because he bet
he could take your virginity.
To then humiliate you and tell everybody.
To get back at you for threatening him
the night of the party.
He's so vindictive.
That is a lie.
Ask him.
-Ready, girls?
-Friends?
Positions, and...
Nadia.
I swear it was her idea.
And you think that's an excuse?
I'd expect it from her.
But I don't know what to think of you.
I had you in my pool, ready for anything,
and I didn't touch you.
Not for lack of wanting to. It's true.
I could have taken advantage, but...
I could've taken advantage,
but I didn't.
So... I should thank you.
For not going through
with your plan to humiliate me.
Do you realize how disgusting it is
to even consider that?
The kind of person that makes you?
You're no saint either.
Excuse me?
You spread your legs for me in my pool,
Nadia.
I had been drugged.
Marina.
I'd offer to pay your dry cleaning,
but I'd be lying. I'm broke.
-It doesn't matter.
-Yes, it does.
You're avoiding me, and I understand.
I screwed up the other day.
-You didn't.
-I did.
I had too much wine, vodka...
too much alcohol.
I wanted to feel brave,
-but I just threw up.
-Don't--
I needed some Dutch courage
to tell you I like you.
Samuel, I'm not good for you.
There's things about me--
What things?
I am HIV-positive.
I don't know what to say.
It doesn't matter.
I'm OK with you not saying anything...
to anybody.
You can stay at my place.
So when they show up at mine,
they'll find my mom and Samu, right?
-Life sucks, Nano.
-Fucking right.
Look at her. She's saying
she wants to meet so we can talk.
I'll pass.
If they want to spice things up,
they should find somebody else.
Do you know why they need
to spice up their relationship?
Because it's bland, Christian.
That's why they're looking
for a good stud. Listen...
The more she can compare...
the more she'll see
that what she has looks expensive,
but it's just a cheap plastic trinket.
-So what are you trying to say?
-Don't be stupid.
That guy's letting you steal
his girlfriend right under his nose.
You can't pass on that.
I won't.
Attaboy.
You can't be doing this to me, Carla!
What do you mean,
you have something else to do?
Do you think I'm stupid?
Why don't you just say you have a date
with that fucking influencer?
You know what?
I pity you for letting people
boss you around like this.
And for having such low self-esteem...
dear.
Stop treating me like I'm being abused,
OK?
You say you're progressive
and that you do what you want with men,
but the only reason you agreed
to be Guzmán's fuck buddy
is that he didn't want anything serious,
and you wanted him really bad.
Oh, sorry.
I was just putting my ovaries
on the table.
Hello.
Son of a bitch!
Check out this shack!
It's beautiful!
Is this yours?
Our parents bought it for us,
and we are furnishing it little by little.
We got the bed last Friday.
Great.
Christian, do you like fish?
Is that a trick question?
We're about to order dinner. Our treat.
-Besides, I think we owe you that.
-OK.
Listen...
The neighbor who called the cops told mom.
So we are in trouble. What's the matter?
Marina.
What's wrong with Marina?
She's HIV-positive, Nano.
That's not the worst part.
I stood there and didn't know what to say.
Instead of telling her I don't care.
Besides, it's not a problem.
I've been reading up online,
and nowadays, it's no big deal.
Instead, I just stood there
and stared like an idiot.
We have it all planned. All of it.
Even our retirement.
-Sometimes, it's too much, right?
-Yeah.
That's why we decided to add some...
-spice to our lives.
-And that would be me, right?
The spice.
Which one am I?
Pepper, cayenne, hot chili?
Forgive us, really.
But... it wasn't so horrible, right?
At least, I hope so.
Didn't you have a good time?
I did.
Would you like to do it again?
Have you ever had a threesome?
I love you more than ever.
He told you, right?
I'm on medication. It's undetectable.
That means I can't infect you.
I don't care that you didn't tell me.
But you kept quiet
because you were afraid I'd bolt.
It's not a problem, it's normal.
But that's why you told Samu,
to scare him away.
-Maybe.
-Marina, please.
You don't know him. You won't be able to.
He'll research it, and tomorrow,
he'll know more about it than you.
Why are you here?
Shit.
Stop toying with my brother,
and tell him the fucking truth.
That you're not into him.
I'm not toying with him.
-I feel something, but...
-Yeah.
Like with me the other night?
No way. That is easy to see.
You felt something, too.
Didn't you?
Come on.
Truth.
This isn't a fucking game!
Did you know she was pregnant?
Did I know?
Whose baby do you think that was?
Why do you think
we were going to run away together?
I went to school to pick her up...
I found her like that.
We wanted to get as far
as we could from here.
Do you know who couldn't stand the idea?
Your fucking witness.
Are you...
suggesting...
that your brother killed her?
Subtitle translation
by Soledad Etchemendy