So, according to you,
everything started
with the arrival of the new students.
When a new species is introduced
into an ecosystem, it is always altered.
The new one can devastate
the flora and fauna of a place,
breed endlessly,
or cause more subtle changes
which end up perverting everything.
Are you referring to the new students
as if they were another species?
I don't want to believe
that Marina's... dead.
Nowadays, we use social networks
to present ourselves to others.
What we show, or what we hide,
says a lot about who we are.
And this is what the pair work
I want you to do is about.
I want you to create
your partner's profile
for a social network.
Wasn't this language
and literature class?
Welcome to Las Encinas, man.
We can demonize social networks,
like other schools do, but...
we can also use them to learn.
Please, take advantage of the opportunity
to investigate, to question each other.
And most of all, adapt this to your goal.
What is it, Christian?
I just have a question.
What can I improve in my profile? Nothing!
It can be improved.
When he was talking about privilege
and intelligence, he didn't mean you.
Boom! Take that.
Guys...
Please, be creative.
Use photos, videos, interviews,
whatever you want.
You have all the school's resources
at your disposal.
Nobody leaves until they have a partner.
Choose one and come by my desk.
Here's your chance.
To do what?
What do you mean, "to do what"?
Our plan for Miss Palestine.
Go and tell her you want to work with her.
You are with me, right?
That way, I'll get to see you more.
You've been avoiding me.
What a silly thing to say.
Of course we'll work together.
So, want to work together?
You won't have much to do.
My profile rules.
And once we upload some photos
of your trophies and the girls you get,
yours will be done in no time.
Then we can smoke a joint.
Shut up!
Samuel.
We can work together if you want.
You and I?
OK.
Want to work together?
-But we have nothing in common.
-Even better.
We can learn more about each other.
Motherfucker.
-Nano, are those burgers ready?
-Almost there. Why the hurry?
Get a move on.
I said you had experience.
They're complaining.
-Samu, don't bust my balls.
-Hurry.
Here you are.
We were so happy in this town
without these snobs!
I don't know where she is.
Carla's avoiding me.
You must have done something.
You have to take care of her.
You won't find another one like her.
I've told you before, haven't I? Huh?
-Put your phone down, please. We are here!
-It's my dad. He wants me to train.
-Sorry.
-Hey, waiter, thank you.
-I've had faster service.
-Sorry. We have new staff.
I wish you were as good at working
as you are at making excuses.
This is overcooked.
You know I can't answer back.
That's why you're doing this.
-He's talking to me.
-Just eat it. It looks good.
She read my message. It's blue.
Why won't she answer?
I get it.
-Is it clear?
-Yes.
Nano, what's going on?
Nothing.
-Besides, they're leaving, right?
-That's up to you.
Give me time.
Good afternoon.
-Nano, tell me what's going on.
-Samu, it's nothing.
Forget it.
Guys, I'm leaving.
-You're leaving? How come?
-Gotta train, I told you.
-But finish your food.
-If I do, I'll be late.
-See you tomorrow.
Should I write to her again or...
send her an audio message?
I'll send her an audio message. Yeah.
Hey.
How much do you want?
It's good, you'll see.
Hey. We can finish this one if you want.
Can I ask you a question?
If it's about the other night,
it's best if you don't.
I was drunk. And... I wanted to try.
Just to try.
Guys... are... not my thing.
-What?
-You wanted to suck my dick.
Come.
You OK?
Shit.
They're freezing.
What are you doing?
Putting it on the seat,
so you're more comfortable.
What is it? Thought the Muslim boy
was gonna rob you, or what?
No, it's not that, but...
I don't feel comfortable.
Let's stop.
What is it?
It was you who wanted it.
Dude...
Are you really freaking out?
No, but, leave me alone, OK? I'm going.
Describe your relationship
with the new kids.
-It was normal, nothing special.
-And with Omar?
He's a friend.
Ander. What's up, man?
Hey.
-How was training yesterday?
-Good.
Very good, man.
-My dad's cracking the whip, but good.
-OK.
Listen.
-You know you can tell me anything?
-Sure, I know.
I mean,
we've been friends our entire lives.
Yes.
I'm off to train.
Now, a hobby.
-You've been recording for ten minutes.
-Give me a hobby, and I'm done.
Seriously, I didn't plan
to work so hard on my part.
I thought they strove for excellence here.
-Tell me something I don't know.
-Fine, but not here. I'd feel awkward.
Let's go.
-Come on!
-What are we doing here?
Don't ask. We have ten minutes
before the basketball players arrive.
And you should know,
I've shown this to very few of my friends.
Now I'm ready.
-Are you recording?
-I'm recording.
You'll end up with a great project.
Why did you make these videos?
For a school project.
That's all.
Marina loved to dance.
Siblings?
One, you know him. Nano.
Nano.
How's it going
in the kitchen at La Cabaña?
For him, or for me since he started?
OK. I'm writing you get along famously.
So we're lying, right?
Then you can write that I get along
with my brother.
Look, I'm happy my brother is out of jail.
It's just that sometimes...
What?
Let's not get intense. Photos.
Do we use what we have, or take new ones?
I can dance, but posing for photos
is entirely different.
Let me see.
This folder.
-Yes, that one.
-OK.
This one's really cool.
What are you talking about?
This one's not bad,
but none of them show your face.
-That's normal.
-Normal, yeah, right.
CONSTRUCTION COMPANY NUNIER, INC.
RESPONSIBLE FOR COLLAPSE
OF SAN ESTEBAN SECONDARY SCHOOL
ENTREPRENEUR VENTURA NUNIER
INVOLVED IN FURIA SCANDAL
What's this?
Sorry.
I opened something I shouldn't have.
-It's no secret he's my father, right?
-Why do you have all those articles?
Well...
Because...
It doesn't matter.
Let's do this later, OK?
-See you tomorrow, Carla.
-Bye.
Hi there.
See? No problem.
OK. I didn't want to complicate stuff
with your boyfriend.
Don't worry. We are only texting.
Fine. I'll go smoke a joint,
and we'll talk later.
What did he say?
The poor thing is clueless.
He's afraid if you see us talking,
you'll suspect and get jealous.
Me? Jealous of that guy?
He's more muscle than brain
and can't tell the difference--
Of course not.
How about we do it again?
With Christian.
I'm so glad you persuaded me to do it.
-I didn't persuade you.
-I want to do it again.
Say yes, please.
We'll talk later, OK?
OK.
So, how do we go about this? My--
My place or yours?
My parents wouldn't like me
to be seen with you.
They don't know me.
All my friends' mothers say
I'm the perfect son-in-law.
For my parents, the perfect son-in-law
prays five times a day, facing Mecca.
Do you do it?
Yes. It helps me find myself.
We're not getting married.
It's a project.
Can't we work on it during breaks?
I've written some questions.
Answer them by tomorrow.
And we're done.
We'll talk tomorrow.
Wow.
I think Miss Palestine is not going
to make it easy for you.
If I were you...
I'd put in a little more effort, honey.
-Please!
-Shut up!
Excuse us.
We have this project--
-Hi.
I'm looking for Samuel.
He's on a break. Out back.
-That way.
-Thanks.
Hey.
Hey, what's going on?
-I was looking for your brother.
-And you found me.
It's gonna become a habit.
Fuck!
How's everything here?
Fantastic. I'm a total chef.
I can tell.
Hello.
They told me you were out here.
-Want some?
-No, thanks. Enjoy.
Listen... Sorry I left like that.
Don't worry.
Want to work on the project?
My name is Marina,
and as you know, I like to dance.
But what I would really like to do
is make documentaries.
Do investigative reports.
The truth is,
that has always been my dream.
Although, I don't know now...
-Why not?
-How could I call myself a journalist
if I now have the chance
to expose somebody, and I don't do it?
Nobody's gonna blame you
for not ruining your father.
Not even if I had incriminating evidence?
There's money in the safe
in my father's office at home.
And, about a year ago,
I needed to take some.
We all know the combination.
It's my date of birth.
So, I opened the safe,
and there were photos,
documents, and some emails.
They were addressed to a minister
in the government.
My father was telling him that,
because the budget was so tight,
the materials might not be
of the best quality.
Was it about my school?
I don't know,
but I think something similar happened
with your school.
Now you know more than any of my friends.
Don't even think of using that
in the project, OK?
Of course I will!
After the part about you liking to dance.
-That you have a corrupt father.
-Don't even joke about that.
-But of course!
-Samuel.
Break is over.
-See you tomorrow.
Waiter!
Bye, thanks.
Hi, how are you? Go ahead, please.
Hello.
Good afternoon.
-Why are you here? What do you want?
-To introduce myself to your parents.
Hi, how are you?
Guzmán Nunier, pleased to meet you.
-I'm your daughter's classmate.
-Hello.
-I came to ask if I may study with her.
-You'd better leave.
Why? What's the matter?
That I'm not a Muslim?
That my father is who he is? What is it?
I said we'd work during breaks.
-What's the problem? Who's his father?
-Dad...
-Guzmán, go.
-He paid for her scholarship.
I think it would be best
if you let me stay...
and work with her.
Why have you come here? To insult me?
Do you know, because of your father,
my son and others
have to travel 30 km to go to school?
Do you know
how many kids could have died?
Sir, I've come in good faith
to ask if I can work with your daughter.
Leave.
Enough, Guzmán.
What do I have to buy so you let me stay
and explain myself?
What's going on?
Guzmán, please. Go.
We know this is a difficult time.
But we need to ask you some questions.
How was your relationship
with your sister?
What kind of question is that?
I loved her very much.
Hi, sweetie.
Have you taken your medication?
Listen, if you have any discomfort,
nausea, or whatever, tell me, OK?
-Hi, Mommy.
-Hi, sweetie.
-Are you OK?
-Yes, great.
You know Mom only talks about my pills
when she mixes anxiety meds with alcohol?
It's hard for her, Marina.
It's no picnic for me either.
Hey.
Hey, Marina.
What did we say?
Huh?
Through good times, bad times, and?
And the times that are fucked up.
What are you doing?
The store's unattended.
I'm going. Don't worry.
-Keep an eye on it.
-Yes. Nag.
HI, ARE YOU STILL FREAKED OUT?
There's money in the safe
in my father's office at home.
We all know the combination.
It's my date of birth.
To give it a sentimental touch.
What are you doing?
Recording fancy girl in your free time?
-It's for a school project.
-A school project.
How modern. Come on, Spielberg,
it's dinner time.
GORGEOUS, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WAITING FOR YOU IN MY BED...
THINKING OF YOU
DON'T SAY THAT, YOU ARE KILLING ME...
-Hi, hon.
-Hi.
-What are you doing?
-Chatting with Christian.
-About what?
-Not much.
But it was getting interesting.
Do you want to join me so it gets better?
We'll have a good time.
What do I tell him?
Tell him you only get turned on
if they know how to play.
And ask him if he knows how to play.
And if he's willing to go all the way.
You are into this!
He wants to know
what my boyfriend would think.
That you're a very naughty girlfriend.
And you want to be worse than naughty.
I am a very naughty girlfriend.
And I want to be... worse than naughty.
What would you do to me
if I were there with you?
I'd treat you like a queen.
Tell him you have your boyfriend for that.
Now, I'm in the mood for something else.
He says...
"I'm so turned on."
Should I continue?
Make him come.
Hey, you.
-Yes, you.
-Christian.
Whatever your name is. I have a question.
Do you know this Muslim guy?
-Nadia's brother?
-Yes, Omar.
-Why? Who talked to you about him?
-Ander, he told me about him.
Buddy, you want to score?
Wow, I didn't think you smoked, but...
-I guess we all have our vices, huh?
-Right. And what exactly does he sell?
-He has grass, paki, pollen, acorns--
-Acorns?
Another kind of hash, dude. Softer.
-They're drugs, right? Okay.
-Joints.
Whatever you want, he can get it.
Give me a call,
and I'll send you his number.
-Already thinking about planting a bomb?
-Yes, on your face!
...on your face!
Hi, Nadia.
Listen, sorry about yesterday.
-It got out of hand.
-I shouldn't be talking to you.
What were you thinking?
I went with the best intentions
to show your father I am a good person.
Nailed it.
After all,
arrogance runs through your veins.
Nadia.
Good morning!
How can I make it up to you?
Relax.
And nothing.
I finished the project without you.
The information I had was enough
to finish your profile.
Martín.
I have a question. It's about the project.
Nadia says she's finished,
but I really think it's incomplete.
-May I?
-Yes, of course.
Is this all you have?
Four photos and...
I don't know.
How much more does one need
to introduce oneself on social media?
Nadia, I think there's something
you haven't understood.
At this school,
we take projects very seriously.
They're as important as exams.
Or even more. This is a demanding task.
Guys,
I thought I had explained myself clearly.
When I read your profiles,
I want to get a clear idea
of who your partner is.
You're making a lot of effort, Martín,
for someone
who doesn't deserve much attention.
No, I don't try too hard.
I think she can do it,
and she can be the best in the class.
You all can if you try.
The emails were addressed to a minister
in the government.
My father was telling him that,
because the budget was so tight,
the materials might not be
of the best quality.
I can't stop thinking
about our chat yesterday.
It was very instructive.
-We'll have to put that into practice.
-I'm all yours.
Your place or mine? Probably yours.
Are you going to meet up
with this moron?
-What about Polo?
-Guzmán, mind your own business.
-My friend's girlfriend is my business.
-Not at all.
-You heard her, man. Go away.
-You can't order me around in my school.
Too bad your school's my school.
Besides, we're both asking you, so... go.
Let me explain this to you, you idiot.
Neither you nor anybody
from your shitty town can say anything
to me.
Know why?
Because, to me, you don't exist.
If I hit you,
that might confirm my existence.
What are you doing?
This nobody is trying to steal
your girlfriend.
"Your girlfriend, my school, my rules."
Your concept of property is a bit much.
If I get the girl,
it's because she wants it.
You calm down, too.
-Sorry, babe.
-Did you hear that? He calls her "babe"!
Look, don't...
Let's go, Guzmán. Please.
That's enough.
So, at your place, then? We'll talk.
Why were you so calm
while I defended your girlfriend?
-Why are you getting involved?
-Because he's stealing her, don't you see?
Don't be old-fashioned.
You sound like a Neanderthal.
Whatever you say,
but I know what I saw.
-So put an end to this, Polo--
-Guzmán, it's arranged.
She's hooking up with him
because I want her to.
It's a game, OK?
Let's see, Polo...
What the fuck do you win in this game?
But, Guzmán, we're using him.
She hooks up with him,
but I tell her what to do with him.
And while they do it...
I watch them.
But, man...
Shit, all right.
I didn't know things were that bad.
-But--
-Listen, what if Carla falls for him?
Anyway...
End this as soon as possible, Polito.
OK?
Martín? I have a question. May I come in?
-Yes, of course.
-Thank you.
I know that...
with the new kids getting
into the school and...
them being at a disadvantage,
it's logical for you
to give them more attention.
How can I say it without sounding rude?
Don't worry,
I'm sure you'll find the words. Tell me.
Do you think
it's OK to pay more attention to a girl
with such archaic and non-feminist values?
You want me to discriminate?
No, just don't pay
so much attention to her.
She doesn't pay your salary,
the rest of the parents do.
I am your teacher, Lu, not your employee.
And I'm telling you
that your contract is renewed annually.
And that the idea of the new kids
getting into the school was not...
popular with our parents.
It was just a front.
Think about it.
About whose side you are on.
Have a nice day.
I wish those three had never come
to the school, that's all.
-Do you hate them so much?
-I'm not the only one, I can assure you.
Hello.
Hello. What are you doing here?
-Want to work on the project?
-Sure.
Do you want to take pictures
since we have good lighting?
-Don't be shy, tell me how to pose.
-I think this is stupid.
Let me see.
Is this how you see me? Only this?
Don't be afraid to sexualize me.
Relax, take a couple more.
Get dressed.
You are so boring, really.
-What are you doing?
-Who cares? No one's here.
Since we are here,
and you're not looking at me...
at least ask me questions, OK?
Well... I don't know.
Why were you hell-bent
on doing this project with me?
To make fun of me?
Since you're not taking pictures,
I'll take one of you. Stand there.
There's good light.
Let's see.
Turn around.
Turn slightly to your left.
To your left, Nadia! Are you dyslexic?
-I should delete it.
-Why?
It doesn't say anything about you.
I have no fucking idea who you are.
I'll wait for you outside.
What happened?
Some men came asking for Nano.
I didn't let them in,
and they forced the door open.
-Let me get this--
-Nothing happened.
They only meant to scare her, that's all.
-I told her it won't happen again.
-Was it the guys from La Cabaña?
Who from La Cabaña?
-What about La Cabaña?
-Come.
Who from La Cabaña?
What did you get into?
Shut the door.
Tell me, Nano...
do you think it's normal for junkies
to come here and threaten Mom?
-I owe a lot of money, Samu. A lot.
-What? You just got out of jail.
I owe it to people in there.
To the people who protected me.
-I promised them a lot of money.
-What are you saying?
-Things were messed up there.
And I had to find a way to get by.
Look at the present they gave me.
I didn't tell you so as not to scare you.
But now, I need to pay up.
If something happens to me,
I don't care, it's my problem.
-But I can't let anything happen to you.
-Are you being serious, Nano?
Do I look like I'm joking?
Help me.
How?
I saw what fancy girl told you.
About her father's papers.
Help me get them.
I can sell them, blackmail him.
You're telling me you used my computer
when I've told you--
Can you think of a better way
to get 40,000 bucks?
If you have one, tell me.
Nano, you're on fucking parole.
I can't let you do that.
If I don't do it, we are fucked.
Mom... you, and I.
Brother, I'm screwed.
I'll do it myself.
I'll get you the papers.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Fuck!
Looking for this?
You have no right to search my room.
How did you find it?
Guzmán, a good friend of yours.
Do you know what can happen
if you test positive for drugs?
-It's the second time I've bought.
-And why?
-Why do you want to ruin your career?
-Come on, it's just a joint.
You are an idiot.
This is the last time.
Carla.
I think we should drop
this thing with Christian.
-Why?
-I've been talking to Guzmán.
For fuck's sake.
As I was telling him about it,
I realized it sounded crazy.
What are we doing?
Are we really going to stop experimenting
and having fun
because of what your friend thinks?
We all know what he's like.
Listen, we are playing with fire.
It's not normal.
It's not normal for people our age
to do these things.
And that's it.
-Right?
-When have you and I been normal?
My mom's a wine-making marchioness,
and your moms are a pair of rich
and influential lesbians.
You and I are anything but normal.
I don't know.
You don't want to relive the other day?
Or yesterday?
Because I can't stop thinking about it.
And I know you.
-I know you feel the same.
-I don't think it's the same.
Our lives are already written.
And I'm not saying they're bad lives.
But, why not stray from the script,
at least a little bit?
I don't know.
-What don't you know?
-I don't know.
-What? That you love me?
-Huh?
-I do love you.
-I love you.
-And you?
Wait in the lobby.
We'll continue talking in a while.
Thank you.
Polo, you may come in.
Sorry, why do you want to talk to me?
They are questioning everybody,
don't worry.
They suspect Guzmán.
Really? Yes.
Good morning!
Good morning.
-Good morning.
-A bit sluggish this morning?
I'm a little tired.
I have to show you what I've done.
I have your profile almost ready.
I am still a bit stuck with yours.
How come?
We can work on it
this afternoon at my place.
Sure.
But my mom's at home.
It may be better to do it at yours.
Of course.
-Are you OK?
-Yes. I'm still sleepy.
-What the fuck did you do?
-Calm down.
-You got me in trouble!
-I'm worried about you. You're my friend.
Then talk to me,
don't snitch to my parents.
You know how I feel about drugs.
-After what happened to my sister.
-Get over it already!
Get over what happened!
And stop messing with the rest of us.
Would you say Guzmán is violent?
You suspect Guzmán?
Guzmán wouldn't hurt his sister
or anybody else.
It's just a draft.
If you want,
we can change the whole thing.
I don't know.
I feel a little exposed, Samuel.
Besides, you end it by saying:
"Sad, intelligent eyes
which seem to have suffered too much."
-Too much?
-I don't know.
Maybe this is nothing but a bored
and vain rich girl putting on an act.
Why would you do that?
To keep guys away
and avoid being upended by love again.
I've never felt that.
You're not missing out, really.
You don't want it to happen again?
I don't know, it scares me.
What are you scared of?
Hello. How are you?
Hi. What are you doing here?
How did you let him talk you into this?
-She's here to work on the project.
-So is Samu.
-Hello.
OK, we're off.
We don't want to bother you.
OK.
Nadia. Don't let him tease you too much.
Whistle if you need me, OK?
Guzmán!
Honey, I'm calling you, and you're...
You're not answering.
I don't know what you're doing,
or where you are.
Please, call me when you get this, OK?
So?
Why are you being so flattering?
Am I a challenge,
or a bet you made with your friends?
Let's see how long it takes
the Muslim girl to fall for me.
What?
Is your self-esteem so low
that you think
I'd only be with you because of a bet?
Then I'm a challenge.
-The impossible turns you on.
-I feel comfortable with you.
We have a lot in common.
Come now, I doubt that.
Well, you believe in your God.
You respect your parents.
You're responsible.
Me too. Look.
Here we go again!
See?
Only I wouldn't strip
to show you I believe in Allah.
-Put your shirt on. Or you'll catch cold.
-We all have our ways, Nadia.
And it is true that I often use my body
and my charm to get what I want.
Maybe I don't quite believe
someone could like me
just for what I think or feel.
-Do you have your cell phone on you?
-Want to take a picture?
No.
No!
-Well?
-Guzmán.
Not so brave now, huh?
-Please!
-Come on, laugh now!
-Come on, stop it.
-Laugh at me now.
-Go on, laugh.
-Please, Guzmán!
-No!
-Look.
-Please!
-No.
-Come.
-Guzmán! Please!
I was winning.
OK. Should we continue?
-Can I use your bathroom?
-Sure, it's right over there.
Right...
I don't feel so good,
and it would be embarrassing...
-Use the one downstairs.
-OK, thanks.
You still need a couple of photos
at the end, but it's ready.
Hi, Dad.
Hi, Nadia.
-Are you at school?
-No.
I'm with Samuel, doing homework.
-Sure, with the waiter.
-Put him on.
-I want to ask him something.
-Eh... Of course.
He's in the bathroom, one second.
-Shit, I have to find Samuel.
-Go.
Marina!
-Have you seen Samuel?
-He's in the bathroom.
-The one downstairs.
-Shit!
Samuel.
-Hello? You still there?
-Dad, one moment.
What am I doing?
Samuel!
-Samuel!
-What?
It's my father.
-Tell him we are studying at your house.
-Hello?
Hi, Mr. Shanaa. It's Samuel.
We are at home, working on something
for school.
-We're almost done.
-What are you doing?
I couldn't find the bathroom.
-It's down there!
-I couldn't find it.
Nadia will be there soon, OK?
Nice place!
Listen, where's your mother?
ALMOST THERE
-She's rarely here.
-Right, of course.
I suppose marchionesses
also have things to do.
-Hello, Mirella.
-Hello.
Hello.
Yeah, well, she always says
they have been social parasites,
and a blight on this country,
but she got into wine.
Into making it, that is,
not drinking it.
Although, every now and then,
she opens a bottle.
-I'll introduce you one day.
-OK. Cool.
Wow, nice bathtub you marquises have!
-Hello, Mirella.
-Hello.
Carla is expecting me.
Hey, you don't see me
just as a sex object, right?
It's OK!
It's OK, don't worry. You can carry on.
On the plus side, I'm more comfortable
than I was at Marina's.
Polo.
-What?
-You haven't told him?
The other day, I was there, watching you.
Did you think you'd fuck my girl
without me enjoying it?
Polo!
What's he talking about? Is that true?
You knew?
Poor guy!
He thought he was hooking up
with a Spanish grandee.
You imagined yourself a married winemaker?
You're making fun of me?
-No, we're not.
-No.
I think you are.
Fucking rich people!
-Let's talk.
-Fucking snobs.
Christian!
-Let's talk about it.
-No! Do you realize what you have?
Take care of her, please, man!
You can't let people fuck her!
And you watching, on top of it!
Fuck off, will you?
Good evening.
How can you be so stupid?
If you didn't want to,
you should have told me.
I did tell you,
but you didn't listen to me.
What's the matter?
Do you care so much
about that bumpkin's feelings?
The only bumpkin here...
is you.
Fuck off!
You don't tell me to fuck off, Carla.
Carla!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HEY, FINALLY
SORRY. I'VE BEEN BUSY
WANT SOME POT?
NO, I'D RATHER SEE YOU WITHOUT AN EXCUSE
-Hi, darling.
-Hi, Dad.
How did it go with Samuel?
It went well. We finished the project.
Were you at Samuel's?
-Dad...
-I didn't expect this from you.
You lied to me.
Daughters like you don't do that.
I don't want those people
to change you, Nadia.
And I don't want you to disappoint
your mother and me.
We have sacrificed a lot for you two.
Don't make us feel we made a mistake.
No more lies.
Don't you have to study?
There is no power or strength saved
in Allah.
Omar, leave me alone, I have to study.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO MEET TOMORROW?
I'M REALLY BUSY
You don't have it?
You said you would get it.
I couldn't do it.
I'm not going to rob her father.
-You'd rather save her family than ours?
-I didn't do it because I like her.
I really like Marina.
You dumbshit!
You have no shot with her. Samu!
What?
You're screwing me over for a girl
who doesn't care about you.
You are an idiot!
Guys, I got all your projects in my inbox,
and I wanted to thank you.
I'm very happy with them.
I imagine you've realized this was
a very important project
to get to know ourselves better,
and to find out what it is
that we want others to know about us.
What is the image we want to project?
What is it we hide from others?
Are we really...
what others believe we are,
or do they only see our best side?
You want me to tell you
what Marina was like?
Marina was light.
Marina was...
one of those people
you meet on a Monday and...
you want to look in the face,
because she will smile
and brighten your day.
Do you have any more questions?
Guzmán...
Maybe there's one thing
you didn't know about your sister.
Look.
We got the autopsy results.
She was pregnant.
Subtitle translation
by Soledad Etchemendy