MOMMY- COME HOME
GUZMÁN- WHERE ARE YOU?
Excuse me.
Darling.
Everything is going to be fine. All right?
All three heads
of the construction company are accused
of alleged embezzlement of public funds,
bribery, and criminal negligence.
Shit, poor people.
That's us. At least I stole to eat,
unlike these rich people.
I meant their families.
But, of course,
you wouldn't understand that, huh?
Always a mean comment.
-Have you talked to Marina?
-No.
You should talk to her.
She must be having a terrible time.
Poor girl.
-Hello.
-Don't worry, man.
-Really, don't.
It's OK.
It's pre-trial detention.
We pay bail, and he's out.
-And how much is it?
-Three hundred thousand.
-We'll pay this afternoon.
-And the trial?
It doesn't matter. They have nothing.
-Then why did they accuse him?
-I don't know, Ander. Shit, I don't know!
Some judge wanted to be on the news,
no fucking idea!
They have nothing against him, OK?
They have no proof.
That's what your dad says, Carla.
Come on, we come in peace, Christian.
Yeah, being called a thief
makes me feel awesome.
We're saying that
if it was you who took the watches,
we really don't care.
Return them, and we forget about it.
How can I forget
what I know nothing about?
How are you?
Not well, I'm not gonna lie to you.
Samuel, I don't want to talk now.
Christian, we only care about one watch.
The one with a red leather strap.
It was my grandfather's.
He died last Christmas.
-My father is very attached to it.
-Can you listen?
Yes.
Sorry. Um...
-Want to talk later?
-Whenever you want.
If it shows up tomorrow in my desk,
we'll forget about it.
Enough already. Why me?
-Am I the only one who's been there?
-You're the only one--
Who is penniless, right?
-And that makes me a thief!
-I didn't say that.
-We all know rich people don't steal.
-Christian, when did I say that?
Carla, are you all right?
What is it?
-Your grandfather isn't dead.
-How much did you hear?
All of it.
Except why that watch is so important.
It's a pen drive, with documents.
Don't tell your brother, OK?
Papers from the business my father
and yours have.
If they were to fall
into the wrong hands right now...
-Stay calm, Carla--
-No.
DON'T GIVE THEM THE WATCH
WITH THE RED LEATHER STRAP
What are you doing?
Reading comments.
Babe, that's the first thing
you should stop doing. OK?
Hey.
What's up with you?
Does your religion not allow you
to console your friends?
Or maybe you can't forgive him
for sleeping with me again.
Really!
I don't care about what you two have.
My dear...
Now that you've taken the veil off,
you should consider removing
that blindfold.
-Guzmán and I--
-Let's see if you get it.
The only man
I'm interested in right now...
is called Dostoevsky.
But, of course, every time there's a man,
even if he's been dead for a century,
you can't help getting in the middle, huh?
He died in 1881. He's been dead 137 years.
You've convinced me.
It's obvious
you don't give a shit about Guzmán.
OMAR, CAN YOU COME TO THE SCHOOL?
Give me a moment, man.
Hey! What are you doing here?
Are you stupid?
-Hi, by the way.
-You know who Marina's brother is?
You know what he might do if he finds out?
-I don't care, I need the money.
-Omar.
What for? What do you want?
-What do you care?
-I care about you, idiot!
I don't want you to...
To end up in jail or worse
for a pair of sneakers, or a motorbike.
I already live in a fucking jail.
This! This dough will set me free.
I need it to leave home.
Do you understand now?
-Omar.
-Let go.
Omar!
Marina.
I wanted to talk to you.
-Sure.
-How are you?
Fine. Well, better.
I'm glad.
I wanted to tell you that we are here
for anything you need.
-Are you OK?
-Mm-hmm.
Now it's exam time,
we'll do everything we can--
Oh, dear!
-Do you have a tissue?
-No!
Open your locker, Marina.
-I'll have to talk to your mother.
-No. She can't deal with another problem.
I don't know, we've all fucked up
at some point, right?
It would be a shame that for one mistake,
no matter how big,
everything went to hell, right, Martín?
Let's see,
Marina is an exemplary student, Azucena.
And we should consider the circumstances,
right?
This could stay between us.
But, it can't happen again.
OK, but to ensure that,
we need to nip it in the bud.
Who sold it?
-What?
-Your dealer.
The one who didn't hesitate
to sell drugs to a minor at school.
I don't know. He never mentioned his name.
You have his number in your cell.
Didn't you text him to meet?
Your phone.
I DIDN'T GIVE IT TO THEM
-No.
-Marina, this is serious.
I only need a name.
Marina, give me the phone! Marina!
-I can't.
-Give it to me!
I'll give you a name,
but don't report him.
Give me the phone.
Omar!
His name is Omar. He's Nadia's brother.
I think this is all getting
a bit out of control.
I can't have a student blackmailing me
whenever she pleases.
I can't jeopardize my job.
-I can't, I'm sorry.
-Of course. What a pity.
Too late. The stork is on its way!
Of course, you're worried about Marina.
Don't worry, she will not talk.
If she does,
let me remind you that you and I
are on this boat together,
and would go down... together.
Besides, do you think I'll let her talk?
You have everything
you could wish to be happy.
Why get into this mess for a shitty trophy
and a scholarship you don't need?
I don't get you.
Martín, do you know why I am thin?
Excuse me?
Because I always see myself fat.
Do you know why I'm the best?
Because I'm never satisfied.
You should learn to be content
with what you have to be happy.
Are you happy earning €1,000 a month?
Repeating the same shit
in class every day?
Besides, who wants to be happy nowadays?
When they can be the best.
Right? Have a good day!
You couldn't wait to tell me
whatever it is at home?
No.
Who sold you the marijuana in your room?
Was it Omar?
No.
It was a girl.
Blonde, bleached hair. And fat.
I mean, overweight.
I only saw her once.
Why? Is something wrong?
We caught Marina with marijuana
that this Omar sold her.
He's Nadia's brother.
-No idea.
-Anyway, I'll have to talk to the parents.
I NEED IT, IT'S IMPORTANT
WHY? WHAT'S SO SPECIAL ABOUT IT?
Fuck, Nano.
What's going on with that watch?
Thank you!
Sorry I got you mixed up in this!
No problem.
It's no sweat off my dick
if those snobs think I'm a thief!
What matters is you're out of debt.
It's over!
Now you can begin to enjoy life.
Working 40 hours and sweating like a pig
for a shitty salary
that doesn't even cover rent.
To enjoying life!
No, Nano,
you and I are going to strike gold.
-Really? How?
-Yes.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Christian, can you leave us alone?
Sure,
want me to make you a sandwich?
No, please leave.
-Here.
-Thanks.
Are you OK?
Yes, but I'm a bit dizzy. It's OK.
We have to figure out
how to return the watch.
If it's so important,
how much would they pay for it?
What?
If their lives depend on that watch,
how much would they pay?
That's blackmail.
-Yes.
-Have you lost your mind?
No, I'm using it! This can be my chance
to escape this shit.
Or to go back to prison.
-It's going to work.
-Sure.
-Your plans never fail.
-So help.
I have the balls, you the brains.
We go 50/50.
We tell them if they don't pay,
we go to the press.
Do you know what would happen
if those papers got published?
To those rich people?
-Why worry about them?
-I worry about Marina.
Me, too.
She's your girlfriend.
I don't want anything to happen to her.
And we aren't giving
that watch to anybody.
We bluff so they pay up.
-Marina Nunier?
-Yes.
Are you a relative?
-Yes, I'm her boyfriend.
-Then you need to hear this.
The tests say you are pregnant.
About four weeks.
If you need anything,
I'll be in my office.
It's OK, no problem.
We were not together four weeks ago.
It's OK.
Whose is it?
Huh?
Don't worry, you can tell me.
Whose is it?
No, I can't, Samuel.
I have to get out of here.
Hey.
Shit, he's not answering. He's super mad.
Polo, it can't be Christian.
He wouldn't risk what he has with us
for watches
when he doesn't know their value.
OK, so now what? Do we apologize?
It's better if you go.
-He's mad at me over the photo shoot.
-And if we get him another one?
-This time for real, no nonsense.
-Carla, really...
Polo, we owe it to him.
And you owe him.
Now more than ever.
How are you?
-How are you, man?
-Fine.
Glad to see you.
I came to see if there's anything
I can do for you.
-Do you have 300,000 bucks?
-Guzmán.
Please.
-Hi.
-Hello.
We don't have the money.
Not for the bail,
not for the lawyers, nothing.
Our accounts are empty.
We are penniless.
Dad left us with nothing.
So I guess he's going to spend
the next 20 years in fucking jail.
-And she's so calm, I don't get it.
-That's enough.
-Why don't you ask for help at a bank?
-Nobody wants to be linked to us now.
What about a friend with money?
Nobody wants to call us.
Not even Carla's father.
And he's Dad's partner. My godfather.
And our consultant.
-That's how toxic we are, Mom.
-Maybe we should call them.
Marina betraying your boyfriend
can't have been nice for you.
I hated her a lot for that.
Because of her...
Because of her, Omar and I...
It's about Omar.
I need you to say you got mixed up,
that it wasn't him who sold you the pot.
I need you to talk to my mother.
Ander, you know she won't buy it.
-I'm really sorry.
-Yes, but--
You don't know his father.
-I'm sorry.
-Marina!
What are you doing? Let me go.
Do you want your mother to hear
about this morning?
And do you want my brother to hear
why you've come this afternoon?
Let go!
Nadia, help us. There's a lot of work.
I'm coming. I have to study.
Right.
Don't argue.
I'M REALLY SORRY. I TRIED.
Hello.
Yes, Principal.
Yes, of course.
My husband can go tomorrow.
What is it about?
I see.
Better in person.
All right. Goodbye.
What is it this time?
-Did you skip class again?
-No.
-Then why do I have to go tomorrow?
-Yusef.
That was the principal of Nadia's school.
I am as surprised as you.
First the hijab.
Let's see what they come up with now.
Forgive me, son.
I know you are changing, maturing.
I also know you are going
to make me proud.
Aren't you?
What are you listening to?
Oh, baby, you look terrible!
I know.
Let me help you.
I have a great product for those dreadful
dark circles under your eyes.
-Leave it.
-Look at me.
You know you can count on me, right?
And I will not breathe a word.
Really. I won't go around gossiping.
As it should be.
Lu, save your breath
and ask me straight up.
I told you about Martín
and my blackmail in confidence.
And friends do not betray each other.
We are not friends.
It's in your best interest to be mine.
Ready.
You look better.
You look prettier when you don't talk.
Do you think after what he's done
I will visit him in jail?
I don't know.
He deserves a chance, doesn't he?
To explain himself.
And he's your father.
He's a thief.
He even stole from his family,
so he doesn't deserve anything.
What he deserves,
that's for a judge to decide.
Your family should always be your support.
-What is it good for, if not?
-You really think I should go?
I think it's what he would do for you.
Come on, Christian.
It would be a photo shoot this afternoon,
same place. Polo will be with you.
Of course,
to make sure I don't steal any socks.
To make sure this time
there are no problems with the list.
Do you forgive us?
Well, let's see...
when I hold the magazine,
hot off the presses
and with my photo on it...
maybe.
-Beautiful.
-Forgive us.
-It's OK.
-All good?
Yeah.
Are you OK?
Yes, I think I'm going to be sick.
What's up with the hippie now?
No idea. She doesn't tell me anything now.
Our friendship lasted about five minutes.
What a coincidence.
Just when the watches went missing.
What are you saying?
Why would Marina rob us?
Come on, Carla.
As if her family had no criminal history.
You're just miffed
about the thing with Martín.
Dear, that only confirms
that this girl is not to be trusted.
If I were you, I'd keep an eye on her.
What can you tell me about these messages?
I wanted to know
if she knew about the theft.
There's no record
of your dad reporting it.
It wasn't such a big deal.
They were valued at over €100,000.
And judging by how insistent you were
with Marina, it seemed like a big deal.
Most of all, when you asked
about the one with the red leather strap.
Yes, well, it's just that...
I wanted to help my father.
That watch had sentimental value to him.
It belonged to a friend of his
who passed not long ago.
-This is the girls' room!
-I'll be quick.
What?
Are you all right?
-Is that what you want to know?
-We weren't together.
It doesn't matter.
But please,
tell me if it's somebody I know.
If you don't care, why keep asking?
And if I don't care about the answer,
why don't you just tell me?
Do you really want to know?
Samuel, let's drop it.
It was a mistake. Period.
-At least there's a solution.
-You're getting an abortion?
Samuel.
-What?
-This is the girls' locker room.
Samuel, go, please.
Shit.
Do your parents know?
No, it's not really
the best moment to tell them.
-Can I borrow your cell phone?
-Yes, of course.
This is the number...
for a clinic.
Many Muslim girls use it.
They don't ask for authorization.
Even if you're a minor.
-But, Nadia, do you approve of me--
-No.
But if you are going to do it,
I'd rather a doctor helps you.
-An underground doctor.
-It's safe.
Believe me.
It worked for my sister.
She asked me to go with her.
I held her hand
all the way there on the bus.
I tried to talk her out of it.
But I think...
I only made her feel worse.
Feel like a murderer.
After that,
she never... confided in me again.
If you're going through with it,
you need someone to hold your hand.
Thank you, Nadia.
And...
And... forgive me for not saying anything
to you yesterday.
I was busy with the exam, and...
Marina, that's very important to me.
I need that scholarship.
Nadia... I am truly sorry.
That scholarship is granted,
and not to you.
No. How?
-Marina.
-Guzmán,
this is the girls' locker room,
and I'm fine.
I'm going to Soto del Real this afternoon.
Mom made it clear she's not going.
Are you?
OK. Tell Dad I said to go to hell.
You and Mom both.
If you want, I can go with you.
Hi, Dad.
And your mother?
-And your sister, how are they?
-They are thinking of you.
Mostly after seeing your bank accounts.
Guzmán.
We needed the cash.
We had problems with the company.
But we'll make it all back,
and more.
Do you understand?
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Are you sure
you haven't spent it all on coke?
Shit.
Don't worry.
It's going to be all right.
Is it mine?
Marina, wait.
-What do you want to do?
-I don't know.
What do you need me to do?
Maybe I need somebody to hold my hand.
-Will it hurt?
-No way.
It's going to be fine.
Don't say that.
I hate it when people say that.
-Hey, it was you who wanted to come.
-What else can I do?
-Give me one reason not to do it.
-I could give you plenty to do it.
You are too young.
You'll have time to have children.
And where would you--
Where would we go with a child?
It's the most sensible thing to do, but...
But what?
But nothing.
-Tell me.
-Nothing.
-Nano, tell me, really.
-It's nothing.
Nothing.
What is it, Nano?
-I'm leaving this shitty town.
-What does that have to do with me?
You and I?
Nano, I am a minor,
and you just got out of jail.
-Not to mention the HIV.
-You are undetectable, Marina.
The chances of the child being infected
are less than one percent.
I don't have a master's on this,
I googled it.
We could go someplace where we could
make a fresh start...
-where you can continue treatment.
-Where?
Far. The farthest the money I'll get
for that watch will take us.
Nano, if I were to leave with you,
it would never be
by extorting my family and their friends.
-Is that how you want to start a new life?
-No, I want a fresh start, with you.
I want to go where nobody knows us.
Where nobody knows about our screwups.
-Or what we've done to Samuel, Marina.
-I won't tell Samuel the truth.
-That would only hurt him more.
-If you come with me, he'll find out.
-Nano, this is crazy.
-I know.
I'm not stupid,
I know how the world works.
But I also know that...
this, the worst that could happen to us,
may be the best thing
that's ever happened to us.
I'm not asking you to say yes now.
But think about it
for longer than five minutes.
And... if--
This is not a yes, OK?
You still have four minutes.
-Look at all this glamour!
-Carlos, how are you?
-Shall I change over here?
-Yes, right here.
Mary, let's start
with the color block outfit.
How about we celebrate
when you are done here?
We have a math exam tomorrow.
It's not like you'll pass.
That's also true, no arguments here.
-I'll let Carla know.
-OK.
Hi, hon. Everything's good here.
But we are really tired
and we have to study.
Better if we celebrate some other day, OK?
Love you, bye.
Are you OK?
Better.
Thanks to you.
It's no big deal.
It is, we have an exam tomorrow.
And you risk getting a measly nine for me.
Seems like you do care for me a bit, huh?
Don't get excited, we are just friends.
I know.
I don't...
I don't want to be your friend.
Well, you'll have to get used
to not getting everything you want.
That's too bad.
Because I've never wanted something
so much.
I bet I'm not the first girl
you've said that to.
No.
But you are the first one
with whom I mean it.
Yes.
See you in class.
Look.
They are great, man!
Amazing photos!
That one I don't like.
I overdid the intensity.
I look cross-eyed.
-So, shall we go out and party?
-Somewhere else?
We can stay here as long as we want.
And there's free beer.
And the marchioness?
She texted.
She can't come, has to study.
Come on, so do I!
What would you do that for?
You're going to be a supermodel.
Quit joking, man. Don't mess with me.
Christian, I mean it.
You've taken the first step.
What's left is the hard part,
getting the cover.
And how do we get the cover?
We talk to the publisher.
-And what a coincidence, she's my mother.
-Imagine that, what a coincidence.
Don't worry, and listen to me.
It won't be easy, let me tell you.
But I think you have what it takes.
Yeah? I don't have abs,
but I can start going to the gym.
-What do you think?
-What do I think?
-Here's what I think.
-Damn, don't think that much, OK?
And see if we can get
the magazine cover.
-Hey!
-That's up to you.
Fuck! Son of a bitch!
-What?
-Son of a bitch! My dick.
OPEN
Dad?
Why is the store closed? It's not ten yet.
Hello?
-What's the matter?
-Did you know?
-Huh?
-Did you know what your brother sold?
Don't lie to me, Nadia! Not you!
We've had too many lies in this house!
How many things haven't you told me?
And where have you been? It's late.
I was with Guzmán.
Wasn't it enough to have him
at home the other day?
What did I tell you
about seeing that boy again?
Forbidden.
It's my fault.
It's my fault!
Too much freedom!
But it's over!
Go!
Nadia, I think you deserve
to know the truth.
Lu has done Martín a huge favor,
and that's why the scholarship
will go to her.
Can you read what you replied
that same night?
You have ruined my brother's life...
and mine.
Why are you still up?
I can't stop thinking about something.
Who the father of Marina's baby is.
And when I think of it,
only one person comes to mind.
You.
She helped you with the theft.
So you've been talking.
-Maybe even seeing each other.
-You think I'd do that to you?
Is that your answer?
No, it isn't.
My answer is this. Fuck you!
Forgive me, man. I'm losing my mind.
I don't know what to think anymore.
-And? Have you talked to your mom?
-About what?
Sorry, I don't speak English.
About the cover!
Do you know what that is?
-They don't give covers to just anybody.
-I'm not just anybody.
Right?
Um, look...
She's right that it's complicated.
I told you that.
What are you saying?
To class.
Christian.
Christian, please.
-I told you I'd try.
-My ass!
I didn't accept last night so you'd try.
Don't fuck with me, I'm not an idiot!
What does last night have to do
with the cover?
-I think there's been a misunderstanding.
-I think you are a son of a bitch.
You thought I offered you the cover
in exchange for sucking my dick?
And you accepted.
Well, I don't know what that makes me,
but do you know what it makes you?
What?
-A wh--
-A what?
-Son of a bitch!
Good morning.
Um...
I've called the agency
and canceled the adoption.
What did your wife say?
-She agrees. What else could she say?
-I see.
What values would we be teaching our child
if we got it by cheating?
What kind of parents would we have been?
I think we'll never know.
Hey.
Shouldn't you be studying?
We were at his mother's studio,
and he starts kissing me on the neck,
unbuttons my shirt,
takes my belt off, and grabs my dick.
-Really?
-Sure.
Omar told me.
Marina got caught,
and then gave him away, yes.
I guess to save herself.
-She hasn't told you either?
-Me?
She's driving me crazy.
-She's made me doubt even my brother.
-What? But why?
I'll tell you later.
-How do you feel about the exam?
-What does it matter?
What do you mean? And the scholarship?
They can't give it to me
if I don't go to this school.
It was hard enough to get my dad
to let me finish the school year.
Nadia, what happened?
Hello, everybody.
So, the day is finally here.
Only pens on your desks, please.
-Done.
-Finished?
-Sure?
-Yes.
Guys, keep working in silence.
Nobody move, please!
Marina!
Marina, what is it?
Nothing.
-Not nothing. What's this?
-Nothing. I don't know it.
Samuel, what are you doing?
I want to assure you
there won't be any favoritism.
Is it about our issue?
Martín, I just want to go home.
I want to settle this problem, OK?
What?
-Son of a bitch.
-Have you told him?
-Bastard.
-What are you doing?
-Calm down!
-What's happening?
He took advantage of his student
and got her pregnant!
-What?
-Martín?
-Azucena, do you think I'd do that?
And accepting a bribe, that you would do?
My office.
Fuck!
Bribe him, me? Please!
-How can she invent such a fantasy?
-It was you who told me.
Really,
she's crazier than she already was.
It's her word against mine.
-Please, with this girl's history...
-Marina's telling the truth.
Excuse me?
We made a deal,
but today I told Lucrecia that--
You're fired, Martín.
Don't make it any harder.
We'll send your belongings home.
Fine.
It's very clear that I had
nothing to do with this, right? That...
That I didn't do anything.
Denying it only insults my intelligence.
And earns you two months of suspension
instead of one.
We are in the middle of exams.
You will sit your exams in September.
-How did you do on the exam?
-Well.
We changed plans at the last minute.
I didn't want to bother you
while you studied.
Thanks for not telling me you were
fucking another so I'd stay focused.
Hey, you fucked him too, OK?
OK, I'm sorry.
Always with you.
That was the deal. To share everything.
Carla, really, it was nothing.
It was nothing!
Come, give me a hug.
-Carla, I didn't even like it.
-This...
was something we did to avoid infidelity,
lies.
To revive a relationship that was dead.
But given all this,
it's better if it remains buried.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Let's go.
-No.
One fifty, please.
I need change.
-Why don't you answer my texts?
-I no longer have a cell.
-And when can we meet?
-I'll be behind this counter for 2 years.
-Omar.
-What are you doing?
Thanks.
Omar, please.
Please.
I can't.
Have a good day.
Bye.
Do you want to know whose it is?
-Do you really need to know?
-No. Marina.
Enough.
I'm tired.
I'm tired of chasing after you.
-Maybe--
-Listen to me! Please.
I'm tired of trying all the time
to convince you about us.
But most of all,
I'm tired of waiting for you to find...
the fucking courage to break up with me!
Samuel.
How would you have reacted
if she had decided to end it with you?
I don't know, because that never happened.
I have never seen this message.
She wrote it.
She never hit the send button.
Read it, please.
"Nano,
forgive me,
but I can't do this.
I can't leave, I'm sorry."
Why didn't she tell you in person?
Was she afraid you might react violently?
Still thinking about the blackmail idea?
I'm not sure.
What are you thinking?
Let's go get them.
Subtitle translation
by Soledad Etchemendy