On the first of June, around 9:30 p.m.,
you entered the school pool.
Marina was there.
You had an increasingly heated argument...
until you picked up the trophy,
and hit her
in the back of the head with it.
She didn't die instantly,
which means you left her there,
bleeding to death.
This is what we believe happened,
and, more importantly,
what the judge believes happened.
Do you have anything to say
in your defense?
Nano?
I'm going to pick you up from school
a little early.
Make your escape during the party,
and we will do the handover at ten.
Hey. What's wrong?
Are you getting cold feet?
Tell me about Morocco.
About Asilah. What is it like?
It's a bit small. A bit dirty.
You can only reach it by car,
taking crappy roads...
But, know what?
It has a beautiful beach,
right next to the souk.
One day, you can pick me up
from my friend's garage,
and we can go together
to watch the sunset, which is awesome.
I was looking at
where I can get medication,
and there's a clinic nearby
where they need volunteers.
Maybe I could help people
who have just received their diagnosis.
I've been through that.
OK, I'll pick you up, then.
But we'll watch the damn sunset.
OK.
Sorry, Nano, I'm just a little...
nervous.
I need one of your hugs.
Hey. Tomorrow, all right?
All right.
What happened?
-Are you all right?
-What do you think?
Do you think we're all right? Huh?
This is the second time
our home's been broken into
by people looking for who knows what
since you got out of the slammer.
What a coincidence, huh?
Your brother could have been killed.
Are you listening to me?
I could have been killed!
Do you even care about us?
-Do you even care about us?
-Mom!
-Why don't we have a cup of herbal tea?
-Right now, I'd prefer some whiskey.
Let me have a look.
Come on.
-What a mess Mom's made.
-Was shaking.
-You or her?
-Both of us.
-I'm sorry about your fucking watch.
-Don't be.
-It wasn't here.
-Who has it?
Of course.
Good. The sooner you have the money,
the sooner you'll be gone.
Right?
We're getting out of here.
Both of us.
Tomorrow.
-Why are you telling me?
-I'm sick of lying to you.
Of not being able to look you in the eye.
-I swear that--
-You'll never lie to me again,
because I'll never listen
to anything you say again.
You are no longer my brother.
It's just a small party
to celebrate the end of the school year.
Are you not going to let me
say goodbye to my classmates?
I want you home
as soon as you get the grades.
Why won't you let her go?
She's done nothing wrong.
She just wants to say goodbye.
Mind your own business.
Omar, don't start with me.
I don't care.
I'm tired of having to put up with you.
-Tired of--
-Of what?
Of your father?
The one who gave you life?
The one who raised you, fed you?
In return, you've only brought him shame.
Please, don't argue.
If I'm not allowed to go, I won't.
She only wants to say goodbye.
Fine.
So parents can go?
And brothers?
Since you're so eager to talk,
you will come.
That way,
you can apologize to the principal.
-Me?
-Yes.
In this family, when you are in the wrong,
you apologize.
We will leave that school
with our heads held high.
You went after my family,
you son of a bitch. That will cost you.
We had a deal.
You broke it when you sent your thugs
to steal the watch.
-Now it will cost you a million.
-You are crazy, kid.
You're the crazy one.
The way you're going,
those documents will end up in the papers.
And you won't see a penny, then.
I'm used to being penniless.
To a shitty life. What about you?
How will you feel
about losing your business,
your house, and your damn family?
Think about it a bit more, kid.
One million.
You have until seven o'clock tomorrow.
Morning.
Are you coming to the party?
-It starts at seven.
-We have nothing to celebrate.
Tomorrow morning,
we have an appointment with the doctor.
What's wrong?
Now you have nothing to say?
I love you very much.
And I hope someday you'll forgive me.
Hello. What?
Are you shitting me?
What do you mean, you don't have it?
Did they search for it?
Of course,
they searched everywhere for it.
They turned the place upside down.
I don't know.
That guy has no brain.
He could send us all to jail,
whether we pay or not.
Do you realize what you've done?
No, we can't give in.
We have to put an end to this,
or they'll ruin our lives.
-Did you really cancel the Croatia trip?
-Somebody had to do it.
Did you expect our families
to travel together
as if you and I were still a couple?
Let's leave the families out of it
until things are definite.
Carla?
-Maybe we can still work things out.
-What parallel world are you living in?
Did you hear her?
Polo, I'll ask you one more time.
Are you really going to let that guy
steal your girlfriend?
See how she ignores me?
-She won't listen.
-So stop talking.
Show her that you love her.
Take action. Do something!
Sure. It's so easy for you to say.
-How?
-Do I have to spell it out for you?
Guzmán... can we talk?
I guess they will take advantage
of the party for Marina to sneak out.
With the blackmail money, right?
So your brother takes your share,
and you rat him out?
I don't give a crap about him.
Believe it or not,
I do care about your sister.
I don't know what to do.
She won't listen to me.
She won't listen to me either.
But you can do something.
You can talk to your parents.
They can stop it.
I could. But I won't bother.
What do you mean?
She can move to the moon, if she wants to.
I'm sick of her.
Sick of protecting someone who wants
to jump off every cliff she sees.
Well, let her jump, then. If she survives,
she might learn something.
-She's your sister.
-And the girl that screwed you over.
You, me, and my entire family.
She stole from and blackmailed us...
with your brother's help.
Why don't you talk to him?
For the same reason
I won't talk to my sister.
Because you know if something happens
to them, maybe they had it coming.
Hey.
-Do you know anything about...
-Omar?
They won't let me see him either.
What's up, guys? Last day!
Olé.
What's up with the long faces?
I'm the one with four failed classes
for September.
You both passed everything,
and you look like your parents died.
Here, have a drink.
There's much to celebrate.
No.
Want some?
Do you know what Nano's doing?
Being awesome, that's what he's doing.
Your brother's an ace, Samu.
Don't you see he'll have a future now?
And you and I,
a house in Morocco on the beach
for this summer.
What more can you ask for?
Cheer up, man!
And you, don't down the whole bottle!
-Let me.
-Don't you dare.
-Let me help you.
-Help me?
Do you know what you're doing
to your family and mine?
You should be ashamed,
betraying your people like this.
They will be all right, Carla.
If your father pays.
You have plenty of money.
Right, like we can trust your boyfriend.
How do I know he won't
take the watch to the papers?
He won't, I assure you.
Right. Like I'd believe you!
The watch is in good hands.
Do you have it?
Your sister has it.
-Did she tell you so?
-Almost.
-What does she think she's doing?
-She's running away with Samuel's brother.
They probably planned it together.
When is she leaving?
My parents are watching her,
so probably tonight during the party.
-I don't think she'll even stop at home.
-Why do you ask?
That means she has the watch here.
-Aren't you getting changed?
-In a while.
I'm delaying it as much as I can.
It's the last time I'll wear this.
Will we see each other again?
My father is making me change schools
precisely so I won't see you again.
Well, hello. How's the happy couple?
-What are you doing here?
-I'm here to contribute some glamour.
Well, a lot of glamour,
to this celebration.
It actually looks a bit cheap.
But, Nadia, why are you leaving?
I'm not an obstacle to your relationship
and your happy ending.
Really, you can stay.
Dear, I mean it.
This woman is very difficult.
-It's going to be hard for you.
-Happy?
Yes.
Who am I to get in between the two of you?
In the end,
there wasn't really anything between us.
-Where's the catch?
-There's no catch here, Guzmán.
Sure, sometimes my competitive side
gets the best of me,
even if the prize isn't worth it.
HAPPY END OF THE SCHOOL YEAR
Give us two.
No, no punch. Thanks.
Look.
Have a drink.
Distract the waiter. OK?
Excuse me,
do you have any bottles, or something...
Hi.
Can you force a locker open?
Why would I know how to force a lock?
Well, I know how to do a lot of things.
That's how it is in the school of life.
Polo has some photos of me on his phone.
I'm afraid he'll post them online.
He's so resentful now,
I think he might do it.
-I'll beat the crap out of him.
-No, that would be worse.
Could you get me his backpack?
It's in locker 134. Please!
OK. I'll see what I can do.
Excuse me. Could we talk for a moment?
There's nothing to talk about.
Just a moment. I want to propose a deal,
so that Nadia doesn't leave the school.
If you let her stay one more year,
I swear, on all things sacred,
I will stay away from her.
I won't even say hi.
-Have you tired of her?
-No.
No.
But you know as well as I do
that we have no future together.
But she has a future at this school,
so don't end it.
You can trust me.
I have many flaws, many.
But I'm a man of my word.
-I have to get back.
-Damn!
Is this the way it will always be?
When will you be free of your father?
And you of yours?
How many matches
will you play this summer?
And how many do you really want to play?
I only want to be with you.
We're screwed.
My father watches me all day long.
He only leaves me alone when he goes
to the bank in the afternoon.
Ten minutes of freedom.
That's all I can offer you this summer.
For one of the students
in the penultimate year,
this trophy not only means
the satisfaction of a job well done,
but also a scholarship to study
at our high school in Florida.
From there, you can go on
to an Ivy League college.
And the winner is...
Marina Nunier.
Hi.
Thank you for the award,
but I think someone else deserves it more.
I don't really have much
to be proud of this year.
So I wanted to take this opportunity
to apologize.
Sorry for all the damage
I may have caused.
For letting down those I love the most.
And the person who's made me feel
so much in a short time.
I tried to stop it all.
I tried...
to be a good daughter, a good sister.
I tried to live up to your feelings,
Samuel.
I wish we had our time machine to go back
and start from scratch.
But I was myself.
Stubborn, unafraid of danger...
and...
always getting in trouble.
I'm sorry.
Why are you here?
And you?
I needed to think, Samuel.
Marina,
stay.
Please.
I don't want you to stay for me.
I want you to do it for yourself.
Did you see the way people looked at me?
I have nothing here, nobody.
They all hate me, with good reason.
I don't hate you.
Not because I don't want to,
but because I can't.
I'm sure if I've forgiven you
after what you did to me,
the rest can, too.
I don't see how.
Well, it's not by running away.
That is not the way.
Much less after blackmailing your family.
And after throwing away your future
to go with a guy you don't know.
Please, don't do something you'll regret
for the rest of your life.
Please.
No.
NANO, FORGIVE ME, BUT I CAN'T DO THIS.
I CAN'T LEAVE, I'M SOR
I'm on my way.
I'm not sure about this.
I don't know.
Where are you?
I'm at the swimming pool. I'm--
OK, I'm on my way.
I'll be there in a minute. Don't move.
-Guzmán!
-What are you doing?
I just talked to her.
She's leaving for good. Do something!
-Who?
-Marina.
-I just talked to her, and she's leaving.
-Leave me alone.
-Go away. Leave me alone.
-Please!
Did you get the backpack?
-You couldn't force the lock?
-I didn't want to.
You don't fool me.
That is Marina's locker.
So what?
I asked you because it matters to me.
-You can still--
-No, I don't want to.
I am not your lapdog,
and I won't do everything you ask.
Does she want to fuck? We fuck.
Does she want a backpack stolen?
I steal it for her.
No.
-What's the matter with you?
-I am fed up, Carla.
I want you to see me as an equal.
I want to be your boyfriend, for real.
And I know I am poor
and you are a marchioness,
and our relationship is only possible
in Disney movies.
But if we're going to try,
I want to really try. To go all in.
I don't want to be your gigolo,
or your thief, or someone you can use.
So laugh all you want now.
Can I tell you something
without you thinking
I see you as a gigolo?
Or like someone I go to
for sex or to steal?
You just turned me on.
-Why are you here?
-The watch, Marina, please.
What?
Give me the watch, please.
Can't you hear me?
-Give me the watch.
-No.
-Give me the fucking watch, please!
-No!
Why the hell do you have to get involved,
huh?
-You stole from my girlfriend!
-She's not your girlfriend anymore!
What?
So...
You thought
that if you got the watch back for her,
she would take you back? Shit!
What are you laughing at, Marina?
What the fuck are you laughing at?
Know what you are?
Huh? You know what you are?
A damn thief, that's what you are!
Yes! Betraying your people
for the first guy from the hood you meet.
Asshole!
-Yeah! Watch it.
-Know what your girlfriend's doing?
Falling for the first guy
from the hood she meets. She's using you.
-Don't fuck with me.
-It will be worse still, know why?
-She's not going back to you!
-Give me the fucking watch.
-She's using you, Polo!
-Is it in your pocket? Answer me.
-She's using you!
-Give me the watch, Marina!
She's using you, Polo!
Like they all do! Like my brother does!
You are their puppet!
I pity you!
Shit.
What the hell?
What happened?
Polo, what have you done?
I don't know.
-But I think she's not breathing.
-Who's not breathing?
Did anyone see you?
Polo, did anyone see you?
Good.
Let's get the blood off you. Come.
All right. Your hands. Give me your hands.
Fucking shirt.
-Christian.
-What?
Do you have a shirt to lend him?
-Can you explain to me--
-Get a fucking shirt!
Look at me!
Get rid of the trophy.
Nobody can see you with it.
Do you hear me?
Can you tell me
who the hell is not breathing?
Polo! Damn it,
who the hell isn't breathing?
Marina.
Your attention, please.
May I have your attention?
I need you to leave the room
in an orderly fashion.
There's been an incident.
I repeat, in an orderly fashion.
Thank you very much.
-Can you calm down, please?
-How can you ask me to calm down? Fuck!
The police are talking to everybody.
They will call on me.
You won't say a word.
-Because you saw nothing.
-But I did! He killed Marina, damn it!
That would be covering it up!
You wanted to be my boyfriend, right?
To be one of us.
For me to treat you like an equal.
Then you must know that, among us,
we always, always protect each other.
Like Polo did.
He did it for me.
And if you had opened that locker,
he wouldn't have had to do it.
You realize what you've done, right?
This is much more serious, damn it!
You want your Disney movie?
Because you've just been given
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
Seize it.
Excuse me, are you Guzmán?
Yes.
-May we speak for a moment?
-Why me?
-Come with me, please.
-Where's my sister?
-Guzmán.
-Calm down, Guzmán. Come with me.
-Where's my sister?
I said, where's my sister!
-Calm down, Guzmán, please. Let's talk.
-Where is my sister? Damn it!
Polo.
Did you get rid of...?
Good.
They'll realize. When they question me,
they'll figure it out.
-I-- I know they will.
-No, listen to me.
You went home because you were very drunk.
Then I texted you to come
because something serious had happened.
Repeat that.
Polo, repeat that.
I was very drunk, and I went home.
My mothers had gone out for dinner.
Carla, my girlfriend, called and said
something terrible had happened.
Then I went back to school.
-At what time did you leave the party?
-I don't know.
-Around nine, I think.
-And you went straight home?
Can anybody confirm
the time you got home?
There was nobody home.
Are there security cameras
in your housing complex?
Maybe we could check the footage
to confirm the time of your arrival.
Sorry, am I under suspicion?
No, these are routine checks,
nothing to worry about.
If the cameras confirm the time
you gave us, it will all be all right.
We are done.
Are you all right? Is anything wrong?
Yes, I'm fine.
Listen...
How about later today
we prepare the summer schedule?
No hurries.
It will take our minds off this.
I don't want to go to any championships.
I want to stay here this summer.
And I don't want to play tennis.
Losing a classmate is terrible.
I can't even imagine how you feel.
But life goes on, Ander.
And no matter how hard it is,
life must go on.
I know. And I want it to go on.
But I want it to be my life that goes on.
The life I choose.
And I don't want to play tennis anymore,
Dad.
It's over.
Over there.
Thanks for coming.
I love you.
When they check the cameras,
they'll see I arrived much later.
They'll know I lied, and they'll catch me.
Fuck, I never should have said
I went home. That was stupid.
-That was stupid.
-No. You were drunk.
It could've taken you longer
than you thought to get home.
We can make something up.
I'm not going to let you end up in jail.
It was an accident.
Look at me.
What happened was an accident.
-And you can't pay for that.
-I killed her, Carla.
It was a fit of rage, you know me.
I didn't want to.
-Don't talk nonsense.
-I'll pay for it.
We must keep a cool head.
Why are you helping me?
Because you helped me
and saved my family.
Listen to me. You and I are not together.
What's more, let's say we hate each other.
That would mean you had no motive
to kill Marina.
Why would you want the watch? You see?
It wouldn't make sense.
You'd have no motive.
Nobody will think it was you, OK?
We are not together.
Where's Marina?
Why won't they bring her body?
I want to say goodbye.
-They need to perform an autopsy.
-I don't care!
I want them to bring my daughter now!
-What is it? What are you looking at?
-Mom, that's enough.
Guzmán.
Where's Marina?
Where is she?
-Omar, I'm off to the bank. Be right back.
-All right.
Ten minutes, right?
I'll cover for you.
Until Dad gets back.
Come.
I can't stop thinking
about that poor girl.
I don't know what I would've done
if it had been you.
Dad, I'm all right.
I never liked that school.
What does the school have to do with it?
That could have happened anywhere.
You still want to go?
Fine.
If you want to go back next year, you can.
But I don't want to hear
about that boy again.
I don't want you to go near him.
I don't want you to do anything but study.
You can go back.
But only on that condition.
No.
If I go back,
it will be with no conditions.
it will be to be a student like the rest.
I don't know if anything
will happen with Guzmán,
or with someone else.
Or if nothing will happen at all.
But if I go back,
it will be unconditionally.
You see? See how they've changed you?
Dad, maybe I haven't changed.
Maybe the old Nadia wasn't me.
She was a girl who tried
to please her parents above all.
Maybe I'm different.
Like your sister?
No.
I don't know who I am yet.
But I'm going to find out.
I hope you and Mom can accept it
and love me.
But I'm going to be myself, Dad. Myself.
We know who killed her.
On the first of June, around 9:30 p.m.,
you entered the school pool.
Marina was there.
You had an increasingly heated argument...
until you picked up the trophy,
and hit her
in the back of the head with it.
She did not die instantly,
which means you left her there,
bleeding to death.
Come with me, please.
This is what we believe happened,
and, more importantly,
what the judge believes happened.
You'd save us a lot of work if you told us
where to find the murder weapon,
the trophy.
Oh, right,
you don't have a shred of evidence.
Nothing.
It's him.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Marina Nunier.
-What?
-Hold him tight.
What the fuck are you saying?
-Grab him!
-What the hell are you saying?
Look me in the face and say it again!
We have a witness, your brother.
A motive.
As her messages prove,
she'd changed her mind about running away.
That's why you killed her.
Samu! You know I'd never hurt Marina.
-Get him!
-You know I'd never hurt Marina, Samu!
They killed her for that watch.
The pen drive had a lot of dirt
on her father, and we wanted money for it.
Those people are nasty.
They broke into my house,
assaulted my brother.
Come on! Look me in the face!
Marina had... She had that watch.
Somebody killed her and took it.
One of those rich fucks.
The marchioness, for example.
-She stood to lose the most.
-We don't have the watch.
Or any proof of that blackmail.
You have the cell phone
I used to talk to that guy.
You have no proof of what you're saying.
Of course, I'm the one who needs proof
to accuse those rich people.
Breakfast is served.
Darling, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Or I will be.
It's all over.
Come, they've made pancakes,
and they are positively yummy.
Do you have anything to say
in your defense?
Yes.
Go to hell.
We can get this to go, and go home.
You've had enough.
Son of a bitch!
If you hadn't come to our school,
this wouldn't have happened.
-Is it my fault?
-Your murderer brother's and yours.
Because you introduced them, right?
Live with that.
No. You could have stopped it,
and you didn't.
You did nothing.
If you're looking for a guilty party,
-look in the fucking mirror!
-What do you mean?
Hey, no! Enough, Guzmán!
For your own good, don't even think
of returning to our school, you hear?
You've been told so many times
that you own the world
that you actually believe it, huh?
See you in class, Lucrecia.
That's if they let you go back.
Guzmán.
What are you doing there?
Can you get down, please?
Samuel was right.
If I had talked to my parents,
or to Marina, she'd be alive.
No.
The only one who is to blame
is the one who killed her. Nobody else!
My sister is dead.
I know, sweetie.
And I know it hurts a lot.
I know because...
if something happened to you, I would die.
And so would your parents.
So please...
don't cause any more pain, will you?
And get down from there already!
I need to hold you.
Come.
Guzmán!
Please.
Come.
Do something like this again,
and I'll kill you myself, you hear me?
Thank you. You're always there.
Where else would I be?
I need you.
No.
I need you, Lu.
ARE YOU COMING?
WE ARE WAITING FOR YOU
It's because of me.
They arrested my brother because of me.
I was so mad at him,
I thought he was capable of killing her.
-You are not to blame for anything.
-I accused him.
-And he's not guilty.
-I know.
There must be a way to prove
it wasn't him.
Even if we had seen the murderer
with our own eyes,
who would believe us, Samu?
It wouldn't do any good.
Christian, I need your help.
He's my brother and your best friend.
We need to do whatever we can.
There must be some evidence, something.
You have to help me.
ARE YOU COMING OR NOT?
Subtitle translation
by Soledad Etchemendy