She was somewhat aloof, but a good girl.
She was one of those rich girls
who paint their nails black
to look like rebels.
Smarter.
She thought she was different...
because she acted all mysterious.
I thought I knew her,
but now I'm not sure.
-Where's your brother?
-In his room. Why?
No reason.
Because there's always people around,
and now we're all alone...
-Is it yours?
-No, my brother's.
-What's all this?
-Samu, what's going on?
No way.
Someone's sending him license plates.
-What?
-Nano!
-Samuel?
-What?
-What's this?
-Who's sending you plates?
-Why do you have my phone?
How can you be stupid enough
to think about stealing cars again
while you're on parole?
You could go to jail again.
Leave me alone. Hi, Marina.
The people you owe money to are
in jail.
-Maybe I could help.
-No, stay out of this.
-Here's what we'll do.
-What?
From now on,
mind your own fucking business.
-Nano, what are you--
-Mind your own fucking business, Samu!
Look who's here!
What's that? What are you doing?
The clothes you gave me.
My dad's forcing me to return them.
So you paid for those clothes?
Obviously.
How could I have paid for them?
-Stay, and we'll talk about it.
-Sure.
How can you return this?
It's cool and you looked great in it.
-Try it on.
-Now?
Now. Right, Polo?
And your butt looks great in these pants.
Put these on, too.
Maybe you both really do see me
as a sex object.
What are you saying?
Tell him he's wrong, Polo.
Take his pants off.
Come on.
Careful. I got stuff down there.
Don't mess around.
What would you call
this thing we've got going on?
Why do we need to define it?
Labels are for clothes.
-Oh well!
-We can't return this.
That sucks!
-Can't return this, either.
-Oh, oops!
No way.
Good morning.
-I'm so tired!
-Why?
Because I'm not sleeping well lately.
I'm taking a medication.
I hope the side effects won't last long.
-The veil!
-Don't worry, I won't say anything.
I've already gotten used
to all this cultural diversity.
Come on, guys. It was a joke.
Nadia, I'm serious.
I think we should meet up
to share some ideas.
We could surprise each other.
How about today
at Guzmán's birthday party?
Oh, no. She wasn't invited, right?
-Lu.
-Sorry, since you're such close friends...
I thought you'd be going.
Maybe it's just an intimate gathering,
right, Marina?
Have a nice day.
Does she practice that at home,
or does she make it up on the spot?
Nadia, it isn't a big party.
It's a family thing.
Marina, don't worry.
Samuel, one thing.
I know you only want to protect me,
and not involve me in your problems...
but I think I know
how to help your brother.
Seriously, Marina. Forget it.
The more you stay away from him,
the better.
Listen to me.
I'm doing this for you.
I know you love him.
-Do you want him to get hurt?
-No, I don't want you to get hurt.
He's dangerous.
He could get you in a lot of trouble.
Look. Remember those files
you told me your parents hide in a safe?
-Yes.
-Well, my brother asked me to steal them.
-What?
-I didn't do it.
I'd never do anything to hurt you.
I want you to stay away from him,
because I almost did it.
My brother is capable of anything.
Understood?
Samuel, we'll talk later, OK?
Marina!
Happy birthday.
-It's your birthday, isn't it?
-Yes, thanks.
It's actually the day my parents chose.
We don't know exactly when I was born.
Who told you?
It doesn't matter.
It was Lu, right?
Who else?
She invited herself to the party.
Do you want to celebrate,
just the two of us?
I'll kick everyone out of the house.
We'll be alone.
I'm not interested.
Damn!
Fuck!
We'll take a five-minute break!
Your wrist is OK, right?
So, what's going on?
Nothing. Why?
You're playing worse.
On Friday,
you have a match you need to win.
I'm allowed to have a bad day, right?
Besides, it still hurts a little.
No excuses.
I know what you're made of.
We share the same DNA, kid.
Enough, Dad. I like it better
when you're not trying to be nice.
Don't I have five minutes?
A toast to the birthday boy, Guzmán.
Thanks.
Well, I have a little something
for the birthday boy.
I hope you like it.
How about that?
Your birthday is the perfect occasion
to start a watch collection, like mine.
Have I showed it to you?
-No.
-I'll have to.
Look, Guzmán. It's always with me.
If only it could talk, right, Ventura?
But not with ladies present.
Ones who grow prettier by the day.
Well, Guzmán, mine is more modest,
but happy birthday.
No... How did you know I wanted this?
I love it!
-I'll take a picture.
-No, wait. My present first.
Well, well. What a great girlfriend!
We're just friends.
Do you like it?
-You shouldn't have, Lu.
-Who else could have bought it for you?
Other girls would need to save
for an eternity to buy it.
-Let's take the picture.
-Yes, sure.
-Excuse us.
-So much for the family photo.
It's fine.
Can you take a photo of me and my sister?
Sure. Stand over there.
This is vintage... or just old, right?
Don't worry about it. It's safe.
No one knows about it.
Everything is at stake.
-Have I ever failed you in these 20 years?
-Marina!
Smile!
How cute!
Hi! Samu isn't working.
What the fuck were you doing
at my place when we hooked up?
I know what you did. Your brother told me.
I wanted to hear it from you.
So, what we had was a lie?
-You did it to break into my house.
-What do you mean, what we had?
-What did you think this was?
-Fuck you.
I fucked you to rob your place.
To keep you away from my brother.
To prove to him you're a rich girl
who falls for jerks.
-That's why I fucked you. And know what?
-What?
And now I can't get you out
of my fucking head.
But you're with my brother.
That's how it has to be.
It's what you both deserve.
Did you come to save me?
There's nothing to save here.
Nano, I want to help you.
Don't ask me why, but I can't stand
the idea of something happening to you.
Look. My father's business partner
has an awesome watch collection.
And that jerk deserves
to be robbed way more than my family.
I don't know, with four or five watches,
you could pay off your debt.
What do you think?
I have to get back to work.
Listen, I've been a mess since I told you
that we tried to steal from your house.
I'd totally understand
if you don't want anything to do with me.
I needed to tell you that.
We'll talk tomorrow. Bye.
How are you doing?
-Hi.
Samuel, really, don't worry about that.
Are you sure? I was freaking out.
Are we OK?
We are better than OK.
Listen, Samuel.
I think it's time to take our relationship
to the next level, right?
-What do you mean, the next level?
-To do it... together.
Samu, are you there?
Hi.
Hi, Samuel.
How can I help you?
I need eggs.
What's going on with you guys?
Can we talk outside, man?
My father needs me.
Omar.
Do you know what's going on with them?
Kid stuff.
One day like this, the next like that.
So now you're okay
with talking to drug dealers?
I miss you, man.
Don't you miss me?
I don't need friends who judge me.
Omar, come on. I'm not judging you,
I'm worried about you.
I can't help it.
And this is your way of apologizing?
It sucks.
I'm sorry.
You're forgiven.
-I have something else to tell you.
-What?
Marina wants to do it with me.
-No. Bullshit!
-I'm telling you.
-Does she? Congratulations, man.
-Yeah.
-That's awesome. Cool.
-Well...
So why the long face? That's great news.
-Not great, fucking amazing.
-I know, but...
-Why are you so down?
-Because I'm a virgin.
Omar, it's my first time. I'm embarrassed.
I'm afraid that I won't get it up,
or that I'll get nervous...
and be awkward with her.
No. Just relax.
-Let nature do its thing--
-I'm worried about something else, too.
If I get nervous, I don't want her
to think that it's because of her issue.
-What issue?
-Her HIV, man.
I'm scared she'll think it's
because I'm afraid of it.
-Let me think about it.
-Is there anything you want to tell me?
-Me? No.
-You're not a virgin anymore.
-Sorry, Muslims don't talk about that.
-Sorry, but I'm a bit of a jerk.
Asshole.
-Another fling?
-Hands off.
-Let me see.
-Let go.
-Let me see it.
-Don't be nosy.
-Let me see.
-Stop. I'm going inside.
Go home and start waxing.
-Waxing?
-That's what I said.
Omar! Should I get waxed?
-Sorry I'm late.
-Don't worry.
Worried I wouldn't show up, huh?
Let's get drinks.
Let's act like this isn't our first time
in a gay bar.
Why the hell are we here?
Because there's more to life
than just school and training.
Or meeting up
in out-of-the-way places.
Besides,
I needed to get my mind off tennis.
Plus, I wanted to show you off.
Tennis is driving you crazy, right?
Why don't you quit?
-It's the only thing I'm good at.
-You're not good at anything else, right?
If it isn't your thing,
you'll find something else.
Look. If I quit tennis,
I'll break my dad's heart.
It's your life, not his.
Besides, believe it or not,
no one dies from a broken heart.
Those two guys won't stop staring at us.
Obviously. We're the hottest ones here.
Enough with the pics, Narcissus.
Narcissus? How could I not be like him?
Have you seen these pics? Look.
I've got a gift, man. I'm killing it.
Listen.
I have an idea about how to convince
your father that you're not being bought.
-What if I get you a job?
-What do you mean, a job?
I don't want a shitty dishwasher job.
I'll have time for that later.
No, Christian. It's nothing like that.
Look.
Have I told you that my mom
is one of the most important CEOs
-in the publishing world?
-Maybe, but I don't recall.
I'm bad at acronyms.
That means chief executive officer.
She's working on one of this season's
most important ad campaigns.
-They're looking for models.
-So?
-I can tell her to get you in.
-You'd do that for me?
-I'll call her.
-You're great, man!
Against feminine men
and those who defended women's rights.
Over time,
those men who defended women's rights...
and mainly women,
reappropriated that word,
starting with the pioneer
and suffragist Hubertine Auclert.
Thus, this word has lost its stigma
over time...
-The phone, please.
-Sorry, it was my mom.
This way, we can share with the class...
-Give me the phone.
-It was my mom.
You know the rules.
I don't care. Give me the phone.
She wants to know
what time I'm getting out.
Nadia, please read.
-Read.
-No.
"Marina doesn't have AIDS, asshole.
-It's HIV--"
-Stop reading that!
What the hell?
Guzmán, calm down. Enough, Guzmán!
-What are you writing?
-Calm down!
-How could you let her read it?
-First, show me some respect.
Second, you know the rules.
You can't use phones.
I had the right to do that.
-A hell of a right you had.
-Shut up.
Marina, do you have HIV?
Nadia, please.
-Really, I don't get it.
-What's that?
No.
Guys, please, calm down. Now!
Marina, you don't have to say anything.
Please, don't.
Guzmán, stop. Please.
I caught it a year and a half ago,
more or less.
And, well... I guess...
this will be a trending topic for a while.
To make sure you're informed
about what you'll be talking about,
I'll tell you, really,
you don't need to worry about me.
I take my medication.
I take tests every four months, and...
the virus I have is undetectable
in the blood, so...
that means that you can't get infected.
Thanks, Marina.
It takes a lot of courage to share this.
Don't you think so, Nadia?
I'd rather not comment.
I don't want to hurt anyone.
Here, man.
It was Pablo who infected her, right?
What? What did I miss?
Did you know?
-Did you tell him and not me?
-He told me when he was really down.
-And because I was there.
-Yeah.
-That's why you can't stand the new kids?
-Those people are nothing but trouble.
You can't judge all of them
based on what one individual did.
Polo, say what you want.
But Christian's using you and won't stop.
Why would he?
Some people have a plan to use others.
They know how to get what they want.
-What are you talking about?
-Do you want to tell him, or should I?
What?
Polo and Carla are experimenting
with Christian.
I keep telling him the risks,
but he won't listen.
I knew that already.
He told me himself at Samuel's party.
-He told you at the party?
-See?
For fuck's sake!
He's telling everyone
because he wants to use you.
He wants to fuck you over. Period.
Nobody uses me.
He won't use me.
When we were little, we were good friends.
Hi.
Can I sit?
Sure, silly.
But then,
we drifted apart and we barely spoke.
How are you doing?
You know...
I really think you were brave.
And I'm sorry you had to go through
all this by yourself.
Don't worry. I had Guzmán and my parents.
Besides, it's been a long time
since we were close, so...
But you can always count on me.
You know that, right?
So, you didn't notice any changes,
anything unusual?
I could really use a friend.
I told you, we didn't talk.
I need so many things right now...
To talk, to vent...
I totally understand.
Would you like to meet up later?
-At your house or...
-Sure. At my house. Great.
OK.
Yes, it's me.
Hi.
I couldn't find you.
-How are you doing?
-What are you doing here?
I couldn't stand any more pitying
or condescending looks.
Did you see how Nadia stared at me?
I was making a friend,
and I've already lost her.
I'm sorry. You had to say it
in front of everyone because of me.
It had to happen sooner or later.
And...
do you know when you think that...
you're brave,
but the truth is you act like a coward?
Saying it in front of the class like that
wasn't a cowardly thing to do.
Samuel,
I'm only brave when I'm forced to be.
So in the end, I have to thank you.
And... are you really afraid
of being with me because I have HIV?
That doesn't scare me at all, OK?
OK.
I'm afraid that you'll compare me
to your ex.
What?
Or any guy you've been with,
and that you'll realize I'm just a kid.
-Samuel, we are the same age.
-Sure, but we're from different worlds.
What worlds?
People from your world have lived
like seven lives more than I have.
Samuel, you're a sweetheart.
-I could do it right here.
-No. No, our first time has to be great.
-And it will!
-Let me set it up.
Calm down.
-Hi.
-What are you doing here?
I came to see you.
You were a bit harsh in class,
-with everything that happened.
-You didn't tell me about your sister.
That's her business. I didn't tell anyone.
You didn't do anything, either.
I thought you were friends.
I didn't say anything
because I care about her.
-If it were anyone else...
-What?
-Nothing. It doesn't matter.
-What's going on, Nadia?
This only makes me see
how different we are.
I don't know why I'm with people like you.
People like me?
What does that mean?
You tried to win a bet at my expense.
Then, you tell me about your father
snorting coke in the cellars.
And now, your sister with HIV.
And you say that our culture is archaic.
So your family's perfect,
everything's great?
No, I'm not saying that we're perfect,
nor that it's great.
But we don't have
those kinds of problems.
Those kinds of problems.
Hello.
Yes, that will be €1.50, please.
-Thanks.
-See you.
Do you know what your brother is up to?
He deals drugs and sucks cock.
Have a nice day.
-What did he want?
-Nothing.
-Carla, thanks for everything.
-No worries. It's the least I could do.
Let's have a drink.
Yeah, sure.
Beer or wine?
My mother speaks highly
of the last harvest.
-Wine it is, then.
-Great.
Shit, there's none left.
-I'll go to the cellar for another one.
-OK.
I'll be right back.
If my mom finds out I've opened
one of the good ones, she'll kill me.
Marina?
It looks exactly the same.
It's been a long time since I last came.
It's still the same mausoleum.
-Well, here's to...
-To friendship in shitty times.
Thank you.
Omar, can we talk?
Yeah.
I don't know how to ask you this,
so I'll do it quick.
Are you dealing drugs?
Who told you that?
Samuel. That fucking son of a bitch!
Samuel knows? So it's true?
I'm going to stop, don't worry.
What were you thinking,
getting involved with that? Why?
Do you know you can talk to me?
About anything.
I don't know, Nadia.
We've never really been the kind to talk.
I know. But you can talk to me.
About anything.
I promise I'll listen to you...
and help you.
Great. I'm going to do my homework.
Take care of the store.
And... there is something else, right?
Do you like guys?
Listen, if you do,
you'll distance yourself from Mom and Dad.
With everything they've done for us!
-I have the right to live my own life.
-Set it aside for a couple of years!
It can't be that difficult.
Look at me.
I'm not an ice cube like you.
Guzmán.
Hey.
Hey!
Surprise!
What are you doing here?
Is the alcohol in the usual place?
I can make the best margaritas.
Lu... I don't feel like it.
I get it. It's normal.
You've protected Marina your whole life,
and now this.
You need to get your mind off it.
Someone who gets you,
who doesn't judge.
I'm here to listen, you know.
We can watch a movie...
-How about it?
-Lu.
I'm not in the mood, OK?
I want to be alone.
Don't you miss what we had?
I'm not talking about the sex, that aside.
I'm talking about us.
You and me.
You get me better than anyone,
and I get you.
We're a team.
I won't allow us to lose that.
-Sorry.
-Sure.
Hi, Guzmán, I just wanted...
to apologize.
I know I've been harsh, and I'm sorry.
I'm done, Lu.
Lu?
Here we go again. What?
-What?
-Get out of the pool room.
-I can't hear you.
-Fine, I'm coming.
Lu, not now.
I just think you're really boring.
Can you stop fooling around, please?
Besides, we're not alone.
I'm turning one of your worst days...
into a good one.
-Bye.
-No!
No way!
-Come in with me!
-No, Lu. I don't want to.
Just for a little while. Don't be boring!
I want you to leave.
OK, then. Help me get out.
I can't swim with shoes on.
-Don't do what you're thinking about.
-I won't.
I knew it.
Of course you knew. You know why?
Because you can't help it.
Because we can hook up with other people,
we can be with other people,
but you and me...
will always be you and me, honey.
Right? Come on, give me a kiss.
-No.
-Kiss me.
Tomorrow, the house will be empty, OK?
Her parents are away.
Carla will be in class.
The code for the alarm is 1-6-4-9.
I'll text it to you later.
To get the watches, go up the stairs
to her parents' bedroom.
There is a bathroom
with a dressing room inside.
In the dressing room,
there'll be some drawers,
and the watches will be there.
1-6-4-9.
That's it.
-Bye.
-They told me to come.
-Really?
-I'm telling you.
-What a nice chat you're having.
He has a casting call tomorrow.
Did you set it up?
Yeah, with my mother.
Of course you did. Thanks so much, man!
By the way, I don't know what to wear.
Well, the less you wear
and the more you show, the better.
Don't you think, Polo?
You like him better undressed, right?
-What are you talking about?
-Let's go to class.
Thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
LET ME KNOW WHEN YOU GET THEM.
-No! Did you get it?
-You know me.
What's going on?
Nothing, Lu was telling me...
-She gets everything she wants.
-Don't say anything.
-What?
-I'm talking about Martín.
She has him eating out of the palm
of her hand.
Martín? Why?
-Tell her.
-No.
I'll tell you myself.
She got him connections in the embassy
to expedite the adoption process.
Seriously?
Yes, I'm his favorite again. As always.
Poor thing,
he was going about it the honest way,
but when you don't have money,
honesty's a luxury you can't afford.
Yeah.
Oh, Marina!
I'm really happy we're friends again.
Fucking great!
Don't you tell me...
That's a fucking bummer.
Damn girl...
Nothing to do all day.
They don't even let you use the Internet.
They needed to spice it up.
Not at all.
I'm not sure why I wanted to go there.
I'm taking a shower,
and I'll be right there.
OK? See you in a bit.
I'VE GOT THEM.
Shit!
-Are you going to tell us?
-Tell you what?
-Carla and Lu tell each other everything.
-It was nothing. Just a mistake.
A mistake, period. Please, drop it.
-A mistake?
-A mistake.
-OK.
-Please.
OK.
It's your friend.
Hey.
How are you doing?
Aren't you going to say hi?
-I didn't know they'd be here.
-Should I tell them to sit?
-It's fucking obvious.
-So what if they see us talking?
-I wanna kiss you.
-Are you drunk or something?
-No.
-Ander, come sit.
-Come.
-Come on, sit.
-How are you doing?
-Fine.
OK. Look, I wanted to say...
as long as you don't sell any shit
to my friend, we're OK.
I support you.
Gay power and all that, OK?
-What are you doing?
-What do you think?
-Don't go. I'm giving you my blessing.
-Who asked for your blessing?
-Don't leave, please.
-Omar!
Blessing?
It's not like you're their best man.
Omar, they're my friends.
-Hi. What's wrong?
-Omar!
-How are you doing?
-Hi.
-What?
-I'm a bit nervous.
-Don't be. Why?
-I don't know.
-Wait for me. I'm out in five minutes.
-OK.
See you in a bit.
Omar, let's just talk about it.
Why did you tell people we're together?
No, no.
Besides, where did you even get that idea?
-They're my friends.
-We're not together!
It's not happening, Ander.
Not now, not ever.
-I don't get why you're acting like this.
-Because I can't do this.
Too many people know.
Even my sister, man.
And you don't know my family.
If they knew, I'd break their hearts.
-I thought nobody dies of a broken heart.
-Hi.
Omar, right?
-Yeah.
-Can you sell me something?
I think we might need it.
-How much?
-It's on the house.
But be careful with it.
It's strong,
and we don't want you to get sick.
Thanks.
Everything OK?
Yes.
Wait.
What do you think?
Are the lights too much?
No, it's nice.
I've got pot. You want some?
-No, we're fine.
-OK.
-Samuel...
-What?
More slowly.
OK.
Fuck!
What? Just relax.
I can't believe this.
I'm fucking it up.
-I'm fucking up.
-Lay down.
Samuel.
Yes?
I want to love you.
-Sorry.
-Relax.
-It's all right.
I wasn't so bad, right?
No. You were great.
Really great.
Samuel, I should leave soon.
-My mom works tonight.
-Yes, but they're expecting me for dinner.
Don't freak out, but someone broke in.
They took the watches and...
they took mine, too.
Yes, everything is in there.
-What's all this?
-I have enough to pay it all off.
Where did you get them?
-Let's say Marina helped me open a door.
-What?
Why did you drag her into this?
Fuck! Why did she get involved?
Because she loves you. Why else?
I'm telling you, it's going to be okay.
So be happy for me,
because I'm fixing everything with this.
It's about time.
Pun intended. This one's for you.
-Put it away.
-It smells like rich people.
OK.
Man.
I just wanted to make sure
you got home safe.
I had a great time.
We can talk before going to bed.
Bye.
Hi, Guzmán.
Hi.
How is your sister?
She didn't come to the first class.
-I guess she overslept. I'm not sure.
-Look who it is.
You were great in your pool last night.
Sometimes I forget how good we are in bed.
So you did it to tell everyone, right?
-You don't surprise me anymore, Lu.
-Was it a secret?
Well, I thought there were no secrets
between friends.
See you later.
Nadia...
-Don't worry.
-It was nothing.
-Just you?
-Yes.
Hey.
I called three times.
My name wasn't on the casting list.
In the end, it didn't work out.
My mom wasn't sure about you. Sorry.
Yeah, fucking great.
Did you really ruin that for him?
Yeah.
What's wrong? I don't owe him anything.
Besides, I'm tired of him using us.
He wants to take advantage of us.
Like we're not using him?
What's really bothering you?
He only wants us for one thing.
-Right.
-In fact, he only wants you.
You're jealous.
What are you saying?
Marina.
How are you doing?
I kept calling you last night.
I called you this morning, too.
Is everything OK?
Yeah, I was just tired, and my phone died.
Sure.
Sure what, Samuel?
You don't believe me?
It's not that. I'm starting
to get the feeling you're avoiding me.
-Don't get paranoid, Samuel.
-Paranoid about what?
I'm starting to feel like an idiot.
If something is going on, don't lie.
The only thing I can't stand
is being lied to.
That's the only thing you can't stand?
Lies?
Fuck, you can't stand much!
Because lies make life easier.
To avoid pain, to avoid suffering.
To avoid hurting people.
-Drop it.
-I'm not sure... Marina!
Marina!
That's my boy.
I didn't expect any less from you.
Marina!
Marina, are you OK?
-Fuck!
-Why did you argue?
I'd never been close to anyone
with HIV.
Marina!
Marina. What happened?
What are you doing? Go get help!
Marina, look at me.
Martín!
Look at me!
Move over, I've got this. Come on.
Can you hear me? Look at me.
Look at me. Follow my finger, please.
Marina!
Fuck, look at those pupils. Damn it.
What did you take, Marina?
What did you take?
What happened with Marina?
You know this means immediate expulsion?
We have a zero-tolerance drug policy.
-No, don't.
-I'm taking you to the nurse.
-I don't want to.
-We're going.
I'm fine. I'm perfectly fine.
Are you sure
you didn't have a relationship
with Marina outside of class?
No, of course not.
I'm taking her to the hospital.
Tell administration.
-Let's go.
-Martín, no! No!
If you tell anyone,
I'll tell them about your deal with Lu.
The adoption.
Wait.
Of course,
it's not fair what they did to her.
No one deserves that.
Did you hate Marina?
Subtitle translation
by Soledad Etchemendy