Samuel.
I have to ask you some questions.
You haven't been
at this school for long, right?
RECONSTRUCTION OF:
SAN ESTEBAN HIGH SCHOOL
No, almost four months.
I used to attend San Esteban.
SWINDLERS
San Esteban, the school that collapsed?
Calm down.
It's going to be all right.
Another woman's after your husband.
Have you noticed anything off lately?
What are you doing?
It's hers. I was just holding it for her.
This kid, I'm telling you.
To win over the locals,
the construction company
funded three scholarships...
to study here at Las Encinas.
I was one of the lucky ones.
Samu!
-What's up, man?
-How are you?
Hello, beautiful.
Shit, sorry. You won't blow yourself up
because I said that, right?
Do you know each other?
He's a buddy of my brother's.
This is fucking paradise, man.
Can't you smell it?
Those chicks pee cologne, dude.
I'm telling you.
Let's take a walk around, OK?
Shit.
They're looking at us like we're Martians.
You get used to it.
Come on, how about a photo?
A selfie or something.
Let's take a look around.
You know you can't use your phone?
If they catch you,
they'll confiscate it for a week.
That's against the Constitution.
-You've read the Constitution?
-No. I'm waiting for the movie.
-It's in the handbook.
-You've read the handbook?
When your name is Nadia Shanaa,
you'd better know
what can get you expelled.
Just in case.
The swimming pool
is bigger than the school!
You like to swim, right?
You were in the same class.
Samuel.
You'd be saving us a lot of time and work
if you answered a simple question.
Why did you have blood on you?
I've done nothing.
I want a lawyer, please.
What else isn't allowed?
Drinking, smoking on the grounds,
doing drugs.
So, they don't allow anything cool.
-Depends on what you think is cool.
-Olé!
Hey!
What the fuck, man?
Sorry!
Don't cry!
This is your classroom.
Wait for your teacher,
and after class, I'll assign you lockers.
-Welcome!
-Cool.
-Are you the new kids?
-Yes.
Good luck, then. You're gonna need it.
What's up, guys? I'm Christian.
Look at this guy.
Hi there.
Hello.
-Not there!
-Is it taken?
-By my invisible friend.
-Oh. Enjoy his company.
Good morning, class. How is everybody
doing today? Please sit down.
Okay. So, as we all know, we have
three new students with us today.
Let's meet them.
Damn. Wasn't this a tutorial class?
In English. It's a bilingual school.
You knew that, right?
Christian Varela.
Yes?
Do you want to introduce yourself
to the class?
What's he saying?
Introduce yourself.
Yes. Hello.
Goodbye?
Okay...
Great.
Thank you, Mr. Teacher.
"Mr. Teacher."
Nadia Shanaa.
Hello. I'm Nadia. I'm 16.
My family is from Palestine,
but I was born here in Spain.
And when I finish my studies,
I'd like to be professional diplomat
in the United Nations.
Wow. Impressive.
You know, every year we choose
our best student, and...
the trophy is rather ugly,
but it allows you
to study the next year at...
Who can tell me where?
Carla.
At a school in Florida.
Which gives you access
to an Ivy League university.
How can you win?
Excelling in all activities,
both curricular and extracurricular.
The more extracurriculars, the better.
Photography, chess, Chinese...
Check out the list.
If I were you, I'd watch out for her.
She'll take no prisoners.
Ridiculous.
Wasn't this a secular school?
Samuel García.
Hi. My name is Samuel.
I've got the feeling anything I say
will be used against me,
-so I'll remain silent.
-How darling!
Don't be afraid.
At this school, we teach values.
Manners and respect are paramount.
The leaders of tomorrow are
at this school.
-I know. That's what I'm afraid of.
-What did the waiter say?
He's talking to us.
-Guys.
-Sorry.
All right. My name's Samuel, and I am,
as your classmate said, a waiter.
Strange as it may seem to you,
sometimes waiters get a seat at the table.
But you don't need to worry.
I'm not here to take anybody's place.
You are still the leaders of tomorrow.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
So, let me continue
with where we left yesterday...
Of all the people there,
you had to mess with my brother.
That was your brother?
And they say the rich don't suffer.
I see.
-My condolences.
-Thank you.
Shall we?
Hey... in case nobody's told you,
it's cool having you in class.
Thanks.
Hello.
Where to? We'll go with you.
-Stop being a dick.
-Watch that mouth.
We're only trying to be friendly.
What's the matter, waiter?
Do you like my sister?
-She's a fan of lost causes...
-Guzmán, go to hell.
Seriously, leave him alone.
Let us have him for a bit.
We want to get to know him.
Or are you afraid of us?
-He is afraid of us!
-He is, yeah.
Waiter... hands off my sister.
Pretend you have a restraining order.
Guzmán... take this.
Nadia.
Can you come with me for a moment?
The principal wants a word.
No one had mentioned the scarf.
Why now?
Per our rules, no accessories are allowed.
My hijab is no accessory.
Besides, everybody has things around here.
Expensive bags, gold watches.
Those are ornamental.
They don't mean anything.
They do. They mean many things.
They mean "I have more money,
more style. I'm better than you."
Nadia, we understand, but--
Look, if you understood...
you wouldn't ask me to give up
my culture or religion.
Nadia, think about it.
It's up to you.
But if you wear it tomorrow...
we'll have no choice but to expel you.
Who do you think calls the shots here?
Don't you have other things
to worry about?
Like the fact that you speak no English.
Come on, it's not nothing,
it's "a little butt."
I got it all under control.
Lend me your notes in English,
and I'll translate them online
to understand.
I'm not giving you my notes.
And you shouldn't be here.
You're taking a spot
somebody else actually needs.
Wait, do you think I am here to study? No.
I'm here to meet the people
who rule the roost.
They're not the ones with the best grades,
but the ones in with the right crowd.
Watch.
-What time's the party?
-Party?
Somebody say party? Hi, I'm Christian.
Hello, do you speak Spanish?
I was talking to my friends.
Oh, sorry.
By the way, are you on Instagram?
I can give you mine if you want.
Yes, please!
It's pekechristian007.
The first one is a k.
Pekechristian.
Pekechristian. Oh, no!
I've fucking had it with these people.
I don't understand
how they got into this school.
Wow, this video! Look at this.
Do not touch me!
Lu, don't be mean.
Pay no attention to my friend.
So, what about this party?
My sister's coming-out party is private,
like our conversation.
Who do I need to talk to
about getting an invite?
You've never partied with me.
You had a roof collapse on you, right?
Maybe that impaired your ability
to take a hint.
Shall I say it in English so you get it?
Goodbye.
-And if I don't feel like it?
-Look...
You're slow,
so you don't get how things work here.
But your friend there
is starting to get it.
Come on, let's go, Guzmán.
Cool video.
Christian, it can happen to anyone,
going too far.
It's the party
for the end of the school year...
There's alcohol.
I don't know,
maybe a fight gets out of control.
What's that got to do with me?
I'm not like that.
Can you interrogate me
without my parents here?
These are just questions.
But if you don't want to cooperate,
we can take you to the station.
With your parents and a lawyer.
How did you get that injury?
Hit myself on a door.
Why do I get the feeling you're lying?
The change may end up
not being all that bad.
How is your new school?
I'm a Muslim, I don't play soccer,
and I was caught reading in the hallway.
I'll be on wanted signs tomorrow.
-The reward will be a reggaeton concert.
-I'm a dead man, then.
Shit, man, I wish some rubble had fallen
on me when the school collapsed.
Christian got 14 stitches.
And a scholarship to Las Encinas,
dickhead.
With any luck, the same will happen
at your new school.
-No such luck, I'm afraid.
-Roofs do collapse.
You're the worst!
Hi.
Look at him.
He looks like a minister.
Little brother!
Wow!
-Doing well in fancyland, huh?
-Yes.
-I'll fight anyone who bothers you.
-Why are you here?
-Aren't you happy to see me?
-Yes! But they let you out?
No, I'm still there. What do you think?
Let's have a beer.
Here you go.
Wow!
This is nice, right?
The three of us together again.
-Let's go out tonight.
-I can't.
-You can.
-I work tonight, Nano.
Just call in sick.
What if I get caught? It's the only job
we've had since you left.
Is this how it's gonna be?
Samu, I didn't leave. They made me leave.
How was your first day?
Very good.
OPEN
CLOSED
How about this one?
-Do you like it?
-Mom...
You showed me yesterday.
The answer remains the same.
You don't like anything, Marina.
Is it that hard
to be a bit more enthusiastic?
Mom and Dad are doing this for you.
For me?
Nobody asked them to.
Sweetheart...
We want to celebrate your coming of age
and to introduce you into society.
As a virginal young lady
looking for a boyfriend.
Marina, please.
What? Are we never going to talk about it?
What are the new students like?
A moron, a fundamentalist,
and one with a raised fist.
-As a joke, they'd be priceless.
-Hey...
Why don't you invite one to the party?
Are you serious?
Why not?
Have you lost your mind?
Hello. No, I told you not to worry.
-OK?
-I think it's a great idea.
Besides, it's my party, right?
Sons of bitches!
Cool.
Hey! Have you seen my uniform?
No? Nothing?
You haven't seen my clothes?
What's up, handsome?
Hello, beautiful.
You haven't seen my clothes?
No? Come on! There we are!
All right, then. Fuck you all.
Enjoy the view! This one too, come on.
You wish you had this ass!
Hey, would you like to come to a party
at my place tomorrow evening?
Why would you invite me to a party?
Because I need somebody else
to enjoy it as little as I will.
Besides, wouldn't you like
to see the look on my brother's face?
OK.
Your hair looks nice today.
Did you have any problems
with the other students?
No. Not with anybody.
How was your relationship
with the other students?
Did you get along? Were you friends?
You're Ander, right?
I've seen all your trophies, man.
I'm crazy about tennis.
Come on, guys!
To your next class!
Anybody left in the locker room?
What are you doing?
-Anything wrong?
-No, why?
OK, then. Off to class.
Thanks a lot.
-You're all right, bro.
-I'm not your bro. I just saved your ass.
You could pay me back.
Guzmán!
-What?
-We've been seen!
-What is it?
-Shit!
-We were seen?
Don't worry, he'll be here soon.
I talked to him ten minutes ago.
Besides, nobody will see you here, man.
Don't worry.
-But can he be trusted?
-Of course!
What's he gonna do? Go on TV
to say a rich boy is buying joints?
Come on! That wouldn't be news.
I don't want them to know at school.
Who's going to find out?
I won't tell. Don't worry.
Besides, I don't have any friends there.
Or do I?
Yeah! Good man!
By the way,
I wanted to ask you something.
-Shoot.
-Why do you all mess with us?
Something happened
with a scholarship student.
The son of one of the cooks.
They didn't offer scholarships
for a full year.
It was a huge mess.
Until you arrived.
Hey!
What's up, man?
-How are you?
-Hi.
I'll introduce you. Mr. X, Mr. Dealer.
Sorry, no real names.
Thanks, much obliged.
You see how polite he is?
You can't complain,
I bring you quality clients.
Don't you forget.
By the way, we'll talk soon.
You owe me one!
Here we go, now we're all set!
-Hey, my man!
-So good to see you!
Twelve, thirteen, fourteen...
Hang in there!
Fifteen, sixteen, that's it!
So, they make a school collapse,
and get away with it.
Can't wrap my fucking head around that!
-When will the others be released?
-What do I know, man?
That's how the world works.
Some of us in jail for small shit,
and the real crooks out on the street.
It figures.
I almost didn't live to tell it.
I got a huge cut in my head.
But, that got me a ticket to fancyland.
It's no joke, Christian.
What if there had been casualties?
This is not OK.
This country is a fucking joke.
Get him a drink. We're losing him!
-There are none left.
-None?
I'll take care of it. I'll be right back.
Man, save and you can buy it.
A little stuck on that topic, isn't he?
I mean, I don't know,
Nano is like a brother to me, you know.
And... my brother's brother
is also my brother, right?
You want my notes, right?
Shit, man. That's fucking gross.
WELCOME.
SHALL WE CREATE YOUR PROFILE?
A GUY
Look at him! Sleeping like a baby.
Catch!
I have an epic idea to end the night.
Jaime, I'm taking it.
Nano, tell me where we're going.
To visit our friend
the owner of the construction company
to give him something to remember us by.
-Get off.
-What?
Get off!
Keep watch.
No! What are you doing?
Don't even think about it!
Let's live a little, Samu!
Nano!
You just got out of jail,
and this is the dumbest shit you could do!
Nano, someone's coming! Nano!
-Huh?
-Someone's coming. Let's go!
Motherfucker...
THI
Come on!
Just one more thing, Nadia.
Help us, and then you can go.
What can you tell me about this trophy?
Why?
We think it's the murder weapon.
What?
We've been told
you wanted to win it more than anything.
Just me?
It's her word against ours.
You want to risk them believing her?
-This is all your fault.
-Mine?
Yes, you and your silly obsession
with doing it in public places.
Sure.
As if you didn't like it.
Hello.
Sorry about yesterday.
We thought we were alone.
If only.
I know we started off
on the wrong foot. I'd like to fix that.
Why don't you come
to my sister's party tonight?
We can get to know each other.
Thanks, but no.
Have a nice day.
Boo!
I love her!
Who? Carla?
Her mother is a Spanish grandee.
Do you know
Marquesado de Caleruega wines?
-No.
-That's her mommy, the marchioness.
That guy, Polo,
has been her boyfriend since they were 12.
That guy? For real?
No, come on, she deserves much better.
You're fucking kidding me!
I'd watch out for the girls here.
Yeah. I'll be watching this one.
Nadia.
How are you?
Listen, I'd like you to come to my party.
Thank you, but it isn't my scene.
You can come in your scarf, or without it.
Come as you want, OK?
It's called a hijab.
Not a scarf.
Hijab.
-And nobody forces me to wear it.
-Lucky you!
I do feel like I'm being forced
to have this ridiculous party.
I don't know. Give us a chance.
We're not all like my brother.
It starts at 8:00.
Samuel has the address.
-Fuck, man, this doesn't draw well.
-Don't make fun of the newbie, OK?
I'm not making fun.
For a first joint,
made with a tutorial, it's not bad.
Why the fuck don't you wanna go
to the party?
Stop obsessing about the party.
I'm not obsessing.
You may be used to all this luxury
and stuff, but I'm not.
This is new to me. I'm excited about it.
What do you think?
-That I live like the rest of them?
-You don't?
-Not even close.
-Then what are you doing at that school?
Kid, I'm the principal's son.
Son of a bitch! You've got connections!
Anyway...
-You want to go, right?
-Of course.
-Are you positive?
-Completely, yes.
-Do you have anything decent to wear?
-Of course I do, man!
What are you doing here?
Nadia wants to go to the party.
My dad wants to be sure
there won't be alcohol
and that parents will be there.
Just say yes. I want to go home.
Yeah, man, don't worry.
Damn!
This is a serious party.
THI
What's up, Samu?
-Hi.
-You didn't expect to see me here, huh?
Let's go in!
Here you have it, a coming-out party
in all its ridiculousness!
What is it for?
In other times, to find a husband quickly.
Nowadays, it's more about networking.
Although the husband thing
is not ruled out.
You're so much fun when you drink.
Wow, you rich people know
how to throw a party!
Are you color-blind?
Or did you not turn on the light
when you got dressed?
Lu, don't be mean.
Handsome guys look good
in anything.
We've already said hi. Are you staying?
I don't know. Do you want me to stay?
-If you say yes, I'll stay forever.
-Well, well, let's start with a drink.
Please.
Ah, move aside.
Can you explain
why you brought the influencer?
-You brought the girl, right?
-It's my home, Ander.
I don't know, he wanted to come.
Nothing's going to happen.
This whole crusade of yours
against them is ridiculous.
Look...
I forgive you,
because you're really drunk.
But I'd never betray you like this!
What betrayal, Guzmán?
What betrayal?
Fucking champagne! Where's the beer?
You've come.
Dad.
Pleased to meet you.
The balls on you, kid, showing up here!
Don't you know we have security cameras?
Shall we talk later?
Only alcohol can make this tolerable.
Here.
Thanks. I don't drink.
It's going to be a hard night, then.
-I'm leaving soon.
-Of course.
Why give us a chance if you've already
passed judgment on us all, right?
Here's everything you hate about the West.
All the sinful decadence.
I thought I was the one judging.
But I can see you've decided
what I think and what I don't.
With a scarf on your head,
you can't possibly think much, dear.
Is this about me
not accepting the champagne,
or are you a born racist?
Forgive me. Oh, no, forgive me.
Sorry, I came here in peace, I swear.
I'm sure you and I
have something in common.
Don't worry.
I've come to Las Encinas to study.
I'm not interested in anything
beyond that.
Let me give you some advice, dear.
You can do it all.
Look at me.
I date. I have fun, a lot.
And I'm at the top of the class.
Or you were.
Right?
So?
What do you think of my party?
Wouldn't you love to set us all on fire?
OK. I'll order a glass of water,
just in case.
Samuel...
Sorry I didn't tell you
my dad's company...
-was the one from your school.
-Right.
-It would have been good to know.
-I'm not like him.
And to be honest,
I think I don't even like him.
But he's done this for you.
Yeah, he's very good at solving problems
by throwing money at them.
Wanna dance?
-What?
-What's wrong?
Don't you see?
It's not about the skirt. I don't care.
It's that Taliban girl.
That little hypocrite.
Wearing a scarf on your head
makes you superior to us?
Please, how ridiculous!
I don't want her here,
but we have to keep her from telling.
I have an idea.
Let's hear it.
I propose a game.
Why don't you seduce her?
Then everybody finds out...
and that's that.
You want me to hook up
with the Palestinian
who walks around in a turban?
Oh, sweetie...
the idea of making a virginal Muslim girl
fall for you doesn't turn you on?
Come on, you woo her, she falls for you,
everybody finds out...
That's it! We cut her down to size,
and she can't act all superior.
Not even if I ask you?
Then I'll let you do
whatever you want with me.
I already do whatever I want with you.
Not even half of it.
I'm thinking today
would be a good day to do it. Right?
I call the tow truck,
and they don't come for me.
Well, I don't know.
Here? Right now?
And why not?
But if you're not sure,
let's forget about it.
Hey.
-Samuel, right?
-Yes.
What exactly did you mean to write here,
on my front wall?
T-H-I...
S.
"This above all:
to thine own self be true."
-Ah.
-It's a quote from Hamlet.
Yes, of course, a quote from Hamlet.
Ingenious.
But...
I think you wanted to write...
thief, son of a bitch,
or one of those names
the press is calling me lately.
Bring the other scholarship kids,
and we'll take a photo of the four of us.
Shaking hands and smiling.
I don't know.
Come on, man.
What's wrong with taking a photo?
It could be good for everybody.
For the town, for the school,
even for you.
I wouldn't feel comfortable doing it.
It's OK, kid.
I'll report your brother tomorrow.
Let's see what happens to his parole.
Think about it.
What did he say?
He wants a photo
with the scholarship students.
-Really?
-Yes.
That's why he wanted me to invite you.
His image makeover bullshit.
He doesn't waste an opportunity.
Samuel, don't play along.
You don't have to.
I don't mind doing it.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I don't know.
I thought you were different.
Hello.
COME GET ME?
Come on, we have things to do.
What is this?
Olé.
We have 15 minutes
before they realize I'm not there.
Are you taking your clothes off?
That comes off, too.
But slowly, so I can see you.
OK. And you too.
Let's do it at the same time.
Like this?
Am I doing it right?
Yes, you're doing fucking great.
HEY, COOL PROFILE
YOURS TOO. WHAT'S UP?
BORED. WANT TO MEET?
DO YOU HAVE ANOTHER PHOTO?
I can't believe it.
Explain it to me, please.
You knew it was him who ruined our wall,
and you let him in our home?
Who?
The skinny kid.
Because he had ulterior motives.
He wanted a picture with him.
What?
Mom, I don't know why you are surprised.
You are the only one
Dad still manages to disappoint.
Those people are poison.
You know it.
Why are you with them every time
I turn around, Marina? Why?
Why don't you leave them alone?
Because I refuse
to let you get hurt again, Marina!
-Pablo did not mean to hurt me!
-Marina!
Now is not the time. Please.
Then when?
Tell me, when is the right time?
Why can't we talk about it?
You've spent a fortune on psychologists
to convince me nothing happened.
That life goes on.
That everything would be fine.
And you know what?
Every time you avoid the subject,
I feel like a piece of shit.
I fell in love with a boy. He infected me.
I need you to say it!
Say it! Say it, Mom!
"My 16-year-old daughter is HIV-positive."
Do you regret tonight?
It was... intense.
But it was good.
You're sure?
Good night.
GOOD NIGHT, GORGEOUS
I love you. I love you more than ever.
You! This is how you thank us
for your scholarship?
-Guzmán!
-By vandalizing other people's property?
-You disgust me!
-What's going on here?
And who are you?
Unbelievable,
the riffraff we have here tonight!
Should I take that as a compliment
or punch you?
Take it as you will.
-Let's go.
-I won't let this prep boy insult us.
I'm not insulting you,
just stating the facts.
One question.
What do you call people who keep millions
that don't belong to them
so they can live the way you do?
Thieves or simply bastards?
How dare you come to this house
to insult me and my family?
Who do you think you are, fucking clown?
-What are you doing?
-OK.
You don't deserve my brother!
Get off me!
Shove your money up your asses!
You! Hey!
You are finished!
Tomorrow, everybody at school
will know you are a fucking criminal!
Forget about your scholarship!
Guzmán. Are you OK?
Did they hurt you?
Does it hurt a lot?
Polo...
Why don't you get lost
and stop making a fool of yourself?
Go!
Guzmán,
don't take it out on Samuel.
He's a good person.
Let's see
what the principal says tomorrow.
Your sister is right.
Samuel is a good person.
Me, not so much.
If you say anything at school,
I'll share what I saw in the shower.
Thanks for inviting me.
Nadia.
Nadia, you win.
I lost my temper.
I won't tell on your friend.
Stay a little longer.
Let me show you we are worth the trouble.
You all are too good
at looking down on people.
Teach me how to look at you.
I promise I'll be a fast learner.
What's going on, honey?
This one needs to be taken down
a peg or two.
Hey.
Are you gonna say nothing all night?
After I stood up for you?
You are clueless.
Do you know what I've done for you?
I had it under control,
and you had to make a mess.
Now I have to clean it up.
I was protecting you, asshole!
Like I have my entire fucking life.
I never asked you to!
Come on, Samu! I won't let those people,
who are a real cancer, laugh at you!
You've been blaming them your whole life.
Maybe you're the cancer.
Is Samuel home?
Is Samuel here?
He's sleeping.
He was up all night hugging the toilet.
He says it's a hangover,
but it's the fear of having to go back
to that school.
He can come back, no problem.
I came to tell him
my brother won't say anything.
Very well.
Anything else?
Coffee, water, beer?
Sit down if you want.
Did you tag my wall?
My letter of introduction.
Next time, finish it.
I liked what you said at the party.
You dared to shout what a lot of us think.
Or at least I do.
Somebody had to say it.
And... is it true you've been to jail?
You love to ask questions, huh?
Yes, but only for a short while.
Sleeping badly, eating worse.
No women,
unless you count my mother, my lawyer,
and my second aunt from Murcia.
I'm not sure why she came.
None like you, I can tell you that.
Stay any longer,
and I'll make you iron.
I'll go.
You'd better.
-Bye.
Here you go. Washed and pressed.
By the way...
fancy girl was here.
She wants you to go back to school.
Subtitle translation
by Soledad Etchemendy