ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS,
EVENTS, AND OCCUPATIONS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
What is it? What happened?
-Did someone die?
-Dead bodies?
-What is it?
-Is it a murder case?
Why won't they tell us?
…or command locusts to devour the land
or send a plague among my people.
If my people, who are called by my name,
will humble themselves
and pray and seek my face
and turn from their wicked ways,
then I will hear from heaven,
and I will forgive their sin
and will heal their land.
Now my eyes will be open
and my ears will be attentive
to the prayers offered in this place.
I have chosen and consecrated this temple…
One of the homeless people had pneumonia,
so they gave him medicine.
It was donated, so they didn't know
about the side effects.
Reports of a disease
that causes the infected
to bite people and suck their blood
are coming from all over the world.
The public health authorities made clear
that it hasn't been confirmed yet,
but similar cases are also occurring
in Korea.
In a shelter for the homeless in Seyang,
around ten homeless individuals
who were staying there were killed.
The authorities stated
that there was a random fight
among the homeless at the shelter,
which caused casualties,
so there may be possible sanitary…
SUSPECTED TO BE AN INFECTIOUS DISEASE
You're eating plants again?
Sae-bom, are you okay?
Yes, I got tested and got myself together.
Just what in the world is going on?
We stopped all the drills.
They shut down the training area
where Lee Jong-tae caused a scene.
He's that man from before, right?
Yes, he is.
He really does have some power.
What if something really bad happens?
If people suddenly start
to go mad like that…
There is a cure for this, right?
I don't know.
It looks like they're
trying their best, but…
I got a call from a journalist.
He said he'll pay me
if I tell him what happened here.
Me too.
Looks like he contacted
everyone on our team.
Hey, don't contact people like him.
We even signed a confidentiality oath.
Right.
-Are you returning to work now?
-No.
I received paid leave for six months.
I stopped by to say hi today
after sending my stuff to my new house.
Are you leaving the public official dorm?
You worked so hard to decorate it.
It's okay.
I got a house.
An apartment.
-With a loan?
-No.
Remember when we talked about
additional points?
The special provision.
I do. Work evaluation, arrest records…
I got the highest points,
but I still lacked points for that.
So I decided to get points
for newlyweds too.
You mean… You're going to get married
because you need more points?
Yes.
Who are you going to marry?
There's this guy who asked me out
when we were young.
I rejected him at the time.
But I asked him
if he still has feelings for me.
It's not because
I don't take you seriously.
I…
I always dreamed
of living in my own house.
That's why.
These are for the clothes we burned.
Thank you.
I feel like I've gotten closer to you.
She's cold.
-Do you need more points?
-That's true, but…
I asked you
because I have feelings for you.
You're not so bad on the eyes,
and you are resourceful.
Hey, I'm a lot better than you think.
Being two years behind? That's nothing.
Plus, it's a newly built apartment.
If you miss this,
you'll regret it forever.
Hey! You can't find
another friend like me.
Okay, sure.
I'm asking you…
to marry me.
I know what you mean.
I'm saying yes.
He said yes.
Oh… Congratulations.
Oh, well…
-When are you moving in?
-Today.
This is the scratch Lee Jong-tae made,
and it's not healing that well.
It didn't get worse, though?
No. They want to draw
my blood every two weeks.
I see.
Are you okay?
What?
Yes, I'm okay.
(I AM) THE LIFESAVER
Aren't you taking that?
I will.
Hang on.
I'm going to go home now.
I'll organize your stuff when they arrive.
You take your time.
-Okay.
You're putting in so much effort.
DEDICATED TO THE SECURITY OF THE HOMELAND
Corporal, have you thought about it?
How much can you pay me?
I talked to the director,
and if there is internal footage
and if we get an exclusive,
I think we can do our best
to give you the amount you ask for.
Why don't you get in?
Let's talk comfortably.
Hang in there, okay?
It's okay.
Seung-young, what are you doing?
Here.
Thank you.
How can you remember
a picture from 12 years ago?
I almost got killed back then.
Anyway, congratulations. You did it.
Though I didn't expect it
to work out like this.
Move!
-Why? What is it?
-My gift for you.
Come on.
My wife started working a side job.
Don't worry. She's all better now,
completely healthy.
We also do delivery.
Hand them around the apartment
and spread the word about our shop.
You should be helping your wife,
not making things hard for her.
About the info
on Han Tae-seok like you asked…
I will do my best. What is it?
He specializes in infectious diseases.
Some of the military academy
students are sent
to a medical school
as commissioned education.
He became a doctor through that, served
as a medic, and finished his service.
After that, he worked
at a pharmaceutical company.
He was the Team Leader
of Competitiveness Reinforcement.
And…
This was taken during his trial
for assaulting the CEO
of the pharmaceutical company.
He didn't look like the type to do that.
Those who look well-mannered
are scarier when they lose it.
Anyway, he was suddenly found innocent,
and he went back to the military.
As a dispatch to the CDSCHQ.
That's weird.
Anyway, try not to get involved in this.
You'll just get yourself in trouble
by meddling in it.
Okay.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
And if you need more rice cakes,
tell me, okay?
-Okay.
-Okay, bye.
I don't want to get involved either,
but I think that'll be hard.
SEYANG FOREST LE CIEL
WELCOME, NEW RESIDENTS
That trainee I gave first aid to.
-He kept coming to mind.
-What about him?
He's in bad condition,
just like Lee Jong-tae.
Even his family can't visit him.
I asked the guys who were
dispatched to the CDSCHQ,
and they said once you go in there,
you can't come out alive.
But I came out alive.
Right.
Only you did.
Is this really okay?
What if everyone is dying in there?
It's so difficult to be happy.
You scared me!
Sorry. You need to be careful.
-I'm sorry.
That scared me.
I'm going to the fifth floor. Thank you.
Please wear a mask indoors.
Okay, I'm sorry.
That hoodie…
Where did you buy that?
It looks genuine, not custom-made.
I'm in the SOU.
The real SOU?
You're a tactical agent
who fights terrorist attacks?
Yes.
Can you please get me an SOU T-shirt?
The one that has SOU
printed in the front and back.
Large-sized.
I'll look into it. Large, you said?
Yes, please do. I'm on the 15th floor.
He's eccentric.
You're early.
We should celebrate with delivery food.
I knew you'd say that, so I searched
for good restaurants already.
Hey, you had this picture?
Jung-kook had the file.
So I had it developed.
Don't you like it?
Well…
But this situation
wasn't that joyful for you at the time.
Do you like it?
Hey! Stand straight.
Okay, here we go! One, two, three!
When life is hard, look at this,
and do your best in life.
There.
Well, you said the district office
can come and check
if we really are married.
This would show why we got married.
It's a very powerful motive.
Right. It looks like
there's a deep story behind us.
It's nice I'm cuffed.
When would I ever experience
getting cuffed again?
Are you passing around rice cakes?
It's Jung-kook's side job.
He wants me to advertise them.
Okay.
-I'll be back soon--
-No, I'll do it.
You get the house organized
and order black bean noodles.
I want a double portion.
Okay.
-Hey, be careful.
-Okay.
Who is it?
I moved in next door.
Aren't the grown-ups home?
Hi.
Thank you, I will enjoy it.
Bye.
What?
It won't open.
The lower floors are public rentals,
and the upper ones are regular apartments.
They blocked it to stop people downstairs
from coming up.
You know all kinds of things.
I know everything.
Kids call us beggars at school.
-How do they come down from upstairs?
-By taking the elevator.
-Are you going downstairs?
-Yes.
One apartment is empty,
and a lady lives alone
in the other apartment,
but she didn't come home yesterday.
You really know everything.
That's better.
Jeez.
Is it okay to do this?
Yes. Blocking an emergency exit
is a violation of the Fire Prevention Act.
If they complain, we can report them.
I see.
Okay then, see you later.
The insurance companies
always say it's 50-50.
Keeping a safe distance,
obligation to look forward. Right?
Don't mind what those parrots
are squawking about.
I saw the footage. And 90-10 is possible.
I'm from Unit 501.
I moved in today, so I brought rice cakes.
Please excuse me.
We're neighbors, so
I'll provide legal counseling for free.
So come anytime and consult me.
Yes, that's what you should do.
SPECIALIZES IN DIVORCE AND CAR ACCIDENTS
"Lawyer Kook Hae-seong,
who appears like a comet in hard times."
Those are separate. Yes.
1:1 COUNSELING CHAT
WITH LAWYER KOOK HAE-SEONG
Yes, you can check and call me again.
That's a separate matter.
IT'S A HIT-AND-RUN
IT'S NOT ME, MY FRIEND DID IT
Yes.
Of course. Call me anytime.
Okay, thank you.
ARE YOU GOING TO TURN YOURSELF IN?
-Who was it?
-Downstairs.
She just moved in.
But you're throwing away food?
You've worked as a lawyer's secretary.
How can you be so gullible?
You shouldn't eat food
a stranger gives you.
So the woman downstairs
gave us poisoned rice cake to kill us?
Honey, you have a psychological problem.
So-yoon, I was once a public defender.
I learned about
people's evil intentions quite early.
Fine.
Then as a public defender,
please go consult them.
That one really needs
an attorney right now.
Good grief.
Of course you'll get caught, you fool.
I'm sure the cops are
on their way to your house now.
WILL I GET CAUGHT IF
I DON'T TURN MYSELF IN?
FIRST, I MUST FIND OUT
IF THE ACCIDENT WAS REPORTED
CAN I GET IN TOUCH WITH YOUR FRIEND?
Who are you?
Hi.
I moved in downstairs.
Here's rice cake for you.
I don't like food made from flour.
But this is "rice" cake.
Nice to meet you too.
Honey.
Hey.
Hey. You're home.
Why didn't you answer the door?
I was washing my hair.
Why did you suddenly
press the doorbell, though?
I didn't press it.
Someone came from downstairs.
The apartment is tiny,
and the security is awful.
Hey, Min-ji, wash your hands first.
You should wash your hands
when you come home. 20 seconds.
Are you taking your meds? Hang on.
Here's some water.
I got five complaints today.
Why do they ask for so much
over a few shots of fillers?
This is why I didn't want to do
a franchise dermatology clinic.
I'm sorry.
You're doing bothersome work
because of me.
I will make you an awesome glass
of nice, cold tangerine highball.
What is this?
Your legs are as hard as rocks.
I must relieve them all today.
Shall I make you
a tangerine highball first?
Madam.
You're being a good boy today.
COLLECT THE COUPONS
Let's eat 20 dishes
and get a small sweet and sour pork.
Okay.
And this.
What is this?
A contract for joint ownership
when it's switched
to a regular apartment in ten years.
Six to four is okay, right?
Because my points are higher.
Of course. You even saved my life.
-Right?
-Yes.
I wanted to have herringbone flooring,
but it's new flooring,
so I can't rip it out.
Still, this is neat.
I can't believe this.
I have a house now.
White or beige curtains
would be nice and natural, right?
Yes.
Should we install blinds for the veranda?
The lighting seems just fine.
Still, I might buy
a few lighting fixtures.
We'll need
some gym equipment for this room.
Nice.
I prefer stainless steel countertops.
But all this is brand new.
Let's use it for now and replace it later.
Should we replace only
the sink and bathroom faucets?
Sure.
I'll need to make a lot of money.
But it's nice.
It's worth earning money for.
I'll work hard too.
Let's do this.
The District Office can come
for an inspection, so…
-Shall we change it? Or move it?
-No, you did a great job.
We must be meticulous until the very end.
Right.
When I was young, we had a house.
But something went wrong
and we kept moving to smaller houses,
and in the end,
we lived in a semi-basement.
It only had one room.
-Back in high school?
-Yes.
I could wander around outside
during the day,
but I had to sleep at night,
so I went home as late as possible.
We crammed ourselves
into that small room to sleep.
My mom and dad
were always yelling and fighting…
If I just couldn't stand it anymore,
I got my dad's car key and came outside.
I can't take this!
You get paid peanuts, and…
I always wanted to have my own space.
My own space, just for me.
And I finally made it,
so the Earth
shouldn't meet its end just yet.
Good night.
You will end up like me too.
What is it?
What are they doing
in the middle of the night?
Do you want me to go talk to them?
No…
I was just startled, that's all.
Hello?
You mean now?
-Who was it?
-What?
It's a guy I know.
It's because of the investigation.
Get some more sleep. You're on leave.
Why are you collecting her blood?
She's already worn out.
We won't take that much.
You got married thanks to me,
so don't be so mean.
Thanks to you? This was all me.
If I didn't help her
with additional points,
Ms. Yoon Sae-bom
wouldn't have asked you to marry her.
By the way, you come into
someone else's apartment so easily.
Did you see the news about
the homeless shelter?
I did.
The article about Next
being given to the homeless there
will be released today.
Due to concerns about
possible side effects,
the drugs in the market
will be all collected,
and those who sold them illegally
will be punished.
That's the government's conclusion.
But why are you telling me that?
Because we're going to
investigate together.
I sent the document
asking for cooperation to your station.
Well, I'm a bit busy.
As you can see, I…
CHIEF
Yes, Chief.
Okay.
Do I have to do this?
Of course, I should do it. Who else would?
So…
What should I start with?
This is Lee Jong-tae's phone.
It's been unlocked.
Meet the dealer as Lee Jong-tae
and make the arrest.
Is he cooperating
with the investigation too?
Something like that.
But do you know
what the most difficult part
of narcotics investigation is?
These jerks are always
full of suspicion and greed.
We can't even meet them
if we don't pay half in advance.
But the police don't have money.
I'm not saying that I don't want to help,
it's just the investigation can't…
Use it for the investigation.
Make expense reports,
and return the remaining amount.
I heard you worked
at a pharmaceutical company.
That you were in some
competitiveness team.
Competitiveness Reinforcement Team.
It's where we steal
other companies' drugs.
I may not be good at making things,
but I am good at stealing.
And beating people up?
Call me when you arrest the dealer.
I will participate as an observer.
By the way, how much is the amount?
You're not going to say that
the amount is wrong later, right?
Corporal Jung Yi-hyun.
I heard your nickname is
"Great Detective."
Because you always logically infer cases.
They call it "reckless"
or "hoping for good luck."
They say the way I think is weird,
but I somehow get things right.
There's a bias that athletes are dumb.
You must show that you both have
a good brain and good physique.
I seriously hate him.
MS. KIM BOK-NAM
Hey, Mom, what is it?
I heard you moved into
an apartment yesterday.
And you didn't even call me.
Come on. Do I have to hear
about you from Yi-hyun?
Mom, I'm tired.
I got tested for an infectious disease.
I got tested for COVID-19
more than five times.
No, not that. It was for
that infectious disease
-that makes people bite other people.
-You mean Mad Human Disease?
It has a name?
Yes, they say it's similar to rabies
and makes people go mad.
I heard humans can catch rabies too.
My goodness.
So dog owners are in a frenzy right now.
Yes, anyway, it was for that.
I got tested for Mad Human Disease
and I'm now in self-quarantine
at my apartment.
I even had a dream
about biting people last night.
Really?
What about Yi-hyun?
Is he okay with living with you?
Of course. We really do love each other.
I'll recover soon and call you
when our wedding date is set.
I'm starting to cough now. I should go.
I need to go buy groceries.
GYM REGISTRATION PROCESS: RESIDENTS
WEEKDAYS: 6:00 TO 22:00
WEEKENDS: 6:00 TO 21:00
-Hi.
What is that? A battle request?
I guess you don't know it.
I ENJOYED THE RICE CAKE, THANK YOU
You're such a good girl. Thank you.
You know they offer deliveries, right?
-Yes, Myungwon Rice Cake Shop.
-Yes.
If you want rice cakes later,
ask your family to buy them from there.
By the way,
are you really a police officer?
Of course I am.
Look.
It's even better than a police officer.
When I get healthy,
I want to be just like you.
-Are you sick right now?
-A little bit.
When I was little, I was also really sick.
So I couldn't go to school for two years.
-Really?
-Yes.
But I'm totally fine and strong now.
You will be even stronger than me,
so you don't need to worry about anything.
Thank you for this.
Where are you going?
To have a battle.
How can I help you?
I live downstairs, and it's been
so noisy since last night.
Are you doing construction work in there?
I'm sorry. I'm moving my furniture, so…
In the middle of the night?
I'm a person with initiative,
so I have to do things when I decide to.
I'm sorry.
That's not initiative, it's an illness.
It will never happen again.
All right, then.
We enjoyed the rice cake.
How did you know it was me?
-We never met before.
-I heard about you.
Your daughter looks just like you,
she's lovely.
You look lovely.
Haven't you seen that man before?
I got on the elevator
a few times with him,
but it seems like
he's not interested in others.
Both him and his wife are doctors,
but he doesn't work and just stays home.
My mom said
they have a legal problem or something.
Perhaps it's because
he just likes to be lazy.
-Okay, then. Bye.
-What about you?
Me? I'm going to work out.
Goodbye.
Are you home alone?
My dad does parcel delivery work,
and my mom helps with
sorting in the morning.
What about school?
I'm doing experience learning at home.
These days, if we tell the school,
we can get 19 days of school off a year.
Come with me.
Let's do experience learning
of sports with me today.
Oh, this is the place.
Hi.
This is nice.
-Hi.
I'm a resident here.
I heard I can come here anytime.
Please wait.
You can bring
your own sneakers and towels.
But first, please write down
your building number and unit number.
Hi.
-Are you going to work out too?
-Yes.
-Here.
-Thank you.
YOON SAE-BOM - BUILDING 101, UNIT 501
The public rental residents
are not allowed to enter.
Why not? Is it because
of the maintenance fee?
Well, the maintenance fee is one thing,
but it's more because of the equipment.
The regular residents paid for them,
so some say that it's not fair
if we let the public rental residents
use them freely.
Okay, I'll work out at home.
-Let's go.
-Ma'am.
But if you get personal training from me,
I can help you with that.
I'll work out at home.
-Did you know?
-Yes.
Then why didn't you tell me?
I thought you'd be able to solve it.
Is there anything else like
the Fire Prevention Act?
When money is involved,
it's hard to solve it.
But still, there is a way.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
Slowly.
-Four.
You're good.
-Five.
Let's go do that one over there.
What do you learn in PE class these days?
-Running.
-Oh, are you a good runner?
No.
I'm totally good at running.
WIFE
MISSED CALL: WIFE
Since you worked out, get some good rest.
Goodbye.
She's cute.
Hey.
Sae-bom, help me.
I got scratched by that trainee.
I was too scared to say it, but…
the wound isn't healing.
Where are you?
I'll be right there.
It'll be okay.
Look at me. I'm okay.
You just need to get tested
and get some rest today.
You'll be fine after.
I'll tell your wife that
you're not cheating on her.
I'm scared to think that I'm going to die.
You won't die!
You didn't get bitten.
Look at me.
It really is nothing.
You just need to get tested
and confirm things today.
I'll ask them to give you
additional points.
You're not thirsty, are you?
STOP
There's one more patient.
Let me see the wound.
Are you sure it was a scratch?
It looks like it was cut with a blade,
done quite recently.
I wish that were the case.
My wound isn't healing properly, either.
It doesn't seem that serious
from how it looks.
Let's test it.
-What is different when it's serious?
-The color.
The color turns dark red,
starting from the wound.
Stay here until the test is over.
Aren't you going to uncuff me?
This is enough space
for you to move, right?
Tell me if you're thirsty.
Ms. Yoon, come out for a moment.
See? I told you.
It's okay.
I'll go have my blood drawn. Wait here.
Nothing will happen.
I'm just going to make money and go.
It's okay.
When something like this happens again,
tell us beforehand.
I don't want to get startled.
I got it. So can you please open the bag?
MYUNGWON RICE CAKE SHOP
They say you should spoil
the people you dislike.
About the trainee…
The one who got bitten by Lee Jong-tae.
I heard he's in bad condition.
Even his family's request to visit
got rejected.
When they're bitten,
they get infected, no matter what.
The condition worsens,
so less time is spent being normal.
We never know when he'll feel thirsty
and attack someone,
so it's impossible for him
to meet any visitors.
What about the cure?
There's none at this point.
Once it gets worse,
they feel thirsty all the time.
They lose their minds
and attack anyone they see.
What we can do now
is to slow down the speed
of reaching that condition.
So it's true that no one
got out of here alive.
You're an extremely lucky case.
If nothing goes wrong, I'm sure
Mr. Lee Seung-young will be the same.
Are you bored? Want something to eat?
Where are you right now?
I have a family.
If I die for nothing, they'll keep
the reason for my death secret.
Sae-bom.
There's a way to make money,
and safety is guaranteed.
Hello? Seung-young!
The call cannot be connected.
Please leave a message…
Is this really okay?
What if everyone is dying in there?
I got a call from a journalist.
He said he'll pay me
if I tell him what happened here.
He put on a biohazard suit and escaped.
They thought he was bringing out chairs.
Where are the seriously ill patients?
Where are they?
We put them in a freezer storage
for food in the basement,
but they increased in number,
so we had to move them elsewhere.
So, where is this "elsewhere?"
A freezer truck.
Damn it.
DAMN JOURNALIST
DID YOU THINK ABOUT OUR OFFER?
You should pay me first.
If you do,
I'll send you the footage right away.
This call is being recorded,
so don't think about tricking me later.
Pay me half of it first, at least!
Send the money and call me.
This…
is a huge story.
SEYANG DREAM CAR WASH
They're in there. Why aren't you going?
Someone's supposed to come here.
Who? Did you ask for backup?
There he is.
What?
Hello, Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok.
What brings you to this shabby place?
I'd like to meet the dealer
with Corporal Jung only. Is that okay?
Sure, that's fine.
I can just wait here, then.
-Hey! You…
-I know.
Stay here.
I hate him, seriously…
By the way, why are you really here?
The remaining Next was kept
in the company's storage.
I want to find out
who spread it in the market.
It seems like this infectious disease
is making a mess overseas too.
Has Next been sold worldwide?
I told you I'm not good at making things,
but I'm good at stealing things, right?
It's a foreign drug.
I stole it while I was
in the Competitiveness Reinforcement Team.
You are an incredible man.
Total of three.
Damn it, turn the light off!
You brought the money, right?
Where is Lee Jong-tae?
That jerk Lee Jong-tae…
I bet you can't reach him.
-There are two of them.
-There are three of them.
The drug.
In the trunk…
Cuff them while I get them.
You assholes! You're all dead now!
What is this?
A Glock. You've never seen one?
I mean, why are you carrying that around?
What do you think you're doing?
Making sure it's dead.
You dare to kill a person
in front of a cop?
Do you think this is a human being?
All of you, hands up!
Hands up…
It's all done.
Oh, really? Gosh.
Hey! How many shots did you fire?
If this was a residential area,
you'd get disciplined again!
Did you do all this?
Since when has that thing
been in that condition?
I don't know.
I just went to his house
to get paid, and he was like that.
He bit his whole family and killed them.
He was banging his head
on the puddle of blood!
-Did it take Next?
-Tons of it.
He's been like that the whole time.
And you did that to someone ill?
What else would I have done?
He was the best guard dog ever.
I didn't even have to feed him.
All of you took that drug, right?
You'll become like that soon.
-Get up, you jerk.
-Hello?
Okay.
Mr. Jung, we have a problem at the dorm.
So?
Ms. Yoon Sae-bom is there.
Why did she go there again?
They're not humans.
What do you mean?
None of them are.
Quiet!
Open this.
Now!
No, don't open it!
Be honest.
You're seeing those people as monsters.
They told us to stop.
Mad Human Disease is spreading
in the apartment.
Those drugs cause
Mad Human Disease, right?
Bad rumors don't help with house prices.
We're stopping them all.
So you lock them up
and wait until they die?
I'm sure there's something
about that woman upstairs.
What's going on in that house right now?
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee