When a teenager disappears,
it's normal not to be
too worried at first.
A party could have gotten out of hand.
Or they might have run away in a huff
but end up coming home.
36 HOURS MISSING
But if no one has heard from them
after 48 hours...
with every second that passes,
it becomes less likely
that we will find them.
MISSING
SAMUEL GARCÍA DOMÍNGUEZ
Samuel has been missing
for nearly two days.
If you know anything that could help us
find out what happened to him,
now is the time to talk.
Tomorrow may be too late.
We were in the same class,
but we barely spoke.
How do we know
that you're not lying to us?
Why would I lie to you?
Good morning.
How did you sleep? Good?
Yeah?
Remember, I need you to cover
for me today and clean the two houses.
I have to take your grandpa
to the doctor.
Okay, Mom.
-Hi.
The chauffeur
is still not used to the schedule.
He is so...
Carla.
What are you doing? What's wrong?
Whatever it is
that you know about Marina's death,
you have to tell the police.
No need to go in person.
Just an anonymous call.
-Do you really think I was involved with--
-I don't think. You told me.
I thought it was only a game.
I thought it was what you wanted to hear.
That it'd turn you on.
Why would that turn me on?
I don't know. You tell me.
Because it worked, didn't it?
So you're a pervert.
I never thought you were so interesting.
I'm not another idiot
that you can make a fool of.
Are you two together?
Not now, Polo.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why? I'm doing it for you!
Samuel suspects both of us.
I'm with him to keep him under control.
Sure. Like with Christian, right?
You're pretty good at that,
grabbing guys by the dick as if it were
a joystick to control them.
Do you think I like it?
You think it makes me happy?
Well, just so you know, since the day
that you told me you killed someone,
I haven't been happy at all.
When all of this is over,
you and I will get back together, right?
We'll be Carla and Polo again.
You are joking, right?
Come on, close the door, please.
I know it's Friday,
but let's not get carried away, please.
Now that's what I call
getting carried away.
There you have it. Taste it.
-I don't know what you find so funny.
-Me.
Don't you like it?
The video's pretty awesome.
I think you look ridiculous.
Weren't you all saying I needed
to stop mourning and start living?
Well, that's what I'm doing.
Since you changed lab partners,
you've been going downhill, Polo.
Well, brother,
it's clear chemistry is not your thing.
I'm better at the practical side
than the theoretical.
When Dad kicks you out for failing,
will you be joking then, too?
You're so good...
So good at being mean.
If you'd actually worked on your part...
Where's your head?
In Soto del Real prison.
That's where my head is.
My father had a stroke.
-Think it's easy for me to study?
-Sorry.
-That's not the only thing.
-What else?
Where do people keep their secrets?
In their texts, pics, and videos.
You want to steal her phone?
If you get caught, you'll be expelled.
No way.
Doing it at school would be a mess.
But isn't there a party
in that fancy club tomorrow night?
That's it. Lots of people around,
not much light, tons of alcohol...
My phone got stolen three times like that.
And I've done it twice.
-Samuel's not like you.
-Come on,
he must've stolen something once.
-Not even at the supermarket?
-I don't even cheat when weighing fruit.
I don't know if that makes you cute
or a textbook loser.
But you're not a thief.
Nor a detective or a spy.
What should I do?
Do nothing after what she said?
No, you're right. It's all in her phone.
And with a little bit of luck...
we’ll fuck the little marchioness over.
Hey.
-Would you help me out in chemistry?
-Have you seen my grades?
Just jerking off as friends, right?
What're you staring at?
Now we don't seem like friends.
Why don't you reply to my texts?
Why can't you look me in the eye?
Because you remind me
that I cheated on Omar. That's why.
Now he keeps calling,
and I don't know what to do.
I feel like shit.
I just need help...
with the exam.
Ask Guzmán for help.
Polo.
-I'm fine!
-Like hell you are.
Move.
Sorry.
-Are you still taking the pills?
-They aren't working like they used to.
I don't understand why you're like this.
Is it because of Carla?
Just fucking ignore everything.
Forget her and move on.
It's not that easy, Guzmán!
It's like your thoughts drag you down,
take on a life of their own.
-They destroy you!
-Are you a shrink now?
No.
But I've been a patient
since I had my first anxiety attack at 12.
But now it's much worse.
Fuck, you're making me feel like shit.
What?
The past few months have been so bad
that I thought I was the only one
with problems. But no.
I haven't been there when you needed me.
You're nobody without me, Polito.
Hey, if you want, I can help you study.
Come to my house this afternoon,
and we'll study together,
like in the old days.
I've been calling you.
I know. Sorry, I've been really busy.
With the move and all that.
How is your mother?
She's fine. It's a divorce,
not the end of the world.
What's this?
Just a gift.
You said your back hurts
from spending so much time here.
Thank you.
Don't get too excited.
It cost eight euros.
It's not that.
Seeing as you weren't answering
my calls yesterday,
I thought maybe you'd met someone
and you were ignoring me.
I hooked up with Polo.
But it really meant nothing.
So why are you telling me about it?
I don't know. I don't know, Omar.
Did I cheat on you?
I don't even know if we're together.
Or when I'll see you
without being surrounded
by melons and zucchini.
What future do we have?
-No future.
-Omar...
Omar!
Come help me with your father!
I'm being serious, Ander.
This is my life, and it sucks.
I know that.
I don't want to drag you down. Seriously.
Go. Hook up with whoever you want.
Kiss whoever you want.
Fuck whoever you want. I'm being serious.
I only want you to be happy.
I only want to be with you.
I want that, too.
But I also want to leave
this shitty shop, and that won't happen.
The number of 4p electrons in a Ge atom...
is four.
Well done, Polito. Relax,
you've got everything under control.
What's going on?
-I didn't know you were coming, either.
-No worries.
Fuck, here we go.
Are we friends or what?
I'm always the last to know about things.
You'll never forgive me
for not coming out to you first, will you?
No. Spill it. What's going on here?
The other day when we were here,
we kind of hooked up.
-But it didn't mean anything.
-You hooked up?
You two hooked up?
When I was there, drunk? In my bed?
We got caught up in the moment.
It was nothing. We're just friends.
-Just friends jerking off.
-Just friends jerking off?
I was worried,
and you were laughing in my face?
Can't you find other guys to fuck?
Guzmán.
Don't get involved, Samu.
It's too dangerous.
You're exaggerating. It's just a phone.
It was just a watch,
and look where that got me.
And that's why.
Don't you want me to get you out of here?
I don't want you to end up
in the hospital like Christian...
or in the graveyard like Marina.
Don't get obsessed with that girl,
don't play her game, understood?
You don't have to get me out of here.
If I don't do it, who will?
Because no one else is doing anything.
We're all going in red.
I'm having this killer dress made.
It's in the reserved area upstairs.
So VIP.
Valerio always manages to get us in.
You can't miss it!
-I won't.
-May I come in?
It's better this way. At our last party,
we trashed your house.
Don't worry, it was no big deal.
Go ahead, and I'll catch up with you.
I need to...
-Don't be too long.
-I won't.
What? Close the door.
Where did you invite them?
The Fritz-Patrick house?
No, the Torres house.
The day when I covered for you...
again.
I know what I'm doing.
I cleaned, left it spotless,
and nobody found out.
No. I found out about it.
-Okay.
-I almost had a heart attack!
If I'd known,
I wouldn't have taken this job.
Mom,
this is what you've always wanted for me.
You've drilled it into my head
since I was a girl.
You even named me Cayetana.
That's why you took the job.
And I'm making the most of it.
Who? Who's making the most of it? You?
Or the girl you made up?
This is what I am...
Yes!
Do you think they would accept me
into their circle,
that I could be their friend,
if they knew I was the cleaner's daughter?
My job is what puts a roof
over our heads and food on the table.
I'm not going to lose it because of you.
If you mess up again--
What? You'll take away
my nonexistent allowance?
Remember that I work, too.
I'm going to stop hanging my head
when I see you in the hall,
and I will greet you as what you are,
my daughter, in front of everyone.
Like I should have done from day one...
instead of asking the teachers
not to mention your scholarship
because you were ashamed.
Is that clear?
Crystal clear, Mom.
Careful, girl!
Snobby asshole.
Hi.
I didn't know about your father.
I'm sorry I hadn't heard.
And I'm sorry for not talking to you.
Don't worry.
I know you had other things on your mind.
Do you have something to say to me
about me having fun?
There's no need for me
to tell you what I think.
It's the same thing
you thought a few months ago.
It doesn't matter. I only wanted to say...
that I would’ve liked
to have been there for you...
and have done something.
What would you have done?
I don't know. Talked.
Given you a hug, at least.
A hug from you...
Just what my father was missing
to finish him off.
Samu!
-Nadia.
-Don't come near me.
Samuel!
Samu!
Private lessons?
Yes. Math.
Well, and a little chemistry, too.
Physics. Listen, basically everything.
A mix of all the subjects.
Adriana.
You could also try studying a little.
Thanks for your notes. I owe you one.
You were being serious.
I don't have time.
-I'll pay you €20 an hour.
-No, thanks.
€30.
Money can't buy everything, Valerio.
€100.
This must be a joke...
This is your tutor?
You do know you're wasting
your time with him, right?
It was difficult to convince her,
but you know me.
When I set my mind on something, I get it.
Really?
Is that why you hired me?
To get on your sister's nerves?
Well, among other things.
Why? Does it bother you?
I'm starting to get used to the lengths
that rich people go to to have fun.
What about you? How do you have fun?
Everything that I like
is forbidden by your religion.
I don't know. Normal stuff.
I'm a Muslim, not an extraterrestrial.
What about sex?
Guys? Or girls?
What makes you think I would tell you
anything about my sex life?
I'm taking an interest.
And I get the impression
that that doesn't happen to you much.
I'm not a prude.
I simply want to do it with someone
I'm in love with.
Wow... You haven't been in love?
-No.
-Sure.
Hey, is lying a sin in your religion?
You're lying to me.
What's going on with Guzmán?
He's a good friend.
And your sister's boyfriend.
I don't know for how much longer.
Let’s say the chemistry...
is not working.
That's the closest you've come to talking
about the course all afternoon.
Open the book.
That restaurant may have been really good,
but the service was horrible.
I had to wait for an hour to get my food.
The orders were wrong.
The food came cold.
It was horrible.
Cayetana,
I need you to wash all these, please.
-All of them?
-Yes, all of them.
The waiter was so rude. It was horrible.
But I must say,
at least the food was delicious.
I have to go. I'm running late.
Okay, that's great. Bye.
Okay, this is the one.
Hold on a second, Cayetana.
I forgot the panties.
Thanks.
May I speak now? Okay.
I don't like having to tell you off.
I don't like it.
I spent the whole summer with you
to comfort you and support you,
to move on from all this shit...
We both decided to do all this,
but you're not helping.
I want to be your girlfriend,
not your fucking mom.
I know, Lu.
And I'm eternally grateful.
But as my girlfriend,
can't you understand
that I had a shitty summer
and I feel like having fun?
And I was with you
all that shitty summer.
You're always telling me to have fun.
That's what I'm fucking doing!
Have fun, then, asshole!
Have as much as you want,
take drugs, get drunk...
-You want to end up a junkie...
-Class is over.
-Excuse me.
-...like your biological parents.
That's sinking very low, even for you.
What's wrong?
Surprise.
Fun is here!
Your...
fun.
Be alert.
Our work here today
is not only to look for Samuel,
but also to watch them.
Those behind a disappearance are often
the first to assist in the search party.
That way, they look innocent
and can control what we find.
Samuel!
-Nadia.
-Samuel!
What are you doing here?
-Why shouldn't I be here?
-Samuel!
I wanted him gone
but not like this.
Samuel!
What are they doing?
The only way for my brother
to get chemistry through his thick head
is through his nose.
Are you worried about Guzmán?
No, I couldn't care less.
He can do whatever he wants.
Why don't you talk to him?
Since you're so worried about him,
he may listen to you.
Rebeka will be right down.
Sure you don't want something to nibble?
Yes.
Come closer, for God's sake.
I don't bite.
You never told me
how polite your friend is.
You know, he saw me
with wads of cash the other day,
and he didn't even mention it.
I didn't see anything.
-You didn't see the money?
-No.
What a shame. It was glorious.
Winning the lottery must be incredible.
The lottery, he says...
All you need for that is luck.
And luck played no part in all this.
It took a lot of work
to get everything that I've got.
What?
I wasn't going to tell you
my life story right off the bat.
But now that we can trust each other...
Listen, I'll tell you something.
When my husband died, I opened
a haberdashery in my neighborhood.
I never studied, and I had no experience.
Nothing. And I did damn great.
Have some.
But...
then a shopping center opened next door.
And the haberdashery went to shit.
So I found another in-demand product.
With no big company
that could come and step on my turf.
It sounds more dangerous
than selling panties and bras.
Isn't it dangerous riding a bike around
with cars passing at high speeds?
How much do you get paid
for risking your life
so that pizza’s hot when it arrives?
They pay shit.
Take a seat.
Mom pays her people very well.
You could get your brother's bail money
together faster working for her.
A lot faster.
One family member in prison is enough.
Thanks.
Why me, anyway?
Do I look like a dealer?
Precisely because you don't.
You won't attract attention
coming and going on your bike.
Anyway, you wouldn't be a dealer,
only a deliveryman.
I haven't been here long,
and I need people I can trust.
Think about it.
Bingo! Look who's coming.
Hi!
Well, I'm ready. We can leave now.
Could I come to that party, too?
Wow, wait a minute, honey.
Let's see...
It's a red party.
And from what I've seen,
you only have clothes in two colors:
boring and mega boring.
Let her borrow something of yours.
I'm sure something in your huge wardrobe
would look good on her.
Let the party begin!
I see.
-Cayetana! We're over here.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-How are you?
I love it!
-Thanks!
-Haute couture, right?
-A Ralph Lauren.
-I know. Gorgeous.
Hi.
Are you all right?
Better than ever, kid.
-I can see that.
-How about a selfie?
Omar,
before you close up, clean the camera,
and make sure
all the receipts are there.
-Yesterday, you forgot a few.
-Sure.
Inspector!
I found something.
-Next to that tree.
-Everyone, stay there.
Fucking hell!
We won't attract attention at all.
Want to play again?
I came to apologize.
I kinda lost it the other day.
-Champagne?
-You can't impress me with your money.
My money’s the least impressive thing
about me, babe.
-I know. I've seen your Instagram.
-Did you like it?
-I did. Except I'm nowhere to be seen.
-That's easy to fix.
Hi. I didn't know you guys were coming.
Shit! Don't you look cute!
You're not still thinking about...
You go do your thing, huh?
Have fun with your new friends.
I'll do one.
-What are you saying?
-I want to do one. How much is it?
Nothing. This moment is priceless.
Nadia, what are you doing?
I'm going to do what you're doing.
Drink what you're drinking all night long.
Maybe I'll understand you
by the end of it.
Or maybe you will realize how scary it is
to see someone you care about doing this.
Is that why you came?
-To lecture me?
-No.
But don't worry.
If this is so harmless,
you won't mind me doing it, too.
Right?
What are you doing?
What the fuck are you looking at?
So we had to take the metro. The smells!
The colors! There was no--
Relax, don't make such a big deal.
This is not a white party.
I'm leaving.
Of course.
Sure. You wouldn't be worried
about spilling anything on you,
wearing last year's dress.
I have better things to do
than spend the day thinking
about what clothes I'm going to wear.
Instead, you think about
the clothes you're going to take off
the next lowlife you want to fuck, right?
I need another drink to put up with this.
Whose round is it?
Mine! I'll go.
I'll be right back.
Valerio... Let's see if this works.
Sometimes my card works,
sometimes it doesn't.
I've worn it out from too much shopping.
What are you doing?
A bottle for my friend!
For...
Thanks!
It's worn out from too much shopping.
-You pay with a card?
-Yeah.
Vintage, huh?
Okay, yes, you're right.
When I activated mobile payments,
I ended up killing the battery
at the Prada boutique in Goya.
And then I had to hail a cab
in the street.
That really was vintage.
So? How do you like Las Encinas?
It's a dream come true.
Thanks.
Please, man, I don't want to go up there.
All I'm asking you is
to tell my friends I'm here.
Let him in. He's with me.
Come.
What are you doing here?
What about the store?
I've had enough of the store.
I've had enough of the store
and my father.
I've had enough of cushions, melons.
-I've had enough of all of it.
-Okay.
No more cushions.
Do you want the receipt to return it?
No, you idiot.
What I'm trying to say is that
our relationship isn't complicated.
What’s difficult
is spending all day in the damn store,
pretending to be someone else.
Closing up, coming here to find you,
and kissing you in front of
an entire club full of people
is the easiest thing
I have done in my life.
Do you have anything to tell me, Nadia?
Don't be afraid.
Whatever you say is confidential.
Nobody will find out.
Not long before Samuel went missing...
someone threatened him
in the hallway at school.
Who?
You couldn't pry her away
from her phone with a stick.
Not even a selfie stick.
What are you doing? What's wrong with you?
Is it Jägermeister? It stains!
-This is a Ralph Lauren!
-Relax, girl.
Aren't you filthy rich? Buy a new one.
It's calimocho.
I wouldn't be surprised if you snuck
the cheap wine in in your bra.
Hey, I said I was sorry.
-You should be sorry for existing.
-Oh, should I? There you go.
What are you doing?
-Please, stop.
-You fucking bitch!
What are you doing with Carla's phone?
Don't tell me you're
a thief as well, waiter.
It must be in your blood.
I didn't have time to break
your brother's legs,
-but as for you--
-Guzmán, leave him!
He got mixed up.
-We have similar phone covers.
-What are you talking about?
Let him go.
Here. All yours.
You know how to unlock it, right?
You're giving it to me
'cause you've deleted
anything that might implicate you.
If something could implicate me,
I would delete it.
I'm not an idiot.
But there's nothing. I had nothing to do
with what happened.
I'm not a fucking idiot either!
Look me in the eye.
It wasn't a game. You meant it.
You were involved with Marina's death.
Get out!
Yes, I did have something to do with it.
You know why?
Because I wasn't there.
She was my best friend
since primary school.
I dumped her and went off with Lu,
just because she was more fun.
Less intense.
I wasn't there, not for the HIV thing,
nor when she hooked up
with your brother and stole the watch.
I wasn't a best friend to her.
And now she's dead.
Where are you? Do you have it?
The main thing is not to overdo it.
Cheers!
I'll have one of those. Whatever it is.
-Shit.
-Okay.
Again?
Excuse me a second.
-How much did you drink?
-As much as you.
Don't you have someone else to bother?
Everyone in here is on something!
Guzmán, please!
You're the one that I'm worried about.
The worst thing isn't
that you're taking drugs.
It's your reason for doing it.
It's not about having a good time.
You want to fill the void Marina left.
-Please, Nadia, don't bring that up now.
-Listen to me.
But no chemical substance will do that.
And I'm scared...
that you'll keep on trying
until you end up joining her
before your time.
And it's a bit too early
to tell which of our gods is right
about the afterlife.
Don't you think?
Guzmán!
Happy now?
And a little smashed.
Or at least I think so.
-This is what smashed means, right?
-Yeah.
-I can tell you are.
-Thanks.
So...
Why don't we have a nice glass of water
loaded with ice?
Thanks.
-Shall we?
-Let’s.
It came out! Sorry.
It's just that I really love this dress.
Though I think it's time to hang it up.
It's very early 2018,
and velvet isn't...
Are you all right?
-What?
-Are you all right?
I don't want to ruin the party for you.
That's what my best friend
should be here for,
but she left without saying goodbye.
I'm here, Lucrecia.
For anything you need.
You can trust me and--
Call me Lu.
Is it true?
The thing about the jacket and...
the blood?
What relationship did you have
with Samuel?
None.
-We hardly spoke.
-Are you sure?
Because one of your classmates told us
that you said something to him
in the hall a few weeks ago.
Do you remember what you said?
What did you say to him, Lucrecia?
I said, "You're a dead man, you bastard."
It's my fault.
I left the door wide open
for Miss Palestine.
And she has thrown herself
into reconquering him.
Lu, you don’t have to look after Guzmán
his entire life.
Anyway, who's looking after you?
So, where are you going?
Our car has arrived, miss.
What?
I almost went down,
but I puked a very, very, very little bit,
-and look at me! Now I'm good as new.
-Sure.
I bet Luis Miguel makes a song about that.
No.
Don't you want to come with us?
Your house is not too far.
No, I already ordered a Cabify.
I think it's this one.
I'll take it and leave.
-Bye, honey.
-See you.
NEXT BUS: 40 MINUTES
It's really weird,
being here, with you.
-What are we doing?
-You think it's weird?
I do.
What about now?
I still do.
A little less.
What about now?
Do you want me to take you home?
Don't you get tired of always playing
the knight in shining armor?
What's wrong with that?
Didn't they used to kill Muslims
during the Crusades?
I forgot that I'm dealing
with an infidel Muslim and not a lady.
It's true.
I'm not much of a lady.
I think...
I've had too much to drink.
No, just enough to do
what you've been wanting to do.
And I have, too.
-Good night, Guzmán.
-Nadia...
What's going on with you?
The pills, the alcohol...
I don't know.
Come on, I'll take you home.
Do you know I've been here over an hour?
Nobody even noticed.
Shit.
How can you close the store like this?
Without emptying the register.
-Anyone could have come and taken it.
-But they didn't.
You say that you're going
to start being responsible,
but you never change. Never.
Your family needs you. And what do you do?
Look at your sister.
You bring her home like this,
wearing makeup, smelling of alcohol.
-Dad, Omar is not to blame.
-Stay out of it.
I'm to blame for everything, right?
There are rules in this house.
What will you do if I don't follow them?
Will you punish me?
My whole life is a punishment. Every day.
Sentenced to run this shitty shop!
Don't talk like that in front of your mom!
Or what? Are you gonna hit me?
Haven't you always wanted me
to be the man of the house,
the fucking alpha male?
Well, there you have it.
From now on, you and I both
make the rules, got it?
You are not the man of the house.
Get out!
Yusef, please, don't do this.
Go and don't come back.
Go!
What’s wrong, Polo?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I'm still your friend.
No jerking off, just friends.
You can tell me anything.
I won't judge you.
I can't.
Why not?
You would never forgive me.
Polo, whatever it is,
it won't change anything between us.
I killed her.
What?
I killed Marina.
Ander.
Please, don't go, Ander.
Don't go, please.
4 MESSAGES FROM POLO
Carla...
Carla, I couldn't help it anymore.
I couldn't keep this secret anymore.
I confessed it all,
everything that happened.
I'm sorry.
Subtitle translation by Aline Saba