Nadia? You were screaming.
Yeah, I was having a nightmare.
Come on, time to get up.
I have to open up the store,
get your father ready...
I can't manage everything alone.
Coming, Mom.
Come on.
It's getting late.
But the alarm hasn't even gone off yet.
-He takes forever.
-What?
Ander, in the shower.
Once he goes in there, say goodbye.
We had to get a bigger boiler
because we'd end up with no hot water.
-Sit down. Want some coffee?
-No, don't worry.
Don't be shy. Come on, kid.
If you're going to stay here,
I want you to...
I don't know,
to feel comfortable around me. Okay?
-I don't know how to thank you.
-You don't need to.
After I outed you to your father
in the school hallway,
it's the least I can do.
Relax. Before...
I became the pink sheep, I was already
the black sheep of the family.
I wasn't kicked out because of that.
Want me to drop you off at school?
It's on the way.
Now that you're back,
you won't want to be late.
-I'm off. I have to meet someone.
-Without having breakfast? And so early?
You...
You're a selfish asshole.
How could you tell me that?
What do you want me to do?
Keep this shit to myself?
Polo, I can't.
-Don't scare me, Ander.
-I can't act like nothing happened.
I can't even look Guzmán in the eye.
You've destroyed his life.
-And you're going to have to tell him.
-No.
-You have 24 hours.
-Either you tell him or I will.
-Ander...
Let's talk about Polo.
Polo? Why?
59 HOURS MISSING
We are investigating
whether anything that's happened here
since the start of the school year
could be related
to Samuel's disappearance.
Did Polo tell you
what happened at the pool?
Oh, boy, I'm gonna ask
the cleaning lady for a mop.
-You're drooling all over.
-What are you talking about?
That suddenly the marchioness
has gone from evil Barbie
-to saint in your eyes.
-All I said was
that Polo's messages
could be about anything.
Sure. I'm just saying that before you were
trying to find out if she was guilty,
and now all you want is
to know she's innocent.
But, hey, that's your business.
-I was waving at you on the stairs.
-And I waved back.
What did you expect? A curtsy?
Are you going to tell me what's going on?
If you don't mind,
-class is about to start.
-I do mind. You've ignored me all week.
We kissed the other night.
You kissed me.
I'd been drinking.
I don't remember what I was doing.
You're gonna act like you don't remember?
Great, but stop playing with me.
Good day.
Look. Your girlfriend just arrived.
Hey.
How's Omar?
Fine. He's at my place,
but we haven't kidnapped him.
You can go see him if you want.
How are you?
Tired, but good otherwise.
Well, pretty fed up.
I can imagine.
I saw you the other day on your bike.
I said hi,
but you had headphones--
I'm rarely seen without my bike.
-I need cash to get Nano--
-Listen.
Maybe it's not the right time to say this,
but I believe you.
I think your brother's innocent.
Thanks, man.
Yeah.
Since we've made up,
I thought we could go have
a romantic dinner, just the two of us.
I said I have plans with Ander tomorrow.
I'm not going to just bail on him.
-Tell him to join us.
-Come on...
And tell him to bring
his Muslim boyfriend, too,
and we can have a double date.
-Well, if it doesn't bother you.
-Of course it doesn't.
He gave me an ultimatum.
What do you mean, an ultimatum?
I don't know what to do.
I've been self-medicating.
That's why I can't sleep.
And it just came out.
-Fuck, what am I going to do now?
-It's okay.
Come. Come here. Calm down.
It's out of our hands, Polo.
Soon, everyone will know.
It's best if we finish this.
Go to the police station
and tell them what you did.
It's important
they hear your version of the event.
that it was an accident.
Nothing will happen to you.
You're a minor.
What do I tell them?
That you thought Marina
had stolen the watch from me.
You had an argument.
You got very angry,
and you killed her by mistake.
Tell them where the trophy is.
And it will all be over.
What about you?
I didn't do anything, my love.
You don't have to implicate me.
That way, you repay me
for what I did for you.
And we put an end to this agony
once and for all.
What do you say?
Will you do it?
-Hi.
-Is everything here?
-Yes, everything you asked for.
Omar, when are you coming back?
Dad needs your help and so do we.
Why not try putting yourself
in his shoes?
Why doesn't anyone try putting themselves
in mine? Fuck. Now I feel free.
You might be free,
but you've condemned me.
I have to take care of the store
on my own. I don't have time for anything.
That's why you want me to come back?
To make life easier for you? Awesome.
That's right. For me, for Dad, for Mom.
They have been moping around
since you left.
And it's not about making my life easier.
It's about having a life.
Period.
Well, the only way to do that
is to leave that house.
You know what?
Dad might have survived a stroke,
but I don't know if he would survive
another of his children leaving.
I have to go back.
He came up on the right like a madman.
I didn't see him coming.
Can't people get off their asses
to get their own churros with chocolate?
Fuck!
Fuck you! Do you get sick pay?
Which planet are you on?
Tell them where to fucking stick it.
Please, Samuel.
Poor people can't tell anyone
where to stick it.
Don't talk to me like you do
to those snobs in class.
No, I'm talking to you
like someone who doesn't need money.
Okay.
There are things we can't have,
not even with all the money in the world.
Tell me one thing you can't have.
My dad never told the construction company
he worked for where to shove it.
When he had the accident,
they blamed him for being careless,
and all we got were a few pats
on the back and a thank-you.
Here. In case you come to your senses.
My mother's offer is still on the table.
I've started working at the gas station
under the Choto bridge.
It's for a temp agency.
It's killing me,
but it's a good way to make money
and save up, so it's good.
Forget about the fucking bail.
Forget about me.
If I have to be locked up for two years
until the damn trial, so be it.
What difference does it make
whether it's 20 years or 22?
-Hi.
-I'm glad you called me. I got you a job.
-Your table will be ready in five minutes.
-Thank you.
Polo, answer me.
Did you go to the police?
Don't ignore me.
Tell him already. Tell Guzmán. Now.
What are you waiting for?
Don't put it off, honey.
NOW.
Darling...
Polo.
What?
We're asking
if you want the apartment in Madrid.
I don't care.
I'm going to Guzmán's house.
-Now?
-Very good, darling.
Go and support your friend.
He's going through a difficult time
and surely needs you.
Do you want anything?
Something to eat or drink?
No.
-Well, just tell me.
-You and I are like chalk and cheese.
Samuel, don't look at me like that.
Like what?
You know. This is not going anywhere,
and if we carry on like this,
we will end up suffering.
I totally agree.
Why did you come here to tell me this?
You could have just sent me a message.
-Want some macaroni?
-Excuse me?
Yesterday's leftovers,
but I can heat them up in a minute.
We can also do things with clothes on.
You and I are definitely going nowhere
with our clothes on.
You're right, then.
We should call it quits.
Do you remember
how we used to sleep over at your house?
Sure.
You came all this way to ask me that?
We played video games till dawn.
Eating popcorn...
And we wouldn't stop
till our hands got sore.
Can we do that tonight?
Sure.
Why?
Why not?
Those are the best memories I have.
What a sad life, Polo! Seriously.
You're my best friend, Guzmán.
More than that.
Do you know you're the reason
I found out I like guys, too?
Well, I didn't know that.
Relax, I got over it quickly.
Polo,
I love you very much,
but not that way. You know what I mean.
I also love you very much.
And I'm so sorry...
I'm so sorry
for any harm I have done to you.
What harm?
What nonsense are you talking about?
What's wrong with you?
Shit, man.
Which game should we start with?
What's up with you? Geez.
Polo, answer your fucking phone!
Did you speak to Guzmán or not?
I swear I'm not bluffing.
You are running out of time!
Polo always seemed like a great guy to me.
You don't have something
to tell me about him?
Something about what happened?
What happened?
After Marina's death,
security cameras were installed
throughout the facilities.
Are you sure
you don't have anything to tell me?
What...
Hey.
Shit...
Hey!
Polo!
Polo! Help!
Help!
Polo!
Okay...
Ander!
God, call an ambulance! Call anyone.
Ander?
Ander, please, come to the school,
I don't know...
He's not breathing.
I think he's not breathing.
Polo!
Please! Polo!
Very good!
Okay...
Very good. Get it out.
Get it out.
Get it out. Ander!
-Thank God! Call an ambulance!
-No! We aren't calling anyone!
-Shut up!
-What?
How are you?
Are you okay?
-Come on.
-It's okay, don't worry.
That's my thing.
Falling asleep at school is my specialty.
What?
Was it a long night?
Order pick-ups until 3:00 a.m.
Damn exciting stuff.
We can do the lesson some other time
if you want. I don't mind.
I'm sure,
but I don't have any more free time.
So you're not going out tonight?
I'm afraid I won't be going out
for a long time.
Really?
Not even if I tell you
that Guzmán might be at the club tonight?
Why are you so eager for me and Guzmán
to get together?
Call me Cupid.
I believe in love.
I've seen how you look at each other.
Do you know how rare it is
to desire someone with all your heart,
and for them to reciprocate?
That's luck,
and you can't be that lucky every day.
Valerio.
Is there anything you'd like to tell me?
Come tonight.
Even death row inmates can enjoy...
their very last night of happiness.
That party will be awesome. For real.
Polo, where are you?
What are we gonna say?
The last thing Polo needs is his mothers
finding out what he did.
He's all right.
We pumped his stomach,
and he'll be out in no time.
-Good...
-I'm calling his parents.
Don't worry...
I've already told them. He's my brother.
They're on their way now.
I hope he's learned his lesson.
Because I don't know how...
He's into those online videos
where people do stupid things.
This week's challenge was
to take as many pills as possible.
We had swimming first thing
in the morning. He couldn't swim,
so I had to pull him out.
Thank God I'm a good swimmer.
He could have died.
We need to talk to him.
I'm a mess. God.
Polo! How are you?
Hey, how are you feeling?
I couldn't do it.
You can tell him if you want.
Do you guys know anything about Polo?
He's not here today.
He was, but he got really sick.
He threw up in the locker room.
He made a real mess, right?
Poor him. Anyway...
Yes, we took him home.
He couldn't manage by himself.
What's going on?
What is this about?
Because Polo and Samuel,
they weren't even friends.
Lots of other people could have reasons
to get rid of him.
I thought you didn't know Samuel.
I don't, but...
people said that he changed
after what happened to Marina.
That he became violent...
and he was hanging out
with the wrong crowd.
Yes?
Hi. Sandra sent me.
Good. Thank you very much, kid.
What's up, dude? Was it easy or not?
Yes, it was almost too easy.
I already told you.
My mother wouldn't put you in danger.
That's how it will always be.
-I don't know if I want to keep doing it.
-Well, think about it.
She trusts you.
Could we start by paying me
for this trip? I'll decide later.
It's just that she's away till tomorrow.
But don't worry.
You'll get the dough right away.
Once you have it, you'll come around.
-Please come in, miss.
-Thank you. I'm one of Polo's friends.
-May I?
-Sure.
-This way, please.
-Yes, sorry.
My cook made chicken broth.
She always says it's the best thing
when you have a stomachache.
Thank you, but you didn't have to come.
Listen...
I'll sit down.
I know we don't really know each other,
and I don't want you to tell me
why you did what you did.
You must have your reasons.
But I want you to know
that if you need anything, I'm here.
And I wouldn't like anything to happen
to you because...
it was hard to pull you out of the pool!
Like... Yes.
Polo, call me.
Thank you very much.
It's okay...
For coming to see me.
-And for lying in the hospital.
-Yeah.
And for jumping into the pool...
and for the resuscitation thing. All that.
You look so cute when you smile.
You look very cute. I'm being serious.
Your eyes screw up and...
Are you embarrassed now? Don't be!
Well, I just came to bring you this, so...
I'll give it to your cook
so she can heat it up.
It'll taste better when it's hot.
I'm leaving. See you in class, okay?
Get some rest.
Well, let's save ourselves some work,
shall we? I ask what's up with Polo,
you say nothing, I insist,
I ask you what's up,
you call me annoying,
I tell you to fuck off,
and we'll have an awesome dinner.
-Hilarious.
-Thank you.
What's hilarious?
He quit tennis.
I know. Hi.
What a pity, Ander.
You don't look well.
Go back to playing sports.
Do yourself a favor.
I'm just worried about you.
-Hi.
-Hi. Did you order yet?
No. I'm actually not hungry at all.
Neither am I.
For fuck's sake, dude,
I told you three times.
Should I tell you in another language?
You're being so annoying.
-Are you letting us in now or what?
-Hey, Luciano, how are you doing?
They're with me. Let them in, okay?
Thanks for nothing, Luciano.
Stop arguing.
-Rum and Coke, right?
-Please!
-You?
-Just Coke. Thanks.
Right away!
So let's see what's going on here.
Bitches are out and about.
We almost didn't get in
because of that stunt you pulled.
I was helping Samuel
get his brother out of prison.
Or rather, you wanted to get rid of Carla
using those crazy ideas
that he has in his head.
And all because you like him, right?
Don't go all advice columnist on me.
You have your issue, too.
-My issue?
-Why did you come here, Nadia?
For that oh-so-cool blond snob.
That's if he decides to show up,
because Nadia won't do anything about it.
The girl that gets 9.5 out of ten
and goes to complain.
But when she likes a guy,
she just sits in the corner waiting
or she leaves everything
to the hands of fate.
Listen up, babe.
Fate is a son of a bitch.
He has a girlfriend.
Sure.
That is his problem and your excuse.
And you?
When are you going to go for it?
Never. Samu likes marchionesses,
and I'm a jester in comparison.
So basically, that's your excuse.
Samu, are you coming to the club?
I want to talk.
Or I'll come by your house,
whatever you want.
Ander, that's enough.
Fuck.
Can I tell you something?
I love your eyebrows.
That's cute.
When I was little,
I got teased for having bushy ones.
I got teased, too.
I'm thinking about changing my look a bit.
Maybe shape them a little...
Get a piercing. Something like that.
I think I would like that.
Not so sure about your sister.
All the more reason to do it.
Cheers to that.
Let me tell you something.
That shirt was a great choice.
-Wow, thanks.
-You're welcome.
-At least somebody noticed it.
-I didn't want to say anything.
Why?
-Because that shirt... It's not you.
-Maybe the shirt is me,
and the dark hoodies I wore
were someone else.
-Come on, Ander...
-Stay out of it. That's his partner.
All right.
Let's talk about each other's partners.
That is the first thing
you've said to me all night.
I've been trying to have dinner
just the two of us all week,
and all I've managed to get is this.
No offense.
What shall we do with these two?
Could they be any more boring?
You speak Arabic?
Two years in Abu Dhabi, honey. Languages.
I don't get it.
I can't believe you're Nadia's brother.
I'm at the club.
-You're actually charming.
-I sometimes think the same thing.
I just saw your...
It's so good reheated.
Who needs a chef when you have
the cheapest microwave available.
You won't see me as a princess
when sauce is dribbling down my chin.
No. I'll do something a lot worse.
I'll ask you what this is.
What are we doing?
It's really noisy outside, isn't it?
Nonstop, all around us.
It's so quiet in here.
I don't know what we're doing.
I'm quite lonely,
and I think you are, too.
So we could be lonely together.
You have some tomato sauce on...
-Where?
-Wait.
Here.
Fucking hell...
Thanks.
-Give it to me.
-Don't, Lu.
The dinner was my idea. It's on me.
-They're my friends. I want to pay.
-You want to, but you can't!
Can we talk about this at home?
Don't make a scene.
-No, I'm going out for a drink.
-What?
-I want to go out, not be cooped up.
-Being with me is like being cooped up?
I didn't say that.
I said I want to go out for a drink.
It's what you say all the fucking time.
You know what? Do what you want.
You will anyway, whether I like it or not.
Maybe we should get going...
I'm going somewhere.
I have something to do.
What do you have to do this late?
So you don't tell your boyfriend
anything either? Fucking great.
-Absolutely nothing.
-Ander?
Just like you.
-Guzmán?
-Ander!
Ander!
If you bottle everything up inside,
it'll eat away at you!
You really want me
to tell you what's wrong?
I want things to go back
to how they were before.
You, me, and Polo.
That's all I'm asking for.
Are you coming?
I thought you would pretend
you don't know me or something.
I'm not drunk.
No?
No.
What do you want to do?
-We can't go to my house.
-And yours, no chance.
There's a place,
but...
You have condoms in all the drawers.
I'm kidding. They are in the nightstand.
Maybe it wasn't a good idea
to bring you here.
-I'm sorry.
-It was what it was meant to be.
Relax. I'm fine.
I'm a little bit scared.
Me, too.
I remember how much you liked the pool.
Let's do it!
I'm really angry.
I think it was really unfair of you
to unload that onto me.
But I'm your friend, and I don't want you
to do anything stupid again.
Thank you.
It was an accident, Ander.
You don't crack someone's head open
by accident.
But I believe you when you say
that you didn't mean to.
You lost control.
I swear, if only I could go back...
There is one thing we can do.
There's an innocent guy rotting in prison
for something he didn't do,
at least until the trial begins.
How much money
can you take out of your account?
Ander...
Do you want me to leave?
Is that what's wrong with you?
No...
Then why are you acting so strange?
It has nothing to do with you, Omar.
So why don't you tell me about it?
Trust me, okay?
It'll pass.
-Samuel?
-In the bathroom.
Hey. You okay?
There was a letter in the mailbox
with your name on it.
I'm going to bed.
I'm exhausted. What a day...
-Where's the money from the Sáez family?
-I forgot.
Mrs. Sáez called to tell me
you stole a dress from her.
I could have died of shame!
Isn't stealing on the Internet
enough for you anymore?
I don't steal!
I do crowdfunding to launch my designs.
To make clothes for yourself
that you don't sell.
How are you going to pay them back?
This has to end.
Mom, we'll talk about this at home.
Don't say anything.
I won't say anything.
You are going to say it all.
In front of the whole class.
You'll say that I'm your mother
and that you're here on a scholarship
because we're broke. And proud.
-It'll be okay.
-Let go.
Mom, please! Don't ruin everything.
For the first time,
I'm starting to feel part of something.
I have friends.
And someone that could be
more than a friend.
-Mom...
-Hi.
Is there a problem?
No.
This young lady's chauffeur
throws his cigarette butts on the ground,
and the school entrance
looks like an ashtray.
Don't worry, I'll talk to him.
Enough of that.
She's a cleaner, not your fucking slave.
-The other day in the bathroom, and--
-Do I stick my nose in your business?
You, with your sunglasses,
your look, and all that?
So much money and so little class.
Listen, Cayetana, it's only eight,
and I'm not in the mood for it,
but you're asking for a slap, honey.
Hey, drug-dealer Barbie.
Thanks, Lu.
You don't want to make trouble with me.
Careful with badass Barbie.
She'd be right at home in my neighborhood.
By the way, Latin Barbie...
Good day.
I was having a rough time.
My girlfriend,
who I'd been with since I was 12,
had left me for someone else, and...
it was hard for me
to come to terms with.
And, yes,
I tried to...
Well, you know.
But now it's over,
and it made me stronger.
Anyway, I don't know
what this has to do with Samuel.
Samuel believed that you were connected
in some way to Marina's death.
That's absurd.
You arrested the culprit yourself, right?
I'm guessing that if you're here,
that means you haven't confessed.
You guessed right.
I couldn't do it to you.
What does that mean, Polo?
I'm a weak person.
If I confess,
I'll end up telling them everything.
That you were an accomplice.
And I don't want to do that to you, love.
Hey.
I forgot to reply to your text yesterday.
What did you want to say?
I can't remember.
Don't worry.
It was probably something stupid.
Hi, darling.
So, did you have a good time at the club?
Guzmán! Let us know next time
you're going out, you bastard.
Good morning, class.
Subtitle translation by Aline Saba