66 HOURS MISSING
I regret that we meet again, Guzmán.
At least it has nothing to do with me
this time.
Are you sure about that?
I have no relationship whatsoever
with Samuel or his brother.
For me, it's as though they didn't exist.
Good evening.
What the fuck are you doing here?
I'm alone.
Come and get me.
You don't have the balls.
You'd only dare go after Carla?
Or my sister.
You don't have the balls!
What I do have is brains.
If I hit you, you'll call the police...
And which one of us is out on bail
and would end up back in jail?
I didn't do it.
I didn't do it, Guzmán.
I didn't kill her.
Are you going to let me wreck it?
Good night.
So you were avoiding both Nano and Samuel.
I didn't go near them.
I didn't want to catch anything from them.
And you don't know anything
about either of their whereabouts?
Nor do I care.
-Are we done yet?
-No.
We've only just started.
Good evening, miss.
Room service has arrived.
Tuna sashimi with a subtle touch...
A very subtle touch of ginger.
I said I'm not hungry.
It has everything that you like.
I know you better than anyone.
Sure. You know me better than anyone.
If you knew me that well,
you'd know that you're the last person
I want to see right now.
What if people find out?
What then?
Excuse me?
We are half-brother and sister.
Nobody was taking advantage of the other.
And we're not planning
on bringing children into the world.
What's the problem?
-Tell me, what's the problem?
-Whatever.
Maybe that you're a junkie?
A little boy with credit cards?
That everything is all a joke to you,
including your own future, including me?
I was already like that when you used
to come to my room every night.
You started this shitty game.
When you kissed me for the first time.
Like the other night at the party.
Sure.
Do you know why I kissed you at the party?
Because you love me?
Because you drugged me.
You know it was undetectable.
What happened to your car?
Good morning.
I came back and found it like that.
Sure.
It was probably the same drunks
that beat you up the other night
for nothing, right?
I'd guess...
I've got the message loud and clear.
I'm a fucking nuisance.
Don't worry,
you'll be rid of me soon enough.
I'm leaving.
-What do you mean you're leaving?
-I'm leaving the country.
I'm not gonna let those bastards
lock me up for life.
That's fucking great.
Your brother and I spent the whole summer
working to get you out of prison,
and now you want to go on the run?
That's great.
If you skip bail,
there goes the bond we paid.
I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
Nano.
Nano!
Samu...
You smell so good. Can we talk?
What you saw the other day at the party
was just a misunderstanding.
I don't want you
to get the wrong impression.
Your brother had his tongue
right down your throat.
Wrong.
Half-brother.
And I don't remember anything about that.
I was drunk.
What can I do to make you
forget all about it, too?
Ask anything you want.
Are you trying to buy me off?
Don't tell me you don't need anything.
Because I can think
of basically everything.
You can stick your money
where the sun don't shine.
Okay...
Pride is a luxury
that only we rich folk can afford.
Looking down on others is a luxury
that you can't afford right now.
So what the fuck do you want?
I want you to go to bed every night
not knowing whether you'll be
the next outcast at school.
Will everyone look you up
and down in the halls?
Will they whisper about you?
Will they make you feel like a weirdo?
Darling...
If I go down,
I'm dragging you down with me. Understood?
-I couldn't get any lower, Lucrecia.
-You're right.
How many broken bones
does your brother have?
Are you regretting it now?
I'm so glad you've seen the light, Samu!
Why aren't you going to report him?
He barely touched me.
Are we waiting until he kills you
before we go to the station?
Welcome to fucking reality, Guzmán.
When a woman reports a guy,
it's her word against his.
The most likely thing is
that she won't be believed.
Anyway, the last thing I want is for that
bastard to end up on the streets again,
even more pissed off at me than before.
Why does he hate you?
What?
I mean, why did he go after you?
He went for all of us.
I was an easy target.
The girl walking home alone.
Good morning.
I have the exam results.
I'm sorry.
I'm what you got in the divorce.
Guzmán.
Guzmán!
-What?
-You have to...
We all have to move on.
He's a fucking murderer.
He's killed once,
who says he won't do it again?
I wanted to talk to you.
You and I. Dinner. Tonight.
Lu recommended a great restaurant.
At 8:30 p.m.
He can't.
Why?
It's Ander's birthday.
We're celebrating like we do every year.
Okay. Tomorrow, then.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, bro.
Happy birthday, dear...
Thanks.
What's up?
Where are we celebrating?
-I'm gonna pass this year.
-Why's that?
We have an exam tomorrow.
And I'm the principal's son.
I should pass at least one.
Shit, man,
why are you acting so strange lately?
Nothing. The divorce thing, I guess.
That's what friends are for, right?
To help each other through rough patches.
With a couple of drinks and some chatting.
We'll celebrate later.
When all this is over.
Exams and everything.
So, you're free tonight, then.
What time did you say?
Carla.
What do you want?
To thank you for not reporting my brother.
They wouldn't have believed me
without any evidence.
They wouldn't have believed most girls.
But your word is not worth
the same as the others.
You're rich,
the daughter of a marchioness.
That is also "fucking reality."
If you had gone to the police,
Nano would be behind bars now.
And you didn't do it because of me.
And you also beat your own brother
to death because of me.
Maybe we should stop doing things
for one another, Samuel.
We should leave it.
What happened wasn't your fault.
Well, I'm always there
when something bad happens.
It's not your fault.
-What if it is?
-It's not.
How do you know?
I just know.
I look at you
and I know you don't want to harm anyone.
Sure.
You've been pussy-whipped.
I often have that effect on guys.
Not on me.
What if we just go with it?
-Weren't we going to leave this?
-We're leaving it.
Little by little.
For someone that's leaving it,
you look very turned on.
Rich kid stuff.
You're fighting hard today.
You only hit hard
when you're defending Miss Marchioness?
-What did you want me to do?
-I don't know...
I thought the idea of all this was to help
your brother, not to send him to hospital.
-That's between Nano and me.
-Excuse me?
It's not your business.
Bullshit. Not my business...
You made it my business
the first day I met you.
You've been doing my head in with it.
Now I should forget about it?
The way you forget about it as soon as
that chick sticks her pussy in your face?
Fuck's sake!
Didn't you want to find out
who killed Marina?
What do you want me to do?
Not throw the fucking towel in!
Get up! Up!
I don't know where to go from here.
So start again from scratch.
You may have missed something.
You never see
what's right under your nose.
Good afternoon.
-Good afternoon.
Nadia, my dear!
I'd like to have a chat with you
in private.
I'd rather not.
I'm being cautious.
It'd be better for you if they don't hear
what I have to say to you.
Lucrecia...
Why did you come here?
Do they know that you fucked Guzmán?
Get out of here.
I give the orders around here.
What are you talking about?
I want you to fail
all the exams this week.
Why?
Because I want you to know how it feels
when the thing that matters most to you
is ripped away.
Your scholarship, for example.
If you don't fail,
I'll come back and tell your mom
and dad that their daughter is a slut.
That she's tried her first Christian dick.
Shut up.
You decide
whether you'd rather be kicked out
of your house or out of school.
Have a nice day!
Bye.
Instagram accounts were the first thing
I looked at.
I didn't find anything.
Because you didn't know where to look.
END OF YEAR PARTY
This is Polo,
the guy that sent the message confessing?
Stop. Go back to one before.
He's not wearing the same shirt.
Why would you change your clothes
in the middle of the party?
Because they get stained
with the usual stuff.
-Vomit, alcohol or cum.
-Blood.
That photo is before Marina was killed.
This one is afterwards.
He had a spare shirt in his locker
just in case he killed someone?
That's not his shirt.
I've seen it before.
It's Christian's shirt.
Christian helped him when it got stained.
He knew why it got stained.
He knew, but he said nothing.
That's why he was acting so strange
all summer.
-And when he wanted to talk...
-Fucking hell, Samuel.
Where are you going?
I love it.
It's really beautiful and all that.
I've been on it many times,
but you have to look for things to do.
-Either that or you get all bored.
-I see.
I love these chopsticks. They're so cute.
-So basically, we got on his yacht.
-Listen.
What?
How about we talk about something else?
It's all about trips
to the most beautiful places,
delicious food, your best friends...
Guilty.
What's wrong with that?
It makes me feel
like my life is shit in comparison.
Maybe it is, but...
I have so many problems
that I have no strength left
to even smile for the camera.
Tell me about something bad
that has happened to you.
I suppose you don't have any problems.
Well, it's hard to live alone sometimes.
My mom is never home.
-Sure, sure...
-And...
-Sure?
-Sure.
With an entire palace all to yourself,
it must be fucking hard as hell.
Tell the waiter about it.
I'm sure he'll end up you giving a tip.
Sorry.
-It's okay...
-I didn't mean to offend you.
No worries.
It's just another photo, bro.
It's not much.
Basically, these motherfuckers
already have a scapegoat.
Let's check it out.
Let's go to the police.
All they'll see, Samu, is the brother
of a stray bullet trying to save his ass.
So then what? Are you giving up?
No.
I'm going out in style.
If they don't catch me
at the border, of course.
If you leave, you're as good as admitting
that you're guilty.
Wait. At least you're not in prison now.
This is worse than prison. Much worse.
In my dingy four by four cell,
I couldn't hurt anyone.
Here, on the other hand,
I feel like I'm radioactive.
Everything I touch turns to shit.
I want to live in peace. That's all.
And so do you two.
With you here.
We want you here.
The other night you didn't want me there.
The other night I was an animal.
Look, I don't know
if I'll ever be able to forgive you.
But if you leave,
neither of us will ever know.
Have you seen the car?
It's worse than me.
What's that got to do with anything?
Next time blondie shows up,
he won't just scratch the bodywork.
-Guzmán?
-I don't blame him.
I don't blame him.
If I believed he had killed my brother,
I'd do the same.
Give me time, Nano.
Hang in there a little longer.
I'm about to figure it all out.
Find a job, don't get into trouble.
Do it for me.
For Mom.
For Marina.
This is the point
where Samuel disappeared.
But the last indication of him
being alive was here.
The last time his cell phone was active.
Do you recognize the area?
Maybe...
Your grandparents have a country house.
That's where Marina's ashes are buried.
What was Samuel doing around there?
Well...
He could have been delivering
lemon chicken. How should I know?
He wasn't working that night.
Now you're studying shots?
I'm keeping Omar company.
I could have kept you company.
But you didn't want that.
Enjoy.
Guzmán...
What's going on with him?
Pour me some more.
Honey, you're really going for it tonight.
"Honey"?
Here we go. Again?
-You're looking fantastic, gayboy!
-Here she comes!
Happy birthday, handsome.
-How's my favorite customer?
-Fucking great.
-Really?
-Really.
I wouldn't say so.
You don't look too good.
-I'm good!
-What's wrong?
I was all wound up at home and I thought
I would come see my friend, the Sultan.
I can't allow that! Let me get you a drink
and let's have some fun.
On the house.
-But first, got anything to say to me?
-Yeah, you look so handsome!
Weird... I thought you'd quit.
Ander is ignoring me,
Lu won't even look at me
and Polo is hooking up with the new girl.
I think you're my best friend right now.
What about that?
Funny...
I thought this was all because of Nadia.
What the fuck would you know
about loving someone who loves you,
but you can't be together because
of the fucking society you live in?
You're absolutely right.
I have no fucking clue.
What the fuck are you doing?
I'm doing you a favor as your best friend.
Do me a favor now. Go home.
-Fucking hell!
-Good night.
Thank you very much.
Get me some rum and coke.
Right away.
Gaydar, my ass!
This song is the authentic gay magnet.
I'm off to scout out the talent again.
Okay, good luck. We'll catch up later.
Hey.
Honey, you look
like SpongeBob SquarePants.
Not again! Don't call me that.
What? SpongeBob SquarePants?
You could also stop doing that,
couldn't you?
Doing what?
You know what. Don't play dumb.
The looks, the little remarks.
I'm not a fool.
Because of the way
you've been acting all night.
Acting?
I'm not acting.
Look, forget it.
I don't want to.
Come on, say what's on your mind.
What is wrong with you?
This isn't the Omar I fell for!
Do you get it? I like the other one.
Well, then I don't know
why you're wasting time with this guy.
-Almost.
-What's up with you?
Hey... Good night.
Do you only use your phone
for taking trashy selfies or what?
Trashy people also run out of battery.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
I was worried sick about you.
That's what's wrong.
It wouldn't be the first time.
Look at me.
From now on,
the chauffeur will escort you everywhere.
Even to the toilet, if necessary.
And you'll have a charger with you
all the time.
What's going on, Mom?
Mr. Biker.
Leave my family in peace.
A bit ironic, coming from you. Isn't it?
You think it's bad that I have a problem
with the guy that murdered my sister?
It was your friend Polo, you asshole.
What are you talking about, you scumbag?
-It was Polo. Listen to me!
-I'm having a shit day
-and now you come to piss me off!
-Listen to me!
He wanted to get Carla's watch back.
Christian knew.
He was going to tell the whole story.
Or do you think what happened to him
was an accident?
Sir!
They're fighting.
Guys, stop now!
This is not the first time...
and I will not tolerate it.
I didn't do anything! He came after me.
Is that true?
It was Guzmán who attacked Samuel.
-What are you talking about?
-Don't play dumb.
I don't recognize him lately.
He must be hanging around
with the wrong crowd.
Don't think you're escaping unscathed.
I'll be talking to your mother as well.
Guzmán, you are suspended.
-For two days.
-What?
We're in exams! You're suspending me now?
Three days. Come with me, please.
You owe me one.
JOB POSTINGS
There's fuck all...
Of course, don't worry, I'll talk to him.
It won't happen again.
Okay. Thank you.
You get out of prison and all of a sudden,
your brother starts getting in trouble.
What a coincidence, huh?
It wouldn't have something to do with you?
-It has everything to do with me.
-For fuck's sake, Nano!
Shit...
Listen, why don't you stop
looking for work
and start looking for a ticket
out of here?
A one-way ticket.
What's going on?
I'm going to fail.
You? Impossible.
Your darling sister is forcing me to fail.
Or she will tell something.
Something?
What?
Think of the worst.
If she threatens to tell on you,
tell her you'll tell everyone
about the Valerio thing.
I promise she will never mess with you
ever again.
And what is the "Valerio thing"?
Think of the worst,
and you wouldn't even come close.
How was your date?
Great.
After so many years,
do you think you can deceive me?
SAMUEL - I want to see you after class,
in the classroom.
How's lover boy doing?
Please... He's not my lover boy.
You know I'm only with him for one reason,
and love has nothing to do with it.
After so many years,
do you think you can deceive me?
Good morning!
What tired little faces you have.
I hope that's from all the studying.
He came after me. I didn't do anything!
What do you think you're doing?
Getting the best mark in the class.
You'll be forcing me to have
a very unpleasant conversation
with your parents.
If I were you, I wouldn't do that.
Not unless you want people to find out...
about the Valerio thing.
What did you say?
In fact, either you fail this test,
or everyone will know.
Have a nice day.
-He provoked me. He said that...
-What?
Some bullshit.
He said that...
-That...
-Guzmán, you can't... Guzmán!
You need to move on
or things will end badly.
For fuck's sake, what if that guy
had attacked you last night?
I'm not afraid of him.
I'm not afraid of him either.
I'm afraid of you.
I'm afraid you'll do something
you'll regret for the rest of your life.
It only takes a second.
If you don't control your anger,
one bad punch, one bad fall...
and you make everything go to shit.
Polo.
Fucking hell...
Can we talk a moment?
I just got the feeling
that you were avoiding me. I get it but...
-Not at all.
-Yes! He is avoiding you!
He doesn't like you, you're not his type.
It's not you, it's him.
He just came out of a relationship
and doesn't want a new one.
Pick the excuse you like most,
the end result will be the same.
-He doesn't want anything to do with you.
-Guzmán!
What, Polo?
If you haven't got the guts to say it,
someone has to do it for you.
So you stop messing the poor girl around.
Right?
I'm sorry. It's for your own good.
Okay...
I don't know how to thank you.
I would offer to send you to rehab,
but I've only got enough
to buy you a coffee.
I'm not that cheap.
How did it go?
What is it that Lu has got against you?
If you want to let me know...
Guzmán and I slept together.
So what?
-It's just sex. What's wrong with that?
-No.
Between us, it would never only be that.
And I knew it.
I knew I would turn my life upside down,
as well as Guzmán's, and Lu's...
But I did it anyway.
Because I'm in love.
As though that were an excuse.
Love is supposedly very beautiful,
but it also turns you
into someone very selfish.
Your turn.
What is the "Valerio thing" anyway?
Do you want to know something, Nadia?
You've become something like a friend.
If I tell you about this,
you may not want to be my friend anymore.
I don't know what to do.
I'm more open than you think.
Nothing surprises me
at this school anymore.
It was a pleasure being your friend.
Are you all right?
You're a dead man, you son of a bitch.
Come on, Caye.
I don't understand what I did wrong.
-You didn't do anything wrong.
-Okay.
We're just at different points
in our lives.
Your life is all rosy
and mine is black right now.
-Very black.
-Yeah, okay, but why?
I'm sorry, but I don't get it.
I wouldn't expect someone like you
to understand it.
Your biggest problem seems to be
deciding which of your ten bathrooms
to use each morning.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
You don't know me.
You don't know who I am.
You think I don't have problems?
Seriously?
You want me to tell you
something ugly about me, right?
Fine...
Fine.
How much time do you have?
Thanks.
Don't you like it?
Yeah, I like it.
It's just that I don't have this console.
But it's the thought that counts.
You didn't have to come
if you didn't want to.
Of course I wanted to come, Ander.
So that mom doesn't bother you.
Look, son,
if you don't like the game, I'm sorry.
It's not easy to know what you like now.
What?
-Do you really have to come out with that?
-It's true.
I feel like I don't know anything
about my son. He's changed.
I don't know who he is!
He used to like things and now...
What does that matter?
-Omar, darling...
-No.
What does it matter if he doesn't like
tennis or girls? He's still Ander.
You only just met him.
What would you know?
I know that they say I've changed, too,
but I haven't. I've always been this way.
I had to pretend so as not to disappoint,
but I'm tired of it.
And anyone who doesn't like it...
Anyone who doesn't like it
will be out of my life.
Ander is also tired of pretending.
If you don't learn to love him as he is,
you will lose him forever.
I don't know what it's like
to lose a child,
but I swear to you,
losing a father is a fucking bitch.
What a time to meet...
Looks like we are alone.
That was the idea.
Why did Polo change
the night of the party?
He threw up on himself.
He put on Christian's shirt.
He had the same one.
They both bought the same one
when we went shopping one day.
It sounds as though you had your answers
prepared in advance.
You are so predictable.
Don't lie to me, Carla.
You are covering for a murderer.
I don't know what you think you're going
to achieve with your questions.
You've been at it for weeks
and you've gotten nowhere.
And you're not going to.
Why are you being like this?
I'm not being like anything.
If you carry on with your investigation,
the only thing you will really achieve
will be ending up like Christian.
Who did that to him?
Polo?
Samuel...
Why do you keep playing this game,
if you keep on losing?
I'm tired of it.
I can say it louder but not any clearer.
My grandparents don't live at that farm.
-I haven't been there in months.
-Sure.
So it's a coincidence
that the last time Samuel was seen alive
was close to one of your properties
and the last time Nano was seen alive
was at your house, right?
The door was open.
Get out. Get out of here!
I'm calling the police!
I'm going. But before I do,
I have a message for your son.
And for your whole family. Let's see
if you can get this straight for once.
Don't come any closer.
That's the number
we were given in the clinic
when she went to have an abortion.
We left before they called us.
Do you know why?
Because we were so in love, we thought
that we could have a kid together.
What a pair of idiots.
I was so madly in love with your daughter
that I kept this shitty little piece
of paper as a keepsake.
It's the only thing I have of hers.
The only thing I can touch.
Do you really think I could have been
capable of hurting your daughter?
Do you really think that?
Thank you.
I think I should go.
See?
That's why we all pretend to be happy,
because none of you tolerate
the misfortunes of others.
The fantasy you made up?
What for, to be just another posh girl?
-No...
-Really?
No, Polo.
So that people like you would talk to me.
Or have dinner with me.
Just so you know, the real Cayetana...
-Cayetana is your name, right?
-Yes.
The real one is a lot more interesting.
Or, at least, different.
I've never met anyone like this before.
Well, at least the exotic species
has kept you entertained.
-You can go if you want.
-No.
Go.
How can I help you?
You don't get it. What now?
I don't have money,
so all you can do for me is help?
Are you for real?
I don't need your help, Polo.
I need you.
But I know that's not possible...
Cayetana.
I'm leaving.
Don't. This is Polo.
Tell your friend to leave.
I need to talk to you.
He knows...
He knows everything. What's wrong?
Does he know that you stole a dress?
Not that part.
And that its owner has called round
all my houses and I've lost all of them?
We will find more.
That's it.
-No.
-Yes...
Not here. I've been blacklisted.
And now what?
How are we going to pay the bills?
Shit...
And now this?
Who the fuck does he think he is?
-I'm going to kill him!
-Ventura, please... Calm down.
Calm down? My ass!
Haven't we suffered enough?
Hi.
Hi, darling.
This is not
because I was suspended, right?
That murderer had the balls to come here.
If you have something to accuse me of,
get on with it.
Otherwise, leave me in peace.
I'm supposed to be studying
with my friends.
We can continue tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
Nano!
Nano! I've got something!
No...
Where is he?
Where the fuck is he?
He's gone! It's your fucking fault!
-That's not true!
-It is!
The typical thing you do
when you're innocent, right?
What do you think you're going to achieve
with your questions?
You've been at it for weeks
-and you've gotten nowhere.
-What's that?
-And you're not going to.
-Why are you being like this?
I'm not being like anything.
If you carry on with your investigation,
the only thing you will really achieve
will be ending up like Christian.
Subtitle translation by Aline Saba