What the hell is he doing here?
GRADUATION PARTY
Sure, private number.
There's no fucking way I'm answering that.
I already have a phone plan.
Rebe.
-What?
-Were you really dealing at school?
Were you, Valerio?
You two... come in.
-Azucena, good morning.
-Good morning, Begoña.
I'd like to talk to you.
Do you have a few minutes?
Actually,
I have an important matter to see to.
Not more important
than what I have to say.
I'll be right with you--
I can always go over your head
and speak to the board.
I'm only asking to meet with you
as a courtesy.
Just a moment.
Damn.
I have to go to Ander's
to get the rest of my stuff.
After that, I don't know...
Maybe I'll perform hara-kiri
over my grades.
Were they really that bad?
On a scale of disasters...
the Notre-Dame fire,
Spain at Eurovision,
-Madonna at Eurovision...
-Damn.
...my grades.
I have to laugh
because if I really think about it...
In the end, I'm not graduating,
I've lost Ander...
and I'm homeless.
What?
Why don't you come to New York with me?
-What?
-Come on.
You've always wanted to travel
and live somewhere
where you could blend in.
New York meets that criteria
better than any place I can think of.
You'll get a job, learn English...
What the hell would I do there?
Where would I stay?
It's crazy, Nadia.
In my apartment?
Yeah, you showed me photos.
It's as big as Central Park.
You can't ask someone
you barely know to put people up--
What do you mean?
We were engaged for a night.
Although, you two are pretty close,
right?
We just hooked up a few times.
-I mean--
-Yeah, we just hooked up. Got it.
I would only stay temporarily.
OK, sure. Why not?
Nobody would know
if someone hadn't snitched.
Valerio and Rebeka were selling drugs,
and Polo reported it.
You're blaming him
for doing what's right?
Samuel, Guzmán.
Come with me, please.
Us?
Now.
Look, Azucena.
You can make an argument for expelling us,
but these two?
-We didn't do anything!
-I warned you.
I said there'd be zero tolerance.
And yet, you've been tormenting him
since Christmas.
This is bullshit.
Polo's mother's behind it.
She was in here right before us.
Am I right?
It's been decided.
You're expelled and won't graduate.
-What?
-Samuel!
You fucking sellouts.
There's no fairness here!
All you care about is money and power.
-Don't talk to me like that.
-Or what? You'll expel us?
Samu... it's not worth it.
What are you doing?
What's he doing? Stop!
-What are you doing?
-Relax.
That's enough violence, OK?
-Are you defending him?
-Yes!
He said he didn't accuse you two
of anything.
And you believe him?
You're doing this so you won't feel bad
about accepting the grant.
You'll accept it no matter what,
even if it means taking his side.
Son of a bitch.
Lu, forget about him.
Nadia, don't play innocent.
You want to smash this bottle
over his head as much as I do.
Admit it.
This wouldn't have happened
if they'd just let me leave.
That doesn't matter now.
We need to think of a way to fix this.
We could--
It's too late. It's over.
-You can't end things this way.
-Carla almost drowned last night.
She almost died because of him.
Because of me! It was my fault, OK?
What are you saying?
I sold Carla the Molly
'cause Valerio refused.
He was going to stop dealing
after your little lecture.
What? You didn't know? Well, now you do.
But you had to go and make a scene.
I guess you couldn't bear the idea
of doing something right for once.
-Why don't you go home, Rebeka?
-Fucking Bodyguard Barbie.
Better yet, just go straight to jail.
-You'll end up there with your mom anyway.
-We have something in common.
Because you also get along great
with criminals.
As long as they pay for your outfits,
expensive meals, and tuition...
But I get it, OK? I really do.
Hold on to him tight.
You know what you'll have once he's gone?
Nothing and no one, hon.
Damn private number!
You don't look too bad...
at least not at first glance.
-I can't remember a thing.
-That's normal.
No, it's not.
I lost control.
-And I helped you lose it. I'm sorry.
-No, you warned me.
I'm the one who's sorry.
I just heard you were expelled.
He got what was coming to him.
Don't blame him for yesterday.
He wouldn't sell to me.
Well, it's the first bit of common sense
he's shown in ages,
-but it's still too late.
-Well, later.
I've been trying to change
for a long time.
Trying...
but you never change.
-You'll never grow up.
-I had nothing to do with what happened.
You're like a fucking baby...
sticking his fingers
in electrical sockets.
For 17 years, I've tried to stop you
from electrocuting yourself...
but it's never enough.
I can't take it anymore.
Have a good life.
He always wins.
I'm fucking sick of this.
-We should've moved on a long time ago.
-We didn't do anything to him!
Not today,
but look at everything we've done
to make his life a living hell.
Not a single day has gone by
that we haven't hated him,
and we made sure he knew it.
He didn't win... We lost.
Guzmán.
-How are you?
-Fine.
I know you.
What they did to you is a disgrace.
We deserved it.
What? It can't end like this.
-I swear--
-Stay out of wars that don't affect you.
They affect me...
if they hurt someone I love.
You can't risk your scholarship.
It's your future.
What about yours? Doesn't it matter?
I'm 17 years old.
I can afford
to put the future on hold for a year.
Hey...
After graduation, we'll throw a party.
We'll have a blast.
Nothing will fuck it up.
I promise.
Give me a light, honey.
You never smoke on the job.
Those kids will be the end of me.
The school year's almost over,
but they'll be the end of me.
What you did is unfair, you know.
-Please, not you too.
-What do you want me to say?
It's not a question of being fair or not.
It's much more complicated.
-You'd need to be in my shoes to get it.
-But Guzmán and Samu don't deserve this.
Focus on the important stuff.
Your exams, for example.
I'm not taking any makeup exams.
Don't start with that nonsense
about favoritism again.
Allowing you to retake exams due to chemo
isn't favoritism.
I'm not wasting my last few days of life
in front of a book.
What do you mean, "last days"?
There's no hope for me...
at least not down the road.
-And...
-Where'd you get that idea, Ander?
Who told you that? No one told me that.
This is all I have. The here and now.
But, honey...
OK, and maybe tomorrow.
But I won't waste my time studying.
What for?
I won't allow
this resigned, defeated attitude.
Mom...
You don't want to study?
What do you want to do, then?
I don't know.
Spend some time with myself.
Start preparing myself.
You'd need to be in my shoes to get it.
HI, YERAY. WHEN CAN WE MEET?
YERAY, PLEASE ANSWER ME.
ARE YOU OK? CAN I CALL YOU?
FROM: MOM
SUBJECT: GOOD NEWS!!!
The lawyer wants to meet
with my mom and brother in Morocco.
-He says he has good news.
-That's fucking awesome.
Maybe this nightmare will be over,
and Nano can come home.
It's not over as long as Polo's free.
You're obsessed with Polo, man!
Forget about him already.
He's already ruined your year,
your life, and everything.
-How can I forget?
-Distance.
Focus on what matters now,
like your family coming home.
-Be like Guzmán. Move on.
-Bullshit.
Here.
-What're you doing?
-Close your eyes. Close them!
All done.
-What's all done?
-Polo doesn't exist.
Polo who? I don't know any Polo.
-Hey, neither do I.
-See?
It really works, huh?
Can I have a napkin?
You really have some balls
showing up here.
I just want to dry off, Omar.
And I want you to go.
For your own good.
Leave!
-Mom!
-Baby, tell me you have a cig.
I'm jonesing for one so bad,
I almost smoked parsley.
So? Aren't you going
to give your mom a hug?
That's more like it.
Tell me you have my lighter.
Why didn't you say
you were getting out today?
I called you a few times this morning,
but you didn't pick up.
-Shit, that was you?
-Of course it was me.
You smell so nice.
And you're so beautiful.
What?
Nothing.
Come on. I know that look.
I got kicked out of school.
What do you mean? When?
Now. Well, earlier.
Why?
What do you think?
Fucking shit.
Well, know what? Fuck school.
If you know what you're doing,
you don't need school.
You've been doing an awesome job
running the family business.
At your own level, on a small scale,
but awesome.
From now on,
it's mother and daughter, hand in hand.
Hi.
Holy shit, Mom.
Get mad at her later.
Let's go outside.
Sorry. I didn't know what else to do.
What's so hard to understand?
We do understand.
Look at you. You got expelled. So what?
Big fucking deal!
You'll graduate next year.
I don't have next year.
What don't you get?
Fine, you don't have next year.
What do you want to do?
Your mom says you want time
by yourself. That's a shitty plan.
Guzmán... none of you
will ever understand.
You can do whatever the hell you want.
If you don't want to study, don't.
I don't even care if you want to skydive.
But don't isolate yourself, please.
Because, if you really are dying...
I can't believe
you'd want to spend your time alone.
Without your family, your friends,
and Omar.
Ander.
-Damn it, Ander.
-Leave me alone, please.
I can't take it anymore.
Hi, Polo. I know you don't want
to talk to me.
That's fine, but I'm asking you...
please talk to your moms.
They could get them to readmit Valerio
and forgive him because...
there's no sense in punishing him
when he'd already learned his lesson.
Please, whatever you decide, call me.
Please, OK?
What are you wearing tomorrow?
I'm not going, Mom.
The students who won't be graduating...
got what they deserved.
And Guzmán and Samuel?
They just broke up the fight.
Those bullies have been making
your life hell all year.
If you're not man enough to face them...
you can't expect me to stand by
and watch my son get beaten up.
How about the striped shirt...
with the blue pants?
You'll look so handsome.
What're you doing here?
What's up with you?
How'd you get in?
I don't have a doorman you can manipulate.
From when you asked me
to decorate the place and make it my own.
Yeah...
Those were good times.
Please, take a seat. Get comfy.
Why are you here, Carla?
I came to apologize.
For real.
You're a really great guy.
"Yeray, you're a great guy.
You're really worth it,
any girl would kill to be with you..."
Except the one who says it, of course.
Been there.
I really mean it.
Carla, the last thing I need now
is your pity, really.
-Please leave.
-All right...
Let's stop playing the victim...
because you don't like me either.
-Excuse me?
-You heard me.
I don't like you,
and you don't like me either.
What about the last few months?
-What do you call--
-You love what I represent.
How well I fit in
with the image you created
to get likes from people
who hurt the old Yeray.
Your body, your clothes, your attitude...
You even created your own social network
to get them to worship you.
All I am to you is another accessory.
And I'm a walking checkbook
meant to save your wineries.
That's what I meant!
We don't like each other
the way we pretend to.
Even so, I was lucky enough
to get to know the real Yeray,
the one behind the selfies.
And I can tell you... he's a great guy.
Much better than the one you made up.
And I bet any girl
would kill to be with you.
Any girl but me.
So...
fuck the likes...
and fuck the wineries.
We've already wasted enough time
doing what others want us to do, right?
You have nothing to prove to anyone.
Now... can I give you a hug?
As a friend, not trying to manipulate you.
-Are you nervous, honey?
-A little, Dad.
It'll be fine.
There's Omar!
-How are you, Mom?
-I'm fine.
You look great.
You too.
How are you?
A bit nervous.
About what? Come on.
Hey.
-Hello.
-Hi, Lu.
I like it.
-Hey, Lu.
-What's up?
Didn't your parents come?
It seems your family knows how
to put problems aside for a while...
to focus on what matters.
I envy you.
In a good way.... and in a bad way too.
You look like a pistachio.
You can't make an exception?
After all I've done
for this fucking school!
-Please!
-I'll take you to court.
Come in, please.
Ventura, do what you think is best,
but the expulsion was justified.
Justified?
On the last day of the year? Oh, please.
My son's entire year,
thrown away on the last day!
-Laura, Ventura, I--
-Lucrecia, honey, stay out of this.
Actually, I wish you'd done more
to help Guzmán.
-Me?
-Yes. Your father's very influential.
-If we all did our part--
-Okay, that's enough.
I'm very sorry.
Polo!
How are you? So?
Why are you ignoring me?
They still haven't signed the papers.
-We'll talk to your--
-Cayetana.
Why are you so set on Valerio graduating?
-So he can come with us and--
-And save our relationship.
Because... without him...
we just don't work.
Polo, don't start.
Don't start.
I get it. You're under a lot of pressure.
-You don't know what you're saying.
-No.
For the first time in a long time, I know.
I'm sorry.
What about... London? Our plans?
See? That's all you're worried about.
London, our plans...
You're not in love with me...
but with the life I would've provided.
Why are you using the past tense?
I'm sorry.
I have to go, OK?
Hey...
What happened?
Nothing.
Hold on... one sec. I won't be long.
Teodoro.
Can we meet at your place later
to close the deal?
Of course.
I'm glad you reconsidered.
The ceremony will start in five minutes.
There he is.
Thank you.
Let's continue.
Shit...
Let me do it.
The students I'm about to introduce...
What should we do?
I really don't know.
All I know is I want that scholarship.
So do I. But we're selling out.
So, you don't want it?
At what price?
Can the winners of the first edition
of the scholarship please come up?
A big round of applause
for Nadia Shanaa
and Lucrecia Montesinos Hendrich.
Bill McKinley will present the award
on behalf of Columbia University.
Good afternoon.
I want to thank our parents and friends
who have come to share
in this special moment...
for us and... for our fellow students.
I would like--
I can't.
Can you speak for me, Nadia?
No, you've already started.
Well...
-I was saying that--
-No, wait.
I would just like to say that...
I would like to--
We would like to...
I think I speak for us both.
We dedicate this award...
to our classmates.
Especially everyone in the back...
who, for various reasons,
cannot join us... up here...
in this graduation ceremony.
Not being able to have them
here with us...
makes this moment...
less happy than we would have liked.
That's right.
We should be jumping for joy.
But we're not.
Because we deserve... this award.
We deserve this moment, Nadia.
My friends are there...
due to a series of injustices.
Including the most serious one.
The one that deprived us... of Marina.
These are injustices...
that we both denounce.
That's right.
And one person is responsible
for all those injustices.
Polo...
How are you? Happy?
I cannot believe this.
Look, this award
that she and I are receiving...
was created by your moms
to clean up your image, basically.
And we're accepting it because,
I repeat, we deserve it.
What else should we do?
Because this has become--
If you feel so conflicted, don't worry.
The scholarship's called off.
-Begoña, please.
-No.
We have always wanted to support
Las Encinas and every student in it.
Who went into the bathroom?
Omar, I don't have all day.
And if I did, I don't have the patience.
Give me a name.
Nadia.
You're accusing your own sister?
You know what?
I promised someone I love very much...
that we would celebrate this day together.
And that we would have lots of fun,
and that nothing and nobody
would fuck it up.
Let's go celebrate at Teatro Barceló!
Hello?
Samuel.
You need to come to the police station.
It's extremely urgent.
Dad, I'm going to the bathroom.
-Wait for me outside.
-OK.
-We don't have the money.
-We'll take out a loan.
So?
You don't need Nadia in New York.
What do you mean?
-I'd never go on my own.
-You'll have me.
Wow! I thought we were just hooking up.
Fuck...
-What?
-I'm sorry.
Sorry I didn't react the way you wanted.
And yes, we hooked up.
And that meant a lot to me.
When your sister asked me
if you could come...
it left me speechless.
I thought Nadia's idea was crazy, too.
And it was more than just hooking up.
Maybe that's why we should do it.
If a suggestion leaves you speechless,
you have to try.
It was all a setup...
to locate your family
and arrest your brother.
I'm sorry.
I swear, I knew nothing about it.
They tricked me too.
And they found them?
Your brother will be repatriated.
Oh, Samuel...
Meanwhile, the killer's
in his suit and tie, about to go free.
-I'm sorry.
-You should be. You're also to blame.
-I told you, they tricked me too.
-Who tricked you?
I'll tell you who.
Your bosses, your colleagues...
the fucking system you work for,
belong to,
and won't do shit about.
That's why it's your fault.
Shit.
I printed the document you sent me.
If you want to review it one last time...
No.
No, I think... you should review it.
Yes.
There's been a change...
in section three of clause four.
About the management of the wineries?
You've been replaced by Carla.
She'll be the sole and exclusive manager
of the wineries and all related assets
as soon as she turns 18,
which won't be long now.
Look...
You'll have nothing to do with it.
Neither will I.
I'll stay out of it.
So...
Carla will be the owner.
Yeray, what you're proposing...
has never been on the table.
It is now.
So, you decide.
Let your daughter support you
as she sees fit...
or your business will go under
and you'll have no way
to support yourself.
She's very young
and has no clue how to run a business.
-Say something, honey.
-I say...
I'm done taking orders.
Excuse me?
I say...
you aren't going to decide
what I can or can't do anymore.
It's over.
I want to do whatever I want...
be whatever I want...
and be with whoever I want.
You have no power over me.
So, what do you say?
Shall we sign?
You know who's to blame? Azucena.
She doesn't command respect
from her students.
-She fears them and spoils them.
-It was a childish prank.
Canceling the scholarship
was an overreaction.
At least I did something.
If it wasn't for me,
the bullies who made your son's life hell
would still be in school.
-Maybe I deserved it.
-What do you mean?
Don't be ridiculous.
After everything that's happened...
the bullying, the tweets,
everything they wrote, all the hurt.
-To top it off, the person in charge--
-I killed Marina, Mom!
-It was an accident, but I did.
-Enough of this nonsense.
-Begoña.
-I don't want to hear it.
Marina had something
that belonged to Carla...
and I wanted to get it
to get Carla back.
-Polo, enough.
-No!
Fuck, Mom.
You always tell me to be a man.
To face up to things, to be brave.
Well, that's what I'm doing.
I killed Marina...
I can't bring her back.
I can't help Samuel and Guzmán graduate.
But don't cancel the scholarship.
At least let someone have a happy ending
in this awful story.
So, please call now.
Please.
Azucena? Yes, hi. It's Begoña.
I'm sorry to be calling so late, but...
I want to talk... about the scholarship.
Hi.
-Have you seen Samuel?
-Nope.
Should we hijack the DJ booth
to liven things up?
No music
can lift the funk hanging over all of us.
So, I lost the scholarship.
You two just had to play the heroines.
-What now?
-Let me use one of your questions.
Where does that leave us?
Define "that."
The fact that I'm not going.
That I'm staying.
Well, taking inspiration
from your answer...
I'd say it leaves us
in a very similar place.
You're here...
And I'm here.
After all the bad stuff that's happened,
that's a good thing, right?
I'd say so.
Hey, sorry, have you seen Ander?
No, but don't stop looking.
Everyone's looking for someone tonight.
Luckily, some of us have found
what we were looking for.
Hey, babe.
Hey.
I didn't graduate.
Me neither.
Well... misery loves company.
What will you do?
-Repeat the school year or get a job?
-No.
I got an opportunity to go to New York.
Really?
Yeah.
But not with your sister, right?
No. I mean, yeah,
at first, it was with her,
but after what happened...
well...
I'm going with Malick.
So, he'll help you get settled?
It all sounds too weird.
Or too perfect.
Yeah, that too.
What do you think?
Me?
Whatever you think.
I think I need your opinion.
Only an idiot would let something
that perfect slip away.
Right.
OK.
-Omar.
-What?
Goodbye.
Hey, sexy.
Not now, Carla.
Why not now?
You don't even know what I'm gonna say.
Look...
it may surprise you to hear this,
but I was thinking--
What the hell is he doing here?
Subtitle translation by Toni Navarro