I don't like you doing this here.
Where should we do it, then, Samu?
What if the cops catch us?
Why would the cops show up here?
We're three innocent schoolkids.
-Your mother's in jail because of this.
-Wrong.
She's in jail because some son of a bitch
sold us out.
But this is different.
We're like family here.
Fine, but it stays here.
Not a word to anyone. OK? Anyone.
Relax, we know what we're doing.
Keep it up, Valerio.
I can't believe it!
Good. You finally learned how to cheat.
I don't cheat, sweetheart.
The thing is, I'm... one of a kind.
And I have great study buddies.
We go at it hard every afternoon...
and every night, too.
You're kidding, right?
No, I don't think so.
This is serious... very serious.
B+
-No, it's his turn.
-Stop!
-Quiet. Which one was it?
-It tickles!
What? OK, potassium nitrate.
-What?
-Take something off.
What do you mean?
He got it right, didn't he?
-Yes, but he's wearing too much clothing.
-This girl learns fast.
-Not as fast as you.
-Oh, really? Not as fast as me?
Show some respect. I'm the teacher here.
I never thought
studying could be so much fun.
Do you realize you could even graduate
if you want to?
You could even go to university.
-For real.
-I don't know.
I never thought about my future.
In fact, it never occurred to me
I could have one.
Well, you could.
You're going to London, right?
King's College.
Why don't you join us?
No way! I don't have the grades
or the money to get
into a place like that.
Neither do I, but his mothers will...
-We got in with our connections.
-Yeah.
My mothers are friends with the dean.
-Really?
-Yes.
I don't suppose they could...
Well...
my mothers are vouching
for Cayetana because...
well, because she's my girlfriend.
I'm not saying that we're not a couple...
but they know her better, longer.
They don't know who you are yet.
-So, I'm nobody, right?
-I didn't say that.
-No.
-You misunderstood.
-It's OK.
-I didn't mean that.
There's a word
for what you two have, but...
there's no word for this.
Don't worry.
You've done enough for me.
Hey, it's fine.
Gin and tonic, please.
What's this blackout thing about?
A blackout, it's just that.
This Friday at midnight,
it's lights out at the club.
That's it?
People dig the dark.
They can do what they want
without being seen.
You could fuck three guys
right under Nadia's nose.
I'd be happy if you didn't say anything.
It's better for her.
It's better for her to live a lie?
If she finds out, she might break up
with me and forget all about New York.
Why risk it?
That's what I'm thinking.
Why did you take that risk?
Why'd you kiss me?
Why do you think I did?
I'm with someone, too.
But my relationship is actually real.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Sure.
I see Nadia isn't the only one
living a lie.
It's on the house.
Your hands are freezing.
It's OK. It's no big deal.
You didn't see your face.
Ander...
Please don't say it's no big deal.
It is.
Chemo's fucking me up...
and I'm scared.
And so are you.
Maybe we should stop acting
like it's no big deal.
Lucrecia, do you have a minute?
It's about Columbia.
Take a seat.
I wanted to tell you that both of you got
the highest possible grade.
We have to ask you to make one last effort
so the jury can make a decision.
Next Wednesday,
you'll need to do an oral presentation
that goes into more detail
on the last topic you addressed.
So? Pretty, huh?
Hey! Wow!
It's the chemo.
I have cancer.
I'm sure you have lots of questions,
but that's what Wikipedia's for.
I get tired real quick.
I hated him.
I blamed him for my illness.
The champagne bottle broke.
The neck fell by the bathroom,
and I went to pick it up to throw it out.
Polo was there.
What are you talking about?
I couldn't hold back.
I stabbed him in the heart with the glass.
You're nuts. Why would you confess?
What's it matter?
I'm almost dead.
I won't let you destroy yourself
to protect someone.
How long has he been sick?
For months.
I found out recently, too.
What do the doctors say?
Not much.
His chemo's almost over,
and we'll see after that.
But he'll make it, right?
Of course he will.
It's Ander.
He doesn't deserve this.
Not everyone gets what they deserve.
You knew, right?
Do you think I didn't want to tell you?
That I wanted to deal with this alone?
-So why didn't you?
-Ander asked me to keep it a secret.
And I thought, what was the point
of telling you?
You'd cure him?
Besides...
sometimes, the truth is...
useless.
Forgive me.
And thanks... for everything.
You're the best thing I've got, Samu.
And the only--
-Don't talk nonsense.
-No, I really mean it.
We've turned your house into a lab,
and you just grin and bear it.
As soon as this batch is done,
I promise you it'll be over.
We'll close the business.
Then you and I will have
a very boring life.
I'd really like that.
We just found out.
What a bummer.
He's tired of hiding it.
It's taking longer than we expected.
And how are you doing?
Never mind me. What matters now is him.
I try to get him to go out, have fun,
forget everything, but...
He's very lucky to have you by his side,
you know?
If you only knew.
I know.
A word of advice.
If you want to keep your romance a secret,
you should be more discreet.
But relax, I won't say a word.
There's no secret romance, damn it.
He's my sister's boyfriend.
Yeah... Heavy, huh?
Look, being cheated on
makes us... stronger.
See it that way.
I know because my boyfriend
cheated on me with your sister.
-When are you going to tell her?
-Never.
Nadia can't leave Malick.
-Why?
-She needs him to go to New York.
He'll be there next year too.
That's why my dad let her apply
for the grant.
If she found out he's using her
as a beard, she'd scrap the whole thing.
-The contract has arrived.
-Has it?
When will it be signed?
It's with the lawyers now.
It will take a few days.
The only thing is...
there's a clause
that allows Yeray to withdraw the funding
-at any time during the first five years.
-What?
He'll be pulling our strings
the entire time.
Five years?
-I'm going to tell that bastard off.
-No.
You won't say a word.
Now more than ever.
WE HAVE TO CELEBRATE TONIGHT, RIGHT?
Have fun.
Hi. I'm looking for--
this book.
Sorry, I've got it.
Nadia... you know it's essential
for the presentation,
and it's not online.
Well, I've got it.
I need to ask you a question.
If you knew someone was being cheated on,
would you tell them?
I'm sorry.
I never apologized to you
for what happened.
Why now?
Because... you never know
how much time we have left in this world.
And now that...
I'm starting something serious
with someone,
I understand you better than ever.
I always thought
you were cold and heartless...
until I helped break your heart
into a thousand pieces.
I'm really sorry, Lu.
I'm done with the book.
-What's up?
-Nothing.
Is that what you wanted to talk about?
Or is someone else cheating?
No, no one.
Forget about it.
How are you?
Fine.
So...
are you training hard?
With the punching bag?
Do we have to speak in Morse code?
You've got to be kidding me.
You need to be careful here, honey.
You should've taken your own advice.
I don't trust a soul.
What a sad life.
I don't want that for myself.
-Well, it's the one you're leading now.
-Yeah.
Until I get the money I need
to pay off the school.
Then, to hell with it.
You'll always need more.
Or do you think
once you've tasted seafood,
you can go back to eating canned sardines?
You should fucking know by now,
every shrimp I'll eat
will be paid for with my own work.
No hustling and no scumbags.
I'm done.
You can see the scumbags coming
a mile away.
It's the good guys,
the ones who look like angels...
Those are the ones
you have to look out for.
What the fuck's that mean?
What I mean...
is that our living room was bugged.
And all the “scumbags”
were taken down to the police station
or are sitting in jail.
All except one.
The little angel.
No... Samu would never do that to me.
-How do you know?
-Because he loves me.
Do you know what that means?
What if you could make sure?
Samu, I need to find out
who stabbed us in the back.
You can't imagine how badly I need that.
Didn't we want a boring life
with no trouble?
Are you with me or not?
The snitch must've been recorded
by the security cameras.
We had them everywhere,
but they were taken away.
The security company
might have a copy of everything.
But my mom doesn't know
which company we had.
The police seized everything.
Contracts, invoices...
Two months ago,
a camera broke, and I kept it.
It should have a sticker
with the company's details.
Why would they give you a copy?
Because everyone has a price.
Look over there.
It's here.
Fuck, there's nothing on it.
You could try calling
all the security companies in the country
to see if you were clients.
But I think that's confidential.
I don't know. It's your call.
Wait a minute...
Maybe I don't have to.
Why are you here?
I came to...
see if I could do anything for you.
If you need money...
I could get the best doctors.
Which country do you think we live in?
I already have the best doctors...
and I don't need to be rich
or a charity case to get them.
Money's your answer to everything, huh?
I just want to help.
But I don't know how.
Do you have plans?
I'm bored out of my skull.
How much chemo's left?
I don't know.
The last session is next week.
Then I'll get the results,
and they'll tell me if I'm done.
Right.
Are you really fucked up after?
Omar says I look like the girl
from The Exorcist.
How's it going with him?
This whole thing's a bummer.
Awful timing.
Well...
bad times are great for finding out
who'll stick with you.
Do you mean Cayetana?
And Valerio.
-You're cheating on her with Valerio?
-No! No cheating.
I swear.
But...
Well, the three of us are together.
Fuck.
You're getting laid more than anyone.
But it's not just about fucking.
There's something else.
I think it's going well.
I guess it's not very normal...
but... who cares about being normal...
if you can be happy.
Shit... You got all Zen,
and you're not even high.
Let me try that.
Just a little.
How does it work?
Badly. At first, it's always bad.
Holy fuck.
It's strong.
Do you like sushi?
I'm not hungry.
No.
I was thinking
we could go on vacation to Japan.
A lot could happen between now and then.
Are you upset because of that kid
in your class?
I see.
I bought you something.
Stay the night.
Tonight and as many nights as you want.
Look at his eyes...
I love you guys a lot.
Seriously, I love you so much.
So, let's see...
You told Ander that we're together,
the three of us?
Correct.
Right... And if he tells someone,
what do we do?
It's no big deal.
We've all been called worse.
It felt good, saying it out loud.
That we're together.
Why should we stop...
when we're just getting started?
Why don't you come to London?
Huh, Curly Locks?
My mothers will be asking
a couple of favors already.
But they can ask for three.
One, two...
and three.
How will you convince them?
I don't know.
Right.
I know a girl who's very good
at making up crazy stories.
To be honest, it's kind of my superpower.
Is it?
What if you show me more
of that superpower?
Like this?
I just can't resist...
Let's all go into the pool!
What is he doing?
-Come on, guys!
-OK!
-In the pool!
-Let's go!
Should we do it in the water? Huh?
-Wow!
Stop!
Look, a full moon!
What's all this?
Can I ask what you're doing?
Hi, Moms!
What's up? Back already?
What's wrong?
How are you?
-I think we know each other.
-Too well.
I've seen far too much of you.
This isn't what it looks like.
We were studying outside, and...
we just felt like--
-Shut up!
-OK, I'm leaving.
It's not that big of a deal.
Having an orgy at home?
Well... just three of us.
-That's not... an orgy, technically.
-Mom.
It's not just sex.
What?
We're dating. The three of us.
How can you be with two people
at the same time?
-Why not?
-What do you mean why not?
Have you ever seen that?
Do you think it's normal?
Didn't your parents say that
when you said you liked girls?
That's enough, Polo!
It's always a struggle with you.
Don't we have enough problems already?
And now this?
Hey.
Hi.
It suits you.
Listen, if you need anything,
anything at all...
I won't shave my hair off
for moral support, but anything else...
Thanks.
I'm fed up with all the sad looks.
I don't know what's worse, chemo or pity.
Pity, for sure.
But it's not all bad.
Cancer has an upside too.
Really? Like what?
Well... I don't know.
I used to feel overwhelmed with life.
My future, my parents on top of me...
We think so much about the future,
we forget about the present.
I only do what I want now...
and I like it.
Sorry.
Another side effect
is that I talk like a Buddhist master.
As if I had an MA in philosophy
and not a tumor.
I don't know about a master's,
but you're right.
SORRY ABOUT THE OTHER NIGHT.
CAN WE MEET?
Good morning.
Hey.
Are you OK?
Yeah, sure.
Just a bit nervous about the exams.
Do you maybe want...
to study with me tonight?
I'm going to the club.
-Who with?
-Friends...
from class.
How's it going?
Fine.
Yeah?
Later.
See?
Told you, kiddo. Everyone has a price.
Some are cheaper than others.
I'll get the hard drive tonight.
You don't even know the guy.
That's why I'm meeting him at the club.
The blackout party.
You can do anything in the dark.
Anything?
-Except crochet.
-I'm going with you, just in case.
OK, Dad.
Rebe, what would you do if you knew
Samu was cheating on you?
-What?
-Where'd that come from?
I don't know. Intuition.
The only way to be sure
is to catch him red-handed.
You're nuts.
What's wrong?
Is it because of last night?
No.
Well... maybe they're right.
I've been a problem my whole life.
That's my superpower.
We'll see...
Polo's mothers might be lesbians,
but they're older.
OK?
They don't get it.
I don't get it either, to be honest.
I'm not going to pretend
I'm modern, but...
girls don't dream of having
a white wedding with two grooms, you know?
It's not what we were taught.
I used to think...
that people were like halves
trying to make a whole.
Or like nuts and bolts.
All you had to do was find
the one that...
fit you perfectly.
But Polo and I didn't fit together before.
Then you showed up...
and now we fit together.
You're the piece that we were missing.
And, hell...
when you find love,
it sucks to have to let it go.
Guzmán, are you coming?
Omar wants me to go
so that I'm not alone all day.
What about your friend Polo?
I saw you last night.
You were having a blast.
Is that it?
We forget and just carry on
like nothing ever happened?
Maybe that's the problem.
I forgave you too soon.
The champagne bottle broke.
The neck fell by the bathroom,
and I went to pick it up.
And then?
Someone beat me to it.
Who?
Guzmán.
He picked it up
and went into the bathroom.
Did you see him yourself?
Guzmán?
Is that Yeray?
Yes.
Aren't you answering?
No. I'm breaking up with him after dinner.
What happened?
-Carla...
-What happened?
You want to know?
What we've been hiding from you for weeks?
Dad's practically been pimping me out
so that Yeray saves the winery.
It's the only reason I'm with him.
I don't love him and I never fucking will!
You knew?
You agreed to it?
Don't make the same mistake I made.
I also met a Yeray...
but I chose someone I loved.
And look at us now.
People outside our social status...
think we've made no sacrifices
to get here.
But they don't know
we're capable of doing whatever it takes
to avoid losing it.
Whatever it takes.
Learning to love that boy
is easier than learning to live
with nothing.
Think about your future, honey.
About our future.
You're crazy, Valerio!
We can't deal at the club!
Remember when my mom
sold on someone else's turf?
We're not making enough at school.
Enough for what?
Life doesn't end when we graduate.
That's when it starts.
What the hell do you need that money for?
I need thousands of euros
within a month,
before the enrollment deadline
for good universities is up.
You too, right?
Or will you go back to public education?
What's up? We going?
Of course!
You see him?
No.
But there's still time until the blackout.
Why don't I talk to him?
I don't trust him.
Relax, Mike Tyson.
I'm the one who taught you how to box.
Be right back.
Your water, sir.
Easy. It's strong.
Why the fuck am I here?
You're having fun like everyone else.
Come on, loosen up.
Guzmán.
Are you not coming to the hospital
on Monday?
You have another pal to go with you.
Resentment is a luxury I can't afford.
Because I don't know
how much longer I have.
If it's only months,
you'd rather not see me again?
If you'd known how long Marina had left,
wouldn't you have forgotten
everything that annoyed you about her
to be by her side?
They say the key to success
is turning your hobby into a job,
so, congrats.
It's a job... and also a secret.
Can you keep it?
I can make it worth the effort.
Wrong person. That's not my thing.
And what is your thing?
What do you need?
I just need to fall in love.
Boom! I have just the thing for that.
This is... happiness...
and love.
How are you?
It's fine, go home. Don't stay for me.
Will you be up when I get home?
I can't dance, let alone fuck.
That's not what I meant, but it's OK.
It's not OK.
We should admit that, too.
Listen...
I don't care if you see other people.
Why are you saying that?
It's not normal...
but I want you to be happy.
You're bitter because of me.
You think I like that?
No... I don't understand, Ander.
It's fine, forget it.
Watch this for me.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Omar, throw this in the trash
without being seen.
-What?
-Trust me.
Go, damn it!
OK.
What's up?
I just...
I just remembered
that I lost your toothbrush.
Can you buy me a new one?
Of course.
No... Buy me thousands...
Millions of toothbrushes!
Sorry. The bathroom was as crowded
as the Tokyo metro.
-Another drink?
-Yes.
Shit.
-What's wrong?
-Where's my bag?
Shit!
Fucking hell!
I'm sorry, Rebe.
The one fucking favor I ask you!
Take this.
Do you want me?
What?
Do you want to fuck?
What about Ander?
Ander's not here.
Right on time.
Nadia!
Hi! Over here!
What're you doing here?
Great hair!
Shouldn't you be preparing
a presentation?
I should be, but I couldn't concentrate.
What about you?
Want a sip?
No.
Me? Same as always,
I just needed... to relax.
-You do seem a little tense.
-No!
Have you seen Malick?
Yes! He's downstairs...
dancing with the plebes.
-Thanks.
-Yup.
So nice to see you!
I thought you'd miss the blackout!
-How come you look so happy?
-Well...
I'm about to have enough cash
to apply to a university in London!
What?
It's amazing what my family will do
to keep me as far away as possible.
You're coming with us? Yeah!
-Really? Awesome!
-That's great!
I couldn't let you get away.
Where were you?
I was looking for you!
Here.
Weren't you staying in?
Malick, is there anything I should know?
Is there another girl?
No! What're you talking about?
So we're good?
Of course.
I was going to tell you tomorrow,
my parents are coming.
They want to meet you.
-Why don't we go home now?
-No, wait.
It's time for the blackout.
So what?
...nine, eight, seven...
Samu, do you love me?
What?
...four, three, two...
Do you love me?
Of course I do.
I love you!
I love you too!
I had to make sure.
What's this?
It's called fluorescent paint.
My bag was soaked in it.
What's that?
Nadia!
The security cameras didn't work.
That kid wasn't a security guard,
and the hard drive was empty.
-Rebeka, listen to me, please.
-No, you listen to me!
Tell me one thing...
-Did you get close to me just for that?
-No.
Was it all a lie?
Hey.
I'm sorry.
You knew. Why didn't you tell me?
Because I didn't want to give you
an excuse to leave the competition,
just when I'm about to win.
Do you think I'll go with him
to New York?
Listen... with a bit of luck...
you'll have guys coming
in and out of your life.
But an opportunity like this
only comes along once.
Plus, he used you.
Basically, you should use him too.
What he did hurts a lot.
Yeah, I know.
You had this idea of building
something amazing with him
and living happily ever after, but no.
And we both know he's not the boy
you're really in love with.
Nadia.
Speak of the devil...
I'll meet your parents...
but I can't promise
I'll be as good at lying...
cheating, and pretending
that I have feelings for someone.
This is taking too long.
What'd you say?
You did the right thing.
Hey...
You did what you had to do.
Subtitle translation by Toni Navarro