OF COURSE I KILLED MARINA.
DID YOU STILL DOUBT IT?
SHE WAS STILL ALIVE WHEN I LEFT.
POOR THING. I SHOULD'VE HIT HER HARDER.
"She was still alive when I left.
Poor thing.
I should've hit her harder."
This is a crime. It's harassment.
What if I told my parents
to pay for a study program?
Would you still think it's a crime?
-What are you trying to achieve?
-We want him out.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO KILL HER.
I HAD NOTHING AGAINST MARINA.
IT COULD'VE BEEN YOU.
Hey...
You OK?
Leave me alone.
-Polo.
-Hey.
-What the hell are you doing?
-He needs to be alone, okay?
And I need you to leave me alone.
-He's got the balls to come here?
-Forget him, please, Valerio.
OK? It's not worth it.
Polo, honey. What happened? You're early.
We have an exam first thing tomorrow,
and I have a lot to study.
What exam?
-It's...
-Polo.
The principal called this morning.
She told us about the Twitter account.
Why didn't you tell us?
So you won't look at me like they do.
They deactivated the account.
Yes, Mom, one account's
been deactivated. One!
As if that would do anything.
I don't want to go back.
Seriously.
You'd be proving them right.
You have to be stronger.
Be a man, son.
You know what I mean.
Well...
if it isn't Las Encinas' own Bill Gates.
How about skipping practice
and studying together?
Hey, I'm talking to you, partner.
OK. My place in an hour?
OK.
Ciao.
Thanks for the lift.
I just want to meet your parents.
Fine...
But hopefully in this lifetime.
Hi, Mom.
What's up?
Are you OK?
Is Dad all right?
I found this university brochure
with your things this morning.
Dad...
Dad.
Look, Dad...
This program is a great opportunity.
My only opportunity...
What other options do I have?
All alone there?
You're just a girl.
She wouldn't be all alone.
-Peace be upon you.
-And peace be upon you, too.
-I'm Malick, Nadia's friend.
-What are you doing?
Next year,
I'll be studying in New York too,
and... I'd be happy to take care of her.
My dad studied at that university
and speaks highly of it.
After that, he diversified
his grandfather's gold mine business.
Now he has
the biggest telecommunications company
in Africa.
It's a huge opportunity.
Why didn't you tell us about him?
I actually wanted to come here myself...
and...
ask permission to take Nadia
to the Madrid mosque.
I go every week,
and it's a pity she can't go more often.
OK.
What happened?
Nothing bad.
Nothing bad?
Since when do you have good news?
Would you mind coming to the station
with me, please?
The prosecutor on your brother's case
seems willing to drop the charges.
He could come back... as a free man.
Your mother, too.
-They wouldn't have to hide anymore.
-What do you mean, "seems willing"?
He has... doubts, due to the lack
of evidence against Nano, but...
I believe we can convince him.
You "believe"?
We went to the same school.
He sat next to me.
-We've been friends ever since.
-Right...
That's how it works?
Sketchy deals among friends?
Power isn't fair... but for once,
you can use it in your favor.
We only ask one thing of you...
We've been monitoring
Sandra López Gallego for a while,
your friend's mother.
We know you've run some errands for her,
but that's no use to us at all.
We need evidence.
We need someone who can enter
her house without arousing suspicion
to plant a small listening device.
I'm not doing it.
-If it's because of your friend--
-Her name is Rebeka.
Think about Nano...
your mother...
your family.
Think about it.
Are you OK, honey?
Yeah.
Tell me if you need anything.
I ONLY USED MY GIRLFRIEND
SO I COULD FUCK CHRISTIAN.
YES, MURDERERS HAVE A HEART TOO.
Another tweet.
Your friends are really something.
Samuel isn't a bad person.
-And neither is Guzmán.
-Right.
He can't be if you went out with him.
You know...
he's like you, but Christian.
You think you're knights in shining armor
who have to save me.
I don't need to be taken care of.
Excuse me?
I wasn't planning to.
Oh, please...
It's true I'll be in New York
next year and everything,
but... you don't have to see me
if you don't want.
I only said that to convince your dad.
Okay...
So much for Allah's perfect son!
You lied to my family?
Thanks to that, you'll follow your dreams,
and they won't worry about it.
It's not so sinful, is it?
So... you decide
what's sinful and what isn't.
I take certain liberties.
I stray a little
to come back with more gusto.
What liberties?
If you want to know,
come to the Silicon Valley party.
No. My parent's won't let me go to clubs.
They will
if you're with Allah's perfect son.
-Where the hell were you?
-Fuck!
-Sorry, my phone died.
-Really?
Well, you read the messages I sent you.
Look, Samu... I don't know what's wrong,
but I can guess.
I wasn't born yesterday.
If you want to be a marquis,
tell me to fuck off and stop wasting time.
You met up with her again.
-I was at the police station.
-No way.
Yeah, about my brother. Same old shit.
Sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm losing it.
I feel insecure around you
for some reason.
Me, who would've guessed?
What can I do to fix it?
I don't know...
You could come and stick your tongue
down my throat, for example.
Let's hit the books.
Were you serious about studying?
-Sure.
-Since when do you want to study?
Since I don't want to end up like my mom,
up to her eyes in shit.
That can't end well.
So...
responding to messages again?
-It's Omar.
-What's going on?
Well, well...
What're we celebrating here?
It's a private party, freak.
This have anything to do
with those messages?
-Don't you have a line of coke to snort?
-Is that an invitation? I love it.
An invitation to leave.
This is my house too,
just so you all know, OK?
We just want to talk privately
for a moment.
OK.
-Have a drink. Make yourself at home.
-Thanks.
Can we finally end this fucking charade?
You need to stop this.
We owe it to Marina.
That's not true.
You're thinking of yourselves, not her,
because you need revenge.
No, we don't need revenge.
But we won't let a murderer
just go on with his life.
Life is too short, you know.
-It's not worth wasting.
-What the fuck do you know about life?
-Why do you keep protecting him?
-Because Polo...
tried to kill himself.
Holy shit, Las Encinas...
I told him I'd tell on him...
if he didn't turn himself in...
and he almost killed himself.
Are you saying this to get me
to forgive him or forgive you?
-Guzmán.
-Listen to me...
He deserves everything
that's happening to him.
I hope one day you get
what you deserve too.
Are we done?
There'll be a photo-call, over 100 guests,
and the best catering in Madrid...
It's not every day
your company goes public, is it?
What color will you wear?
Why?
-Are you buying a tie to match?
-No.
A car.
Is that all I am to you?
An accessory that matches your new car?
You know...
those movies where the fat kid
with the sweaty hands
never gets invited to the party...
or to anything really?
Well, that's me.
Used to be me.
And now... it's my party.
I decide who's invited or not...
and I'm taking
the most wonderful girl in the world.
I just want everything to be perfect.
You're the centerpiece of it all,
so all the accessories have to match you.
Tell me what you want...
anything...
and it's yours.
Yeray, what I don't have can't be bought
with money.
Well...
-Thanks for driving me home.
-That's OK.
Good night.
Wait!
What time should I pick you up tomorrow?
Yeray, I don't know
if I can go after all.
Why not? I mean...
Who's that?
My dad.
-Good evening, sir.
-Good evening.
I'm Yeray.
-Carla's classmate.
-I know who you are.
I saw you in the latest issue
of Forbes. Impressive!
Congratulations on your IPO.
We're throwing a party tomorrow.
I was just telling Carla...
Hey... why don't you and your wife
come with her?
Of course.
We'd be delighted.
We'll be there.
Pleased to meet you.
What's the uniform for?
You have chemo today.
I'm not going.
What?
I'm not doing chemo.
Not worth it. You saw the chances.
Ander, we talked about this.
I know we did...
but I'm fed up...
with this "strong and optimistic" crap.
All this "fight until the end,
keep smiling" stuff.
Imagine the fucking pressure.
I'm not well.
I don't have the strength.
Don't make me feel bad about that too.
-I just want to be by your side.
-I want you by my side too.
But with my decisions, not yours.
Look, Polo isn't here.
...of the collective unconscious.
Maybe something happened to him.
-I wish.
-What could've happened?
He's scared shitless, that's all.
Samu.
I thought up our next tweet.
We'll let everyone know
that Polo attempted suicide.
-Guzmán, man...
-What?
It's his sister, Samuel.
I don't know what I'd do
if anyone touched my family.
What if we wait a little?
-Maybe this was enough.
-Why do you think that?
Guzmán, Samuel, are you following me?
Come on.
Let's say heroism is a choice.
Polo, you have a visitor. Cayetana.
Nothing. You should go.
OK... Just let me try something.
What are you doing?
Please... just let me.
Polo, it's me.
Polo...
Go to school, go on.
Andrea...
let's let them talk, OK?
We'll be in the living room
if you need anything.
OK, thanks.
Thank you.
-Let's forget about Polo, okay?
-A bottle of champagne, please.
-Don't let that come between us.
-Just get away from me, OK?
Here you are, guys.
Hello, sweetheart!
Where's Mom?
In bed with a stomachache.
Go get changed.
I want to be early.
-I'm not going.
-What?
Why not?
Why should I?
I'm not going to embarrass myself
looking for investors
to save the wineries.
Know what Yeray ordered to drink
with dinner?
Coca-Cola.
He has no clue about wine,
nor does he want to.
I don't know. I mean...
he seemed... very interested.
I'm not going to play along with you.
-Carla...
-I'd rather stay in and look after Mom.
-I'm trying to look after her too.
-Really?
Yes. She's not ill.
She's devastated.
She just found out
we're on the verge of bankruptcy.
So...
if you want to take care of her...
you know what to do.
Well, well...
Don't you look elegant.
Come here. Give me a kiss.
Hey, I'm glad you're okay.
You had us fucking scared.
You almost got me killed.
Is this how you talk
to your future mother-in-law?
We're off to a bad start.
You're playing with fire.
The thugs, the police...
Why don't you stop?
Samuel... you're a good kid.
Thanks.
That's not a compliment.
Tell me, where has that gotten you?
You live in a dump,
you work for a pittance,
and let's not even mention your brother.
So I should become an asshole?
You need to do what's best
for you and your family.
And if others get hurt along the way...
Tough shit.
And if that makes me an asshole...
so be it.
As for you, you'll see.
So, where's being a good kid gotten you?
Yeray... Congratulations!
Wow.
I wasn't expecting to see you.
Carla convinced me.
She really wanted to come.
Well... that's not what she told me.
Well, excuse her.
I don't know where her head is lately.
Why don't you come by the winery one day,
and we'll make it up to you?
You might be interested.
We're looking for investors.
I'd like to tell you all about it.
Sure.
I'm sorry, but they're waiting for me.
-Enjoy the party.
-OK.
Yeray.
You know the only good thing
about being poor?
People approach you for who you really are
and not for your money.
-Yeray--
-Just in case it happens to you.
I guess the family wine business
isn't going so well?
It's true.
Your money made me change my mind.
-How romantic.
-But you know why?
You made it all by yourself.
No help, no cheating.
No desperate parents asking for favors
and making a fool of you at a party.
Yeah...
What do you like most about me?
My face?
My body?
My last name?
I can't take credit for any of it.
But everything you have,
you earned yourself.
Now, that's sexy.
Hey. Everything OK?
All good.
Holy shit.
Is this a club or a retirement home?
I'm running to the bathroom for a sec.
-How are you?
-Fine.
-I'm sorry.
-What?
When you saved Polo's ass,
I thought you were a coward.
But, no, you were brave.
You did what you had to
to protect your family...
even if you had to pay a very high price.
I get it now.
I didn't sacrifice much.
You lost Lu...
you lost Guzmán, and you lost me.
I knew you for like five minutes.
In five months, you'll be gone,
and in five years,
I won't even remember your name.
Samu.
Damn. What's with the long faces?
What do you say we have a drink now, guys?
No fucking way.
Motherfucker.
-So much for "maybe that's enough," huh?
-Come on, guys.
Now it's time to go over to that bar
and get that drink.
Come on, let's move.
Let's calm down. It's all right.
Testing. Can you hear me?
Good evening, everyone. Thanks for coming.
It all started with an app
that's so great for finding a partner,
that none of our users last
more than five minutes.
-I know that was a bad joke...
-Hey, I'm with you.
So, it all started as a dating app...
and now... it's much more than that.
You're too nice for your own good.
And I'm an idiot for listening to you.
People here do whatever they want, Samu.
Fucking bullshit.
They want a comprehensive experience,
they want to meet partners...
-Guzmán!
-I'm going to the bathroom.
...they want investors,
even travel companions.
Our VIPs...
You're right.
Where the hell are you going?
Ready?
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five, four,
three, two, one...
I want a gin and tonic. What about you?
You drink alcohol?
Don't tell your father... or mine.
OK. So are these your liberties?
Imagine you could choose
three wild cards for tonight.
I've already chosen one: alcohol.
And you?
-Seriously?
-Seriously.
No need to be Allah's perfect children.
Sometimes it's enough
to be a good child... and you are.
Has anyone come up to you?
-If we leave, they win.
-And what do we gain?
What do we gain by staying here?
Being looked at like zoo animals?
How are you two doing?
He brought it on himself.
Polo wanted to die.
No, that's not true.
-Please.
-No.
I'm begging you.
Don't tell anyone what happened. Please.
What do you want, Valerio?
Who sent you? Guzmán or Samuel?
What're you talking about? No one.
It's not like that.
I'm not one for obeying orders,
and I don't like bullies either.
-Fine.
-I don't like how they look at you.
Why's that?
I was looked at like that
my whole life.
You don't have to hang out with us
out of pity.
Who said pity?
I'm here because... you guys
are the most interesting couple here.
-Sure.
-Who?
I mean... you're talking about us?
Yes, Polo.
And yes, I know everything.
Your threesome with Christian...
which also really turned me on.
Do you know why?
Because you're different.
And you, young lady...
A top fraudster who fooled us for months.
-Give her a big hand!
-No need, thanks.
You are...
Wow!
You are fascinating.
Much more so than when you were
just another dull rich girl.
OK, Valerio,
but... I'm not as fascinating as you.
I mean... you've snorted
your family's entire fortune.
Exactly!
Absolutely right.
How do you see it?
I think it's crystal clear.
We're unique.
Let's drink to that. Cheers.
I know how I want to spend my...
-my next wild card.
-Oh, really?
Surprise me.
I want to kiss you.
-No.
-No?
No problem.
I'm going to kiss you.
Damn! What a twist!
Forget it. Samuel isn't answering.
It's not...
What if we look for him
and throw our own party?
Hello?
No... I don't think so.
Guzmán.
-Go home.
-He should go.
Come on.
Excuse me. Do I know you?
Are we friends? I don't think so.
Then get out of my sight.
Get lost!
-Why don't you leave him alone?
-Shit, man... I don't feel sorry for him.
He's sick, for fuck's sake!
What do you mean, "sick"?
What did you say, Omar?
What's he got?
So you kept quiet about that too?
You told him?
-Sorry, Ander, I had to--
-I told you not to tell anyone!
It's my business!
What did I do
to deserve to be out of the loop?
Nothing.
You didn't do anything wrong.
In fact, you were right.
I kept Polo's secret,
and it's eating me up inside.
No way!
What?
That's why you don't want to do chemo?
You're not doing chemo?
Get out, Omar.
-Excuse me?
-Go away!
Ander.
Why don't you want the chemo?
Do you want to die?
You'll go to the hospital
even if I have to drag you.
Whatever you might have done
has nothing to do with it.
Nobody deserves that.
Excuse me. A gin and tonic, please?
What's this?
You didn't even take it off
to shower.
It's my wild card.
Your what?
Better you explain it to him.
This is my brother, Omar.
Malick, a friend.
I told Nadia that...
it's good to take a break from the rules
so you don't explode one day
and say, "To hell with it all."
Maybe that's the secret
to not ending up like me.
Omar exploded
and said, "To hell with it all."
He left home.
Why?
I don't get along with my father.
And he can't handle
having a queer son.
-I didn't know you were...
-Queer?
Yeah... I'm queer.
Any problem?
-No, of course not.
-Right.
Too much of a wild card for you, Malick?
Anyway, I have work to do.
I'm going back in.
Let's have one last drink.
-The last one?
-Yes, the last one.
-All right. The last one.
-OK?
-OK. Champagne. My favorite.
-Last one.
-Bartender! Bring one here.
-OK.
Last one.
Well...
-Do you like him?
-No.
-No, what?
-Easy.
I'm just... glad someone
can bear to talk to me.
-Finally.
-It's fine if you like him.
I wouldn't mind if...
-I wouldn't mind...
-OK.
-...trying...
-Shut up.
Excuse me. I hate to interrupt,
but you're looking a bit shy.
-What's up?
-He does.
One last dance?
-Not me.
-The last one, come on!
But you guys go ahead.
Why do you care what they think?
I mean, Polo, you're not
what they think you are.
So now...
you're going to have fun
and have one last dance with us.
Last dance. Come on!
There's a new tweet.
STOP STARING AT ME.
BEING A MURDERER ISN'T EASY.
I EVEN TRIED TO KILL MYSELF.
Polo.
-Guzmán.
-It wasn't me.
Who did it, then?
What do you want?
You have a thing for going missing,
don't you?
Samuel...
-You don't want to be with me.
-It's not that.
I was overwhelmed by the situation,
that’s all.
I'm sorry.
Shit.
I thought I'd bagged
the one good guy in the class.
I'm really sorry.
Can I stay over tonight?
Fine.
As long as we don't sleep.
Come on, let's go.
-I'm going to the kitchen to get a drink.
-OK. There's water in the fridge.
Polo.
We read that stuff...
on Twitter... about...
I'm sorry.
No... We're sorry.
We shouldn't have forced you
to go to school. You were right.
We'll do whatever you say.
Whatever you want.
All I want is to disappear.
Get away from here.
OK, then...
We'll look for a new school abroad.
We have friends in London.
You can finish the school year there,
if you want.
Yes.
You're leaving?
Thank you.
A lot.
Hey.
You're all set?
What're you doing here?
Nothing. I like hospital coffee.
It's with milk.
Thanks.
-Hey!
-What are you doing here?
You wanted to get rid of me?
You just fucked that up!
What the hell?
I want to leave, too.
I want out. I was going to leave!
But now I can’t get admitted anywhere.
You used a new account
to forward the tweets to every school.
-No one wants to be involved with--
-A murderer.
With all this fucking shit.
Happy?
No.
We didn't do it.
-You didn't?
-No.
Then who did?
Who?
FORENSICS
Cayetana...
Your turn.
YOU ARE THE OPPOSITE OF A MURDERER.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
Come with me.
SETTINGS &gt; PROFILE &gt; USER
DELETE ACCOUNT
CONFIRM DELETION: YES
ACCOUNT DELETED
Subtitle translation by Toni Navarro