Good morning.
Would you like some coffee, tea?
Some toast with ham and tomato?
No? Nothing?
Of course not. You're on duty.
I hadn't noticed.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
What are you looking at? Want a picture?
It's not like it's the first time
someone's been arrested here.
She's right.
Before, we just had a murderer
and a wannabe con artist.
Now that the narco has been arrested,
Las Encinas looks like Guantanamo.
Shall we go to class?
Look at you two together.
Are you friends again?
Step by step.
Sure.
I don't get what's going on
at this fucking school, really.
Ready for Valentine's Day?
There'll be flowers, the best restaurant,
-a few surprises...
-Please.
Actually, we always celebrate
at Lu's, right?
-Yes.
-I don't.
I was never asked,
-not for Valentine's or anything else.
-Yeah.
As for me, I don't feel like it this year.
I don't want to throw a party
because I'm crazy busy with exams
and the Columbia program, so...
Is that why?
Or because you ended up alone?
What did my mom say?
The usual stuff:
"How are you? How was school?
Is your mom some mobster drug dealer?"
What if she was?
Was it my fault that my dad
went to jail?
Can we help you?
Well...
would you lend me some cash?
For the bus, the 314.
I take it to visit my mother in jail.
For fuck's sake. Here.
Take a taxi.
-Hey, Lu.
-What?
It's not my business,
but the whole party thing...
It's because you don't have
the money to host it, right?
Right, it's not your business...
darling.
Okay.
Fuck.
We even have an audience.
They have everything here.
Spoiler alert.
You won't be winning Mother of the Year.
Hey. This is just a bump in the road.
It's nothing we can't handle.
We always hang in there.
"We"? Don't kid yourself.
There's no "we" here.
Baby, you're pissed off, I get it.
I'm telling you,
I'll be out before you know it.
Sure... What the hell will I live on
until then?
Never mind.
I'll have to break the piggy bank.
Rebe...
Fight.
Don't let them win.
Keep boxing.
You're letting yourself go.
I know Valentine's Day
is a Christian thing...
but it's just dinner.
I told you I can't.
Besides, it's my mother's birthday.
I see.
But thanks for the invitation.
Honey...
Go! It's OK.
Mom.
Would you like to celebrate with us?
It's a Michelin-star restaurant.
Thanks, son, but...
it's a little out of our price range.
It's on the house.
The owners are friends of my father's.
Mom, you deserve it.
Bring whoever you want.
Omar will come, too, right?
Omar will always have a place
at our table...
but he won't take it.
Thank you for the invitation.
We will go with you.
When do I get what you promised me?
It's not easy. We need time.
What do you mean?
If it isn't the Queen of the South!
What a surprise. Come in, please.
Be careful, a horse's head
could turn up in your bed.
-Come on in.
-Sure.
-What are you doing here?
-What about you?
I've been calling you.
Who were you talking to?
The phone company. The bastards kept me
on hold for half an hour.
I didn't realize it
with all the commotion, but...
I can't go back home.
Can I crash here?
Yes.
Thanks, Samu.
You're the only one I have left.
It's no problem.
But only because
you're my only option.
This Valentine's Day will be different.
I'll be planning it.
-"Reverse Valentine's"?
-That's right.
Come on, seriously. It's so archaic,
boring, cheesy...
Flowers, chocolate, colors...
And we girls act like fucking objects,
spending hours at the hairdresser's
to look pretty for them.
It's over.
I had this great idea
that it should be the other way around.
Let the boys show some...
skin.
The girls will get dressed up
in elegant tuxedos--
Smoking jackets, to be clear.
We have to bring our own drinks?
Yes, everything's reversed.
The guests bring their alcohol
and their food,
and I, the hostess and queen of the night,
will just enjoy it.
That way, the lowlifes
won't think it's an NGO
and take everything home.
Clever...
Whatever, we'll have our own party.
Don't mind her.
You guys coming to the party?
-No, they're not.
-Is the party at your house now?
No, and you got kicked out of yours.
For using, I guess.
Since when do you have something
against drugs, Guzmán?
Remember, you used to beg me for them.
I have something against traitors...
and murderers.
Why are you defending them?
-I don't need to explain myself to you.
-Enough, Valerio, please.
What do you say, Lu?
-You mean me?
-Yes.
What a dilemma. I'm like Switzerland here.
A rich, beautiful country
that doesn't get involved
in anyone's wars.
-Lu.
-What do you want?
Can we talk for a sec?
Fine...
-but you'll need to get cleaned up first.
-What?
What the fuck, Lu?
You fucking ruined my life, asshole.
Lu, I just want to talk--
Come. You can't let them
exclude you like that.
What'll we get out of it?
A shitty night with everyone ignoring us?
You won't be alone. You'll be with me.
It won't do you any good.
Do you get that?
That's too bad.
I hate everything that's good for me.
I also hate vegetables, exercising,
I hate hanging out
with the right people...
and I hate doing what people expect of me.
Still...
it's absurd. We can't go
as a threesome to a Valentine's Day party.
Why not?
I like you both.
I don't know what they told you,
but the thing
between Carla, Christian, and me...
didn't end well.
Damn, Lu was right.
You have to turn all this around.
-Or maybe you guys don't like me...
-We do.
-I mean...
-We do?
But that's not the point, because...
this is just crazy, right?
A beautiful kind of crazy.
Come to the party with me.
Our lives are complicated enough.
Good work, Lu, as always.
Nadia...
you have two days to redo this.
You won't get into the program
if you don't.
I know you can do much better, OK?
-Nadia, are you all right?
-Yes.
The teacher must've used
all his red ink grading this.
At least he gave you a second chance.
I wish I could use it.
-What?
-I don't have time.
My parents go to rehabilitation every day.
I watch the store.
Just tell them you can't.
You should know I can't do that.
-How are you?
-Hi.
Guzmán, right?
-Yes.
-Malick.
Nice to meet you.
Nadia's told me a lot about you.
Really? She never mentioned you.
You don't talk that much lately, right?
Thanks for your concern. See you tomorrow.
Bye, man. Nice to meet you.
It's Mom's birthday.
-She'd be so happy if you came.
-And Dad?
He wants to see you, too.
Right.
When I tell him I'm with an atheist guy,
he'll have another stroke.
You don't need to say it.
Sorry, how's this your business?
Apart from paying for the meal and stuff.
He's my boyfriend.
Right, and he's my boyfriend.
I can't take him to dinner,
I can't talk about him,
I can't say I love him.
My happiness makes our parents unhappy.
Can you imagine what that's like?
No, right?
Have a nice day.
It would be after dinner.
Some music...
A quiet party, you know?
Lucrecia is organizing it.
Isn't she that friend of yours
who speaks Arabic?
Yusef, let's go to rehabilitation.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
Buying asparagus.
What's up, Malick?
Hi, Nadia, what's up?
Thought you'd be studying
after what the teacher said.
What did he say?
It's just that...
I haven't been able to spend much time
on the Columbia program.
Working here in the afternoons
doesn't leave me time...
for schoolwork.
I'm sorry, honey. What can I do?
I have nobody else.
It's OK, Dad.
I told you because you asked.
She's missing out
on a great opportunity,
-and you're doing nothing.
-Guzmán!
Are you telling me how to treat my family?
I clearly don't have to...
You've only driven away two kids.
-Are you here to insult me?
-I'm worried about Nadia.
Others aren't, so they keep quiet.
It's true what they say...
You don't respect anything.
Malick! Guzmán, go now.
If you're so clever...
-what do you suggest I do?
-Hire someone.
How did I not think of that?
Everything's easy if you have money.
If you care about her future,
you'll find a way.
Guzmán, please!
If you're so worried,
why don't you do it?
You want to help her, don't you?
Or is getting your hands dirty
beneath you?
Sure... Unpaid work, I suppose.
Three euros an hour.
People working in the fields earn less.
Deal.
You won't last one day.
Can you pass me an apron
or whatever you wear?
I'll never forgive you for this.
-I'm doing this for you.
-No, you're doing it for yourself,
out of pride.
SHANAA GROCERIES
Want to take a picture?
Get out of here.
I'm working here, dammit.
What the fuck!
Is this how you work?
Scaring away customers?
-I'm not a circus monkey.
-Circus monkey?
-Be careful.
-So... what else is there to do?
Finish cleaning
and organize the boxes inside.
Tomorrow, you'll do it all again.
And again and again...
Did you think one day would help Nadia?
You'd need to be here every day
until the end of the school year.
Bye.
Fuck!
It's not that I don’t even have the money
to buy you a beer.
The problem is I don't know
what I'll live on until she's out.
-That is, if she gets out.
-She will.
Maybe this will push her to stop.
You'd live a quieter life,
without thugs and the police.
I'll have to thank the snitch in the end.
I know there's a snitch in all this.
I'll have to go home
and break the piggy bank.
What?
My mother makes slits in an armchair
we have in the basement
so she can stash cash for emergencies.
The cops sealed off your house.
-What if you get caught?
-What'll they do? Huh?
I don't know,
and I don't want to find out.
If anything happened to you,
I'd never forgive myself.
Samuel... this isn't your fault.
Rebeka, look--
What would you like?
I admire you... Seriously.
Being up-front and honest takes courage.
Right. Is that why you want me to lie?
You think I don't lie?
My dad loves me
because he doesn't know me.
Okay, surprise me. What's your secret?
Can I get a gin and tonic?
OK, man. You want to compare?
Know what the Koran says about lying?
No... Haven't read it for ages.
It says that lying is fine
as long as it achieves peace among people.
My father's 65...
I want him to die in peace.
Well, listen...
this abominable sin...
is on the house.
Why are you worried about me?
You don't know me.
Because I'm in love with your sister,
and I want to make her happy.
Thanks.
What're you looking at?
Nothing... just the restaurant
for tomorrow.
Should I reserve a table?
Could be cool, right?
Something different.
There'll be lots of hot guys
showing some skin, for once.
Sounds like fun.
Sounds dumb.
All right... I'll go on my own, then.
Fine. I hope you have a fucking ball.
If I want us to go together, that's bad.
If I go alone, it's worse.
And if I stay in with you,
you treat me like crap.
What the hell should I do, Ander?
Don't spoil the little time I have left.
That so much to ask?
Let's go to class.
-Give me a clue!
-Nope!
So serious, Lu! Happy Valentine's Day!
Ander!
I think... you should lay off Omar a bit.
Why?
Do you know how lucky you are to have
someone who's always there for you?
Don't blow it, dude.
Thanks.
Sure.
Happy Valentine's Day.
If you bring someone, bring more to drink.
I'm going solo.
But if they're there, I won't stay.
Bonnie and Clyde?
I set rattraps in case they come.
Aren't you Switzerland?
You know? I'm not.
I don't want to leave you
on your own in this war.
We've always fought side by side.
We're... Lu and Guzmán, right?
I'll get another one.
-No, you said this was the last one.
-Just one more!
Shit!
Careful, guys. Guzmán!
Help me clean up
before anyone else gets hurt.
Where's the neck?
Excuse me.
Rebeka, would you come , please?
Come with me.
Whatever you have to say,
you can say it here.
The Parents Association
has made things very difficult.
The charges against your mom are serious,
and the school's reputation is at risk.
You're kicking me out, right?
We'll offer you the chance
to drop out voluntarily.
Your record won't be tarnished.
Shit... How thoughtful!
You just have to sign this document.
No.
Kick me out.
-Let the whole fucking school know.
-What?
Let everyone from here to China know that
when a rich kid's dad went to jail,
-he didn't get kicked out.
-Don't shout.
-What's going on?
-Go back to class.
Let fucking everyone know
that I'm getting kicked out!
But if your moms fund a scholarship,
you don't get expelled,
-even if you're a murderer!
-Ander!
-You can't expel her.
-We're not. It's voluntary.
-Then, I'm leaving too.
-What?
If she leaves, I leave.
Me too.
And me.
And me!
What's going on?
I'll try to talk
to the steering committee.
OK?
Go back to class, please.
What a mess you've made, kiddo.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I need you to...
help me mess things up a bit more.
What?
Don't! You can't touch that.
It'd be too obvious.
This way.
Go over.
You're heavy!
Fuck! Shit!
Be careful!
-You have springs in your shoes?
-And much more.
Come down.
-Why the hell do you have that?
-To peel fruit. What else?
Is it there?
I don't know.
Nothing.
Fuck.
She didn't say anything?
Nothing.
Just that I was letting myself go.
That piece of--
What?
She said, "Keep boxing."
She told me to keep boxing.
Fuck.
I can't believe this.
Do you like my Bumblebee?
-What?
-Bumblebee, Transformers.
Never mind.
I wish you signed things
as fast as you bought cars.
So you only like me
if I invest in your wine business?
No. I like people who keep their word.
That investment isn't a car.
It's 10,000 cars.
It's not like pulling out your credit card
and buying... I don't know... this?
For the party?
You'll look very sexy in it.
It's for you, right?
-The roles are reversed tonight.
-No.
Just because your friend
has gone all feminist,
I'm not looking like an ass
for our first Valentine's.
We'll look like asses
if we don't follow the dress code.
Everyone will stare.
Let them stare...
at how amazing you look
on my arm.
Maybe I'd rather go alone.
What does that mean?
Nothing.
-How are you, Yeray?
-Great.
Honey, don't be so fussy.
You should thank Yeray
for being so considerate with you.
With me, right?
Put that dress on
and stop behaving like a little girl.
Please.
We haven't closed so early in ages.
There isn't much business
at this time anyway.
But don't worry about that.
Focus on what you need to do.
What about the store?
There's no need to open every day.
Or go to the hospital either.
I'm already perfectly fine.
What do they say? "Strong as a mule."
"As an ox," Dad. Strong as an ox.
Strong as an ox.
Are we still waiting or...?
Yes.
No.
We'll order now.
Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
Dad.
Son.
We need to get rid of this now.
How much can you get for this shit?
This is Molly, so a few thousand.
-What's it matter?
-I don't have money to buy food.
I don't care if we eat
rice with tomato sauce forever,
-you're not doing this.
-He's right.
You're not doing it. I am.
I'll sell it.
We'll be partners...
and go fifty-fifty. How's that?
Partnering with you
is even worse than pushing drugs.
-That's a no.
-What's wrong? I'm a reputable guy.
-We'll flush it down the toilet.
-No!
Let's think this through...
before doing anything stupid.
And that goes for you both, OK?
How's school going?
Well... I'm doing my best.
Between work and helping at home,
I don't have much time.
Great. You must be grateful
to whoever has taken you in.
Who do you live with now?
Ander and his mom.
-Ander is...
-A friend.
Mom, you met him at the hospital...
Remember?
Oh... yes.
How is he?
He's fine.
What's wrong, honey?
Don't say it's nothing. I know you.
The thing is...
he has leukemia.
What?
Ander?
I do my best to help him.
I go with him to chemo,
I look after him...
School isn't the most important thing
right now.
Son, you are a very good boy,
but... that isn't your duty.
Let his family take care of him.
Ander is my family.
His family are his parents,
his siblings...
He's my boyfriend, Dad.
You just need to focus
on your studies
and keep out of trouble.
Did you hear me, Dad?
You're a very smart boy,
and if you focus--
-Did you hear me?
-And did you hear me?
I'm sorry. I can't.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Lía, honey, you brought champagne!
Thanks!
So good to see you! Thank you.
-What about the booze?
-It's over there.
Perfect. I love the outfit. It's amazing.
Who invited you two?
Where's the booze?
No, you can't bring that here.
Go to the nearest store
and bring some alcohol, OK?
My God, look who's here.
Stunning.
-Thank you. You, too.
-Thanks.
-Enjoying it, huh?
-Nothing I haven't already seen...
enough of.
I thought as much.
I'm impressed. I love it!
I don't remember hiring a magician.
I think table three
just ordered their check.
We were just saying
how genius this party is, right, Rebe?
Put the bottle over there.
-Thanks, hon.
-Thank you.
I'd say it takes one genius
to appreciate another.
But tonight, we're judging you
by your appearance.
-You look spectacular.
-Thanks, babe.
You should smile more!
-Very handsome, but too serious.
-What's next?
You slap our asses
and harass us on the dance floor?
-Hey, Samu?
-What's up, man?
-Great.
-And yes...
-Take it as a compliment.
-OK.
This is a cool party.
I know. Me and my ideas.
Polo, Caye, I'm in my house.
Well... my former house.
This party's looking pretty good.
Let me know if you come.
Look at this circus, Daddy!
Good evening.
-All good?
-Yeah, I don't think I'll be staying long.
Give me a second.
You know today is the other way around.
Why don't you fucking go "home"
and read a book?
I don't believe you...
The most persistent competitor
of all time!
You still want to be
with Guzmán, seriously?
-It's not a good night to be alone.
-It never is for you.
This is such a great party.
Balloons, screens,
people bringing their own drinks...
How much did this cost you? Ten euros?
Bullshit.
I'm out of here. This party sucks.
-Have fun.
-Thanks.
-We stick out a bit, huh?
-Yeah, just a bit.
-Hi.
You didn't understand
the dress code either, right?
"Reverse"?
Apparently, we're not the only ones.
I see. Excuse me.
Should I resend you the invitation
so you get the idea?
I'm sorry, Lu.
I will always be a refined lady.
Sure...
Where do I leave this shit?
Right here.
She's so classy.
Pathetic.
Sweetie, we're leaving soon.
I don't want to see you
more than strictly necessary either.
Well...
-Let's enjoy the party.
-Let's.
-To us.
-Cheers!
Lucrecia, your turn.
Your turn.
I can't do it, Nadia.
I can't.
You have to lie.
Listen to me. You have to lie.
Hey.
Hi.
Bathroom.
It's occupied.
Right.
I didn't have time to change.
It's fine, man. No worries.
You don't want anyone
to question your heterosexuality.
Omar...
I understand you.
What do you understand?
You have no fucking clue--
Ander! How are you? You OK?
-Have you seen Omar?
-Omar? Yes. In the bathroom.
Down... downstairs.
Which? There are like 20.
There's one in the kitchen downstairs,
very far away.
The last one. He's waiting for you there.
You look hot!
I understand you a lot.
A lot.
The duck was delicious.
-Wasn't it?
-It was.
I really liked it.
And the presentation was awesome.
Babe, Polo.
How are you?
Great.
You?
Fine.
Hey, thanks.
For what?
For making a scene.
It worked.
You're stubborn.
Yup.
-Arrogant...
-That too.
-But you're also a good friend.
-I didn't do it to be your friend.
I did it...
because I love you.
And... do you love me? You love me...
don't you?
Yes...
I love you.
But it's not enough.
Everything's so easy with Malick.
He makes my family so happy.
I could have a future with him.
Not with you.
Love isn't enough.
Hey.
Why are you here?
I...
I came to apologize.
And to see how sexy you looked.
It's OK, don't worry.
-Omar.
-What?
-Everything's OK.
-No, it's not fucking OK.
I'm really fucked up.
The only one I treat like shit
is you...
because I know you'll be there
no matter what.
No matter how hard I push you,
you come back.
That's not fair. You don't deserve that.
You deserve to be loved.
Will you forgive me?
No.
Dude... you can smile and everything.
What do you want me to do, Rebe?
Someone I care about
threw their life away for that shit.
Samuel... look at me, please.
What?
If this means choosing
the cash or you...
I'll flush that shit
down the toilet right now.
I'm getting all romantic, huh?
After saying something that romantic,
we could at least kiss--
Hi.
-Hi.
-How are you?
-Fine. You?
-Fine.
-This is Ander. Malick.
-What's up?
-Nice to meet you.
-Likewise.
You look amazing.
But you didn't understand
the dress code, did you?
I do feel a little out of place.
Especially looking at you.
Well, you know...
What? No. No way.
Oh, yes, way.
You just have to undo this button...
Well! I see you've...
gotten to know each other.
Come on! Take it off!
Take it off!
Uh...
I found out.
And I'm really sorry.
I'm here if you need anything, OK?
Don't worry about it. I'm OK.
Of course I'm worried.
We're family, no?
I mean, I can't believe
your own sister kicked you out.
-I mean...
-Well,
I didn't literally get kicked out.
I left voluntarily.
She's a little out of her mind
ever since my dad disowned her.
-What?
-No.
-Your dad did what?
She's penniless, completely broke.
-Holy shit.
-I don't believe it.
That's what the whole party was about,
people bringing their own drinks.
She's so smart. I'm in awe.
-The party was cool anyway.
-Sure.
I'd have liked to go, you know?
With my see-through top...
man, was I looking good!
I'd have liked to look at all the guys
the way you look at girls, you know?
We can fix that.
Look at us however you want.
Right, Polo?
Right.
In fact, tonight...
you're in charge.
-I'm in charge.
-You are.
Whatever you want.
OK.
Your wish is our command.
Kiss each other.
Just like that?
Yes.
Come here.
Slowly, so we can enjoy it longer.
Now, Polo... undress him... slowly.
Go down.
Down.
I didn't tell you earlier...
but you look amazing.
I know.
Thanks.
Shall we dance?
No.
I'm fine like this.
To us.
Cheers!
-Rebeka, do you have a minute?
-Yes, sure.
I spoke with teachers and the board,
and you can stay.
Thank you.
Having said that...
I need to remind you we are very strict
with the monthly payments
and the payment deadlines.
And this month...
Damn, the fine print.
If we don't receive the payments...
-I'll have no option--
-Right.
An awesome excuse to kick me out.
We already talked about it!
Samuel, either I sell that stash
or I'm out.
And, man, I don't feel like
letting them get away with it.
-Fine, start dealing.
-Remember how those guys reacted
-when we went on their turf?
-Hey.
I know somewhere with no competition.
Where the market is huge.
Where?
Las Encinas.
You must be joking!
Lu, do you have a minute?
Maybe.
I just wanted to...
ask you to be nicer to Cayetana.
To ease up on her a bit,
just leave her alone.
Anything else? I'm in a hurry.
Since you're asking...
Make sure everyone leaves us alone.
You're good at that.
They'll listen to you.
Why would I do that... Polito?
-My name's Polo, not Polito.
-Whatever.
The Columbia program
is sponsored by my mothers.
And I don't think
you can afford to lose it.
-What do you mean?
-Yeah.
Since your father left you penniless.
Was it you?
Did you kill him?
No.
We know each other
more than we'd like to, Lucrecia.
And I think you're lying.
Tell me the truth.
Why are you so shaken up?
What's wrong?
I'm shaken up
because I saw who killed him.
Subtitle translation by Toni Navarro