GRADUATION PARTY
You don't have a fever.
-I'll take you to the doctor's.
-No, it's fine.
I just need to rest.
Up to you.
Still sleeping down here.
Omar.
I'm not in the mood now, OK?
Not now, not the other day,
not yesterday...
What's going on?
You're over me.
Don't say that.
No? Come on, say it. You're bored.
Don't be a drama queen.
Omar.
I don't know, man.
This should be a nonstop hormone fest.
Fucking, kissing, going places...
Having fun.
-We're like a retired old couple.
-Can I talk?
If it's not that, what is it?
We're together, we live together.
We're more or less independent.
And the coolest thing we do
is watch Netflix?
It's a fucking joke.
Jesus, check out the hunk!
Too bad the new guy
didn't end up in our class.
Him? He's not really new.
He was here on a scholarship
three years ago
and had to leave. His name is Yeray.
That's... "Free Yeray"?
Yeah! That's what they called him.
I don't know why.
Forget about him.
I already have.
ROOM FOR RENT
Are you hanging those here?
Samuel, people here shit
in bathrooms as big as your house.
I'm just printing.
I can't afford toner.
Rebe to the rescue. I'm fine, thanks.
Yeah, fucking great. You wish you were.
Your mom leaves you,
the marchioness screws you over,
Polo is out of jail...
Are you here to help
or make me feel shittier?
Problems should be handled
like fuck buddies:
one per day.
-What are you doing?
-Here.
I have the perfect roommate for you.
Hey, buddy!
-Sell the car and live with him all year.
-You know what, babe?
My dignity is not for sale.
You lost your dignity
200 lines of coke ago, sweetie.
Sorry.
A dignified life is having a roof,
not a car.
No matter how good the car looks.
Looks amazing. You know what?
I prefer to see the world
in my own colors,
not in his gray palette.
No offense. Thanks anyway.
What a huge idiot you are.
-Yeah, a giant one.
-Here.
For you, sir.
-What's this?
-This guy's number.
Yesterday, the school signed
a program of studies
with Columbia University, in New York,
that guarantees access to that college.
The program and the courses
will be fully funded.
Candidates will present
their own academic projects
-by the end of the year, and the winner--
-Funded by whom?
A generous sponsor.
-As I was saying--
-Yesterday?
I saw Polo's mother in your office.
I mean...
if Polo's mom's publishing house
wants to sponsor it, so what?
You're always--
They've already bought you off.
Not the rest of us.
They don't need to buy us off.
Polo's been released.
Thank you.
You want to take the prize
without feeling guilty, huh?
If Nadia wants to apply,
it's her business.
Maybe we should all move on.
-You're not serious.
-I believed you.
But the court didn't.
I believed you, not Polo...
who's been my best friend
my whole life.
Maybe I fucked up again.
Drop it.
Were you serious?
-About what?
-Moving on.
Believing me.
Polo...
we've been friends for a long time.
For our sake...
look into my eyes.
Did you kill Marina or not?
No.
I didn't do it, Guzmán.
Then maybe I was serious.
I don't know. One day, Guzmán
is looking for revenge like a viking,
and the next day, it's all over?
What do you mean?
Should I not believe him now?
I know you want everything
to go back to how it was...
but that won't happen. Ever.
He's trying his best.
I'm going to do the same.
If he believes me, I believe him.
Ander, how will you go to the hospital
on your own?
-Walking or by bus or cab...
-Right.
-What about your mom? And Omar?
-They don't know and won't find out.
-But--
-Is that clear?
OK... fine.
But only if I can come.
-No way.
-No?
Too bad, because yours truly
will go to the principal's office,
your mom's office,
and tell her faster
than you can buy that Coke.
Your call, hotshot.
Good morning. I'm here to fill out
the application for the study program.
And about time too.
May I come in? Nadia!
Are you applying too? Great.
I thought you wanted St. Andrews.
I do.
-Then why apply? This is for Columbia.
-Why not?
You shouldn't put all your eggs
in one basket, right?
With your record and your references,
you could go to any university.
Let's see if I understand...
You're telling me not to apply?
The call for applications
is open to anyone.
I'm just saying that...
those who, fortunately,
can gain access to the best education
through other means,
could perhaps leave this opportunity
to people who are less fortunate.
My application. Have a good day.
Lucrecia!
-Hi.
-Azucena is right. You don't need it.
That's not your business or hers.
-Are you doing it just to annoy me?
-Yes.
Because I love to beat you.
It's much more fun.
And that pleasure is priceless.
Welcome to the competition... hon.
Let the Hunger Games begin!
You don't need to keep pretending.
You can come back to class anytime.
-I don't need your permission.
-I know.
But don't do it for me.
I'm sick of you saying what I want to hear
and then double-crossing me later.
-What do you want now?
-For you to come back.
It's all over.
Even Guzmán thinks Polo is innocent.
Seriously?
I guess when you feel lonely,
you don't want to keep losing people.
That's how I feel, at least.
I just want to get on with my life,
but the people I care for move away.
Even my mom left.
Polo's out...
Guzmán's getting close to him again...
All that shit you started,
and everything's like before.
No, not everything.
-What's changed?
-You and me.
You and me, what?
"You and me"?
There's no "you and me."
So let's change that.
I don't want to lose you too.
Come back, please.
Hi.
Hey.
Can I sit here?
Yeah, sure.
I can't get used to it.
I just want to get out of here...
and avoid their stares.
What?
Let's go.
I don't feel like being here either.
I never do, but even less so today.
Where should we go?
I don't know, out.
My place, my folks are out.
We could play video games.
Great! Sounds perfect to me.
It's important that you tell us
everything you saw.
Anything you think could be useful.
Everything. Any detail could be key.
Lu, since you always say you didn't send
the video of me and Guzmán
to the whole school,
I won't tell anyone about you and Valerio.
How do you want me to not tell?
A meme with a gradient background?
A GIF and little colored letters?
I need that study program.
You don't.
Withdraw from the competition immediately.
Wow. You really are smart.
It takes a very special person
to carry out that sort of threat.
My dear, you're incapable of such a thing.
May the best one win.
Kisses.
Bitch.
Beer at this hour?
Who cares? It's the plan that matters.
What?
Nothing, I just...
never thought we'd do this again.
Sorry for getting mushy, but...
I just wanted things
to be like before so bad.
Thank you.
Come on, now you're getting mushy.
Drink your beer.
You're back.
I have the best reheated macaroni
on the planet at home.
When are you coming for dinner?
Fuck.
Do I know you?
Sorry.
Shit. What?
What?
Ander, fucking say something.
Sing, dance, but lighten up a bit.
You're a pain in the ass.
I'm an introvert, okay?
-You're the definition of pigheaded.
-You shouldn't be here.
-You're right. It should be your mom--
-Stop it!
They'll tell me what the treatment is.
It'll be no big deal, and I'll go home.
I don't see the fucking need
to tell everyone.
Well...
you told me.
I mean people who love me.
Hey! I love you.
-You don't love me. I turn you on.
-It's a form of love, hot stuff.
See how good it feels
when you lighten up a bit?
Tell me about you.
Tell me a secret nobody knows.
Since you know mine...
Well...
I mean, it's something, but it's not...
I think there's...
a girl who turns me on too.
Congrats!
-Nadia, right?
-No way.
Worse. The marchioness.
That's normal. She turns me on too.
Even turns Omar on!
What about boys?
Who?
Samuel.
-I don't believe you.
-It's true.
I mean, he's hot.
I'd do him.
Ander Muñoz?
You can come in.
WHAT IS CHEMOTHERAPY?
Acute lymphocytic leukemia
is a fast-growing cancer.
That means we have to be faster.
We'll start chemo this week.
We'll hit it with everything we've got.
We'll do two six-week cycles,
but they'll feel longer than that,
to be honest.
With such intensive treatment,
the side effects will also be intense.
It's all on that brochure,
but it won't be easy to prevent fatigue,
nausea, vomiting, and dizziness...
Also, nerve pain at the joints.
You won't feel like eating,
going out, or doing anything.
And, yes...
your hair will probably fall out.
It's the first thing everyone asks.
Over the next few months...
Ander?
Yes, Rebe. I'll tell them.
OK? As soon as I get home. I promise.
Yeah, that too.
But, I mean...
You'll die of old age.
You know that, right?
Carla.
Are you OK?
Excuse me?
You were never one to skip
so many days of school and...
-Well, I'm here if you need anything.
-So...
you keep staring at me in the hallway,
you know I don't skip classes,
you know my name...
You've only been here for two minutes,
and you're already creeping me out.
Sorry,
I didn't want to bother you... but...
-do you really not remember me?
-Creeping me out big time.
Three years ago,
I uploaded a picture to Instagram,
and I got ridiculed and body shamed
by half the school.
Body shamed? You?
Well, I used to be...
Well...
That's you?
-Yeah.
-Shit.
"You disgusting fat fuck."
“I'd donate some clothes,
but they wouldn't fit."
-OK, I get the picture.
-Wait.
Read... this comment.
"You are the ones who are disgusting.
We hate someone
when they represent something
we hate in ourselves.
Yeray, ignore them
and keep showing yourself as you are.”
I posted this?
Shit. I didn't know I was so intense.
When I saw a girl like you
defending me in public...
What do you mean, a girl like me?
Pretty...
Intelligent...
-A marchioness!
-I can't take credit for any of that.
But for defending me, you can.
It helped a lot.
I'm glad I helped you three years ago.
You bet it all on black, and you won.
By the way...
it's time to collect your prize, right?
Well...
I'm not too big
on prizes right now, but...
I'm happy to see you again, Yeray.
We'd made up.
I realized there was no real evidence
against him.
Only my desire to blame him.
So we talked it over
and gave each other a second chance.
After all, he was my childhood friend.
I never would've hurt him.
I'm going to make it, right?
Well, of course you are.
I'm crying because I'm still shocked,
but of course you'll make it.
You're not saying that
because you're my mom?
Of course I am.
I won't leave you alone for a second.
But you're going to make it
and get better.
Go on, honey. Tell him.
This is about teamwork...
and we need to start now.
Fuck, Ander, I asked you yesterday!
I didn't want to tell you.
But it'll get obvious, and my mom
will have to deal with it, so I told her.
And I won't?
-No.
-What?
This isn't your problem, Omar.
OK, it is. We're together...
but we haven't known each other long.
We hooked up because we were less
than 500 meters apart in the app.
Otherwise, we wouldn't have met.
Two days later, you moved in!
Am I right?
Are you pushing me away
to play the romantic hero?
To save me from the pain
or some shit like that?
I'm relieving you of a burden
that isn't yours. That's all!
You should be out and about, fucking!
That's what you should be doing!
You said it yourself...
You should be at a nonstop hormone fest,
not here with me!
Do you want me to leave?
Whenever you want.
This is quite a party
you're having here, huh? I love it!
My mom's business meetings
turn into parties.
Happens every week. Typical.
-What do you want?
-A quick favor.
-I need you to help me out.
-Money?
-Pass. Sell the car.
-Not money.
Co-caine!
You're joking, right?
No, Rebe. It's a favor,
and favors are returned.
So don't worry.
I know shit goes down at your house.
Rebe, bring the good gin from the cellar.
Honey, I told you to let me know
if you're bringing a date.
-A date? He's not a date.
-Valerio, ma'am.
I'm Rebe's classmate.
I'm Sandra...
not "ma'am." We're like family.
What family? You just met him.
It's a pleasure, Sandra.
What are we celebrating, then?
Nothing, just drinks and snacks
with friends.
Sounds like fun.
-Why didn't you mention it?
-All right, I'll get the gin.
-You, go the fuck home.
-Language!
I taught you some fucking manners!
Ignore her. I'm in charge here.
-Would you like a drink?
-Hell no.
Of course I would.
How could I say no to such a proposal?
She seems to be the one in charge here!
Guzmán... listen to me.
School's out. They'll see he's missing.
When they see you and I are gone--
He'll tell us where the trophy is,
then he'll go to jail.
How do we make him confess?
The towel will prevent any marks.
Did you set this up?
You had to make your mom believe
you were dead.
I didn't have a choice either.
Polo!
Wake up! Come on, wake up.
Some of your classmates
say that you were...
very aggressive with him tonight.
I didn't do it.
But if I knew who did,
I wouldn't tell you.
That means you know.
That means I'd never tell you.
Carla.
How are you?
Fully recovered?
I'm going upstairs. I'm a bit tired.
One thing, darling.
This kid... Samuel...
What?
You ran your mouth off
when you thought he was gone,
you went back to school
when he asked you to...
He's controlling you.
How unlike you.
He's not good for you,
and it's not good for him
if I see him near you.
Get some rest.
Tell me where the trophy is.
Polo, tell me where the trophy is,
and this hell will be over for us,
over forever.
Put it on silent.
MOM
Polo...
tell me where the trophy is.
please... tell me where the trophy is.
-Tell me!
-Guzmán, stop!
Fucking stop!
Stop!
Kill me.
I...
didn't want to kill her.
It was an accident, Guzmán.
Son of a...
But you're doing this to me on purpose.
You're capable of killing me.
Guzmán!
-Guzmán, stop it!
-I'm not a murderer!
Let him go!
Guzmán, let him go!
-Let him go!
-Fuck!
-Where are you going?
-Let go!
-What are you going to do?
-Are you protecting him?
How's the party going?
We're having a great time, right?
Mrs. Robinson...
Are you trying to seduce me,
or is it just me?
I saw you hogging the coke
as if it was yours.
There’s nothing I enjoy more
than entertaining my guests,
and there’s nothing I hate more
than being hustled in my own home.
Forgive me, Sandra.
I don't want you to think
I'm ungrateful or rude.
I wanted some,
and I've been a little low on cash lately.
All that private school and fancy clothes,
and in the end...
-How old are you?
-Nineteen.
OK... you're old enough to vote.
You want it?
Yes, I'd like a little.
How badly?
It helps me feel better about myself.
A lot.
One gram.
Undress.
Come on.
Two grams.
On your knees in front of me.
Didn't you want it a lot?
Let's see what's "a lot."
I'm cutting you a good deal.
Come over here.
Three grams.
Look at you...
Do yourself a favor. Look at yourself.
Get out of here.
It'd be your word against ours.
I'M INCAPABLE, RIGHT?
THIS IS A COUNTDOWN.
You're bluffing, right?
Ten, nine...
Do you want to see if I'm bluffing?
...five, four...
You're not withdrawing?
I'll start by telling her.
She'll love it.
She'll spread it in no time.
Have a good day... dear.
Nadia.
I can't withdraw.
I need it as much as you do.
My father knows.
I'm an embarrassment to my family.
They cut me off. I have no money, Nadia.
Right. Am I supposed to believe that?
I'm not lying to you, Nadia.
You don't know how fucking awful it is...
to show you my feelings.
But I have no choice.
I need...
that scholarship, Nadia.
And I won't rest until I get it...
even if... I need to grovel.
If you knew about me what I know
about you, would you use it to win?
Probably.
But I hope you won't do it...
because you're better than me
that way.
Only that way.
YESTERDAY WAS A SHITTY DAY
I NEED TO BE WITH YOU
WAIT FOR YOU AFTER THE BELL?
Are you OK, Guzmán?
You applied to Polo's moms' program.
It didn't bother you before.
It's complicated.
With you, everything is.
Everything's easy with you?
No... I guess not.
You know the feeling of waking up
and not knowing where or who you are?
I feel that every day.
I suddenly remember
that my sister's dead...
but I also remember
you'll be in class when I come in.
And that's the only reason
I get out of bed.
You don't make my life difficult.
Actually, you saved it.
That video made me...
lose a scholarship.
My future.
I also could've lost
my family, my home, my life...
I know it wasn't your fault...
but every time we're together...
Good luck with that program.
COFFEE? TEA? CHAMOMILE? ROOIBOS?
I'M WILLING TO READ OFF
THE WHOLE DRINK MENU...
I'm fine.
First time and first session?
I'm Alexis.
If you need any tips or advice
on how to handle this,
or need to trash-talk someone...
you know where I am.
Thank you.
See you later.
Bye.
Hi.
I'll get you some juice.
The nurse said you may have
a metallic taste in your mouth.
Are you staying?
I'll see where I end up tomorrow.
But for now, I'm here.
I won't hold your hand.
You want to be tough.
It hasn't been long, but I know you.
This takes three hours, right?
Did you bring your charger?
My battery's running low.
COLUMBIA PROGRAM
ADMITTED STUDENTS LIST
So?
I'm not doing anything. I wasn't going to.
Welcome to the competition.
Let the Hunger Games begin.
LET'S HAVE THAT COFFEE
Hey! Yes...
I do feel like collecting my prize.
Or at least trying it.
Text me, OK?
Want to come with me
to my startup's IPO?
Sure. No idea what that is,
but it sounds great.
-Just text me.
-OK.
Hey, still looking for a roommate?
Everything's good with me, now that
I have a roommate. All good. You?
What's wrong?
I can't say. It's about a friend.
If I tell you, he'll kill me...
before he dies himself.
What?
Life flies by, Samu.
We think we'll fucking live forever,
so we keep bitching about stuff
or listening to other people's shit.
What about my shit?
Nobody listens to that.
Not even me.
And before I know it,
maybe it'll be too late...
and my time will be up.
I don't want it to be too late.
I don't want to regret not doing
what I want.
So do it.
Do whatever you want to do.
Right.
I dove into a pool with no water.
Happens sometimes.
Well, all the time.
No...
Not all the time.
Call an ambulance, please!
Call an ambulance!
Polo!
Polo.
Subtitle translation by Toni Navarro