GRADUATION PARTY
FIVE MONTHS EARLIER
But... that can't be true.
All right. Thank you.
He's been released, hasn't he?
-Do I really have to go back?
-Why wouldn't you?
Did you do anything wrong?
Then you should go back...
and with your head held high.
Go on, get dressed.
Why the hell didn't we hear he was out?
Same reason we didn't hear
he'd been locked up.
One of his moms is influential.
She owns newspapers and magazines.
-But that won't get him out of jail.
-Don't you have anything to say?
-Or will you say nothing as usual?
-At least she finally talked.
Some people knew
and never said a damn word.
Ander? Holy shit! You knew too?
So, everybody knew but me?
Stay out of it.
This has nothing to do with you.
Correction. I have nothing to do with you.
I just would've liked to have known
that the boy sitting next to me
was a fucking killer.
Polo didn't do anything.
You expect us to believe you
of all people, Liar Barbie?
-Should we remind the class who you are?
-No need. Thanks.
All they have against him
is a statement from a jealous ex.
You don't get it, do you?
So, this whole show you put on
was totally pointless, right?
-Too bad.
-Like we needed your opinion, lowlife.
-Excuse me?
-Sit down and listen up, please.
Your classmate has been released on bail.
There are charges against him,
and he's still being investigated.
I told his family that I cannot allow him
to come back given the circumstances.
So, he won't graduate?
Fortunately, it seems
all this will be resolved soon.
What?
The judge has requested a confrontation
between Polo and his accuser in two days
to compare their accounts
and decide whether to pursue
or drop the charges.
I know it's hard to distance yourselves,
but I urge you to do it for your own good.
This week, we have representatives
from the world's best universities
coming to meet you.
With any luck, they could offer you
admission or a scholarship.
This is a crucial time.
There's a lot at stake. Stay focused.
Don't let the past ruin your future.
Good morning.
Merry Christmas, happy New Year,
happy holidays, happy everything!
Leave. Now.
-Why are you here?
-I'm going to class.
-Excuse me.
-Hey!
-Why aren't you in Chile?
-Because I'm a responsible student
and I'm here to finish the school year.
Where are you sleeping? Who are you with?
Who needs to sleep here?
Baby, please.
This isn't a game, Valerio.
You know what Dad will do
when he finds out you're near me.
Maybe he'll buy me
another ticket to Chile,
and I'll be able to live off that
for a good while.
Listen up and try to get this
through that drug-addled brain of yours.
Dad will kill you when he finds out.
And that's not a figure of speech.
Yeah, of course.
I mean, after all,
I'm the one who corrupts minors...
and you're the innocent,
virginal victim, right?
Because that's what you told him.
Did you bat your eyes at him
when you said it?
Do you know why he believes me?
Because I'm a model daughter.
Good, healthy...
And, above all, a liar.
If you'll excuse me.
-What are you doing?
-What you asked me to do.
Distracting you
when I catch you obsessing over it.
-Do you need to do that by hitting me?
-Well...
I can think of another way. Come on.
Here, start playing.
-Seriously?
-Come on. Pretend I'm not here.
Look at the TV.
OK.
Which game?
A fighting game? With jacked guys?
Whatever. It doesn't matter.
Just shut up, play, and enjoy.
Hey, what's this?
What do you think, Omar?
-The usual.
-No, right here.
On your groin.
It's like a small lump. Look.
-I don't know. I have no idea.
-It's probably nothing.
What could it be?
Nothing.
But you should see a doctor.
Just in case.
Yeah.
-Should I keep going or...
-Yeah, don't worry.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Just get it checked out.
Come on, relax.
They haven't found the trophy.
He'll never be convicted without evidence.
Carla will get him convicted.
You don't know what they're like
when they're together.
One look from her,
and Polo will shit his pants.
-He'll end up behind bars.
-You don't know that.
He deserves it.
Since you're rich,
this'll blow your fucking mind,
but people don't always get
what they deserve.
What the hell do you want?
I spent Christmas
in a fucking juvenile detention center.
Where were you? Skiing in Andorra?
Shopping in Milan?
Yeah, it was a blast
watching my parents' marriage go to shit.
Do you think it was easy for me?
We could go back to the way it was.
-All you need to say is you made it up--
-The way it was?
I used to live in fear of someone
finding out what happened.
I don't want to go back to that.
-Listen to me.
-I'm going to tell the truth,
but I'll give you a chance
to do it first.
Confess and you'll get
a reduced sentence.
Then it'll be over.
What a mess, right?
No comment.
Sure, because the killer
being the classmate
of the victim's boyfriend and brother
is something you see every day, right?
Didn't you hear Azucena?
I'm focusing on my future.
Oh, shit.
So, that's why you were shut away
in your house all break, ignoring texts?
-You were prepping for these interviews.
-If you want to talk, talk to Samuel.
I'll pass.
The "missing person" can go to hell.
-I don't take shit from anybody, Nadia.
-Weren't you crazy about him?
I got over him, like the flu.
A tropical flu. Lasted for months.
When I see him now,
all I can think about is how much
the jerk looks like Harry Potter.
It was like a spell, but someone went...
and when I look at him now...
I don't feel anything.
-I wish it were that easy.
-Huh?
Nothing.
Just keep trying.
Carla will come around.
-Why?
-Because she still loves you.
Only someone who's madly in love with you
would try to hurt you so badly.
What did you do to make her so spiteful?
Me? Nothing, Mom. I just--
Regardless, nothing justifies
what she's done. I mean...
these are serious accusations.
Cayetana, isn't it? Or is that a lie, too?
-Begoña!
-Look,
love is an incurable illness.
No pill, therapy, or surgery
can put an end to it.
I could forgive a person in love
for almost anything,
but there's no excuse for what you did.
-Mom.
-It was a scam.
You can't afford to be seen
with someone like her.
No. We're together, OK?
She's sleeping over.
-If she wants to.
-I do.
Goodbye. Thank you.
Peace be upon you.
And peace be upon you.
May I see your backpack, please?
Is this an excuse to flirt with me?
-Do I look like I'm trying to flirt?
-Well, it's working.
Your backpack.
-I'm a Muslim, too. I don't steal.
-It can't hurt to check.
Sure. How come
you didn't check that lady?
She wasn't suspicious.
Just like at the airport, right?
At security checkpoints,
they only search people like you.
Need to see more?
Have a nice day, sister.
Hello.
-Mom, we have to talk.
-A letter came.
Well, not a letter.
Here.
ASILAH
I have a job, a house...
I'm doing fucking great.
And it'll be even better
when you're back with us.
-I don't want to get my hopes up.
-But he's locked up, Nano.
The inspector told your brother
that when the bastard confesses,
you'll be able to come back.
Did she really say that? Is she that sure?
Is this really going to end well?
Well, of course, honey.
It's going to end well.
It's not a lost cause.
-At the hearing tomorrow--
-No, Samuel.
Those people always land on their feet
and have nine lives, like cats.
And if they run out of them,
they can buy more.
He'll get what he deserves.
Honestly, honey,
it's like you were born yesterday.
I'm sick of this. All of it.
Your brother had the right idea.
He's gone somewhere
where nobody knows him,
nobody looks down on him.
Somewhere he can start over.
-What if we join him?
-What?
I'm fed up with struggling here.
-Obviously.
-What do we have to lose?
My spot at the best school
in the country.
For fuck's sake, Samuel.
The same school that's made
your life hell from day one?
Where they look down on you?
Would you really miss anyone there?
How are you, darling?
"Darling"?
So I'm no longer a "fucking lying brat"?
I'd like to erase what happened
these past two weeks more than anyone.
-But only you can do that.
-Get out before Mom sees you.
Don't do it for me. Do it for Polo.
You said yourself it was an accident.
He took a life,
but he did it while trying to save ours.
Does he deserve 30 years in prison
for that?
How considerate of you,
worrying about my ex.
And the police potentially finding out
about your shady business
has nothing to do with it?
I'm worried about your mom.
-She's got nothing to do with this.
-Not yet.
But if you don't retract your statement,
if the investigation continues
and they find me out,
I'll have to give the police
a bigger fish to fry.
If I talk and they look
into the winery's accounts--
-Those are your accounts.
-With her signature.
Your mom will lose everything.
She'll only have her name,
and it'll be worthless.
Why don't we both keep quiet?
Things could go back to normal.
Carla, I'm asking you to do
whatever it takes to save this family.
Nobody is accusing you.
We're going to talk to everyone.
I heard the glass shatter,
and I ran over.
But I didn't push him.
It seems that nobody pushed him.
According to witnesses,
the glass was broken.
He lost his balance, and...
If it was an accident,
what are we doing here?
He lost his balance
because someone stabbed him in the chest.
It's in the hands
of that fucking brat again.
I say we go to court tomorrow
in case she gets any funny ideas.
We'll see if he has the balls to lie then.
-Can we change the subject?
-No. Today, we talk.
College representatives are coming
in two days.
Someone from Oxford will be there.
Remember?
Marina wanted to study there.
She was a rebel,
but she busted her ass to go
to one of the most expensive universities
in England.
We used to make fun of her.
That was taken from her, too.
Who she was and who she could've been.
That's what
the murderer deserves: nothing.
It's called justice.
It's your word against hers.
What if there's someone else?
Who?
They can't find Christian.
Ander.
MEDICAL RECORD
I NEED TO SEE YOU. IT'S REALLY URGENT.
When did you notice it?
Yesterday.
Have you had any of these symptoms lately?
Fatigue, dizziness, bleeding nose or gums?
I don't know.
-What could it be?
-Anything or nothing.
-Are your parents with you?
-No.
-I'm 18 years old.
-OK.
When the results arrive,
we'll send you a message
so you can come get them.
We should have them tomorrow.
ALL COOL. WILL KNOW SOON,
BUT IT DOESN'T LOOK BAD.
Waiter!
Are you talking to me?
I need a dose of your finest beverage.
Champagne. The usual.
-What are you celebrating, Mr. Chile?
-That you're here.
You don't have a friend in the world.
Do you think someone who buys
a bottle of champagne can be alone?
I'll have friends any second now.
Declined.
Well, that's easy to fix.
This is worth seven bottles. Your call.
You've seen too many movies.
I'll say it again. You don't have a friend
in the world, right?
What about you?
Are you ordering a drink?
I'm more into fucking.
-I guess we should stop. Huh, champ?
-First time it's happened.
Yeah, and I'm a virgin
and a cloistered nun.
With all the drugs you take,
it's a wonder you can fuck at all.
-That's what the blue pills are for.
-Oh, sure.
There's no problem chemistry can't fix.
Chill.
I was trying to get over one guy
by getting under another.
But that would've required
you being a bit harder.
How can I make it up to you?
I'd be happy sleeping
in each other's arms
and being all romantic.
Or you fingering me
and getting me off.
-Do you have a place we can go?
-No. I'm sleeping in my car.
Like it?
I stole it in London.
Sorry. I know it hurts
to be judged by the color of your skin
-or for your clothes.
-No worries.
It gave you an excuse
to flirt with me, right?
OK, another rich kid.
-You all think you're irresistible.
-Weren't you apologizing?
I was finished.
-So this is your flirting face.
-I don't have one.
-What's your name?
-Malick.
-I'm Nadia.
-I know.
Tomorrow, university officials
are coming to talk to you.
They don't have time for all of you,
so write down your first choice.
Hopefully, they'll interview you.
We'll collect your forms in a minute.
Polo, for fuck's sake, stop calling me.
-Why does he insist on talking to Ander?
-He's scared because--
Ander could say Polo confessed
and corroborate Carla's story.
-Convince Ander to testify.
-Me?
-He's your best friend.
-He's a filthy rat.
I won't beg him for help.
If the hearing doesn't go well,
they'll close the case.
It'll be fine, Samu.
You may have fucked her,
but you don't know Carla like I do.
Go talk to Ander.
Carla!
-How are you?
-How am I?
Don't come near me
-because I swear I'll hit you--
-Listen.
I'm sorry I put you in this position,
but you can't back down now.
If I go forward, I'll lose my family,
the wineries, everything.
-What the hell will I have left?
-You'll have me.
I love you.
Only if I do as you say.
You'll toss me aside once I've done it.
No, it'll prove you're the person
I fell in love with.
Look, there's Sleeping Beauty.
In the car?
-What?
-What the fuck, Valerio!
You said I needed to save money.
Living in the car is cheaper
than paying for a hotel room.
Sure. That's why you're selling
your jewelry? Where's the ring?
Not yet at least.
I see you didn't leave
a single detail out, right?
Your limp dick.
Damn!
You need help, dumbass.
With her?
Things are worse for you than I thought.
-No offense.
-That's a bit offensive, sweetheart.
-Do you mind?
-Sure.
-Thanks for your help.
-Don't mention it.
You're gonna sell the car,
buy a ticket to Chile, and fly back.
Your mom
should deal with this divine retribution.
Bad news. She won't pick up the phone.
What happened?
I thought: "Christmas is a busy time.
She must be at the beach house."
But I called using a different phone,
and she answered.
I said: "Merry Christmas."
And she hung up.
I see.
Come and stay at home.
Dad will be traveling for a few days.
And then we'll see, OK?
Hey.
-Hi.
-I have something to say.
If you have any decency left,
you'll tell the judge--
I have to go.
-I'm talking to you, asshole.
-This isn't a good time.
Well, fuck you, then.
RESULTS AVAILABLE.
PLEASE COME TO THE CLINIC.
Hello. Do you have to wait much longer?
How are you?
I'm sorry, Mom.
Darling...
all you've done is tell the truth.
Sometimes... that has a price.
We might have lost people along the way...
but whatever happens...
we'll always have each other.
Carla, I'll always be by your side.
Always.
-Ander hates me.
-What are you saying?
-What if he talks?
-He won't talk, OK?
Maybe not today.
What about tomorrow?
The day after? Next week?
Do I want to live like this,
wondering if I'll get caught?
Stop it. Do you hear me? Stop it.
Don't say that again.
What other choice is there, my love?
I could tell the truth.
Ander Muñoz?
You can come with me. I'm Julia.
Good afternoon. Let's begin.
Before the court clerk proceeds
to read your affidavits,
do you confirm
your versions of the events?
Anything to declare?
I...
-I wanted to say--
-I made it all up.
I'm sorry.
I was very angry at my father and my ex.
My father was always very strict with me.
I made it all up to hurt them.
But now I realize I've gone too far...
and I deeply regret it.
I'm sorry for all the pain I've caused.
I hope you can forgive me.
I told you to speak to Ander.
Go to hell!
What about your girlfriend?
If she loved you,
she wouldn't have stabbed you in the back.
Do you know what you've done?
What were you thinking?
About my future.
Let's go home, honey.
We'll talk later, OK?
I didn't talk to him all night.
We hadn't spoken in a long time.
What did you do after he fell?
I ran down to the dance floor.
That's all.
Were you serious about leaving?
The sooner, the better.
Have you heard?
What should we do?
What do you mean? We forget it.
They let him go. It's over.
-So we let him get away with it?
-It's none of our business.
How so? Of course it's our business.
It's yours.
-Polo confessed to you.
-Omar,
I have my own problems.
I don't need anybody else's.
What's wrong?
Have you heard from the doctor? Ander...
He said it's nothing. Just a scare.
You scared me, you jerk.
Can we just lie on the sofa
and not talk?
OK. Want to play video games?
-Is it good?
-Delicious.
I'm glad you're home.
Thanks.
Dad will be back in three days.
We've got time to plan what to do.
He won't listen to me.
He'd listen to you if you told the truth.
I can't do that, Valerio.
Even if I wanted to.
I can't. I just can't.
Wasn't he away for three days?
-What's this scumbag doing here?
-Fucking hell.
-What's this-- Hey, answer me!
-Dad, chill.
Can we talk about this
in a civilized manner? Like...
Norwegians.
I appreciate you had the courtesy
to sit at opposite ends of the table.
I only told him to come
because his mom won't talk to him.
I don't care.
No more taking advantage of my daughter.
I'm your kid, too.
You're a degenerate
who sexually abused a minor.
I didn't want to get the police involved,
but enough's enough.
-Dad.
-It's a crime, and you will pay.
First with a restraining order.
And then, maybe, even with jail.
Please.
I'm being very civilized...
and very Norwegian, Lucrecia.
Anyone else would have killed him
for raping his daughter.
Valerio did not rape me.
OK?
-You are a child!
-So is he.
You're under his spell.
You don't know what you're saying.
I know perfectly well what I'm saying.
Nobody ever forced me
to do anything. Ever.
I fucked Valerio because I needed him.
I wanted him...
more than anything in the world.
Love isn't a crime...
and he's no criminal.
And I'm not the perfect daughter...
or the innocent child you think I am.
So you're an adult now.
You didn't want to see it,
and I was happy with that.
But I am.
Very well.
From now on, you'll live like one.
Legally, until you turn 18,
I have to provide you
with food and shelter, but that's it.
Forget about money, luxuries, outfits,
and expensive universities.
-What are you saying?
-You're an adult.
And when you turn 18,
I want you out of this house.
You're already 19, so I don't need
to spell it out for you. Go.
Hi.
How are you?
-I don't know what I'm doing here.
-Right.
Why didn't you answer
my messages yesterday?
That's what you're worried about?
We need to get rid of the trophy,
then this will all be over.
It's safe with me.
-OK?
-What?
-Listen to me.
-No, Cayetana.
-Polo.
-No.
It's too risky
to try to get rid of it now.
And it's safe with me.
What do you mean?
Polo.
Hey, Polo. Look at me.
Hey... Don't worry. I'm on your side.
I'm the only one on your side.
OK?
Your résumé is impressive, Nadia.
Thank you very much.
But... I'll be honest with you.
I don't think
we'll grant you the scholarship.
Why not?
At our university,
we look at grades and hard work...
but also the student's life
outside the classroom.
Well, I have all sorts of interests.
I'm very curious.
I work at my parents' shop.
I'd like to give them a better life.
I'm sure of that.
But we've heard about
a video going around.
That's not working in your favor.
For our scholarships,
we're looking for model students.
How'd it go?
-Would you rather tell me over coffee?
-What?
I'm a good Muslim.
-I'll introduce myself to your parents.
-I'm not a good Muslim.
Are you the only one who hasn't heard?
"The one who repents from sin
is like one who did not sin."
Muhammad said that.
I wouldn't go against him.
-You know about the video?
-I've heard about it.
And you still want to buy me coffee?
What kind of Muslim are you?
One who lives in this century.
And I didn't say anything about buying.
-If the girl wants to pay...
-Sure. But aren't you loaded?
My father's loaded.
Richest man in Senegal.
But here, I must be
the... third or fourth richest?
-Second, if I'm really lucky.
-Where have you been all this time?
What kind of university
would you like to attend?
I'm sorry, but I don't give two shits
about this.
It's not a good time for this.
I won't finish the school year here.
In fact, I might drop out today.
Look, sir. I just want to live well.
No cheating. All legit, you know?
But with my shitty grades...
Well, you tell me, mister.
Look, the cousin of a dear friend,
the best student in the class, by the way,
is very interested in finding out
about the whole scholarship thing,
in case she couldn't afford to pay
for her studies for some reason.
I can easily afford university,
but just in case...
I want to go
to the London College of Fashion,
but I also want to be with my boyfriend,
and he's not sure of his plans.
Whatever we do,
we'll do it together or in the same city.
He can't live without me.
So, Ander, where do you see yourself
in five years?
In ten years?
What do you want to do with your future?
Excuse me.
INFORMATION
It's over. Do you hear me?
I won't tolerate any more of this!
Do you know how embarrassing
this is for the school?
From now on, the slightest misconduct
or lack of discipline...
will mean immediate expulsion.
No excuses, no exceptions.
That means you won't graduate.
-That's unfair.
-Very well.
Let's talk about justice.
All charges have been dropped
against your classmate.
He's a murderer.
The person who accused him retracted
her statement.
It's gone on her permanent record.
She may even face legal consequences.
So to make things crystal clear...
if anyone so much as touches
a hair on his head,
I'll see to it
they don't finish the school year
and that it goes
on their permanent record.
Understood?
I can't leave.
Why should we leave
as if we've done something wrong?
Why should Nano have to stay in hiding?
No. I won't let them get away with it.
-We need to find a way--
-To do what? What are you going to do?
Fine.
I'll stay with you.
-I won't leave you here alone.
-No. Nano needs you more than I do.
And you need to get out of here.
I swear,
you both will be able to return soon.
Who'll take care of you?
Mom...
who takes care of whom in this house?
I don't know what to say.
It's OK. It's water under the bridge,
if you ask me.
All is forgiven.
I just want to leave all this behind us...
and start looking ahead.
We haven't found the murder weapon,
so... we're searching everybody.
Can I check your bag?
I would never hurt him.
Not him.
I loved him.
Subtitle translation by Toni Navarro