I need the trophy.
What?
What are you talking about? Huh?
Polo, come...
Where is it?
-In a safe place where nobody can find it.
-I want them to find it.
I want them to know I did it
so all this will end.
No.
No one will know you had it.
-No.
-I don't want you to suffer.
You don't?
I've been suffering for months
by your side.
Supporting you.
You want to throw it all away,
and you're asking me to help you?
Cayetana, it's my decision. My life.
-I'm tired of everyone deciding for me.
-When have I ever done that?
Did you contact the British school
so they'd reject me?
What?
What's he talking about, Cayetana?
-No...
-Of course.
It had to be you.
I did it because I can't lose you.
I love you. All right?
You want me by your side,
knowing my life here is hell?
-That isn't love.
-Hi!
Why are you here?
What's going on? Everything OK?
-Lu, stay out of this.
-What a threesome you've got yourself.
Yesterday, I still thought
this was like a horror movie.
Two monsters fighting
over a damsel in distress.
Now she's in tears
over two monsters who aren't worth it.
One is the bastard who came to fuck up
our lives. Right, Polo?
Perhaps the monster isn't who you think.
-Valerio...
-Please!
Can we talk for a sec?
Fine...
but you'll need to get cleaned up first.
What the hell, Lu?
Fuck!
-You fucking ruined my life, asshole.
-Lu...
Lu, I just want...
to talk about your scholarship.
Just ignore him, please.
Be right back.
Want a sip, Marchioness?
No... thanks.
No wonder you don't want anything from me
after the other day.
Well, it wasn't entirely your fault.
Carla, I wanted to apologize.
I sold you the Molly out of jealousy.
I knew you weren't okay
and could've gotten hurt.
And all for what? A guy.
It's not your fault he's in love with you.
And then I say I'm a feminist.
Fucking patriarchy.
Don't beat yourself up over it.
I was jealous too.
You? Why?
He was with me,
but all he did was think about you.
Yeah, I was with someone else,
but all I did was think about him.
We really hurt each other. I'm sorry.
Don't get carried away, blondie.
It takes more than that
to bring me down.
I'm worried about Samu.
Why?
Haven't you realized it yet?
That kid worships the ground you walk on.
He'd go to hell just to warm up a pizza
if you asked him to.
He eats out of your hand.
So, don't clench your fist...
Can I have a napkin?
You really have some balls
showing up here.
I just want to dry off.
And I want you to go.
For your own good.
Omar... give me a napkin, please.
Omar, go get more bottles.
-Where are you going?
-Let go!
-What are you going to do?
-Are you protecting him?
No, you idiot. I'm protecting you.
Say you stab him in the heart,
then what? You'll end up in jail,
your mom will be devastated,
and Polo's moms will want revenge.
When will this nightmare end?
Valerio, please. Let's forget about Polo.
-It's over now.
-A bottle of champagne, please.
-Don't let him come between us.
-Just get away from me, OK?
Here you are, guys.
Polo was right. All this was crazy.
-You made us think it was possible.
-Yeah, because it was possible.
It didn't end
because there are three of us.
It ended because of who we are. Glasses!
Thanks! Cheers.
Son of a bitch.
Lu, forget about him.
Nadia, don't play innocent.
You want to smash this bottle
over his head as much as I do.
Admit it.
Is it true your mother's out?
It is, and she's eager
to get back to business.
I need her to send someone to scare Polo.
-Excuse me?
-To scare the living shit out of him.
Literally scare him to death.
What're you talking about?
How much have you had to drink?
I just stopped someone
who was headed straight for you,
but I won't be able to stop everyone
who wants to slit your throat here.
Thank you.
I didn't do it for you.
Why the fuck did you come here?
I'm going to turn myself in.
What?
Tomorrow.
Tonight.
I'll never be able to fix
all the damage...
I've caused you...
and Samuel...
but at least my moms will pay
for Nadia and Lu's program.
That's why I came.
To tell them in person.
To ask your forgiveness...
and tell you it's over.
Great.
Now get out.
When I get out of prison...
someday...
will you forgive me?
Never.
-I'll get another one.
-No.
-No, you said this was the last one.
-Just one more!
Shit! Careful, guys! Guzmán!
Help me pick this up
before someone gets hurt.
-Where's the neck?
-I don't know. I haven't seen it.
Rebeka.
I said no.
Do I need to spell it out for you?
I'm never going to send anyone
to scare Polo.
But your mom took care of that kid.
I'm not like my mom.
Get that through your fucking head!
So, nobody's taking him out?
I would if they let me.
Watch out for the broken glass!
Let me do it. It's my job.
Just what I needed...
You have to be kidding me. Shit, Polo...
Can't you wait one night
for him to be gone?
Are you still defending him?
Talk later, guys. Cleanup time.
Look for the bottleneck.
Get out of here, Polo.
You think I don't realize I'm not welcome?
Do you think I need you
to tell me that... every day?
What the fuck did I ever do to you, Lu?
Huh?
Nothing.
What about Carla?
And Ander?
Guzmán...
You don't know
how much you're hurting him.
You have no fucking idea
how much it tortures him
that you're still alive.
That you're breathing the same air as us.
Mark my words, Polo...
I'll always protect my loved ones.
Guzmán...
doesn't love you.
Lu...
stop groveling
for once in your fucking life.
But you're an expert at groveling, right?
You are.
Until they leave you
for someone better, right?
At least Carla loved me at one point.
Has anyone ever loved you, Lu?
Did you think that by being
the most stylish...
the richest...
and the smartest, they'd love you?
-Shut up.
-But nobody loves you.
-They envy you...
-Shut up.
...fear you, despise you...
That's why they don't love you.
That's why you're alone.
Shut up!
Polo.
Polo?
No, I didn't...
Polo, I didn't mean...
I know.
I'm so sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-I know.
Forgive me.
Polo...
Lu?
What happened?
Polo!
Polo.
Call an ambulance, please!
Call an ambulance!
Polo?
Polo.
I forgive you.
Don't worry.
Careful!
-Move aside.
-Don't let anyone near him.
-Come on.
-Polo!
-Please.
-The police are on their way.
Calm down.
I didn't mean to. I didn't.
It was an accident, Lu.
-It was my fault.
-No.
We'll say it was an accident.
Nobody will believe that.
Everyone saw her throw a drink
in his face.
-But it's true!
-The cops don't want the truth.
They want to close the case,
find someone to blame,
and lock them up 20 or 30 years.
We have no choice.
Yes, we do.
We can put an end to this nightmare
once and for all.
We've all suffered enough.
Too many lives have been shattered.
We'll walk out of here together, free.
And we'll leave this shit behind forever.
Her fingerprints are on the bottle.
We could break it.
Not here.
The noise would give us away.
Are you guys for real?
What if there are other fingerprints?
What if they found
all of our fingerprints on it?
It would be the same as not finding any.
Polo did something horrible...
but he wasn't a murderer,
and neither are you, Lu.
He wouldn't want you to waste your life
paying for one mistake.
Nadia.
You're risking the scholarship
in New York.
What?
Before coming, Polo convinced his moms
not to cancel it.
Fuck!
If we go to New York...
we'll go together.
Did everyone touch it?
We're missing one... The most important.
We could make it look like a suicide.
How will we do that?
-Where are you going? Stay back, come on.
-She's like his widow.
Can't you let her say goodbye
before they wrap him up like a sausage?
Shit, have a little decency.
Go ahead.
Come on.
Hey, thanks for this.
I really loved you.
So much.
If only I had loved you better.
I'm sorry.
Cayetana.
Cayetana!
For fuck's sake, Cayetana!
Come on, Cayetana, that's enough.
Let go of the bottle. Let's go.
Don't let anyone touch the body.
My God.
It's done.
What will they do now?
Interview us one by one...
which isn't a problem,
because no one saw a thing.
Agreed?
Someone saw me.
What?
Yeah, when I went
to pick up the bottleneck...
I bumped into a group of...
girls, I think.
Fucking hell.
Did anyone see you go into the bathroom
with the bottleneck?
Yes.
It's OK.
I need you to remember who it was.
It's important. We have to talk to them.
Who was it?
-I can't remember.
-Fuck...
-What if those girls talk?
-Have a better idea?
I hated him.
I blamed him for my illness.
I couldn't control myself,
and I stabbed him in the heart.
You're crazy. Why would you confess?
It doesn't matter.
I'm as good as dead.
I don't care if I die
in the hospital or in jail.
No fucking way.
You won't sacrifice yourself
to protect anyone.
Who's going to sacrifice himself?
We need a decoy
to throw the cops off track.
Not just one.
We need a lot of decoys.
It's important that you tell us
everything you saw.
Anything you think could be useful.
Everything. Any detail could be key.
Guzmán...
Wait, you're saying
we should all accuse each other?
That's right.
If witnesses saw Lu go into the bathroom
with the bottle, it's over.
But if the police have witnesses
who saw me, Samuel, or Valerio--
-Those testimonies will be worthless.
-Exactly.
So, now the question is...
Who accuses who?
It was Samu.
He went into the bathroom
with the broken bottle.
It wasn't me.
If I knew, I'd never tell you.
-That means you do know.
-That means I'd never tell you.
Although, maybe...
I saw Valerio go in just after Polo.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
Cayetana was jealous of my relationship
with Polo.
As soon as I saw her follow him,
I knew what would happen.
What time was that?
Twelve thirty...
No, 12:45.
I know because that's
when I take my allergy pill.
I was going to the bathroom,
but I saw Polo go in.
Then, I thought I'd better not...
because I didn't want to bump into him.
That's when I saw someone
follow him into the bathroom...
carrying a glass object.
Who did you see?
I just feel so bad
because of everything
he's going through--
Cayetana... who did you see?
Ander.
Guzmán.
He picked up the bottleneck
and went into the bathroom.
You saw him?
With your own eyes? You saw Guzmán?
Omar.
Nadia. That's all I know. Can I go?
-Carla.
-Rebeka.
I didn't see anything at all.
Hey... You did the right thing.
Hey.
You did what you had to.
Nothing will happen to Guzmán...
or to any of us.
Omar, Polo's dead.
I've been talking about death for months.
The more I talked about it,
the less I feared it.
But now I've seen it...
and I'm scared shitless.
What can I do for you?
What do you want? What do you need?
I need you.
What about the guy you were with?
That was nothing.
What do you mean?
I made it all up...
just to push you away.
I'm sorry.
If you wanted to get rid of me, congrats.
You did it, man.
Omar...
Lucrecia, your turn.
Your turn.
I can't, Nadia.
You have to lie.
Say you saw someone else go in.
It doesn't matter who.
Do you remember when Dad asked you
who messed up the car?
Or who stained the carpet,
or who dyed the dog pink?
I need one more story.
Lu, I need you to lie.
But this time it's not for me,
it's for you.
Please.
Several witnesses have told us
they saw you arguing with Polo.
Did you throw a drink in his face?
Yes.
And at least two people saw you
go into the bathroom
with the bottleneck in your hand.
Did you do it?
Did you kill him?
No.
We know each other
more than we'd like to, Lucrecia.
I think you're lying to me.
Tell me the truth.
Why are you so shaken up?
What's wrong?
I'm shaken up
because I saw who killed him.
Who?
I don't know. I don't...
What happened tonight, Lucrecia?
I've never seen you like this before.
And I don't believe
you're this upset over Polo's death.
You weren't even friends.
What do you know?
Polo was my friend.
Despite everything...
we're all friends.
More like a family.
We might not say
we love each other every day...
but you have no fucking clue
what I've been through with these people.
Year after year...
and all the years to come!
I'm shaken up...
because it hurts my soul...
that... the best people I've ever known...
have to go through this shit again...
like with Marina.
They don't deserve it.
If I'm crying, if my voice is shaky...
and I don't know what to do,
it's because...
But I didn't do it.
Thanks, Valerio.
Carla.
What did you want to tell me?
I'm leaving...
to study abroad.
Alone?
That's the idea.
What about visits?
That depends.
Will you bring macaroni?
Come here, come on.
It's a pleasure
doing business with you again.
You know I've been away for a while,
but I'm back now.
Good morning.
How are you, baby?
I'm tired.
What's wrong? Party hard?
Go to bed and get some rest.
No, Mom. No.
I'm tired of dead bodies...
police, threats...
I can't do this anymore.
All I'm asking for is a boring life.
Come on, baby.
And all I'm asking
is that you quit this shit.
Please.
Tell them to leave.
Because if you don't,
I'll be the one who ends up leaving.
Inspector.
An anonymous call
warned us of the presence
of a suspicious box in a park,
about 100 meters from here.
I called you because if we find...
Polo's fingerprints on the trophy,
we'll have to reopen the investigation.
I know it's a difficult moment for you...
He did it.
He confessed to us just before he--
That same night.
Your brother is free.
He can come back anytime.
He's not coming back.
He doesn't trust you...
and neither do I.
I don't believe you've been honest
with me either.
What happened that night
at the club, Samuel?
What wouldn't have happened
if you had done your job.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, Samuel.
Would you like a beer?
Yes.
Did the police really buy
the suicide story?
At least they have a culprit
who can't contest it.
Carla...
Can we talk for a moment?
-Sure, I'm leaving.
-No. With you, Cayetana.
Of course.
You can go to Oxford, Columbia, Harvard...
whichever university you want.
We'll pay for it.
-We'll pay for housing too.
-No, but... Seriously...
It's what Polo would have wanted.
You were the only one
who always stood by him.
We didn't know how to do that.
You deserve it.
No, I don't deserve it.
Besides, public university is great.
Seriously, and I think...
it's time I accept
that my resources are limited...
that I have the family I have...
and that my last name is what it is.
And I can still achieve
whatever I put my mind to.
Of course you can.
Carla, I guess you know
that you can't leave to study abroad.
You're in charge of the wineries.
I have a trusted contact here
who will report to me.
You'll work hand in hand.
Who?
Valerio!
I don't know if you know Valerio.
This is my dad.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, he has a great résumé, this kid.
I don't know what you heard,
but the reality is much worse.
I heard you didn't even graduate.
And yet, I ran
my own highly successful business.
Yes, an illegal business.
Since when are you scared
of breaking the law, Teodoro?
Relax, I'll mostly be taking care of PR.
I'm the best at partying.
Do you think this is what
the wineries need?
Valerio is a good person...
and we really need that.
-Carla, I hope this is all a joke--
-Let me tell you about my plan.
I think social media will be crucial
for marketing...
If we want to sell, this will be key.
Nadia, hurry up!
-You have your passports and tickets?
-Yes.
-You're not checking that bag?
-No, I'll take it with me.
-Are you taking winter clothes?
-Yes.
-It's cold there.
-I know, Dad.
I'll call you when we get there.
Good.
Omar...
I'm sorry about that boy.
What boy, Dad?
Your friend... Your boyfriend.
I'm really sorry.
Guzmán won't make it on time.
Why not?
He's with Ander.
He's getting the results
of his latest round of chemo.
I guess we'll find out when we land.
Your parents aren't coming?
No... They're on a business trip,
as always.
No, that's not true.
My parents say
they no longer have a daughter.
You'll always have a family here.
Of course you will.
Thank you.
Look after our little girl, please.
Like she looked after me.
Hi, Nadia.
First, let me apologize.
This will probably be
the corniest message ever.
But I wanted to say that...
if you ever decide to come back...
I'll be here...
waiting for you.
We have to go.
Yes.
You look familiar.
Andrés, right?
Román.
I don't care how hard you push me away,
I'm a fucking boomerang,
and whatever the diagnosis is,
I'll be by your side.
-Omar--
-Even if the chemo lasts 100 years,
I'll be at your side in this hospital,
repeating the school year.
Listen.
So what if I graduate when people retire?
I don't care.
But I won't leave you,
because I love you, dickhead.
I haven't stopped loving you
for a single day.
You won't have to.
I'm in remission. They just told me.
But that was a really beautiful speech.
Hi, Guzmán.
You know I'm a bit... competitive,
so here's a warning:
this is going to be
the corniest message ever.
I promise I'll come back for you.
I MISS YOU ALREADY
TWO MONTHS LATER
Hi.
Hey, man!
-I never thought I'd be glad to see you.
-Same here.
-I don't know anyone here.
-What do you mean?
Isn't anyone gonna tell me
how hot I look?
You look divine, darling.
One rich kid, two, three...
Rich kids everywhere.
Las Encinas is fucking awesome.
-Should we go in?
-Yeah.
Let's see what surprises
await us in class.
Subtitle translation by Toni Navarro