-You're still in bed? Are you all right?
-Yes.
My head hurts a little...
but I'm starting to feel better.
-Your room looks like a pigsty.
-I'll clean it up.
No, come and have breakfast.
I'll send in Mirella later.
-Is everything OK?
-Of course.
If you're not going to try to hide it,
at least tell me the truth.
I'm feeling great, Samuel. Is that better?
Is there anyone sitting here? No?
Well, there is now. Me.
It's important that you tell us
everything you saw.
Anything you think could be useful.
Everything. Any detail could be key.
I don't know any of this shit.
Wake up.
I have a question.
One of the problems is poorly formulated.
Look. You can't do the ionic bonding
between sodium and chlorine
because sodium's atomic number
is incorrect.
Hey. You owe me an A.
I don't want a standing ovation,
but you could thank me.
Thank you,
but you shouldn't have risked it.
You're not OK.
I have an MA in interpreting
passive-aggressive behavior.
Look, you're crying out for help.
Can you tell me what's going on?
Guess who finally got themselves
a big house...
fit for a party to celebrate
the end of finals? Who?
-And you'll be in charge of it all, baby.
-Why me?
The house is for the two of us
to enjoy this summer.
The sooner it feels like yours,
the better.
Lucky me.
-Are you being sarcastic?
-She's being herself, darling.
Meet the worst version of Carla.
You should love and accept her
as she is.
Good luck.
Call me.
I don't know.
Any girl would kill to have...
everything I'm offering you,
and you don't seem very excited.
I'm sorry.
It's just that...
I didn't sleep well last night.
-I see.
-But everything is fine.
You worry too much.
What do you want?
Look, I won't pretend
I'm not to blame here.
Like that's possible.
Malick being into men and cheating...
is something I can't control.
But the fact that he cheated with you...
Did you consider how I'd feel?
Do you have any respect for me?
I obviously didn't think about you
when I did it.
Or about Ander or anybody else.
I needed to do it, and I did it.
Fine.
-Fantastic.
-Yes, Nadia.
I make mistakes, I trip up,
I lie, and I disappoint people.
Just like everyone else.
-Even you.
-What?
You haven't told Mom and Dad
Malick likes guys, have you?
You're not thinking about them.
You're thinking about New York
and yourself.
There you go. We all have our faults.
Gay, a cheater...
and involved with my brother.
What a catch!
God, I can't wait for this year to be over
so I can leave Las Encinas.
You'll achieve
whatever you put your mind to.
You'll get out of here for sure.
And I'll miss you so much.
-Don't go near her again.
-Why?
She's not OK! Can't you tell?
Easy. I'm taking care of her happiness.
I'm giving her a good price.
-Let go.
-You got Rebeka into this.
-You won't do it to Carla, too.
-Did they ask for your help?
As far as I know, those two girls
want you to stay away from them.
I want you out of my house this afternoon.
COLUMBIA PROGRAM GRANT RECIPIENT
SOON
YOU ARE INVITED TO OUR POOL PARTY!
Oh, my God.
Happy? Out of everyone
who didn't deserve to win...
you... are the only one
I'm not ashamed to lose to.
Well played. Congratulations.
Nadia!
It'll be OK. You'll see.
-Isn't it my job to be cheering you up?
-You had nightmares all night.
Don't say it'll be OK. It's bad luck.
I'll shut up.
My therapist said it was best
to always imagine the worst.
Then you see
that the worst is not that bad.
That was when the worst wasn't croaking,
right?
Yeah... when I got anxious about grades.
Oh, my God.
What's the worst that could happen?
If the doctor looks at your file,
and he says, "Almost."
"How wonderful, Ander.
All those families waiting for
an organ donor are gonna be so happy."
"You're cured, Ramón.
Sorry, this isn't your file."
Enough now, OK?
Ander, the doctor will see you now.
It'll be OK.
Fuck you.
I don't have good news.
The results of your bone marrow biopsy
and the CT scan
are not what we were expecting.
The ratio of lymphoblasts
is still much higher than 30%.
What does that mean?
For the time being,
we'll have to continue with chemo
and increase the intensity.
-For how long?
-We can't determine that yet.
Until we get results.
What if we don't?
Let's not imagine the worst.
You decide to trash school property
on the last day of finals?
-Well done.
-What can they do?
Expel you
three days before graduation, loser.
I don't give a shit!
What?
Just what you need. A good party.
Among other things,
but we'll start with that...
-I'm not going.
-What do you mean?
-No excuses or anything?
-I don't need an excuse.
I don't owe you shit.
You and I are not friends.
-What are we, then?
-We were accomplices.
A shitty excuse for accomplices.
We tried to make his life hell,
and that asshole is as happy as can be.
I mean, he can't kick you out
just because he wants to.
-You can sue him. It's illegal.
-I could if I had a contract.
-Why did he do it?
-Roommate issues.
He saw us together.
-When?
-At the blackout party.
He knows I care about you.
-That's why he wants to hurt you.
-I don't want to live with him.
Yeah, OK. So where will you go?
I'll think of something.
It's not my first rodeo.
Amazing. We turned his living room
into a drug depot,
and he didn't complain.
But if you sell to the chick he likes,
-he blows a fuse.
-I'm going to stop.
Stop what?
-I don't want to do this anymore.
-No way.
You didn't see him.
Samuel could rat me out.
He'd screw me over for the year.
And for the first time ever,
I'm doing well.
-He won't tell.
-I hate it. I want to go to London.
I have really good things going on.
What is it that everyone sees
in Little Miss Marchioness?
She's a viper.
If she bit her own tongue, she'd die.
Fuck.
But somehow, she has everyone
eating out of the palm of her damn hand.
But suckers like me...
all we get is a slap in the face.
It's not happening.
We're not closing the business.
We're going all out.
More than ever.
We'll make a killing
at Yeray's pool party.
I'll pass.
Don't you need money to go to London?
Leave me alone.
What happened isn't Valerio's fault.
He shouldn't pay for what I did.
Let him live at your house
until he finds someplace else.
And why would I?
Because I could tell Azucena
you almost smashed a student's face in.
You'd get expelled
and have to repeat the grade.
How would you like that?
Then I'd tell her
why I almost smashed his face in.
Because he's a fucking drug pusher
who's dealing at school.
He'd get expelled too.
But he'd repeat the grade
in fucking prison.
That's not true.
Didn't you know he's selling to Carla?
So, you haven't noticed
that she's been walking around
like a zombie for weeks?
I'm guessing she needs that shit
to get through the day.
-What the hell?
-I don't need that stuff.
My hatred for you is enough.
I have so many reasons to hate you.
One of them is you'll be leaving
without giving a shit
about all the pain you've caused.
Get out of here.
I'm off. I'm meeting up with Yeray.
-Is everything all right?
-Just perfect.
-Are you OK?
-Yes.
I'm very proud of you.
Of how your attitude's improved,
how you're listening to us,
and how you've grown up.
You're a woman now.
No, a lady.
A marchioness.
Gorgeous.
Have fun.
Fuck, you're so annoying.
Drop it already, please!
Just say...
"Mom, I haven't quit the business
because I like living the good life,
and I shouldn't have trusted Samuel."
Say it, and I'll shut up.
See how easy it is? That's better.
Anyway, so tell me,
what did you do with him?
What do you think? I got rid of him.
What?
I broke up with him, Mom.
I'm not like you.
OK, babe. With that attitude of yours
and your willingness
to take over the business...
you're actually becoming a bit like me.
You were right after all.
I'm turning into her.
I need her to send someone to scare Polo.
-Excuse me?
-Scare the living shit out of him.
Literally scare him to death.
-Rebeka!
-I said no.
Do I need to spell it out for you?
I'm never going to send anyone
-to scare Polo.
-But your mom took care of that kid.
I'm not like my mom.
Get that through your fucking head!
Hey, baby, we're back!
Come in, you've already been here.
Let's see what room we put you in.
There are so many.
If you show me the way,
I'll leave a trail of breadcrumbs
so I can find my way to your room
and... have some fun.
Hey, you look so handsome.
Did you talk to them?
-Did they say no?
-I wanted to talk to Valerio first.
How did you get the tuition money?
-I told you.
-I know what you told us.
But now I'd like to hear the truth.
It's no big deal.
Is that why you didn't tell us?
-Tell us what?
-He's a fucking dealer.
It's a temporary thing.
But yes, that's how I'm making a living.
Dealing drugs?
-Yes.
-And you're selling to Carla?
Her money's as good as anyone else's.
Why?
She's not just anyone! She's Carla!
She's never taken drugs.
She's afraid of getting hooked.
That's just the way she is.
She gets hooked on a perfume,
a purse, or a boy, and can't let go.
People change, Polo.
It's been a long time
since you were with Carla.
-You have no idea what she's like.
-Guys, stop.
She or any of your buyers.
You don't know if they can handle it,
because you don't care.
You can save
your moral superiority speech.
You think you're better than me?
You're right.
I'm no better than you. I'm worse.
I'm probably worse.
The fraudster,
the murderer, and the dealer.
Sounds like a joke,
but it's not fucking funny!
-What’s wrong with you?
-What's wrong?
I just woke up, Cayetana,
and I don't like what I see
one fucking bit!
Get out.
Both of you, out.
Leave me alone.
Shush.
MALICK: HOW DID IT GO?
I have to go to work.
There.
They mentioned a "rust effect"
or something like that.
No idea. But I paid a premium for it
like Cristiano Ronaldo.
The house looks great.
Oh, God.
Does this mean that you like it?
It means that I want to get
in the pool right now, with you.
Come.
Now?
Yes.
Undress now,
or I'll pull you in fully clothed.
It's so nice.
It's a saltwater pool,
but I don't think it's really all that.
-Don't you like that I'm enjoying it?
-Yes.
I love it.
We’re going to throw an epic party.
It's like being in jail,
about to finish serving your sentence,
and when the day comes... Boom!
They say no.
That you're going to remain behind bars
for maybe a month, a year, ten years...
or forever.
-You aren't in prison.
-What?
You can leave whenever you want.
-What are you talking about?
-You can leave him, Omar.
I can't do that.
-You can't or you don't dare?
-Are you lecturing me about bravery?
QUR'AN
-Thank you.
-In the name of Allah.
One of my daughters at university,
in America...
What's going on?
-Malick and I were thinking...
-Malick and you?
Listen to him.
Malick and I think it would be best
if you went to America...
engaged to be married.
Did you know what these two were planning?
You want that, right?
Just a second. Come.
-Was this your idea?
-No.
It was your father's suggestion.
It'd be good for us.
Your family will leave you alone.
And I'll give my family what they expect,
at least on the surface.
If I get married now,
I'm guaranteed my freedom forever.
-It's a mere formality.
-No, it isn't.
You've seen my parents.
For us,
it's a serious lifelong commitment.
-Do you really not care about anything?
-It's not that.
I just put my own happiness first.
And you should do the same.
Do you think your parents
have your best interests in mind?
No. They're thinking
about their happiness, their honor,
what people will say.
Wake up.
Either we keep pretending...
or you can forget about New York.
I don't need a pep talk to cheer me up.
I didn't call you here to cheer you up.
Nadia turned down the scholarship.
She says she won't change her mind.
And since you came in second...
Nadia.
You're nuts if you think
I'll settle for your scraps.
I don't want to live a lie, Lu.
So you don't want to live a lie?
Well, grow some fucking ovaries
and tell your father you're accepting
and going alone.
Because you don't need a man
or anyone else, Nadia.
Be the woman who managed to beat me.
The one that I admire, damn it!
The one I can't stand.
I meant, "the one I can't stand."
Because I can't stand you.
OK?
People are staring.
Hey, guys, gals, and everyone else.
No more suffering.
The exams are over!
No more uniforms!
Fuck.
People are going wild.
Really? That's great.
-Are you coming?
-In a minute.
Let me help you.
-You don't need to do this.
-Get this end.
You'll be better off downstairs.
Omar and I will take turns sleeping
with you in case you need anything.
COMING TO THE PARTY? I WANT TO SEE YOU.
IT'LL BE NICE TO GET OUT OF PRISON.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO BACK, OMAR.
YOU CAN LEAVE HIM.
-What do you want?
-I want to drag you to that party.
No fucking way.
I have nothing to celebrate.
Finals are over,
and we're alive. Is that not enough?
Ander is sick. Really sick.
Chemo could kill him before cancer.
-You forgave Polo because of Ander?
-I didn't forgive him.
-You've gotten over it.
-Never.
Have fun at the party with him.
I'm not going.
Listen, Samu.
I used to think about him day and night.
And you know what I realized?
If I can't put him behind bars,
I don't want him in my fucking head.
He doesn't deserve to be that important.
Think about it.
What's wrong, honey?
Malick and I are not together.
What?
But we weren't together...
the last two years either,
and, as you know, I passed...
with the best grades.
I didn't need him... or anyone else.
Just me and my own hard work.
I want to go to New York.
No, sorry.
I am going to New York.
-No.
-Dad!
Listen to me.
Just this once. Please.
I'm not the little girl you want me to be.
I haven't been for a long time.
If only I were...
everything would be easier...
and I would continue to believe
that you do everything to protect me.
And not because you are afraid
of losing me,
like you lost Omar... or May.
I swear to you...
that if I go to New York,
I will always come back.
You will always have me.
But... if you stand in my way...
Thank God you're here.
-I've run out.
-Of what?
-I didn't bring any with me.
-OK, fine.
You're here to make a killing.
Do you think I'm dumb?
-Drink champagne. It's better for you.
-No, thanks.
-OK.
-Wait.
What do you want? More money?
How much?
I know those cravings well.
I'm sorry, but I won't sell to you.
I should have never sold it to you.
Carla. Carla, darling.
Today is your lucky day.
-Is it?
-Yes.
Two grams for 90. Just for you.
In the palm of your hand,
just like everyone here.
-The offer ends in ten, nine, eight...
-I thought you didn't deal.
Don't think so much, honey.
There you go. Enjoy.
Carla, what are you doing?
What's that?
Molly. Want some?
-Now you're doing Molly?
-Didn't you want to live large?
This is the full experience.
Full experience?
Don't treat me like an idiot.
I know how that makes you feel.
It's great until you come down.
You get depressed.
It takes you ages to be yourself again.
You sound like a Health Department PSA.
I get enough of that from my father.
You should listen to me.
-Come on, you'll get totally loved up.
-What? Loved--
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Don't ruin my party, please.
All I wanted was to be
the coolest girlfriend.
Isn't that what you wanted?
So, Lu, how is your first day
as a loser going?
Fucking awesome. I'm actually doing great.
I don't need that scholarship.
I mean, I only applied for it out of...
Well, for the competition. And my résumé.
I can go to any university I want.
And my father will pay for it.
Thanks, I'll order another one soon.
Why is that your fifth gin and tonic?
Are you trying to forget
how little you care about losing?
Cheers.
Yeah, sure. Cheers.
Hi.
-Nadia!
-Hi.
You take the concept of the burkini
to the next level.
I'm in a hurry, Lu.
I need you to sign this so I can take it
to the school office before it's closed.
What is it?
Azucena will let us share the scholarship.
But the budget remains the same.
So we will each have to get by with half
the money for food, accommodation...
I'm used to scraping by, but you...
Do you think I'm going
to let you laugh in my face?
Come on, stop being so you and sign it.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
People are staring.
Nadia.
I've dreamt so many times
about running away with you.
And now you're going with some other guy.
And with Lu.
-I'm not going with Malick.
-Seriously?
You're not together?
-Where does that leave us?
-You're here, and I'm leaving.
Can I give you a hug?
Sure.
-You're late.
-Are you leaving already?
-Yes.
-Are you sure?
You look like you could use a drink.
A drink and a buddy.
Yeah. Let's go.
Tell me you're not angry.
Tell me you're as happy as I am.
Holy shit, Yeray.
I wish you could feel
what I'm feeling right now.
It's as if electricity was flowing
through every cell in my body.
Let's take a selfie. You like that.
Fuck, what a long face.
Another one. Smile.
I don't need chemicals to be happy.
You are enough for me.
Shame you can't say the same.
Come on... it doesn't matter.
Some of us need a bit of help
to let our hair down.
What's wrong with that?
Your life is perfect.
I don't get why you need to take anything.
Oh, darling...
You're kind of a pain in the ass.
Maybe I need to get high
just to put up with you.
With me?
Yes, you, your scheduled life,
and the five-year sentence I'll be serving
because of that contract
you're signing with my father.
But I accept that you're locking me up
in this palace with a pool.
That contract is just business.
It has nothing to do with you and me.
Each plan you make with me
feels like another nail in my coffin.
Malick.
We need to talk.
OK. Let me dry off a little.
No, it has to be now.
Do you love him?
How many times have you fucked?
Once.
Three. Or four.
It depends on what counts as fucking.
Was it just sex?
No, it's not just sex.
Are you in love with him?
I don't know.
-You are or you aren't.
-I don't know what being in love is.
I just know I'm crazy about him.
And how does he feel about you?
Good, I suppose.
Because being at your place,
by your side...
it's hard.
Don't tell him about this, OK?
The only swimsuit I have
with no holes in it is here.
OK. You forgot how to sew?
Don't do this to me, Polo.
Don't do this.
We have a good thing here.
Something worthwhile.
Are we really going to throw it all away?
Just like that?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have taken it out on you.
-My problem is with Valerio.
-What he did was wrong, OK?
Whatever happened
to "everyone deserves a second chance"?
Where the fuck were you?
You could at least reply
to my fucking messages.
We need to talk.
So?
I've been seeing Alexis.
I'm with him. I have been for a while.
What?
I should have told you weeks ago.
But with the tests and all that...
Now it doesn't matter.
Omar, I don't have time to waste.
I want to end this.
Are you kidding me?
He gets me.
We speak the same language.
The fucking language of cancer.
And you don't.
No. It's not true. No way.
Why do you think I told you
to hook up with other guys?
I felt guilty about cheating on you.
So, you do fuck him?
Cheating is not just about fucking.
It's about wanting to be with him
and talk to him...
I'm sorry.
So what do I do now?
I don't know.
I'm not going to lie to you.
The sooner you go, the better.
Samuel will let you stay at his place,
right?
We can talk about it tomorrow. I'm tired.
So, that's it?
You son of a bitch.
-Have you seen Valerio?
-I haven't seen him in a while.
Shit.
Help! Grab her, please!
Grab her. Get her out!
Carla!
Hey, Carla!
Carla, hey! Call a fucking ambulance!
Hey! Call an ambulance!
Carla!
Hi, hey... We need an amb--
Rebeka, wake up!
-Law? Really?
-I want to be a lawyer.
Make sure no more assholes
get off the hook.
Become a judge, then you'll make sure.
-What about you?
-Business.
But putting assholes in jail
sounds pretty good too.
-I could do a dual degree.
-I'd like to have a friend in class.
I'm not going to a public school.
-A few nights out, and I'll convince you.
-No fucking way.
Good morning, my narco queen.
Here's what's left. I'm done, OK?
I'm done too.
Flush it down the toilet,
I want nothing to do with this shit.
-Easy. What's going on with you?
-What did you give Carla?
-What the fuck did you give her?
-Let go of him. He didn't do it!
-OK? No!
-Samu!
Stop! Calm down!
Samu, stop!
Samuel, fucking stop it!
Samu! Guzmán, grab him!
Fuck.
I know you hated Polo.
Yes, ma'am.
But I'm sure you know
I wasn't the only one.
But I can tell you that...
I saw who went in the restroom
after him.
It was Samu.
Subtitle translation by Toni Navarro