Guzmán.
I need to ask you a few questions.
What happened?
LAKE CLUB
Look, I need you to tell me
what you saw here tonight.
What happened?
Guzmán.
Relax, son.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Boys, lanes one and two.
Girls, three, four, and five.
-Any particular reason for this?
-For what?
For dividing us by gender,
not by skill level.
The best swimmers could be in lane one,
and the worst in lane five.
Just split up like I told you to.
On your marks…
Your next follow-up's not till next year,
which gives us three months to relax.
Azucena.
Please, come in.
Muñoz, go to class.
In his own words, the school has been
a truck going downhill
with no brakes for two years.
Fuck.
And he's here to fix it.
Starting now, it seems.
With no notice. He fired me
with the school year underway. At my age!
Fucking school. I'm going with you.
Don't be silly. You're staying right here.
See?
I should've gone backpacking.
I told you. Why am I wasting my time here?
Honey, this is your last year.
Then you're done.
I know. What's the point of graduating?
In case you change your mind
and decide to continue your studies.
Stay here with Omar.
Don't worry about me. I'll figure it out.
Where'd they find this dude?
Discipline.
Excellence. Achievement.
You might be asking yourself
what a CEO
is doing running a school like this.
The answer is very simple.
Like with any family,
whenever one of its members has a problem,
the father
quickly swoops in to the rescue.
And I think
we can all be in agreement that…
Let's be honest.
For the past few years,
Las Encinas has steered off course.
Thanks so much
for honoring us with your attention.
Shit, sorry. I just worked late--
No, no, no, no, no, no. No excuses.
No, I can't tolerate excuses.
Want some words to live by?
And this really goes for all of you.
Don't ever waste your time on excuses.
Instead, focus on…
those three simple words.
"Discipline, excellence, achievement."
Welcome to this brand-new chapter
of Las Encinas.
Great race today.
-Great rival.
-Honestly, I gave it my all.
I needed to get to know you better
so I could outthink your strategy.
I kinda just go into turbo mode
and don't think.
Well, maybe that's the secret,
not thinking too much
and going into turbo.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Ari.
Guzmán. Welcome to the school.
Thank you.
Hey.
-Were you at the new principal's talk?
-Yeah.
Doesn't he seem like that basic dude
who says he's nice but is just a poser?
But he's not a poser. He's really cool.
You know that 'cause…?
He's my father.
You're joking.
Ciao.
See ya later, Ari.
Hey.
What's up?
Hey, your eyes are wandering.
Wasn't checking out your package.
I was looking at your scar.
Was it serious?
Yeah, it was.
The fuck was that?
Car accident.
Yours?
Leukemia.
I almost died in the accident.
Bedridden for two years.
I had to do physical therapy
to move again.
They thought I was a goner for sure.
Until it miraculously went into remission.
But it could come back.
All right. You win.
It's nice, you know? Your package, FYI.
Since I was looking at your scar anyway,
I kind of thought…
Sorry. Didn't mean
to make you feel awkward.
That's okay.
And he's nice, too. All right.
When they're cute and nice,
they're straight.
My gaydar is pretty great.
You might want to get it tuned up,
your gaydar.
Nice ass, dude.
Since I was looking at your scar anyway.
I just got here from London,
so I'm a little lost here.
Well, let me know
if I can help in any way.
Great. Then you can take me around Madrid
and introduce me to the gay nightlife.
I don't know many gay clubs, you know.
Are you serious?
Mm-hmm.
Hey there, handsome.
This is Patrick.
Just got here from London.
Starting today, he's in our class.
My boyfriend, Omar.
Well, nice to meet you.
Kiss him hello.
Okay.
They kick you out of London
for being too European?
No. Because my father's
the school's new principal.
Omar Shanaa?
Can you come to my office a moment?
Our peaceful coexistence at this school
is built on the basis of honesty.
That includes all of us.
The principal must be honest
with his students and vice versa.
Can we agree on that?
So let's be honest.
Shanaa. Do you deserve a scholarship here?
-Of course he does--
-Please don't interrupt.
I mean, my sister also came here
on a scholarship, so--
Yes, it's an impressive record.
Your sister's, I mean.
She really did deserve to be here.
-Do you think you do?
-Azucena saw something in me.
Could you tell me what exactly?
Because if you failed
at an average public school, then, well…
…I don't think
it's because of your academic excellence.
I couldn't study
because I was taking care of my boyfriend.
He had leukemia.
I don't know if you've had
to take care of someone 24 hours a day--
Yes, I have. I'm aware of all that.
And… I really think
what you did was commendable.
I really do, but we need to understand
that when we are talking
about scholarships,
they're awarded for academic achievement,
not our personal circumstances.
You following so far? Good. Hmm.
García.
And you?
I have an 80% GPA.
But you were also expelled
for serious misconduct. Isn't that right?
Yes, but that was
due to personal circumstances.
And in this situation,
we're only assessing
academic achievement, right?
Since I don't want
the rest of your classmates
to think you're getting some kind of…
some kind of preferential treatment,
I'm gonna give you a placement exam
based on this past academic year
so that you can prove that you are,
in fact, deserving of the privilege
of having a scholarship to this school.
Hold on. What are you talking about?
Preferential treatment and privilege?
-Benjamín, I didn't go here last year--
-That's all for now. Have a good day.
I really dig your vibe.
If you don't think that's awkward.
Thanks, I guess. I don't know
what vibe, but feel free to say it.
It's not awkward.
I mean, your attitude,
the way you look,
the way you walk down the hall.
Honestly, just all of you.
Shit. You just gave me a full-body scan
in one split second.
Name's Rebeka, with a k.
And I let people
I think are cool call me Rebe.
Hi, Rebe.
I'm Mencía. Encantada.
My pleasure.
I'm sorry you're pissed off, Ander.
I'm not to blame
for the actions of my father.
for being pissed at what he did.
The thing with your boyfriend
and the other guy sucks.
And the mom thing.
-Let's be honest. This school needed--
-What?
Look, man.
I'm not saying your mother and Omar
were dealing drugs or killing anybody.
At least not that I know of.
But who knows, if someone like my dad
had been here to be,
maybe, more on top of things--
Here to patch things up with me
or just bust my balls, dude?
Patrick, what is this?
Look at him. He was just
puttin' the moves on me in the shower.
-Now he's some kind of badass?
-Ander, calm down.
You think I hit on you?
You don't have a fucking clue.
You and your father
can both go fuck yourselves.
Go on.
Come on.
Patrick.
What's up with this guy?
Okay, all right, all right.
Let me see if I get this straight.
The Barbie on the right
and Sauna Ken right there
are the new principal's children,
and today is your first day too.
Look, if it's any consolation, though,
I have pretty much exactly
the same opinion you do
about both my dad and my siblings.
Uh…
No.
Not gonna work for me.
Good luck now, sweetheart.
Maybe today you'll even talk to me.
Or not.
I get the hint.
Dad, it's always the same thing.
We come into a new place
like a fucking bulldozer.
-Watch your mouth.
-Sorry. Like a bulldozer.
And in the end,
we're the one they take it out on.
Can you define "bulldozer"?
Firing the other principal
out of nowhere, for example.
But that's what I came here for.
He didn't warn us
we were leaving London either. You know?
That's how Benjamín operates.
Mencía, please, let's not.
I got the cold shoulder
from my whole class today.
And you did, too.
Like, seriously,
you don't always have to take his side.
Did that happen?
No. It went great.
Let's get glasses to toast.
Sure, so I made it all up.
And the exam to kick out
the kids on scholarship? Why do that?
I get that you want to fix things,
but pace yourself.
What are you gonna have left
for next week?
You just got here. Your first morning,
you've turned the place on its head.
-Bam! I don't--
-Let's change the subject.
We're supposed to be celebrating us
all being in Madrid together,
if I can get a waiter.
-Ari. Jesus.
-Why's everyone so slow here in Spain?
And there's all these weird smells.
Um, like patchouli.
-Ari.
-Patrick.
Dad's on a mission.
We're here to support however we can.
No, we're only here 'cause we're minors.
If I was old enough,
I wouldn't be here looking at your faces.
You know, I almost forgot
how much of a treat you are.
Okay, look, I'm going home.
It's been fun,
but I'm sick of this posing.
-Mencía, sit down.
Forget it. With that attitude,
we don't even want her here.
Although, I do agree with Patrick.
-Maybe the exam for the scholarship kids…?
-Oh my. Some backup.
I mean, maybe you can give them
a weekly evaluation till Christmas
or something more gradual,
where they could study.
Would you please stop interfering
in my work?
Mencía is enough on your plate.
You're not making any progress with her.
Dad.
No, it's okay. He's not wrong.
I need the restroom.
I know, but this is super weird.
Nadia, please.
I'm gonna lose my hard-on. Fuck.
Nadia, I'm begging you.
I'm really sorry.
It's just… No can do. Can't do it.
Fuck. This is a nightmare.
I just wanna touch you.
What?
How's my brother doing?
Your brother's fine.
Your guy's there,
adapting, working hard, studying.
-You're looking out for him, aren't you?
-Of course I'm looking out for him.
I promised you I would, and I'm doing it.
You can picket all you want, do graffiti,
bend over backwards. It won't do anything.
Awesome. So why exactly
did you join us at the sit-in then?
To show you I'm on your side
and not your enemy.
And also, definitely
to bust my old man's balls a bit.
I guess I'm getting kicked to the curb.
No, maybe there is a way.
Benjamín has one massive weak spot,
my sister, Ari.
So I thought, if you sweet-talk her a bit,
she's the only one
able to convince my father.
We'll do it. Any volunteers?
You.
-Why me?
-What do you mean, "Why?"
The girl's bougie, pretty,
and apparently kind of a bitch.
So, basically, your type.
No, no, no. Samuel's invisible to Ari.
She'd be more into Guzmán.
Not all girls
are looking for rich guys like you are.
Cayetana, can you go back to mopping?
You missed a spot. Thanks.
Oh wow, you guys
are friends with the cleaning lady?
Ah, it's a long story, but, um…
we'll tell ya another time.
You're so inclusive. And I'm here for it.
And yeah, she's right. For Ari,
a guy like Samuel's practically invisible.
-Thanks.
-Guzmán.
No, forget it. I tried something like that
once before,
and you know how that turned out.
It ended with you getting together
with my sister.
And we're very happy together, Omar.
You don't have to fall in love with her,
you know.
-Just convince her to talk to her dad.
-Yeah, I know. But no.
Help me, O-Guzmán Kenobi.
You're my only hope.
Help me, dude.
-What?
What is it?
What is what?
-I mean, what's making you smile?
-I'm not smilin'.
Nothing. It's just, I think
maybe I kind of like your vibe too.
-Well, thanks.
-Thank you for havin' our backs out there.
So, do you have any plans for tonight?
You're lookin' pretty good yourself.
Do you want a drink… or anything?
Sounds like a plan.
Hey, are you and your brother and sister
triplets or something?
Patrick and Ari are the twins.
I'm the baby and the smartest kid.
-That's why I skipped one grade ahead.
-Ah.
Hey, can you please bring us two shots?
You know, it's funny.
I didn't take you for one of those girls
who falls apart over some dude.
Yeah. Me neither, believe me.
Until this one guy showed up…
and completely fucked me over.
Got it.
Guys are great if you wanna fuck
and take the edge off just a bit,
but when you wanna take things
to the next level…
I don't think I've experienced that level.
-So what's his name?
-What?
The guy who fucked with you.
Oh, uh,
one of the guys taking the exam. Samuel.
Who, that short dude?
Well, I mean, look.
He doesn't seem as short
when he's lying naked in bed.
-Yeah, sure.
-But you're right.
Well, I'll do what I can
to get you to totally drive his name
out of your mind
and replace it with another one.
That'd be…?
Mencía.
You're like a little time bomb, aren't ya?
And… And the fact is, right now,
I'm not sure I'm ready to have things
blow up in my face… again.
I get you.
But this has been great. Really great.
I mean, actually, it's been, like, months
since I've hung out with someone
the entire night like this
and felt so… so relaxed,
so… comfortable,
so good.
Well, that's just a small taste
of that whole next-level thing
I was telling you about.
I gotta peace out. Okay?
So, I'll see you.
I'll see you, uh, in class.
In a few hours, I guess. Ciao.
Thank you, María.
Where's Mencía?
It's always the same with you.
You're a train wreck.
-Are you just coming in right now?
-Yeah. It was a night.
I, um, I actually had to take a friend
to the, um… to the ER.
I'm dead tired. I'm going to bed.
Dad, I got her.
Mencía, are you seriously
not even gonna bother coming up with
a more credible excuse?
This is none of your business.
Stay out of it.
Of course it's my business
because you're hurting me too.
I mean,
haven't you hurt us all enough as it is?
Wow, Ari.
That was an incredibly,
incredibly low blow.
-You know what I was trying to say.
-For the last time, get out of my face.
Oh, hey.
Well, you weren't a big fan
of the sit-in and protest, I gather.
We've learned
we've got to have each other's backs here.
-Well, I'm partial to helping my family.
-Yeah.
Hey, why don't we start over?
Just pick up
where we left off after the race.
Wait, from what point?
The point when you said
my dad was a poser pretending to be nice?
No, when you said you needed
to get to know me better
so you could beat me or whatever.
-Mm-hmm.
-You know what I think?
If you knew me,
you still couldn't beat me.
But I'm willing to let you get to know me
just a smidge.
Then we'll see.
Wanna go get a drink after school?
Hmm.
Ander,
it sucks that things got fucked up today.
'Cause the way we started out
was fuckin' amazing.
Why don't we go out tonight
and patch this up?
There's a gay meetup thing today
at the Barceló Theatre.
Great music and hot guys.
And don't worry about your boyfriend.
I'm, uh, gonna try to steal
the answers to the test
from my dad somehow.
And?
He's implying
if you go out and suck his dick…
…then maybe, sure,
he might give you the answers
to the exam tomorrow.
Ander, Mencía was very clear.
Ari's our target.
You don't have to go
anywhere near Patrick.
-Okay?
-Mm-hmm.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Let's cut to the chase.
-Thanks. Okay. About what?
What do I need to know about you
to beat you?
Why so obsessed with winning?
Oh, 'cause you're not obsessed?
I used to be.
Then life put my priorities in check.
Come on.
You sound like an old man.
What are you, 40?
Well, when your sister dies
at the age of 16,
then your best friend dies,
and your girlfriend starts a new life--
Wait, you have a girlfriend?
Of all the things I said,
that's all you heard?
Well, I already know
what it's like to lose someone
and have your whole life
turned upside down.
You don't look
like you've ever lost anything.
What's the last thing you've lost?
A hamster?
My mother.
And almost my brother too.
She died in a car accident.
I'm sorry. I'm a dickhead.
I've lost three hamsters.
And I'm still trying to get over it.
You also bring your girlfriend here?
The past's the past, you know?
Hey.
In our class,
is everyone as personable
and charming as you are,
or are you one of a kind?
Well, thanks.
They're just on their guard
'cause of your father.
But if you loosen up, they will too.
-You'll be one of the gang.
-Loosen up?
The whole exam for Samuel and Omar,
you don't think that's a bit cruel?
Look, maybe there are other ways to prove
that they deserve the scholarship.
Hmm. Could you ask your dad
to maybe let up a bit?
I already hinted as much,
but once my father
makes his mind up about something…
I see.
But, anyway, maybe I can try again.
Hey, would you?
That's fucking great. Thanks.
Really, thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
No.
Uh, do you wanna come out to dinner
with me and your sister?
Go out with… why?
So we can spend some time together
and open a dialogue.
I think it's a good idea.
Patrick suggested it, but--
But he's not coming? That's Patrick.
He makes a mess and then runs away.
-Are you coming or not?
-Yeah, no. Sounds good, but I'll pass.
Okay, look, um,
I'm tired of making an effort with you.
-I'm done.
-Dad, come on.
No, just… just forget it. It's clear
you're not capable of handling her.
Now that's more the tone
I expected out of you, Benjamín.
Let's be honest, it was…
Well, it wasn't really your thing.
That perfect father-of-the-year vibe.
You couldn't even fool yourself.
How's this?
From this moment forward,
you're blocked from accessing my money
on all your accounts.
I'll give you whatever is required by law.
No more, no less.
Fine. Then I'll just get a job, won't I?
-Oh, you will?
-Mm-hmm.
In what?
You haven't worked a day
in your miserable life.
Mencía. You brought this all on yourself.
I don't know how to make you understand
you don't have to fight Dad and us.
Look, Patrick went out
with some classmates today.
And I--
You had a date with Guzmán,
and you're floating on air, aren't you?
You're such an idiot.
Guzmán went out with you
to get those guys out of that exam.
I know 'cause it was my idea.
Yeah. Ari, they're all using you.
So drop it.
He's majorly in love with his girlfriend
and wants nothing to do with you.
All he wanted
was to talk you into convincing Benjamín
because that's all anyone
is going to be interested in you for, Ari.
Or did you really let yourself think
a guy like Guzmán would be interested?
Have you taken a look at yourself?
Wake up! You look like an idiot.
I'M LEAVING HOME RIGHT NOW.
I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU.
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU WHERE WE MET LAST NIGHT.
Shit.
May I?
Thanks.
Can I sit with you?
Listen, thanks for the drink,
but I'd rather just keep sitting here.
-Alone.
-Well, when you put it that way.
Someone stand you up?
All right, all right.
See you later.
Hold up.
Sorry.
I feel like a bitch.
You didn't deserve
the way I just treated you.
Have a seat if you want.
What's in the bag?
I'm kinda looking for a place to crash.
Ah?
Excuse me. Another round.
This place is great.
Welcome to paradise.
What's the matter?
Is it about Mencía?
No.
I'm okay.
-Benjamín.
-Yes, uh, dessert.
-Ari, you want to share--
-No.
I'm not here to take your order.
I'm working bar up there.
Sorry to bother you,
but I'd like to talk to you.
Right now?
You're unbelievable.
-Oh, did you already tell him, or…
-What? Tell me what?
This is about tomorrow's exam, I assume?
Because it seems like everything
is about that damn test.
-Ari.
-No, he's gonna ask you to excuse him.
-Is that it?
-No.
-Right?
-If I have to take the exam, I'll take it.
It's about Omar.
Please don't make him take it.
-Anything for dessert?
-Wait just a second.
No. Yes, we do want dessert.
Dude, can you take a walk
and come back in a few? Okay?
Listen to me. You asked him
whether he deserved to be at Las Encinas.
Well, he does, I promise.
He always gives 150%.
He helps his parents,
his boyfriend, and he helps me.
Because I'm his best friend,
and we live together.
And he's the only family I have, sir.
And I'm so sick of it.
Losing all the people
I care about the most.
-Samuel, what's going on here?
-Nothing.
I am so sorry.
-No, no, really. It's no big deal.
-I'll take care of this.
Of course, this will all be on the house.
My apologies.
Go collect your things
'cause you're fired.
You think I should listen to you?
Forget about the exam?
Find another evaluation method?
No.
Give them the exam tomorrow.
Hey, Satan. What are you doing?
Satan? Moi? I'm a sweet little cherub.
Cherub, my ass, dude.
-What're you up to?
-Nothing.
Well, go do nothing over there.
I have a boyfriend.
Yeah, but did you know it's not cheating
if the action's over the clothes?
-Oh, it's not?
-Uh-uh.
So, that's that. So back the fuck off.
Don't misbehave. Hey!
But I'm not doing anything.
It sounded like
you wouldn't hook up with me
even if someone paid you, right?
Are you hooking up with me right now?
You aren't, are you? So, that's that.
Here's a secret.
It's riskier to try and tell yourself no
than it is to say yes.
And your clothes are on,
so it's not cheating.
Stop, man. Stop.
Look, how far would you go to help Omar?
Or is this no longer about helping him?
Okay, that's enough. All right?
I'd do anything I could to help Omar.
Just like he did everything for me
when I couldn't get out of my fucking bed.
I'd do anything but betray him.
It's all yours.
No need to worry about your father
or anything.
Whatever you need,
as long as you need it. Okay?
Um, but hold on a minute.
I don't know if--
No,
I have more than one room in my name.
-It's for work.
-Oh.
Meetings, celebrities, and all that.
Um, well, okay.
What do you do, then?
Um, you know
when a politician's really powerful?
Like a president or a minister,
for instance?
Well, actually, they don't have
that much power. 'Cause I'm in charge.
-Like Rasputin.
-Ah.
I read a lot. I'm also extremely smart.
Yep.
Well,
if you ever need anything or get hungry,
call up room service and have them
put it on my bill. All right?
Appreciate it.
Are you all right?
Uh, yeah. Fine.
It's just that, I mean,
it's a very big room
to sleep in all alone.
Would you consider staying here
and sleeping with me?
-Just sleep, you mean?
-Yes.
-No.
-No?
Okay. Good night.
Armando.
You're name's Armando, right?
-Mm-hmm.
-Um…
Come on and stay.
Dad, Mencía's gone.
She'll be back.
Yeah, but Dad…
She can't go far without any money.
And I think we're used to this sort
of stunt she pulls to get attention.
16 MISSED CALLS
EVERYTHING IS OK
Shanaa, in an hour, you and García
take the exam in the computer lab.
That's it. I'm completely fucked.
Hello, pretty boys.
Leave us alone, will you?
You might be interested in this.
The answers?
So, you went out last night after all?
Well, you have the answers there.
That's what matters.
I see.
Is there anything I should know, or…?
Mm, no. We just danced a bit.
-Right?
-Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I didn't think
he'd give them to us. But look.
How do we know these are even accurate?
-Why would I wanna dick you over?
-To get me out of the way? I don't know.
Look,
we got off to a fucking terrible start.
And this is the only way
I could think of to apologize.
If you wanna know if I really mean it,
just use those answers and find out.
LOAD EXAM RESULTS
Seventy-three out of 100.
You passed.
I spoke to your manager…
to ask him to hire you back again.
I explained to him
that you were only trying to help.
Thank you.
But García,
let me offer you a word of advice.
Sure.
Stop fighting other people's battles
for them, and focus on your own.
All that being said,
you displayed great confidence,
your argument was concise,
direct, a clearly stated thesis.
And although you went a little overboard
with the emotions,
it was a sound strategy.
I can never have too many students
at this school
who have such a facility with words.
Welcome.
All right.
How do you think you did on the exam?
Um… mm…
I did okay. Uh, I think so.
You just think?
Ninety-seven out of one hundred.
Someone who got an almost-perfect grade
knows they did.
It takes someone who's incredibly dense
to get almost 100%
when they're trying to cheat.
Yeah, well…
Mm, either dense or a hard worker.
Okay then.
I guess I'm staying right here
with my scholarship,
my uniform, the works.
That'll be all.
Great. Have a good day.
And?
-So? Tell us.
-That's awesome. Look at you!
Really, what did you get?
Uh, 97.
-You serious?
-You did?
And look at that. You were so worried.
That's so wild. That's crazy.
Yeah, and he was so worried.
Hey, dude. Um…
Hey, thanks a lot.
I mean it.
-It's nothing.
-Thank you.
-Ah, yes!
-Oh man!
Did you tell your father yet?
-No, I haven't.
-So, all we did was dance?
-You don't think that.
-Your sister's gonna flip.
Seriously.
Mm.
Hi.
Guzmán.
This is your girlfriend's Instagram, yeah?
-Yeah.
-Hmm.
I've been chatting with her.
She is such a sweetheart.
We got along super well.
Told her about our date yesterday.
The way the sparks flew, all of it.
Come on.
Go to your posts. Move it!
You ready?
Guzmán, get in the water.
I told you
I only needed to get to know you better
so I could beat you.
You lied to me to get what you wanted,
and I just lied to you.
You.
What?
Tell your friend I haven't written
to his girlfriend so he can breathe.
If either of you thought
you could dominate or get one over on me,
well, think twice next time.
The girl is alive.
I repeat, the girl is alive.