Did you team up
with his family to bring him here
and shield him
from the rumors in his country?
What rumors?
What?
Nothing.
Is there something I should know?
Care to maybe enlighten me?
-No, nothing.
-Where's Mencía?
She won't pick up.
I've texted and called a thousand times.
She's not even here?
I expressly asked you to make sure
this kind of thing didn't happen.
I'm sorry, but I can't keep an eye on her
24 hours a day.
We can stop if you need to.
I want you to feel comfortable.
So you don't get the wrong idea,
this… is our last time doing this.
See what happens.
Yes, Mom.
Benjamín said he'd be here
with his three kids.
They'll be in my class.
Don't worry.
Thanks. I love you.
Let's talk tomorrow.
It's a pleasure to meet you in person.
The pleasure is mine. Welcome.
I'll introduce you to my children.
Patrick.
-Hello. How are you?
-A pleasure.
-The pleasure's mine.
-Ariadna.
Hello.
How are you?
Nice to meet you.
Her blood alcohol content
is three milligrams.
And if she's not used to drinking…
Did she fall, or did someone push her?
Well, we actually don't know for sure.
These first 48 hours will be
the most critical for your daughter.
Phillipe Florian von Triesenberg
is the second youngest heir in Europe.
-He opened le Bal two years ago.
-Wow. Hmm.
-The debutante ball in Paris.
-Hmm.
-You know?
-No.
But above all, I mean, come on.
Isn't he so pretty?
Not only is he a babe, he's a fashion icon
and a patron
of all the best international designers.
And I bet you didn't know
he's fluent in four languages.
He grew up
in the best boarding schools here,
in the UK,
and Switzerland, so he's super elegant.
He's handsome,
and he's got royal and commoner,
French and Spanish blood.
It's in his blood.
Let me see if I'm right.
Are you putting together
some animated fantasy in your head
where this dude, this Florence,
is gonna make you a famous designer
and give you some kind
of royal happily ever after?
Florian, not Florence. And no.
I just wanted to share this information.
Great. I'd like to share that you'd
better get your helmet on, Cinderella.
You're in for a head-on collision, kid.
That's why they set up the gate
and the cameras?
Because this guy's coming to study here?
Yeah, that's exactly what it is.
And the measures
aren't gonna stop there either.
Look. A better picture of him.
-Gee, thanks.
-I'll be right back.
So, this necktie is a choice. Okay.
What's goin' on?
You have a minute?
What do you want?
Sweet-talk me into convincing my dad
to remove the cameras?
No.
I came to tell you I'm sorry.
-It wasn't all a game. I promise.
-What part wasn't?
I really enjoyed
our walk around the reservoir.
Walk? I remember you calling it a date.
Okay, our date.
So, the date was real, then?
And what else was real?
-The connection between us.
-Yeah, I thought it was real too.
-The laughs about my guinea pig.
-Your girlfriend?
My girlfriend is very real.
I'm really sorry.
I'm gonna let this slide…
but don't have a connection
with anyone else
as long as you have a girlfriend.
Okay?
Okay.
It's a deal.
Hey, there's been a weird vibe
between you and Ari ever since the date.
Flirty banter at the pool, talking alone,
staring deep into each other's eyes.
It's all a little--
We had a misunderstanding,
but that's cleared up.
Aren't you going to try
to get together with her?
Samuel, I have a girlfriend.
-Oh, all right. Wasn't sure there.
-What's the matter? You into her?
Who, me? No way. Don't worry.
I'm not gonna hit on her or anything.
Oh, okay, all right.
"Oh, okay, all right," what?
Would you lose it
if I did make a move on her?
No, I don't give a shit.
-Good, 'cause you have a girlfriend.
-Yeah.
-But I'm saying this for you, not for me.
-What?
I say this as a friend.
You're out of your league with her.
Oh, I see what you're doing.
You're either jealous, or you've gone back
to being the classist prick you were.
Look, I'm saying this
to protect you, okay?
I know you got a taste of a marquise,
but be real,
Carla was the best you're gonna do.
Ari isn't just out of your orbit.
She's fucking Pluto.
You're Earth. Understand?
-Like fucking Pluto, huh?
-Yeah.
Okay.
Come on. Don't be pissed at me.
Where were you last night?
Out.
Can I at least ask who with?
A friend of mine.
Okay. Which friend?
Benjamín, I'm leaving.
Otherwise, I'll be late for class,
and you'll get upset with me.
Mencía. Mencía!
Uh, excuse me.
Yes?
It's saying, "Criminal record"?
Which part don't you understand,
"criminal" or "record"?
Because they're both
pretty common words, Parrilla.
No, I got that part.
What I don't understand
is why they're asking about our personal
and immediate family's records.
Isn't that private information?
Hmm. Actually,
in your case and your mother's case,
that info's public and well known.
You can leave it blank.
The Principality of Triesen
is asking for information
about their heir's classmates, not me.
Though it doesn't seem unreasonable
that they would want to assess
who is taking classes
and sharing this space with him.
Right?
Rebe.
Are you all right?
Fuckin' peachy.
Come on.
Stop stressing yourself out about it.
Are you serious right now?
He's kicking people out.
That's not exactly what he said.
Cool. Shut up. I wasn't talking to you.
-Okay.
-You said it yourself.
This dude pretends to be polite,
but he came here looking for blood.
Who will be the first to go, huh?
Go ahead.
My mom spent last semester in the clink.
I was dealing with stuff here.
We're two for the price of one
for that son of a bitch Benjamín.
Okay, I get
that we wanna blame those around us
rather than accepting responsibility
for our mistakes,
but in this case, as you all heard,
this is the royal house's decision,
not my father's.
Don't worry, Rebeka. You're not
the only family with criminal records.
Take Samuel's brother.
What about your dad?
Did you forget? Though he's rich,
they know him by name at the precinct.
Right now, as far as the royals
and Benjamín are concerned,
you and I are no different, dude.
Same level of total bullshit.
PEEP INTO THE CLASSROOM.
GIVE ME TEN MINUTES.
THAT'S ALL I'M ASKING.
Rebe.
I really like you.
And… I have this sneaking suspicion
that you like me too.
So I don't understand why you keep
running away from me like that.
And what makes you think
I like you in that way? Hmm?
Well, I mean,
for starters, the last time I…
I did this to you…
…it also took you a while to pull away.
Look, I'm sorry,
but I just don't…
You need to get out of here.
The room needs to be searched
top to bottom.
So, tell me.
Has the world ended since I kissed you?
Huh? Tell me.
Has anything changed regarding
the way things were just five minutes ago?
Your dad's face. Now he's got
a reason to kick me to the curb.
Okay, so now you're gonna use my dad
as an excuse to avoid dealing with this?
Mencía, please drop it.
Let's just go about our separate ways.
It's really not that hard. No.
Could you just do me this favor?
We'd better not go near her,
'cause her shock waves
might blow us right into next week.
-They have a little something going on?
-Sure seems like it.
Think Rebeka went off on her
just 'cause she's a girl?
-No, she's not like that.
-That's not it.
I know what the problem is.
I mean, I can imagine.
Why don't you ask her
to the Lake Club for dinner tonight
so I can talk with her?
Because if I ask her,
she'll tell me to go fuck myself.
Dad says when you disappear all night,
it's 'cause you're off with Rebeka.
Oh, well,
if Benjamín says it, then it must be true.
And he also says that
she pays for you.
Mencía, do you know
where Rebeka gets that money from?
From the ATM.
Exactly like you.
Yeah.
Benjamín caught us kissing earlier.
Got a problem with that?
Are you serious?
'Kay, so you're a lesbian now, or what?
Who cares?
I'm really not into labeling myself.
Not in what I do or what I feel.
-I don't know. You get what I mean?
-Sure.
That you're a bit of an attention whore.
Mencía, I, um… I hope you understand
I'm not gonna let you get with this girl.
Rebeka's bad news.
REBE, SORRY TO BE A PAIN. CAN WE TALK?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
-Hey, a message from Mencía.
-The hell are you doin'?
HI, ARMANDO.
MAYBE WE COULD MEET ONE MORE TIME.
IF YOU WANT TO.
Fuck. Nadia pushed our video call back
another hour.
Why am I always the one who has to adapt?
Sometimes I think I'm the only one
who's making an effort here.
It's cool. I'll just be here,
slowly losing my mind.
Come on. Chill out, dude.
I mean, you guys are cool, though, right?
We're fine. Thanks, Omar.
Shit, the only way we see each other
in a bar is if you visit us at work.
-Things have changed this school year.
-I almost miss the old days.
Well, actually,
I'm still serving you guys drinks,
so I haven't really noticed
a difference personally, but…
You know what we should do?
Do like before and throw a real banger.
-All right. Please.
-Yes. So, what's the overall… vibe?
-High-class or low-class?
-This will be strictly for us old-timers.
We can have the party
at our house, right?
Although,
why are we only inviting the old-timers?
Who do you want to invite?
Who do you not want to?
-Well, Benjamín's kids, for one.
-Yeah. No, Benjamín's kids are out.
See? So now I'm curious
who it was you wanted to invite to it.
Ooh!
-Samuel, just the old-timers. No one else.
-All right. Okay.
Hey, have you seen the lake?
I haven't, but it's not like
my life depended on it, either.
It's beautiful. Come on. Check it out,
and I'll go and meet you in five minutes.
Great. Just what I needed.
-Move, or you're in the water.
-Not until you hear me out.
-We've been like this for several months.
-And that's not long enough.
I know I really hurt you,
but how can I make things go back
to the way they were before with us?
Look at me.
Okay.
Anything else? Whatever you want.
Okay, look, Samuel.
What do you think?
That with a couple hugs and kisses
and "I'm sorry,"
everything's gonna be the way it was?
I already know you're sorry.
No shit. You goddamn better be sorry.
Then please, just tell me what to do.
Don't do anything.
You did more than enough.
You've royally fucked me.
You lied to and humiliated me, dude.
What else could you do to me?
So after all of this, it's up to me,
and not you, whether we can be friends.
Okay.
Is there more
to this besties heart-to-heart chat,
or are we done here? Okay, then.
I'm just askin'
that you don't shut yourself off
from other people.
Just 'cause I'm a dick and fucked you over
doesn't mean everyone else will too.
Hello.
You're new here, honey.
Mm, yeah. I don't come here much.
He looks familiar. He a friend of yours?
He regularly comes here…
with girls like you.
What do you mean, "like me"?
Aren't you a bit young
to be doing this, sweetheart?
Doing what, exactly?
Look, lady, you've no fucking clue
what's going on between us.
Of course I know, dear.
I'm sure it's an awesome hourly rate.
At least I hope it's awesome
because young skin is worth twice as much.
Although, I've always felt like experience
should be worth more, but…
Get your hands off me.
I just hope you know what you're doing,
if you really think you're so grown up.
-Is the little guy still sleeping?
-Shh, I'm tryin' to concentrate.
Omar, could we talk for a sec?
Great. Just what I needed.
A verbal play-by-play.
Well, it's just that…
well, sex isn't just shoving it in.
-Oh, it's not?
-No.
What do you mean?
It's about skin.
And wordplay.
Mm… and… fantasies.
What are these fantasies of yours?
Well, the other day,
with Patrick, he… made a move.
I thought you said all you did was dance.
Well, you know. The usual horsing around.
Sure, the usual stuff.
-'Cause that's the norm.
-Shut up and listen.
At one point during the night,
we were super high.
We were dancing,
sweating, rubbing against each other.
And he started kissing me over my clothes.
He said, "It's not cheating
if your clothes are on."
I let him for a sec.
Then I stopped him because of the guilt.
You felt guilty 'cause he made you horny?
-Can I be honest with you?
-I mean, yeah. We're always honest.
Not horny.
Horny as hell.
And he wouldn't stop. I kept saying,
"Stop, stop," but he kept having his way.
He started kissing me all over my neck
and then very slowly working his way down.
And when he got down to my fly,
I could feel his breath.
A hard-on? What does that mean?
What?
Phillipe?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh. It's just… how's your shoulder?
That's fine. Leave her.
-Recover from that accident?
-I did.
-Yeah?
-I'm fine. It was nothing.
-Oh.
-Thanks.
That accident.
I'm sorry for straight-up jumping you,
like, phew.
I just had to say hi to you.
If… If I didn't, I wouldn't have…
I wouldn't have slept for,
I don't know, weeks.
Um, Cayetana. An honor.
Enchanté. And keeping you up
at night's the last thing I want to do.
I was told people in Spain
give each other two kisses on the cheek.
Yeah, we do.
But are you allowed to do that?
-Of course. Nice to meet you.
-Yeah?
-Phillipe?
-Nice to meet you.
-Welcome to Las Encinas.
-Thank you.
Cayetana, I'm so glad you're here.
Someone spilled coffee
in the computer lab, and it's gross.
Can you go clean it up?
Um…
Was the cleaning lady bothering you?
Uh, no. Not at all.
I was just introducing myself to everyone.
Employees included.
Au revoir.
Cayetana.
Trust me. I get the concept that,
for a cleaning lady,
one day becoming a princess
is as alluring as honey is to flies.
But remember,
honey isn't meant for the donkey's mouth.
Don't go after someone who isn't for you.
Ciao.
Did they throw her in there on purpose?
Who was it?
They don't know a thing.
Or they don't want us to know anything.
Are you okay?
I'm gonna…
uh, splash my face with water.
-He turns you on. Admit it.
-Jesus. No, he doesn't.
See?
All right. Ander, he's attractive.
Anyone can see that.
I didn't get hard 'cause he turns me on.
I got hard 'cause he turned you on.
So, yes, I mean, I guess it turns me on,
imagining you being turned on by him.
So fine, that's true.
Yeah, you see how fantasies work?
Yeah.
Let's get in the shower.
So, if you're turned on by Patrick,
and maybe it turns me on
that he turns you on…
What? Ask him to join us?
I mean, if we establish
it would still always be you and me
with another person.
Like a couples' deal. That's all.
-Oh, now it's your turn getting a hard-on.
-Well, of course.
I mean, as long as we promise each other
it stays me and you, then…
We'll always stay us.
-How the hell do we pop the question?
-I don't know. Just try asking the guy.
People must do it all the time.
Boys,
I need you to vacate this area.
Come on.
Why, Dad? Uh, I mean, Benjamín.
It'll only be for 15 minutes,
so out you go, please.
Come on.
I wonder if this guy's balls
are as blue as his blood.
Okay, let me get this straight.
Your father kicked us out of the showers
so the fucking little prince can be
by himself?
Hey. Go complain to Benjamín.
I'm out here half-naked,
just like the rest of you.
I think that was a bit over-the-top.
Look, I can't take credit for it.
That was all your father.
You serious?
Can I ask what you're doing out here?
We thought if His Royal Douchiness
is too good to share the showers
with all of our plebeian asses,
he probably won't want to share the class.
Maybe it's not the poor dude's fault.
Maybe it's his parents, or…
I… I mean,
it's probably hard being royalty.
So now you're taking his side
just to suck up to Ari?
No.
I know what it's like to be shat on
for having less than everyone.
We're shitting on him for having more.
Jesus, Samuel,
you're so quick to sell out.
-What do you mean? I'm not selling out--
-Yeah, yeah. Whatever.
You're really bustin' my balls, man.
I am? I wonder why.
-Don't test my patience. Okay? Bye now.
-Unbunch your panties.
Yeah?
Two cocky guys fighting over you.
They're fighting over Phillipe.
Um… uh, I don't know.
Am I allowed to look you in the eyes or…?
I'm just a cleaning lady.
I get it if His Highness doesn't want his,
um, cool friends to see him
with the janitor.
Hmm?
Oh, you don't have any.
But actually, I'm thinking of starting
a special little club
for everyone getting the silent treatment
at this school.
-Oh yeah? And who would be in it?
-You.
Me, depending on the day.
Well, this club doesn't sound very fun.
-No?
-How do I quit?
Hmm. It's complicated.
Well, to start,
you'd have to win over the club's founder.
That would be me.
And second, you'd need to tone down
that royal cockiness
just a couple of notches.
I accept.
As long as you tone down
the groupie behavior
a couple notches as well.
Ouch.
I'm sorry.
The founder's kind of been
a lifelong fan of yours
and knows too much, honestly.
And now it feels
like she knows you personally.
Look, if you want, we can start over.
Yes, that's better. Let's do it.
-Nice to meet you.
-Likewise.
-I'm Phillipe.
-Cayetana.
Although, um, I was told people in Spain
give each other two kisses on the cheek.
Yeah.
Enchanté.
I mean, half the planet would kill
to have Phillipe von Triesenberg
at their party.
What happened to old-timers only?
Guys, the only thing Phillipe wants
is the same as any normal person,
rich or poor.
He just wants to fit in.
Can he come or not?
-Sure, invite him. Why not?
-Yeah?
Awesome.
Ari!
You comin' tonight?
-Where?
-There's a party at my place.
Okay.
Hmm. You won't like it.
-It's not on-brand for you.
-Guzmán.
I've been to humble homes before.
Yeah, but it's not the house.
It's the theme.
What theme?
To celebrate that us OGs
don't mind sharing everything,
including the showers,
unlike the little prince,
we're gonna have a party, and it's, uh,
a good old towel party.
-What do you mean?
-No, shut up. That's cool.
Each person
is only allowed to bring one towel.
And to be honest, I don't see the prince
or you being into it.
What? No way. Phillipe doesn't mind
getting undressed in front of whoever.
The thing
with the showers was imposed on him.
Well, I'm bringing my best towel.
Unless you don't want me there,
'cause I get the feeling you don't.
Me? No, it's good.
Since you're officially invited now.
So, there's no possible reason
you wouldn't want me there, right?
-None at all.
-Great.
-Thanks, Samuel.
-Don't mention it.
-See you there.
-That's right.
Mencía.
We'd love for you to come to a party
at my house tonight. Are you up for it?
Uh, yeah, sure. Thank you.
You got it.
It's on me. What do you want?
-Let's do shots.
-Right now?
Of course. To warm things up.
Go big or go home.
You go this full-out on everything, or…?
After spending two years in bed,
unable to move,
I'm not really someone who sits around
waiting for things to just happen.
I see what I want, go for it, and get it.
Cheers to us.
-Ugh, that's nasty.
-Ugh.
All right, I'm going to the john.
You've got a better way with words.
So, what were you saying earlier?
You go after what you want,
and you always get it?
I want it all.
Like, all the time.
You mean you want everyone all the time?
A slight difference there.
Listen, don't get it twisted here.
The libertine lifestyle
and partying doesn't make me happy.
What I actually want
is something really… worthwhile, you know?
But that feels practically impossible.
Why's that?
Okay, well, assuming your soulmate
hasn't already died or not been born yet,
the possibilities of finding them
are one in 10,000 lifetimes.
Honestly,
I don't buy the whole soulmates thing.
It means just a marketing gimmick to me.
But sure, all right. I'll humor you.
So, what do you call you and Ander, then?
Pfft.
I mean, call it whatever you want.
But, uh…
…you know when you fuck somebody
and look 'em in the eyes,
and in that moment,
time stands still?
And for five seconds,
you get this feeling.
There's nothing else but them.
And you can't help yourself but to smile.
Of course you know it.
Because you got to have that
with each other in this lifetime.
Hey. Welcome.
-Hi.
-Come in.
Check it out. That there's the bathroom.
And my room, in case you want to change.
-You want a drink?
-What?
-Do you want a drink?
-I don't drink alcohol.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
Ari. Come on. Get your towel and drink up.
-Patrick, I don't drink. You know that.
-Yeah, except for when you do.
Come on. I want Ira to come to the party.
She's awesome.
Who is Ira?
She's like your cool alter ego
when you're drunk. Your dark side.
Ari, Ira.
That's the dream team.
Hey there.
Here, come on. Let's summon Ira.
Okay, I'll have a little,
but just 'cause my mouth is dry.
Sure, whatever.
Unfortunately, there's no garbagemen
here for your amusement this time.
Garbagemen who?
About seven in the morning?
It was August, in Biarritz.
Want me to show you the video?
-No.
-I figured.
I came up with the towel party idea.
-Hi.
-And I said, "Why not?"
Hello. How you doing?
I'm great. How are you tonight?
I'm great.
I have an idea. Wanna dance?
Or chitchat a bit?
Or chitchat while dancing?
Excuse me.
-Is Nadia your girlfriend?
-Yeah.
-Oh.
-Hey. How are you, sweetie?
Mm, are you naked right now?
No, I'm wearing a towel.
Hi. Look.
We're dressed in towels
at your brother's house.
He's having a party.
There they are.
And that girl is?
Oh, she's one of the new kids here.
They just joined our class.
Guzmán, I can barely hear you.
Can you please find a quieter spot?
You can't hear me? Wait, one minute.
Are you just gonna stare at me,
or are you gonna come out and say it?
-Do I really look that bad in a towel?
-Not at all. You look fuckin' awesome.
It's just that,
once it gets to be this late,
between the hot outfits
and the buzz, well…
-What do you expect?
-What?
Well, so…
It's just… we wanted to ask you if, uh…
-What?
-Let's see.
Mm, well, would you like to, um,
join us to… uh, to, like,
Go on a… a night out?
-No.
-A party?
I mean, to like…
You mean a three-way?
Yes.
Well, why didn't you just come out
and say that?
'Cause of what you said earlier.
That now you're looking to settle down.
The thing about the five seconds
versus going around,
having meaningless sex.
This late and dressed in a towel?
Now is not when you settle down.
So, to your room?
Now? Already?
Come on.
-I think we should talk.
-Hold on.
Oof.
Nadia, are you seriously
gonna get mad at me for partying?
You're in New York.
You can do what you want,
and I'm fine with that.
Well, I'm not angry or anything.
It's just that I'm here studying,
and you're--
And I'm partying. Say it.
Look, um…
I mean, don't you realize that
this only goes to show
that our lives are like night and day?
Like, literally.
Does this seem like a normal,
healthy relationship
that's going somewhere to you?
Yes.
To me, it does. Yeah.
Okay, look, I'm sorry.
But, really, I'm very sorry.
I… I just have a lot of baggage.
A shit ton.
Just packed full of… of insecurities,
full of fears, full of--
Shh.
It… It's hot,
but it bums me out just a smidge
when you keep shutting me up like that.
Just sayin'.
I want you to forget your fears, okay?
Like, I'm in a towel.
I can't be that scary.
Yes, queens! Bravo, bravo, bravo!
Long live love. I'm so here for it!
Oh, Mencía, I'm so over the moon for you.
Honestly, girl. It's true.
I'm just so glad to see you super happy
and, like, content.
Mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah! Ah…
You deserve the absolute best, honey.
And so do you, Rebeka.
Mwah!
What are you doin'?
I'm making an executive decision.
No more looking
for the perfect place and time.
The place is here.
The time is now.
I thought you didn't drink.
Funny, and I thought
you didn't undress in public
'cause your nipples
are too fancy and royal.
-Oh.
-Oh, fuck.
Who's that hunk over there?
He's in our class, I think.
-Really?
-Pretty sure this is his party.
Oh yeah, he opened the door for me.
-Hi.
-Hi there. How are you?
-Great, how are you?
-I'm great now.
Oh, I'm so glad.
I didn't think you'd come.
-Why not?
-Because we're not part of the same class.
What do you mean?
Phillipe just told me we were.
You are messing with me.
No.
We're not part of the same social class.
Not like our school.
Oh, all right. I get you.
Well, when I drink,
I forget all about stupid old class.
-Really?
-Yeah. In every sense of the word.
-Yeah.
-Because "class" is super polysemic.
And polysyllabic.
So, when I drink, I forget every last bit.
-Mm.
-That's why I don't drink.
I get the feeling
she prefers waiters to princes.
-Tough break.
-It's possible.
-I know.
-Mm-hmm.
-Wanna dance with me?
-Sure.
Come on, then.
I really admire what you do.
But why? What have I done in my life
to make you admire me?
Shit, where do I start?
You can wear whatever you want,
but you gamble on young designers
who normally get zero exposure,
and you give them just that.
Yeah, that's it.
Who was your seed designer?
Huh?
Those of us who like fashion
all have that one special designer
who planted that first seed.
For example, mine is Silvio Alessandro--
…de la Guardia. Sadelagu.
-You're kidding me. He's yours as well?
-Of course.
What's the matter?
You're used to smiling and all the girls
falling at your feet, aren't you?
Well, just maybe,
that tactic won't work with me.
Sure.
Let me see if I get this right, okay?
What you want is to play it cool
and reject me
so that eventually,
I'll end up falling in love with you.
-Oh.
-I can tell you how that tactic ends.
Badly, right?
Best scenario, you are in the friend zone.
Oof. Friend zone?
-Mm-hmm.
-Fatal.
-Isn't it?
-We don't like the friend zone at all.
-We don't like it?
-No.
-Here's the problem.
-What?
I wanna kiss you, but I won't
take advantage of a drunk girl.
-Are you drunk right now?
-No.
-You're not?
-Then I'll kiss you.
-Okay.
Nadia.
Hi.
Hey, listen.
I've been thinking.
And you're right.
We're in over our heads,
and we can't get them above water.
It doesn't make any sense to keep trying.
Let's give each other
a couple days to think it over, okay?
Okay. That would be good. Get some rest.
Oh no, the garbagemen.
Now the alcohol's out of your system,
you've remembered class again.
What? What class? You mean at school?
Uh, no, I don't… I don't drink.
I don't know what alcohol
you're talking about.
Don't worry.
I'm good at staying in the background.
It's where I live.
I don't want anyone
to get expelled because of me.
No one should pay for their family's sins
because of who my family is.
It's a matter of control and security.
My family didn't ask for even half
of the measures you put in place.
Besides, I've had the chance
to meet my classmates,
and I feel welcome.
I don't see any danger in them.
Very well.
Which measures should I get rid of?
The cameras, perhaps?
No, not the cameras.
I'd prefer it if you kept them.