Mm.
I thought you said
Omar wouldn't be home till later.
-He said he wouldn't.
-Well, fuck.
What are you doing?
He won't go to bed for another half hour.
This whole situation's
totally freaking me out.
How do you think I feel?
But I'm the one who's having to lie
and move my plans around to see you.
What? Do you think
I don't wanna see you during the day?
That I don't wanna have a drink with you
or give you a kiss when I go to class?
I really don't know.
You want that?
Does it really matter?
Do you care how it feels to constantly see
you and Guzmán making plans together?
And then, I just get the leftover crumbs.
That means,
to you, this is just sloppy seconds?
-No, it's not.
-Then what is it?
Tell me, 'cause I'm not sure.
You're the one setting the pace here.
You're coming and going.
It's all been your decision.
Well, of course it's my decision.
I'm the one coming,
going, and essentially doing it all.
Because you just passively wait around
for others to do things.
Like when my dad got you out of the bar.
The hell does that mean?
It's obvious, Samuel.
You're always waiting for everyone else
to make your decisions.
Wake the fuck up and live your life.
You have the all-clear.
You have the same.
Start sticking your neck out a bit more.
Till then, you don't get to demand things.
Did you do it, Samuel?
I'd never hurt Ari.
Then I bet… you know who did.
Comin' through.
-Good morning, Benjamín.
-Good morning, Your Highness. Welcome.
-If you would come with me.
-I'll see you later, okay?
ARI, SORRY ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO REACT.
Hey. Morning, buddy.
Whoa. Relax, dude.
-Jesus.
-Hold on. Wait.
What's wrong?
Put speed in your coffee this morning?
-No. Why?
-Have you seen Ari?
What? Why would…?
What do you mean, have I seen--
-What the hell's the matter?
-Huh?
Listen up, I need you to text her.
Tell her you'll meet tomorrow
at the Lake Club.
-Why should I? She's your girlfriend.
-Because I wanna surprise her.
Do me this favor.
Say it's to talk
about the debate or whatever.
-Okay, but what should I write? I mean…
-Great. Thanks a lot, man.
Fuck.
SEE YOU TOMORROW NIGHT AT THE LAKE CLUB.
All done.
-Look, she's replying.
-Huh?
I said, she's replying.
-Let me see.
-What?
Well, you just got a message.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THE LAKE CLUB? DEBATE?
Just keep insisting you need to meet her
outside of the school.
-C'mon, tell her.
-Yeah, sure.
I'D RATHER MEET OUTSIDE SCHOOL SO WE CAN
TAKE OUR TIME PREPARING OUR ARGUMENT.
-All good.
-She's sending something.
-Okay.
-Let me see.
-She answered.
-Let's see what she said.
-Shut up. I wanna hear what she says.
-No. It's my phone, dude.
-Shh!
-What?
Is that all?
Is that all you have to tell me?
As though last night never happened?
"Last night"?
What happened last night?
Hmm.
Okay, well, um…
That's, uh, um… I mean, that's exactly…
What she's talking about there
is the debate.
It got heated,
and she wanted to apologize--
-Samuel.
-And it's no big deal.
I don't know what's wrong, but listen.
Make sure she comes.
That's all. Thanks, pal.
Man, oh, man.
You've been MIA since we saw Ambar.
You didn't miss me either.
-Jesus, Patrick.
-What?
Hey, I had a fuckin' awesome time. Thanks.
Well, I'm glad you did.
I know that look, dude.
I've felt that way a hell of a lot.
Well, I was a dickhead
and got too carried away.
Come on. You're not.
We've all lost our minds over someone.
-Or something.
-No.
I don't.
I always decide when,
how much, and how long.
That's great.
But Ander's very Ander.
When he wants you,
you feel like the king of the world.
But when he shuts down
or tosses you aside…
Come on. Cheer up, man.
You'll be back
to fuckin' everything that moves soon.
Hey, so, well, I've been thinking
that it'd be a good idea
for you to leave Armando's hotel room.
I mean, don't you think?
Why? I thought he didn't mind.
No, he doesn't, but…
It's just…
…I'd rather not have anything to do
with him anymore.
-That's all.
-See.
I knew it.
He left the concert 'cause you fought.
What did he do? I'll smash his face in.
It's nothing.
He just gets really annoying and intense.
Don't worry about it, kay?
I'm sure my old lady
won't slam the door on me.
But if she makes me choose,
I know what I'd do.
Like, I'll go live under a bridge.
I don't even care.
So, um…
…why don't… we make the most of
this last night at the hotel?
Um, okay.
I mean, if you want to.
-Yeah. Yeah, sure.
-Yeah?
Which bridge
do you think you'll live under?
-Hey, I'll come up with one.
-Sure you will.
A school full of girls from good families,
all waiting for my son to look at them,
and he falls for the janitor?
She wants to be a fashion designer.
She's a very bright and intelligent girl.
I know that sort of intelligence.
I've seen it in all the other
Little Miss Nobodies after him.
Cayetana will behave
and stick to the path set for her.
How do you know that?
She has shown unconditional support
for her boyfriends before.
She'll be with him no matter what.
She has everything to gain.
-They're mine.
-Are you sure?
Yes.
Wow, Phillipe.
They're pretty good. Very good.
I mean, a prince, a designer, and hetero?
You'd be my mythical Prince Charming
if you weren't a predator.
Ciao.
They're not mine, though.
Then whose?
Caye, you forgot this.
-Where were they?
-In the printer.
Ah, okay. Thanks. Anyone else see these?
I don't know.
Me. What's the matter?
Are you afraid I'll tell the principal
you're using school equipment
without permission, Cayetana?
No.
Snitch on me, then. I don't care.
They're very good.
Ari told me that.
Oh, really?
To be fair, I thought they were his.
And for something a prince
was doing on a whim, they weren't bad.
Okay.
What?
He heard your message.
-Guzmán?
-Yeah.
Why'd you ask me
to meet up about the debate?
He's planning a surprise.
He'll be the one at the club tomorrow.
You wanted me to take a stance, and I am.
But for my friend.
I can't keep sneaking around
and repeatedly stabbing him in the back
like this.
It's Guzmán or me.
Now take a stance and make up your mind.
You'll throw a New Year's Eve party.
The media will be there,
and there'll be a photo shoot.
I want you to invite all your friends.
You can bring that girl if you want.
Cayetana.
So, Benjamín filled you in.
Do you really like her?
Very much.
Have you at least given
other girls a chance?
I don't want other girls.
I want her.
Fine, you'll introduce her formally
at the party.
That's part of your campaign
to clean up my image, right?
We're not together right now.
You mean you can't win
your peasant girl back?
Don't call her that.
Do you want her back or not?
Yes, Mom.
Well then, do what you need to do.
What's happened to you here in Madrid?
Hmm?
I don't recognize you anymore.
-Why are you here?
-Just visiting my friend.
Sure, I'm not busy.
Want a Mahou?
Okay. In the room with the fireplace?
It's quieter there, okay?
Guys, we have a guest.
This is Armando.
Alumni president
and a former student at Las Encinas.
He just came by to make the association's
very generous annual donation
to the school,
and he wanted to meet all of you.
No, we already know him.
Isn't he your friend from the concert?
-Uh, yeah.
-Oh.
Uh, you're friends?
We've bumped into each other
while having drinks.
-I see.
-How are you?
-Hi.
-Hello.
Yeah, Patrick and I get along well.
And no, it's not your business.
I don't know
if you guys intend to take things further.
Actually, no. It's not important to me.
Well, to be totally honest,
I wasn't planning on it,
but thank you for your indifference.
If I didn't know better,
I would say you're a little bit jealous.
What the fuck?
I know you,
and I think you're very jealous.
It's not jealousy. It's concern.
Excuse me?
Omar, Patrick cozied up to you
two seconds after I pissed him off.
Just sayin'.
I cozied up to Patrick.
Mainly 'cause you left him
in a fucking shambles.
Not my fault
if the guy has an imagination.
Uh, yeah, no.
It was a little bit your fault, honestly.
Patrick may be intense,
but he's not a dumbass.
Omar, I'm just asking you
not to get your hopes up.
'Cause you're really into him,
but all he wants is to get even.
The hell?
Omar.
So, he hit on you
because you're such a catch,
but I'm just a rebound?
You've got guts.
Look, I'm just worried about you.
No, really, you've got a lot of nerve
to go around making one-sided decisions
and getting upset when I try to get over
the damage you've done.
I'm not upset.
You're like the dog in the manger.
You don't want me, you don't want Patrick,
but you also don't want us to build a life
without you.
If I'm just your buddy
and Patrick was a booty call,
why don't you just let us
do our own thing?
Leave. I have to work.
We've always had rules.
You're telling me
they're more oppressive now than ever.
I'll tell you there were way more rules
in my day.
Before, people will say,
in their day, there were even more.
And so on, ad infinitum.
Well, I doubt when you were studying
at Las Encinas,
it felt so much like a… a bunker.
Even back then, it was very strict.
Trust me.
You had to do a balancing act
to skip class or break a rule.
The previous principal
had kinda loosened the rules.
But now
my father's reinstating them all, right?
Hmm.
If you'll excuse me for just a second.
Sure.
Mencía?
Yeah?
You okay?
I'm great.
Never been better, Benjamín. Why?
-Thought you were a vegetarian.
-Look, I'm not making anything up.
Everything, then.
-I need to use the bathroom.
-What's gotten into her now?
What the actual fuck
are you doing in my house?
-Your dad asked me to stay for lunch.
-In general. Before that.
Why'd you show up
at my house in the first place?
I always deliver the annual donation.
Armando, don't give me that shit.
You could've easily given it to him
at the school or a fucking bar.
But you showed up here, so tell me why.
To fuck me over?
Me? Fuck you over?
What are you talkin' about?
You think you can blackmail me
so you can fuck me forever, don't you?
It really pisses you off
that you can't have me
whenever you want, I guess.
You can't end a relationship
over a tantrum.
You and I don't have a relationship!
So, we can talk about the menu
for the remainder of the week later on.
That'll be all for now.
-You've been tense since you saw him.
-Yeah, well, I'm tense by nature.
-Will you tell me what's goin' on?
-Nothing. We're friends. I told you.
How do a minor and a former alum
three times her age become friends?
We told you already. We met at a bar.
I'm gonna sit back down.
Honey.
What?
I know that our rapport
is pretty much, uh, nonexistent.
And when we do talk,
it's a declaration of war.
I think you can deduce that…
…even if I don't tell you…
Well, I don't want you to deduce.
I want you to know
that if there's something happening to you
or you're worried about something
or you have a problem,
well, you could tell me.
And with just one phone call,
I can get rid of, uh,
whatever it is that's the problem.
For you or your brother and sister.
That's good to know.
If… If I need that call,
I'll be sure to… let ya know.
Okay?
Okay. I've talked too much already.
Now your turn.
What are you doing after graduating?
You have to join the alumni.
Well, honestly, I would love
to join the alumni association.
Oh yeah.
And have Armando
introduce us to his old classmates.
-Nothin' beats a boomer.
-Patrick!
You have such a one-track mind!
I'm going to tell my father,
and it's going to fuck up your life.
A bunch of old guys
in a room, lookin' back on their lives.
Who knows
what they get up to in there?
Everything?
Even how you've been making a living?
Accept it. You are mine.
You're so annoying.
How is it, Armando?
I hope everything's to your liking.
Everything's perfect, Benjamín. Thank you.
How have my kids been treating you?
It seems you've really… hit it off,
haven't you?
Your children are a pleasure.
A toast.
-Sure.
-Oh, yes.
-But it's bad luck to toast with water.
-Not with water. Come on.
Well, that's what you're getting,
all right?
I WANT TO SEE YOU TONIGHT
WHAT TIME SHOULD WE GO TO THE HOTEL?
I'M SORRY, REBE. I CAN'T GO.
Yes?
-Hi.
-Hello.
-Can I come in?
-Yeah, come in.
It's just that my mother decided
she wanted to come here
and spend Christmas with me.
Uh-huh.
And since it seems
she can never have an empty schedule,
she's putting together a networking event
with young entrepreneurs.
A get-together
to strengthen business ties and all.
Oh. Hmm.
How fun. Yippee.
Uh, I requested
that she invite our seed designer.
-Ah, Sadelagu?
-Mm-hmm.
Wait, wow.
Is Sadelagu really gonna be there?
-Yeah.
-Oh.
I don't know. I was hoping
that maybe you'd like to come with me,
meet him in person,
and show him your designs.
Okay,
you're… you're joking right now.
No. You have talent, Caye.
Thank you so much, Phillipe.
I… I don't know what to say.
Say nothing.
Really, thanks a lot.
So, is that a yes?
Dress code?
Hello. Good evening.
Cayetana Grajera.
Thank you.
I think I'll leave you alone.
-Where can I find your father?
-He's over there, schmoozing.
Wow. Christian Dior?
Grajera Pando.
Wow.
Yeah.
To be honest, I never imagined
I'd meet Sadelagu at such a solemn affair.
Dreams come true wearing charcoal gray
and holding a tumbler.
Hmm.
Hey, look.
-Is that…?
-That's him.
-It's him?
-I'll get him.
Okay.
Really?
You'll enter the lion's den
to make sure you get what you want.
He invited me without my asking.
Sure.
And leaving your designs
out in plain sight?
Just coincidence?
Yeah, it actually was.
You were very quick
to get over your doubts about him.
There's not a foolish hair on your head,
but you're stupid.
And a climber.
You're just a stupid climber.
Oh shit.
What the fuck is this?
If you don't mind.
So, do you like it?
It's delicious.
I've never tried it.
Fashion, I'm told,
is what brought you
and Phillipe together, right?
Yes. And especially
our mutual admiration for you.
-Oh, come on.
-But anyway…
Sorry. I had to.
Really. Meeting you is a dream come true.
Mm-hmm.
Charge it to room 973.
It's on me.
Um, I'm sorry.
Do you have maybe five minutes?
I'd love to show you
some of these sketches I made.
Sure.
Really?
I have all the time in the world for you.
The thing is, I'd rather take a look
at them in my room, you know?
It's just,
I find it way more comfortable and quiet.
-Uh…
-What do you say?
Why are you with him again?
Rebe, look. I'll explain later, okay?
What do you mean, "later"?
Is this how you show
you want nothing to do with this dude?
Mencía.
I need you to go now.
Come on.
You coming?
Yeah. Hell no, I'm not going away.
Mencía, let's go.
Mencía, what is this?
I'd rather send my designs
to your workshops
and we'll talk whenever you're available.
Everyone,
here are your New Year's Eve invitations.
I'm so excited to start the year with you.
Samuel.
I just don't understand, Mencía.
You wanted nothing to do with him,
and now you're together again?
That's how I am. Capricious and volatile.
Ander.
Well, maybe it's true.
I mean, you and I've gotten closer
tryin' to forget him.
Now let's forget him, okay?
-What?
-Your invitations, guys.
I WANT TO START THE YEAR WITH YOU.
PHILLIPE
What are your rates like, Cayetana?
For designing a dress, not mopping.
I want a dress for New Year's Eve,
and I'd like to look truly spectacular.
Well, I'd have to crunch some numbers.
Two grand? Not including materials.
What are you up to?
You have talent.
And dignity.
Plus, the 2,000 euros
are a tax-deductible donation.
God, I can't stomach you.
Cayetana,
I want your talent, not your friendship.
So, yes or no?
-I'll start concepts and get back to you.
-You have three days.
I only need two.
Oh, and I want a 10% bonus
for every 500 likes you get.
Five percent.
-No, no.
-Omar.
-No.
-Yes.
Come on.
I said no.
No way we're gonna fuck here, Patrick.
No, it's just a spell. I'm an exorcist.
Yeah, a spell, my ass.
Ander?
I don't know any Ander.
So, have you forgotten him?
It's cool.
Poco a poco. Hmm?
Trust me, Ander's not forever.
Oh, baby.
Do you know
one of the thousands of ways
you and I are the same?
Without fail,
it doesn't matter if the people
we love hurt us again and again
and again and again,
we never leave their side.
We keep letting ourselves get punched
in the gut and take it like champs.
Bam, bam, bam!
For those we love, we'll do what it takes.
You and I are fighters.
But do you know how we're different?
I wait for the people I love…
to hit rock bottom,
alone and ashamed, and come back
with their tails between their legs.
But you're not like that.
You refuse to just sit by and watch
if you know they're about to hit bottom.
You don't give up, and you never stop.
And I think
that's one of your best traits.
Maybe you're me, but the improved version?
Hey, I said, "maybe."
Come here, sweetie.
Please, come in.
So, you go to Las Encinas?
-Yeah. We're in class together.
-Mm.
-Uh, I'm Patrick.
-Great.
-Uh, is Ander here?
-He is. Just a minute. I'll go get him.
Okay. Thank you.
Hey there, handsome.
Patrick?
Patrick,
I think I'm a victim of butt-dialing.
Honey,
your friend Patrick is here to see you.
-Patrick?
-Yes, he's downstairs.
What's this about?
I'll tell you later, kay?
Ander? How are you?
What the fuck?
Hey, can we chat for a sec?
Look, Ander, you really don't get it.
You think
the whole world revolves around you?
It doesn't.
If I'm with Omar, it's because I like him
and I wanna pursue something.
And if that pisses you off,
then honestly, that's your problem, dude.
It's fine with me
if you two are together.
As long as you're honest
and don't hurt him.
-'Cause Omar's not like me.
-I know. That's why I like him.
No, I'm saying
he's someone you could really hurt.
Because he does have feelings for you.
And I hope you do too.
He's not just someone
to pass the time with.
Unlike me?
That's right. I was… a palate cleanser.
To get rid of Omar's scent
with a couple of fucks and a few kisses.
Well, relax. I'm not like you.
I only hope I can make him feel
half as good as he makes me feel.
Look, man.
If I hurt you, I'm sorry, all right?
I thought it was clear
that it was just sex.
Because at least to me,
that was super clear.
'Cause I never had doubts
about my feelings for Omar.
Like, when I got cured,
I traded backpacking around the world
just to be with him.
I've always loved him.
And I always will.
So, don't play mind games with him,
don't use him,
and, above all,
don't you dare break his heart.
Don't worry.
You can answer your WhatsApps.
I'll get out of the way… forever. I swear.
Fuck.
Why the long face?
It's nothing.
Honey, when are you finally gonna tell me
what's going on?
Have I ever told you
how annoying you are when you shut down?
BEFORE I GO: MOM, GUZMÁN, OMAR
Thank you.
Hmm.
-What?
-It's good.
And you were against it
'cause it's not French.
-Yeah.
But you should so serve it
at your New Year's Eve party.
Well, there's something else
I'd like to have
at my New Year's Eve party.
-Hmm?
-Or rather, someone else, I should say.
I would love it if you would come.
I am.
Yeah, but… as my date.
That sounds like a couples plan.
Yes. It is.
Except we're just friends, remember?
Yeah, but we're friends who are exes.
And exes…
can get back together for Christmas.
-Hmm.
-Hmm?
Don't tell me
you haven't thought about it.
No.
Something great just happened,
and that's all I really think about.
Is it something great…
that you'd be willing to share with me?
I am sharing it.
C'mon,
aren't things fine the way they are?
Yeah, sure.
-It's okay to change our minds, right?
-Calm down. We're just making out.
And I don't even know why.
Look, Phillipe, we'd better…
Okay.
Wait.
Stop.
What?
We'd better not.
Why?
Friends is better.
You sit there. I'll sit here.
But Caye,
I'm more certain than ever.
Yeah, and I no longer see you as an idol.
I don't have to swoon
when we're together, you know?
Yeah, but what if it's the idol
who does the swooning?
No, really, I mean it.
I think it's better
if we just be friends, okay?
Phillipe, stop.
Stop. Hey, I said stop.
You like to feel
you have power over me, huh?
-What?
-All girls do.
What are you saying? Stop.
Stop it, Phillipe.
Get off me. Get off me! Let me go!
I don't want to!
Okay, seriously, let me go, Phillipe.
Oh my God! Please, enough!
Stop! I already said no. I said, get off!
Shit.
Cayetana!
My girlfriend's here.
Sorry I'm late
to my own freakin' surprise.
They decided to block the entrance
in the middle of December
so that they could prune or something.
Thank you.
-You all right?
-Yeah.
-Are you sure?
Why's this extra plate here?
I'll have them take it away.
Aren't you workin' today?
Hold on a minute.
You said he canceled on you.
What do you mean, I canceled?
Samuel, have a seat.
Wait, why should he have a seat?
Ari, can you tell me what's goin' on?
Guzmán…
I've been seeing Samuel.
Seeing him as what?
Was it or was it not Guzmán?
Samuel, are you listening to me?
I'm sorry to put you in this situation,
but I think what I have with Samuel
isn't just a fling.
Samuel, I've fallen in love with you,
and I don't wanna leave you.
But Guzmán,
I'm in love with you too.
Guzmán, look at me.
I don't wanna leave you either.
Look at me!
Listen, I know you're probably thinking
I'm crazy right now.
But I think that I'd be crazy if… if…
if I were to give up on either of you.