How are you?
Who did this?
Shh. Relax, sweetheart.
The doctors are confident
you'll recover your memory over time.
Finally, after 20 years, I get to sleep
with a girl from Las Encinas.
But I had to pay.
-I went to your school, too.
-Oh, really?
Yeah.
And don't worry.
Some of us come out of there all right.
Hey, mind if I share your number?
With who?
My buddy.
I raved about you.
Didn't you want to expand the business?
Actually, I do.
But it's gotta be in this room, though.
Everything included.
-So, the same as with me?
-No. Not the same.
'Cause your little buddy pays double.
I want you to join the debate team.
You did a nice job defending Shanaa
when I first got to this school.
I think you've got talent.
And if you choose to apply it
to serving noble causes, well,
you could one day become…
a brilliant lawyer, for instance.
I'm sorry,
but I don't want to be a lawyer.
Getting there would mean
you'd have to work hard, consistently,
every day after class.
Wait, hold on. I can't. After school,
I work every day at the Lake Club.
Hmm. You'll have to quit.
How much do they pay?
Why?
Las Encinas
is capable of offering you 25% more
for completing
assorted administrative computing tasks.
The hours would be compatible
with the debate team.
If you don't mind me asking,
well, uh, are you tryin' to help me?
-He said I'm really good.
-He's got ulterior motives.
They don't offer this sort of thing
to people like you.
-What do you mean by that?
-Come on, Samuel.
Two days ago, he wanted to kick you out
'cause you weren't worthy.
What's your point? He just said
I could become a great lawyer.
-Yeah, and you believe him, right?
-Fuck you.
-What are you saying?
-Samuel.
-Come on, let's go. Go on.
-C'mon. Don't be pissy with me.
Hey. What's up, Gonza?
Samuel, make sure Mencía stays out there.
-Why?
-I'm gonna give her a surprise.
Uh… What the hell is this?
The key to suite 428.
"Gran Hotel Brenwhorf."
For tomorrow?
Oh, shit.
Why didn't I switch to girls way earlier?
Come on. I don't think I was that bad.
Know what?
Actually, now that I look back on it,
ya done fucked up.
Busy tomorrow night? I'm free.
We said today. I have plans then.
Ah. Who are you seeing
that you can't move around for me?
I can do today. Mañana, no.
Forget it.
I can't meet tomorrow, either.
Almost done. Give me a minute.
Coffee?
You think that's all you have to do?
I erased it.
Your video.
I did it this morning.
You can't erase that you recorded
without my permission.
But I am telling you, it wasn't personal.
I swear.
I can't trust anybody.
Look, Phillipe.
We should end things here,
because it was never gonna work out
between us.
You're a prince,
and I'm just… the fucking janitor.
There's no planet
or parallel universe
where you and I
would have ever worked out together.
Even before you recorded us.
Let me make it up to you.
Just let me…
let me prove to you that behind the title,
there's a real person.
Maybe I'm not interested in that person.
What if I was just drawn to that person
because he was a prince, but that's all?
And you were just drawn to me
because I was easy prey.
-No.
-Yes.
-Just another groupie, right?
-No.
Cayetana…
End of story.
You go your way. I'll go my way.
We're more secluded in the books
than in the showers.
Stop. No more.
I'm not doing anything.
Am I gonna have to beat it into you?
Relax just a little, will you?
It was just sex, not a marriage proposal.
You could care less 'cause you have
no one that you might really hurt.
Ander.
Look, whatever Omar's deal is,
we can talk our way through it.
The three of us, like adults.
Yeah, sure.
Why would he want to see you,
when he won't even see me?
Well,
we can at least try, right?
Just set up a time for the three of us
to meet, and I'll sort this thing out.
Just trust me.
Hey, can we maybe go somewhere more chill?
Just a little longer. Come on.
-Please. I'm begging you.
-C'mon. Just a little longer.
-What are you doing?
-All right. Come on. Your turn.
-No, no. No fuckin' way.
-Come on.
-Do it. Come on.
-I don't want to.
Oh, God, Ander.
Patrick. Patrick!
Hey. How's it going?
-Mm.
-How's it going? Huh?
Hey, turns out you don't need
much clothing to be happy, right?
What's going on? Did you two plan this?
-What's the deal?
-No. I swear.
-I'm not into this. I'm outta here.
-No, just stay a bit.
-I'm dead tired. I said no.
-Hey. Why are you in a rush?
You say you're tired? Great.
I have just the thing to wake you up
and get your ass off the ground.
-What is it? Magic?
-No.
This is G.
-And what's that?
-GHB.
A little squirt,
and say goodbye to being tired.
And goodbye to inhibition, repression,
self-consciousness, all of it.
Listen, it can't be worse for me
than chemo.
Dude, this shit kills people.
What's the matter?
You afraid to let go now?
Imagine that.
Listen, Omar.
I said no.
I think we both really just need
to loosen up and relax a little bit.
I'm not interested.
For chrissake, no means no.
-A little squirt?
-Yeah, thanks.
Where did you get this?
You're searching my room?
Is that where we are?
-Is this from Rebeka Parrilla?
-No, you leave Rebe out of this.
-Her mother was in jail on drug charges.
-This has nothing to do with her.
Then where'd you get it?
I'm not about to give it back
until you tell me where it came from.
I mean, you don't even know
why she had the hotel room key.
-It could be for anything, like maybe--
-Jesus Christ, dude.
You're supposed to be
the star of the debate team.
-Scared to see what the bad ones are like.
-Look, all I meant to say was--
Doesn't matter what you were gonna say.
What's wrong with me? Huh?
Tell me. I want to know.
Am I too much or not enough?
You would know,
since you fooled me like she did.
I'm really sorry, but…
but sometimes people make mistakes,
and it has nothing to do with you.
Yeah.
It's not about what you do or don't do.
It's entirely our fault.
The fact that the rest of us are assholes
doesn't mean you're defective or bad.
The opposite, actually.
Hey.
You're the most fucking awesome girl
out there.
If you can hold on to one thing,
hold on to that.
Maybe you won't be so bad,
on second thought, with that debate thing.
Ice cream sound good to you?
I want, like, a shit ton.
-Good, 'cause we got chocolate.
-Fuckin' awesome.
Yeah, that was something
my dad always told me.
-Yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
Hey, man.
Evening.
-Evening.
-Do you have a reservation?
-Yeah.
-Yes.
You look great.
-Thanks. That's nice.
-Can you take our coats?
Thanks, Samuel.
-I'm out.
-No, Omar.
Listen.
There's no way I can go to bed now.
I mean, I'm high as shit.
That sounds like your problem, Ander.
Don't worry, buddy.
I'll be his babysitter.
Omar.
Omar!
Hey, just try a little. It's fun.
I promise you'll like it.
I said no.
Please, Omar. Listen to me.
Take whatever you want and leave me alone.
Why's that so hard to get?
Well, hey.
At least look on the bright side.
-Now there's more for you and me.
-I don't want more, man.
Ander!
Hey! Watch out!
Uh… Can you…
Can you give me a hand? Patrick.
Omar. Omar!
-Omar!
-I think your friend's calling you.
Out of the way.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Patrick. Patrick.
Patrick! Patrick!
Look at me.
Close the door.
-I'm gonna puke.
-Jesus, Ander.
What are you doing?
You need a shower.
Come on. It'll do you good.
Come on.
All right, fucking help me out here.
Feeling better?
Nah, man. I'm pretty sick.
Okay, go lay down.
I'll be there in a minute.
-Come on. Let's go.
-No, no, no, no. No.
You all right?
I feel so cold.
Please don't leave me.
Okay. Scooch over.
-That's kinda personal.
-It is?
-You're the girl of a thousand questions.
-Yep.
-Why do you wanna know?
-Sorry, we're, uh, closing up.
Your father said
I should join the debate team.
-He did?
-Yeah.
-Well, I'm on the team, too.
-For real?
Except you can't, right, bud?
I mean, you don't have time
between work and school.
Actually, I'm seriously considering it.
Oh yeah? What about your job here?
Well, that's kinda up to me.
-Just the bill?
-Yes, please.
Want a ride, or did you bike here?
I biked.
Samuel, don't forget the coats.
Benjamín,
I think I will join the debate team.
We're late for class.
Omar. Are you working at the club tonight?
Uh, yeah. Why?
I need you to do me a favor.
-Cut that shit out.
-What's wrong with you?
Hangover.
Wait, you went out?
I thought you said
you couldn't hang out last night.
Who are you seeing later?
Um, I told you
I'm just doing some odd jobs
so I don't have to depend on Benjamín.
Yeah, like what?
Great, then we're even.
Mencía,
you can't keep doing this.
Dad doesn't want you seeing Rebeka.
Stop adding to the tension.
Children aren't to blame
for the way their parents choose to be.
The same goes for Rebe.
Hello?
Okay.
-Hi.
-Hey there.
-Want to go?
-No. Come say hi to my dad.
I know.
Why are you here?
Mm, I have a meeting with your dad
about the debate team.
Why couldn't you meet at school? Why here?
Um, Benjamín requested it.
What's goin' on?
You sure?
-Mm, never mind.
-Samuel.
I was actually worried
you'd changed your mind.
-I almost did.
-Come in.
Uh, Dad. Say hello to Guzmán.
Of course. How are you? How's your family?
We're all great. Thank you.
-Uh, let's go to my office and talk.
-Sounds good.
Um, can I get a black coffee, Ari?
Want anything?
Me? Uh, if you could get me coffee
with a little milk, that'd be great.
I worked my butt off
at every job imaginable
to pay for my studies, too.
What?
Thought I got everything
on a silver platter?
Well, uh…
I don't even remember my father.
-Yeah, I don't know mine either, really.
-Hmm.
Thankfully, I was given a scholarship
to a private university in London.
And well,
of course, I went back home ecstatic.
And my mother,
the first thing she said to me
was,
"Don't you ever forget that we aren't,
and never will be, like them."
"Like them," she said.
And from that day on,
I set out to prove that
there's no "us" and "them."
The future's decided
by someone's merits, Samuel.
Right?
I'm sure she was proud
of everything you did.
Just like your mother must be.
Ah, Ari.
So you're going to be Samuel's partner.
His what?
You're gonna make a great match
on the debate team. I can tell.
Yeah.
Um, I'm going out with Guzmán.
Thanks for the coffee.
-She can't handle visitors.
-Yeah.
Go home.
Huh?
I don't want you bothering her.
Hello?
Hey, Cayetana.
It's Omar. How are you?
Hey, listen. So, I'm calling
just to confirm your table
for tonight at the Lake Club.
What?
-Good evening, miss.
-Omar, what's this about?
Why is there no one here?
Your table's ready.
Will you come with me?
-Omar.
-Here you are.
Welcome. Have a seat.
Okay.
-Thanks.
-You look pretty.
-Omar, I'm leaving. This is absurd.
-Bonsoir.
-Good evening.
-Oh my God!
-An aperitif?
-Phillipe, what is this?
I don't mean to be rude, mademoiselle.
I think you've got the wrong person.
I'm just your humble waiter.
I won't see you as anything different
just because you played a waiter
for me tonight.
-Is it to your liking?
-Are you listening?
Mais non, s'il vous plaît.
It's my first day.
Yeah.
-Hmm, yeah. Not cold enough.
-Really?
Sorry for the inconvenience.
I'll bring you another. Anything else?
Oh, yeah. This napkin,
it's dirty.
I'm sorry.
I'll, uh, bring another right away.
Stick to English, why don't we.
Hmm.
-Can I make any sort of recommendation?
-À la carte?
-Mm-hmm.
-Let me see.
Uh…
Oh.
-I think I know what I want now.
-Right. Tell me.
Trust.
That's really all I want right now.
Cayetana, I would've taken the same steps
with anyone.
Well,
I don't care about anyone else.
You made me doubt myself
and got me in my head.
And I don't know about you,
but when we were together,
I just forgot who we were.
We were naked, and it was just us two.
And I forgot.
And I just hope
you'll manage to forget it, as well.
I'm sorry.
Can you forgive me?
I'M COMING TO THE CLUB TO SEE YOU.
I'M VERY BUSY. IT'S BETTER IF YOU DON'T.
Hey, you two.
Let's go. Gotta get out of here.
We gotta clean this up
before our first reservation arrives.
Come on.
And only because you are thinking it,
this isn't a third date, you know.
Oh no?
-No.
-Oh.
It's just some little performance
I put on like the total fool that I am.
Okay, great.
Actually, the third date
is gonna be back at my place.
If you're interested, of course.
-Yeah, I am.
-Yeah?
Mencía?
Take it off for me.
Aren't you forgetting something?
That's one hour.
Then let's not waste any more time.
Pizza? No, we agreed on sushi.
-One of them has anchovies. Chill out.
-Dad, that's not fair. We said sushi.
Dad, come on.
Is that the way you'll be defending
your position in a debate?
-He's gonna clobber you.
-You've gotta be kidding me.
Where is Mencía?
She went out earlier.
Who'd she go out with?
With Rebeka, I think.
-And why did you let her?
-Because I can't--
-I didn't want her near that girl.
-Hold on.
Rebeka is one of the best people
I've ever known.
My daughter has 3,000 euros in her room.
What?
Where does a kid get 3,000 euros
when she's going out
with a dealer's daughter?
Can you connect the dots, García?
Or should I?
But she doesn't do
that sort of thing anymore.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
-I have to answer it.
-Hey, hey, hey, hey.
-Not right now.
-Um, look, man. Let go of me. Okay?
What?
I said I'm not into this game.
Please let go of me.
Enough of that, huh?
If you really want me to pay you,
behave like a professional.
Except I told you, I'm not a professional,
so let go of me.
Shh.
Uh, Patrick.
See if she's at the club
or if anyone's seen her there.
We'll go to Parrilla's house.
-She's not at Rebeka's house.
-Nobody asked for your opinion.
-I'll go get the car keys.
-I don't want you driving like this.
She's into something serious.
-Oh, please. I hope Guzmán isn't home yet.
-I can drive your father's car.
-I'm going with Samuel.
-What are you saying? No, no, no.
If she calls,
you have to be here to pick it up.
Let's go.
-Patrick?
-Have you seen Mencía?
N-- No. Haven't seen her all afternoon.
Patrick!
Get out. The fuck is this guy doing?
Yo, can I ask you what's going on?
-Fuck!
-Hey. Stop. Calm down.
You!
-Fuck, you scared me.
-What the fuck are you doing here?
-What?
-So now you're going after Omar?
What are you talking about?
First, you're in his bed,
then stalk him at his job.
-Is that how it works?
-My sister disappeared.
Right. You think I'm an idiot?
Listen, I'm not fucking lying.
Mencía's missing.
And you're not an idiot, just blind.
Omar came looking for me.
At the ball.
You fucked him at the ball?
He fucked me, to be precise.
You must think
our family's completely bonkers.
No, not really. My own family--
I mean,
we have good reasons to be the way we are.
When Mencía was a little girl,
she ran away from home,
and we didn't even realize it
until it was dinnertime.
So my mother grabbed Patrick
and went to look for her with the car,
and soon, it got dark out.
My mom started getting
more and more nervous,
and they got into an accident.
Patrick was bedridden for two years after.
My mom died instantly.
Holy fuck.
My father still misses her every day.
-She had 3,000 bucks on her?
-Did you give it to her?
I didn't.
Who do you think you're talkin' to?
Mencía's not answering,
and we've been there two hours–
Are they worried about her?
I gotta run. Ari's in the car waiting.
Oh shit, the hotel room key.
Please, let me go.
Hey… can… can we stop?
Are you even listening to me? Please?
Who is it?
Room service.
Uh, no, no.
We didn't order anything.
It's a bottle of champagne for you, sir.
Courtesy of the hotel.
Leave it outside.
Hey, I… I think maybe I could go
for a little bit of champagne.
Hmm?
Who are you? Get the hell out!
What the hell is this?
Rebeka's calling me.
Mencía!
Where are you?
Okay, but are you all right?
Oh my God!
Well, I'll see you at home, then.
Hurry back, okay?
See you there.
So, back to your house then?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, are you in the mood for pizza?
Sounds good.
-It's not what it looks like.
-Oh, it's not?
Explain it to me then.
'Cause this
could only be one fucking thing, Mencía.
Please don't you treat me like that, too.
Rebe…
you know I'm only doing this
so I can afford to get out of this place.
Hopefully, with you.
I'm sorry, kid.
Do you think
this is some kind of game, huh?
I don't give a fuck.
I don't give a shit why you did it.
But that asshole could've done
all sorts of awful things.
Don't look at me like that.
I can't take it.
Not from you.
Don't scare me like that ever again
in our fucking lives, you brat.
Ari.
-Samuel García?
-What? What?
-Come with us.
-What is goin' on?
-Let's go.
-What's going on? Ari?
Ari. What's going-- Ari!
Ari!