Bravo! You look great out there!
Sexy!
I don't know
what came over me or what I was thinking.
I'll meet you in half an hour
at the pier on the lake.
Please come and hear me out.
-I never got that message.
-It looks like it was sent to me.
I never got that message, I'm telling you!
'Cause it's not the same at all.
Why isn't it the same thing? Go on.
-Why?
-Because it was only sex for you.
So now you're hooked on him?
That's the deal?
No fuckin' way.
No fuckin' way, Omar.
Are you fuckin' kidding me right now?
Look, Ander… No. I… I mean-- No, no.
This can't be.
Please, man.
I'm fucking confused as hell. Ander!
-Let's go to the lake and talk, please.
-To talk about what?
What's there to talk about?
Rebeka's sleeping,
so go the fuck back home, okay?
-What are you doing? What's up? Hi.
-Hi.
Please move.
Believe me. I had no idea
what I was getting myself into.
You did it enough times.
You'd think you'd figured it out.
Rebe, I can't change something
that's already happened.
You know I desperately wish I could,
but that's not an option.
I can change my behavior from now on.
You serious right now?
Do you really think
I'd fall for that shit, huh?
When I got home,
I made up an excuse
they never even asked for
because you and I both know
they didn't care what I'd been doing.
They were just relieved to see you.
Well, yes.
And I liked feeling… that sense of relief
because it's the same relief I felt
in that hotel room when you hugged me,
even after everything you saw.
No, wait up.
Come here.
Don't ever do that to me again.
Have you seen Ari?
She told me
she would meet me here.
I would start
with a more personal approach,
then I'd go to the data.
Because data is boring.
It's really our emotions
that transcends it all.
EMOTIONAL INTELLIGENCE
How was your weekend?
-Uh, good. It was pretty nice out.
-Yeah.
How's Mencía? Did she open up?
-No. With her, it's best not to talk.
-Right.
Okay.
-All right, show me what you got.
-Okay.
No, no. Stay right there.
You're fine where you are.
I can go first if you want.
I'm really eager to.
Very well.
Prisoner reentry is just a utopian ideal.
Experience has proven it.
It all depends on the prisoner's will
and choices, not on institutions.
I'd like to point out, we are the country
with the biggest percentage of prisoners--
-Not the most crime. They're not related.
-Whoa. This isn't casual barroom banter.
Wait your turn to respond,
and please don't raise your voice again.
We're the highest in all of Europe.
A hundred and twenty-six prisoners
for every 100,000 citizens.
And that, Samuel, is a fact.
A hundred twenty-six prisoners
with 126 families,
friends, and loved ones.
Prisoners have people close to them.
You've thought about that?
Of course I thought about it,
but that's not what we're talking about--
We are. It's not the kind of thing
you can just gloss over.
What's your focus? People or numbers?
What?
Numbers, so you can distance yourself
and dehumanize them.
I mean, imagining myself,
Samuel García, being dragged into jail.
Looking at a bunch of years ahead of me.
And imagining every Samuel García in jail.
My family and friends
might be able to help me,
but the system won't let them.
Because after a stint,
all you'll ever be seen as is a felon.
And that's what happens
when you reduce people to labels.
You erase their humanity
in a single stroke.
Same with numbers.
On that note, uh, I'm done.
Thanks for listening.
Okay, we need to refine it a bit.
But keep up the good work.
What on earth did you do all weekend?
It's best
that Samuel thinks he can beat me.
Well, I'm pretty sure
we just saw that he can.
And if that happened, well,
I would be extremely disappointed,
to say the very least.
You! Where were you Friday afternoon?
-Excuse me?
-Mm…
I said,
"Where were you Friday afternoon?"
Wow. Envy really isn't a good look on you,
Ivanka.
Isn't it enough for you to be fought over
by two guys already?
-I was with her.
-From what time to what time?
I don't know off the top of my head.
Um, yeah. Why the inquisition?
My sister had bruises on her body.
-"What time period?" I asked you.
-I have no idea.
He just told you we were together.
Well, just in case, don't go near Mencía.
Are we clear? Not at all.
No idea. Who knows what that was.
PHILLIPE VON TRIESENBERG ABUSE
NO RESULTS FOUND FOR YOUR SEARCH
Ari,
you shouldn't make false accusations.
I have my reasons.
Oh, well, if you're so sure he did that
to her, why don't you report him, then?
That's precisely why, Cayetana.
'Cause I don't have real evidence yet.
And I don't normally report people
without it.
-That's the kind of girl I am.
-Hmm.
Well, the girl
from his country didn't have evidence,
so I guess the both of you
must be the same kind of girls.
Honey.
Look, I totally get
that you're really into Phillipe and all,
and I never for a moment
said he doesn't like you back.
The thing is, it's not the same.
Because you always expected a no
from a guy like that,
while he expected a yes.
People like Phillipe
don't understand the concept of no.
I'm sticking my nose
in someone else's business,
but if I were you,
I wouldn't wait to have proof with him.
Maybe once you have proof,
it'll be too late.
If there's one thing
you and I have in common,
it's that we're both women, honey.
And if women don't lend each other a hand,
who will?
I understand
that, right now, you're mad at me.
I just wanted to say
I'm here for you if you need it,
if you want.
Nobody forced anyone.
You don't need my forgiveness.
Yeah, but I'm just--
I'm sorry about what I said
and how I told you,
so forgive me for that.
Okay.
If you need me to forgive you
for something, then sure, I forgive you.
Cool.
Uh, thanks.
Ander…
just a reminder, you spent a whole year
tied to a machine, doing chemo.
No one should make you feel
like you have to beg or feel guilty
or ask permission.
OMAR, I NEED TO SEE YOU.
What's the matter now?
Without you,
I wouldn't have survived cancer.
What you did was incredible, and, um…
I won't ever forget it, but…
No, don't say it.
Omar…
maybe the cancer took its toll on us.
Please, no.
Not on me, no.
I mean, okay, yes,
I've been in a fucking mental fog,
but I'm not anymore.
When I thought about losing you, I--
Listen, uh…
I only love you, Ander.
Listen, though.
I'm not talkin' about Patrick now.
I'm… talking about me.
I thought I'd die, but here I am somehow.
I mean, I just wanna live.
There's a ton of things
I still have to do. A ton.
But… you can do them with me.
It's me, dude.
It's Omar.
It's me.
-I know. I know.
-Omar.
And you have to keep being Omar.
But that's why I'm thinking
it's best we end this here
because I don't want this
to become something else entirely.
Thank you.
Thank you, Omar.
From the bottom of my heart.
And I'm sorry too. I really am.
I was thinkin'
of taking you out to dinner tonight,
so you can clear your head a bit.
You sidetracked me last weekend already.
Rather be at the library
with him on Saturday?
Come to dinner at my place.
We can hang out together a while.
With your dad?
Not what I had in mind, to be honest.
Yeah, but after that,
everything goes smoothly.
Hmm.
Ari, García's gonna be coming over.
That way,
I can go over both of your arguments.
-How's it goin'?
-All good, thanks.
I'm goin' to your place for dinner.
SHARE MY LOCATION
DID YOU BLOCK ME?
What's the matter?
Armando.
Wait, what?
What the fuck does that asshole want?
We're calling the police now.
Hey, hold up.
Want my family knowing about it?
Oh, so you care about your family now?
I mean, yeah,
my family and the entire school
and kinda the whole world.
Just relax, okay?
It's all good.
I can handle this guy.
Do you know that, until the age of three,
all I ate was chocolate?
Oh really?
Psst, hey!
Some dumbass guy sure as hell
isn't gonna spoil our…
…chocolate party.
No, Mencía, I said--
Sorry, I couldn't resist.
You know I just can't help myself.
Mencía.
-Thanks.
-Samuel?
No, I don't want any, thanks.
Gotta stay sharp for tomorrow's debate.
Hmm.
The winner's going
to the European debate competition,
where they'll have to present
but have to do it in French, right?
Hmm. Well, yes.
What would you do?
Don't you speak French?
I have a decent grasp of it.
Yeah, for a local yokel, maybe.
What?
But don't worry.
Because since Ari's gonna win,
that won't be a problem, right?
You know, you should thank him, Samuel.
Why?
Because people like us rise
to the challenge when we're questioned.
I'm sorry. People like you?
Yeah, people who studied on scholarship.
Ah, right.
And haven't been as fortunate
as the three of you here.
I'm the one who's competing with Samuel,
Guzmán, not you.
-Me?
-Yeah.
I wasn't. I'm not worried.
I don't see you spending Christmas
with his family
in some shithole in Morocco.
-What?
-Yeah.
His brother ran off there.
His mom went as well.
I was told he'd been exonerated, though.
More like he didn't wait
to get the verdict.
So you're saying his brother
fled the country while on probation?
Just so you know
the gem of a brother-in-law you'd have.
See you tomorrow.
Mencía!
-What are you doing here?
-I'm trying to have a conversation.
-You're following me.
-I saw your Instagram.
Mencía, please.
I just wanted to apologize.
What for?
I found out what happened… and I'm sorry.
Son of a bitch is done.
He can forget about his career
and basically everything.
Can I drive you home?
I gave it up.
Maybe you should get a new cell phone.
-Why?
-Doesn't that guy have your number?
Yeah, but I mean, I blocked him, so…
Yeah, but he might give it
to someone else, harass you, whatever.
Right. I hadn't thought of that.
Well, thanks.
Where are we?
It'd be nice for us to have a drink
before heading home.
No, uh, I don't think my girlfriend
would think that's a very good idea.
I'm sorry.
All right, but at least
let me take you home-- Mencía.
Mencía, please.
Mencía.
I'll take you home. I will.
Hey.
I'm here to get all my stuff.
Right. Yeah, Omar let me know.
Do you want me to help you out?
No, I can do it alone.
Okay.
Wanna check to see
if everything's there? Nothing's missing?
You okay?
It's just that…
No, no, this can't be real.
I mean, okay,
yeah, it's true I had doubts about it,
but I don't anymore.
I know what I want now.
I can't believe this hurts so much.
And if it hurts this much,
it's because I really love him, isn't it?
This is the worst part.
I can't breathe.
You think that knot
in your stomach will never go away.
But one day,
the knot starts to loosen up,
and it hurts less and less…
until you suddenly realize that…
…you haven't thought about him all day.
You can't even remember
why it once hurt so much.
But there's no way I can forget him.
I can't, and I don't want to.
Shit, I mean, it's Ander.
It's Ander.
Oh yeah. He came looking for me.
Why the fuck did you tell me you quit
and then lie to me?
-He came to apologize to me.
-Yeah.
Look, this video shows your mother's POV.
But what do you see?
'Cause it seems like you only see
what you wanna see.
Haven't you asked yourself
why your mother knows this guy?
Why he might've been
at the door of her place? No.
Because all you see is I'm lying to you.
What the fuck are you tryin' to say
about my mother?
Your mother saw us together
for the first time
when the two of us went to her spot.
We went there to have a drink and, um…
also, so your mom could…
sell him some coke.
No.
No, no way. That's impossible.
-My mother quit that for me.
-No, Rebe. I quit that shit for you.
I quit for you,
and you still trust your mother,
who, ironically,
is the only one here who's lying.
Patrick.
Yeah?
Uh…
why don't we skip classes today
and go out somewhere?
How come?
Don't know. I wanna treat myself.
Plus, they're having
that freakin' debate thing.
They won't notice we're gone.
Okay.
What sort of plan do you have in mind?
Hmm.
Was hoping you'd come up with it.
-Mencía, have you seen Ander?
-Sorry.
-Have you seen Rebe?
-No.
FYI, I'm ditching class.
I'm throwing a thing at the house,
so cover for me. Pretty please?
Fine. I'll text when the debate's over.
Listen, don't trash the house, all right?
Don't wanna invoke the wrath of Benjamín.
Okay, love you.
DEBATE DAYS
Hey.
The dress code is topless.
That's the spirit.
Hey, what's goin' on?
Yeah, good stuff.
Hey. Where's the bathroom?
Well said, Samuel. Thank you.
Ariadna, when you're ready.
Thank you kindly.
Reentry depends
on the prisoner's willpower,
not on institutions.
Some may say, after jail,
they have been conditioned
to relapse into criminal behavior.
But maybe change isn't what they want,
or change isn't possible.
Recidivism rates speak for themselves,
not to mention concrete examples.
On this matter, I'm sure my opponent
is intimately familiar
with the case of a man accused of murder
only two years ago.
And the accused
spent several long weeks in jail,
then decided to flee while on probation,
thus breaking the law
and adding to his previous offenses.
My opponent is familiar with this case…
EMOTIONAL INTELLIGENCE
…because that man is his brother.
-Why did she say that?
-Why'd you use that?
It's best to put a name to the data.
Simple as that.
Mentioning my brother
is completely inappropriate.
His case is well known
to everyone at the school.
I don't think
I'm revealing any state secrets here.
I'm sorry, Samuel,
but I think Ariadna's right.
Samuel's brother--
-Samuel. Samuel!
-He'll come back.
-What's with the childish tantrum?
-Maybe we're not that similar.
-I'm over being questioned every day!
-This is how you live your life?
You wallow in misfortune
and use it as an excuse
to stay stuck in the exact same place.
Don't give me another Jedi master speech,
'cause I'm over it.
No, you wanna hear from the Jedi master?
You're gonna love this one.
Know why I have so much respect
for the art of debate?
Because like all other arts,
it represents life itself.
And you can load up on arguments
and reasons.
You can…
…prepare to the point of exhaustion.
You can feel superior and indestructible.
But without fail,
something unexpected comes up
without warning
and can shatter your protective armor.
Without fail.
And that…
is when you discover how weak you are.
When you realize everything
you thought about yourself,
that everything you had prepared…
is absolutely useless.
-I was looking for you.
-Oh, hi.
Uh, wanna come sleep over
at my place tonight?
Um…
Sure. Yeah, okay.
So you can… either run away,
playing the victim
and hiding behind a series of excuses
that aren't even yours,
like that thing with your brother…
or you can choose to rise up
and fight to bring out
what you would like to become.
Let me know what you decide.
EMOTIONAL INTELLIGENCE
And then poor Samuel just walks out,
right in the middle of the debate.
Ari didn't know what to do.
-She was stunned.
-Hmm.
Um, any chance you're hungry?
-Yeah, a little, yeah.
-Yeah?
I'll see if they can make something.
We can have it here.
-Okay? Okay.
-Okay.
Oh, I have to grab my cell pho--
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I just wanted to put on some music.
I thought we would trust each other.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm so sorry. I don't know.
Ari's been doing a number on me all day,
and I just…
Yeah, but Ari has no idea
where I was on Friday.
-I know.
-You do 'cause I was with you.
-Wasn't I? Don't you get it?
-It's just… Please, I'm sorry.
You have so little self-esteem
that you can't understand
how someone like me would be with you.
And you look for any excuse
to ruin a good thing… all the time.
Will you always remind me of my station?
Looking for flaws
under some kind of microscope.
Closer and closer each time
till you no longer see me.
-You're wrong. I do see you.
-No.
Okay? I see you, and I like you.
I like you so much it hurts me.
I-- I'm not like those girls from before.
I'll go tell the driver
to come pick you up.
If you want, you can check
that I deleted your video.
Snoop around as much as you like.
Honey? Can you not hear me?
I've been hollering at you forever now.
-Are you alone?
-Oh shit.
The house stinks of testosterone.
-Does it really?
-No.
Thank you.
What's this?
Don't know.
It came while we were partying.
A NEW NUMBER SO YOU CAN START
FROM SCRATCH. BIG KISS, ARMANDO.
I RAN AWAY FROM HOME.
I didn't tell you about Nano
so you'd use it against him.
And, Ari,
that whole winning-at-any-cost thing?
-It wasn't cool.
-Well, you're the one to talk.
I'm not the only one who's obsessed
with competing with Samuel.
No one would ever guess you're friends.
Well, we are. Seriously.
Samuel's a cool guy.
He's the best thing I've gotten
out of these past two shitty years.
And it's true that when he got here,
yeah, I looked down on him.
But look,
the guy had everything against him,
and he's beaten the odds every time.
But be real.
You still look down on him a little.
Not anymore, honestly.
In fact,
that's why he makes me so jealous.
And maybe, well,
he makes me scared I might lose you.
You're scared of losing me?
I mean, okay,
not like scared scared or terrified.
A little scared.
What?
Do you like that I'm scared of losing you?
I like that you're not afraid to say that.
I don't know
what came over me or what I was thinking.
I'll meet you in half an hour
at the pier on the lake.
Please come and hear me out.