If personal data
is the modern equivalent of oil,
the data of the most influential families
is gold.
I understand,
but the risk isn't worth the profit.
The profit
is immeasurable, Benjamín.
What? You want it all for yourself?
For you and your precious holding, right?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I have evidence, Benjamín.
Evidence that could destroy you
in a second.
You and all your companies.
Just share the wealth with me,
and nothing will go wrong.
CHARITY AUCTION
LAS ENCINAS AND LAKE CLUB
Good morning,
ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to our auction.
The proceeds of which will be put
towards funding scholarships
for… for students who show promise
but who might not have
the financial means to attend Las Encinas.
The ones who are truly deserving.
Because we all know
those who change the world do so
with their talent,
regardless of their background.
So I'm appealing to your generosity.
And I hope, together, we can make
this fundraiser truly unforgettable.
Thank you all.
Patrick?
No idea.
Omar? The guests' party favors are…?
-In the storeroom.
-And the canapés?
-In ten minutes.
-Great.
-You see where the dossiers got placed?
-I think over there.
-All right. Okay. Thanks.
-No problem.
Oh man.
Uh, hey there.
Yeah. Hi.
Uh, Mencía, this is Jess.
And Jess, Mencía.
Ah, so this is Menci, is it?
"Menci," huh?
-You told her about me?
-Nah. Just gave her context.
-Right.
-Mm.
Well, it's a pleasure, Jessie.
Jess.
-Right.
-Mm.
Mencía. Found them.
Mm. Thank you.
-Give me the phone.
-Let go.
-The phone.
-Don't have one.
Hand it over.
Now.
No, I… I don't--
-Excuse me.
-Oh.
-You dropped this.
-Thanks.
Of course.
-I was gonna give back the phone.
-Give back my laptop too.
Fuck you.
Omar stuck his neck out to help you,
and you just stabbed him in the back.
Today's really important
for him professionally.
So don't you dare
fuck this up for him. Clear?
-What were you doing?
-Kicking Bilal out.
Was he here?
Stealing.
Yeah. Sure.
He pickpocketed a phone.
You made that up.
Just admit you were dickin' around.
Think whatever you want.
I can separate our work
and our personal shit.
You clearly can't.
Are you here to see me?
-I can't stay long. I only have a minute.
-Only one?
I just had a fight with Omar,
and if he sees me here, he'll kill me.
When you're not studying, you're working.
When you're not working, you're worn out.
Look, I'd love to hang out with you
all the time and study, but I can't do it.
Pretty please?
See you later, okay?
Thanks.
For you.
Well?
What?
Let's meet new people today.
C'mon. You first.
What are you into? Businessmen?
-Ugh, so boring.
-You're not wrong.
-Okay. What about students, for example?
-No, no, no. Yeah, no.
-No more students, please. Ever.
-Okay, um…
Well, then, over in the back, the uh…
What are they? Drug dealers, I guess.
I mean, look at them.
-Close enough. They're soccer players.
-We're in trouble.
The one in the middle is
Iván Carvalho's father. Know who that is?
-No way.
-Mm.
As far as eye candy that won't make us
think too hard, they're not bad, right?
Yeah. Who needs interesting conversation?
-Maybe… they could surprise us, right?
-You never know.
Hi. What's up, guys?
-What's up?
-You boys care if we join you, or…?
Of course not, gatinhas.
Sorry, what?
Sorry. He said, um, "You're beautiful."
-Ah.
-Oh.
Literally, "cats." Little ones.
So, we're little kittens, huh? Okay.
You soccer players
sure are direct, aren't you?
There you are, already scoring goals.
Ooh!
I think, like,
even a little bit. You know?
Excuse me.
I hate seeing
so much potential go to waste because
you don't believe in yourself.
-My potential isn't paying my bills.
-You mean you're scared?
I'm not scared. I'm realistic.
That makes me unreal? Hmm?
What I've achieved,
coming from the same place as you,
is that unreal too?
-You know what I meant by that, though.
-No, I don't know, but you can explain it.
Not only are you scared,
you're making excuses.
That's a shame.
There are influential people here today
I wanted to introduce you to
for future internships, but…
…since you're dressed like a waiter
and not like a guest…
What do you think I should do?
Hang up my uniform?
Priorities, Samuel.
Benjamín, I hope everything's good so far.
If you'll excuse us…
-Do I have to be on your back all day?
-He pulled me aside. What should I do?
Your job, dude.
Or were you
just on another break of yours?
Since you'll make
my life miserable anyway…
-What's this?
-I quit.
Let's see how you get by today
with one less waiter, Omar.
Hey, Samuel!
Dammit, dude!
You little sh…
Sir?
You okay?
Hello. I'd like a sparkling water.
With lime, not lemon.
And a little baby sprinkle
of turmeric. Thanks.
Hey, sweetie.
-What's wrong?
-I quit.
I mean, fuck this shitty job.
I'm out, you know?
-Seriously?
-Yes.
Oh, honey. That's great!
-Baby, let's order something to celebrate.
-Not now.
Gotta return the uniform,
tell the manager, and find your dad.
He's introducing me
to important people. Know where he is?
-My father?
-Yeah.
-He's someplace.
-Okay.
Hey, but why can't you just stay with me?
Later, all right?
We'll celebrate later.
Actually, I don't want a sparkling water.
I want a gin and tonic.
Any brand will work.
No, make that two gin and tonics.
Uh, um… Can I come up for air?
I mean, just so… just so… so I don't die.
Like, not suffocate.
I mean, that kinda thing.
Yeah, but every minute I'm not kissing you
is one I can't get back.
Yeah.
Okay. Which Twilight film
did you escape from, dude?
Has no one shown
strong feelings for you before?
It's not that.
No, no. No. But just pace yourself, okay?
Pace yourself a smidge.
-Smidge? I'm pacing myself.
-Yeah. Let me grab you one. Okay?
-I want a gin and tonic.
-No. Absolutely not.
-I am getting you some water.
-No, not water.
Your sobriety's as existent
as your filter right now, all right?
Wait for me here.
I'll wait forever, boo.
Hmm. Okay.
Jesus H. Christ.
Why the computer?
To organize the auction.
The bids, the purchases
and sales, the participants--
Your dad went
from not trusting you to total trust.
That's because I have earned it.
It's what you always wanted.
To be daddy's little girl.
How's your little girl doing?
I mean, wouldn't it be cheaper
to buy a box of suction cups
and just, like, get it over with?
Then you wouldn't have to try
to speak to her.
She's like glue to your boo.
I think the word
you're looking for is "affectionate."
And super thoughtful,
and she's basically all over me.
-She's smothering?
-She's not smothering.
-Oh, no?
-No, I did not say that.
It's just I'm not used to having someone
give me all the attention that I deserve.
You know what?
Don't want that drink anymore.
Good luck with the auction, all right?
I've been lookin' for you.
Something wrong?
No, nothing. Just the stress
and pressure of all this stuff.
It's nothing.
Of course. Well, you're doin' great.
You think so?
Mm-hmm.
I'm… proud of your work today.
I didn't know you drank.
Only once in a while.
Why'd you text me, Ari?
To come get fresh air.
-Iván, can I ask you a question?
-Yeah.
Your father and you are filthy rich,
isn't that right?
What?
I meant that you don't have more
only because there aren't enough days
in the year.
What's this all about?
Just tell me. C'mon.
Are you and your father
filthy stinking rich or not?
Well, obviously, my dad is.
I knew it.
Why ask?
Is that what you want? A rich guy?
Oh, no, no, no. Uh-uh.
What I want is
a guy who doesn't need anything.
Who doesn't need me.
Understand that?
Mm.
Let's go.
-Come here.
-What are you doin'?
-This isn't yours, is it?
-No.
-Do you know how to drive it?
-Not at all.
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo!
Sir?
Hello?
Hey!
You're not supposed to use the boats!
What the fuck, guys!
Bilal!
Well, what… what I'm interested in
at Las Encinas is trying
to remove the barriers
that challenge so many young artists
that have lots of talent
but, uh, not the resources.
That's interesting
and very necessary.
So, Dad, I have to go organize
the auction items now.
-It's about to start, okay?
-Mm-hmm. Better?
I am. Thanks.
And that's pretty much been
my line of work over the last few months.
Hmm?
Could I borrow you?
Mm, yes. Ah, excuse me, please.
I did it.
I just quit my job.
I'm going all in on Las Encinas.
On any internship or whatever it takes.
That's if you still wanna help.
Hmm.
Uh… uh, yes. Can you bring me
a blue pinstripe suit to the Lake Club?
Size?
This guy's been dead a really long time.
That's impossible.
He disappeared. They said he ran off.
Huh?
This guy, I know who he is.
Well, at the time,
it was such a big scandal
because if my father married my mother,
it would be the first time a…
a commoner married…
Am I boring you or something?
-Huh?
-I said, am I boring you?
No. No, no. I'm listening.
I'm sending a super important text,
but… but it's done now.
-Go on. Tell me.
-What was I speaking about? Huh?
Your family and… all that stuff.
"All that stuff."
I'm gonna go get something to drink.
-You checked out, didn't you?
-No, no. I was paying attention.
Do you want a…? Oh! Whiskey? Rum? Vodka?
-What do you want?
-Nothing. I'm avoiding alcohol.
-A Long Island. To make you less uptight.
-I said no.
Were you not listening?
Okay, baby.
How about an orange juice, then?
An orange juice, yeah. All right, then.
Thanks a ton.
Well, let's move on, without further ado,
to the first lot in the auction.
A rather unique sculpture.
Made of Murano glass, of course.
-By the artist Angelo Davide--
-Hey, excuse me. Dad!
I'm sorry.
-Generously donated by the Monte family.
-Dad, I'm sorry. I'm here now. Hey! Sorry.
Please. I'm sorry. Move.
The starting price
for the bidding is set at 10,000 euros.
-C'mon. Move. Fuck.
-It's…
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Patrick.
Ooh. I'm sorry.
Oh my God.
Have them clean this up
and settle the payment for the sculpture.
How am I supposed to…?
Samuel really kicked you out of the house
because of me?
No, Bilal. I made that up.
I'm gonna call the police.
Uh, please wait until I leave.
Or else they're gonna pin this on me.
Ah, fuck!
My cell must have died in the water.
Do you have one?
No. Otherwise, you wouldn't steal one.
I can't go back to the club
like this, with my uniform wet.
I can sneak in and maybe find someone.
Okay.
Look for Rebeka.
Brunette, in a tracksuit,
long nails, tacky jewelry.
Um, uh, likely
with another chick, making out.
With another chick? For real?
Save the homophobia for later,
when there aren't dead bodies
lying around. Okay, man? Okay?
-Sorry.
-Thank you. Find Rebeka.
Why don't I find Samuel?
It really bugs me
you're not talking 'cause of me.
-And he's your best friend.
-Find Rebeka.
-Go on.
-Okay. Okay.
Fuck.
Okay. So you're totally gonna deny
that you're here with me
because I'm a young woman.
One that you can…
Uh, I mean, potentially take to bed
so you can keep thinking you're still
an energetic, young 20-year-old, right?
I am not in the habit of,
uh, sleeping with girls
in my son's circle.
Oh, well, that's too bad.
You even have a moral code.
-Yeah, I do.
-Hmm? Yeah, for sure.
Well, maybe I should throw mine
out the window,
and then I can start setting my sights
on mature, older men
with their heads screwed on straight,
like yours is… maybe.
That's a great idea.
And stop setting my sights on
these lost, messed-up,
and confused spoiled brats all the time.
Hmm?
Well, I finished my drink.
Have you gone to see the pier?
No.
No? Oh, it's beautiful.
You have to see it.
If you wanna head over there,
I'll get a couple of drinks
and show it to you.
Right now?
Yeah, now, if it's okay with you.
Yeah. I think that'd be great.
Okay.
No. You sit down!
-Know the price of that sculpture?
-You'll pay for it.
Well, I'm sure for you,
it's like peanuts.
-Are you high right now?
-No.
Have you seen your eyes?
It's a reaction.
-A reaction to what? To being a disgrace?
-As if any of this affects you.
'Cause now you have that suck-up, Samuel.
The perfect son you can play daddy to.
Since you can't stand
the selfish queer you got as a real son.
-Come on.
-That you're ashamed of every day.
You gonna cry about it?
Right now? You're such a child.
It must have been real torture
for you to outlive Mom
and have to always lug us around
with you, right?
You think everyone is so mediocre.
Even your family,
beginning with your children.
You even thought Mom was weak.
But she chose to see the good in everyone.
In her children!
Even in a pathetic man
with delusions of grandeur like you.
Stop it!
Hey!
I said stop it!
You've never laid a hand on us
before this.
Mm. Mm.
Benjamín's having me consider
a career in law.
Right now we're just trying to find
the right university for me.
Excuse me just a moment.
I'll be, uh, right back. Just a sec.
Excuse me.
Why are you here?
-Samuel, I'm sorry.
-I told you to leave.
-Listen to me--
-Leave, or I'll call the police.
-Omar needs your help.
-Okay. So what?
I quit. What's the problem?
We found a dead guy's body
floating in the lake,
and Omar knows who he is.
Huh?
It's so cold!
Let me help you.
Ah, it's so cold.
-Just to warm us up a bit.
-Yeah.
Better?
What? Huh?
Patrick.
What's wrong?
Can I help?
Leave me the fuck alone, all right?
Uh, excuse the interruption.
It's time that we continue on
with the next lot,
which is a unique donation
from one of our most illustrious guests.
Uh, from Cruz Carvalho,
who's actually here with us right now.
Uh, Cruz?
Okay. I can't see him right now,
but I assure you, he's here.
Okay. As I was saying, this is a sculpture
by contemporary artist Carlos Moncas.
It's signed by the artist and comes with…
-Hey.
How's your evening going? Well?
Super happy. Great.
It's just great.
-Fucking awesome.
-You feeling a little too fucking awesome?
-No.
-No?
I'm fine.
Are you on drugs?
Oh, Caye, Caye, Caye.
Can I not be doing well
unless I'm with you?
The royal arrogance. Two points.
-And you?
-What about me?
You can't have a prince,
so you chase the king of soccer? No?
Ah, I figured it out. That's what this is.
Two Long Island iced teas.
Wow. They don't have
anything with more alcohol?
You don't control me.
No, never.
Getting anything?
-I ordered two gin and tonics.
-Mm!
Two gin and tonics. Mm.
Perfect for getting to know someone.
Oh wow. You got it.
Ah, thanks.
I mean,
maybe that's what we have to do.
-What is?
-Open up more to other people.
Stop being… so stuck on each other.
Mm-hmm.
Caye,
what you and I feel… is very special.
But I don't think
it's going anywhere, honestly.
Because you're held back
by your need to look after me.
And I'm held back by the constant need
to never disappoint you.
So, it's probably best
we go our separate ways.
And… and breathe freer.
No?
Sure.
-Hmm?
-Mm-hmm.
Do I hear 15,000? 15,000.
Going once. Going twice.
Thank you, sir.
What the fuck, Bilal?
Hey. Now that you're both here,
I feel awful
you guys are fighting because of me.
Shut up.
I need to think.
I've tried to figure out what to do.
Should I tell Ari and Mencía
or maybe call the police directly?
I don't know, man. I'm lost.
This is way above my pay grade.
Maybe we should call the police.
Don't you think?
Fuck it. Of course we should call.
Come on.
No. Don't call them.
Then who?
Fucking Benjamín? No way.
Rebe.
She and I
helped Guzmán dump this guy in the lake.
Excuse me?
This very beautiful Bohemian glass goblet,
property of
our beloved Herrera de Miguel family
for over six generations,
which has a starting price
of 15,000 euros.
Who will offer 15,000?
Ah? Sold.
The next lot.
Mixed-media oil and collage.
The work of the virtuosic hands
of Argentinean artist Gabriela Rosales.
A starting price of 12,000 euros.
One-of-a-kind diamond necklace,
crafted with olivine
from the Kilauea volcano
in Hawaii, inspired
by the extinct Russian Czarist Empire.
With a starting price of 200,000 euros.
What's cookin', Samuel?
What?
And it's sold.
Charge this for me and keep an eye on it.
Okay. Excuse me, sir.
Please, can you charge this phone?
Yeah? Thank you.
Menci. Uh, I have a favor to ask you.
I'm busy enough with the auction.
Yeah, uh, the thing is,
this is an emergency, you know?
I need to pop out for a moment.
It'll be just a sec, but I'll be back.
Could be longer, or it might be quick,
but I'll be back.
Can you stay with Jess?
You're kidding, right?
Look at her.
So drunk, she doesn't know where she is.
Stumbling all over.
I can't leave her along
because she might crack her head, crash--
Rebeka, you're asking your ex
to look after your… I don't know.
-I don't know. Your girlfriend?
-We're just friends.
Okay. Your "just friend."
No. I mean, I don't care.
I wouldn't ask you to do it
if it weren't important.
Please, Menci.
I'll go get her. Thanks.
Sorry about earlier.
Ah, no problem. Don't worry.
You feeling better?
Yeah.
What happened with your father?
I always felt like an outsider
in this family.
You know?
As if I had to apologize
for having survived
the accident that killed my mother.
Clearly,
my dad wanted a different type of son.
They all want a different type of Patrick.
Everyone.
-Nobody loves me as I am.
-Come on.
Don't say that.
No, seriously. I'm over it.
No one ever notices me.
Like, I do my own fucking thing,
I keep not needing anyone,
and I can still get whatever I want.
And I'm sick of it.
That's not true.
That no one notices you.
No one.
Not possible.
Holy shit.
-You seem kinda intelligent.
-Yeah. That's 'cause I am intelligent.
That's 'cause you
an intelligent bitch.
Why'd you let her get away, then? Hmm?
What do you mean?
You still seem to like her a bit.
A little.
You know,
she won't stop talking about you.
It's like, "Menci this."
It's like, "Menci that." You know?
-"Menci." She calls you that.
-Yeah, I know. She calls me Menci.
Hmm.
-You can imagine that gets under my skin--
-Listen.
I have to work, okay?
So would you mind not…?
Appreciate it. Thank you.
Mm.
Excuse me?
Can I please have another one of these?
Thanks.
Mm.
You like that she talks about you, right?
I mean, if you like her,
she's all yours, dude.
No problemo.
If you wanna be with her,
I'll step aside, hundo P.
Thanks.
But… say it, you know? Be clear.
But what you can't do is reject her
and be there, constantly just…
…orbiting around her.
Tell her you're out of the picture
because I'm already fed up
with her talking about you all day.
What? Not gonna say anything?
I mean, like, if you'd rather go on
doing damage
but playing the victim…
Well, great, sugar.
Like, what can I say?
But be careful, okay?
Yeah.
Because you might have to deal with me.
And if you come
between Rebe and me…
…I'll get you out of the picture.
Yeah, sure. I'll make sure she finds out
what a shit person you are.
So you won't fucking see her ever again.
I swear.
Understand?
I gotta pee.
I've been holdin' it for a while. Cool.
Holy-- That's a fuckin' smell.
-Rebe, c'mon.
-Absolutely not.
Man, that smell is seeping
into my bone marrow.
-I can't. Let Omar help.
-No. Don't drag Omar into this.
At least try. C'mon.
No, I can't do it, dude. I can't.
Rebe, we did it once before.
Then he had just died.
Now he might decompose in our hands.
-Who knows?
-Just try. Please.
Don't think about it. Just grab.
Grab that.
I told you, man.
I can't, Samuel. I told you that.
Hey. Omar's fucking upset.
Oh God.
Omar. Omar, hon. We wanted
to keep you out of it to protect you.
Who knew about this?
Guzmán, Rebe, and I.
And Ander?
Who knows? Guzmán might've told him,
but it's hard to say.
Dude! When exactly did you guys
become a bunch of murderers?
-Hey. We didn't kill him, okay?
-And?
You're accomplices.
Uh, sorry, but let's
not lose perspective here.
The world's way better
without this piece of shit in it, okay?
I mean, he was a victimizer,
abuser, rapist. Should I go on?
And you gave me shit
because of a computer?
Can you help us? We really need you, man.
For what?
Are we sinking him again? Ten-hut.
We're just a bunch of fucking kids!
We don't know
what we're doing with our lives,
never mind how to handle a body!
That's it.
-We're gonna call the police now.
-No.
-Think about Guzmán and the two of us.
-Can you think about me? Huh?
What about me, dude?
-I found him. I know everything now.
-I'm sorry, Omar.
Things just are how they are, okay?
You're my best friend. You always will be.
Well, now your best friend
is telling you to call the police, okay?
A FRESH START. KISSES, ARMANDO
Fine.
I'll call them.
But I'm asking you one last favor.
You don't know anything.
Hurry up. Leave.
EMERGENCIES