Omar!
C'mon. You're not the only one
who lives here.
Omar, fuckin' come on.
This is Bilal.
I told you about him.
Why is this guy here?
I mean, dude,
he needed to crash somewhere.
-And you didn't check with me first?
-Samuel, this is also my house.
Sure.
I dunno. Next time, tell me.
C'mon.
-I'm so fucking hungover.
-Does your head hurt?
Crazy night, huh?
-It was intense.
-Hi, hi.
Look. Speak of the devil.
You sleep over at Samuel's?
-Yeah, why?
-No reason.
-Wait till Dad makes an appearance.
-We'll see if he talks to you.
'Cause since we got home,
he hasn't said a word.
-Mm.
-Good morning.
Have a good time with Samuel last night?
Mm… Yeah, I guess it was okay.
What do you mean, "okay"?
That's an underwhelming review of an orgy.
All right, go shower and get changed.
I don't want you to be late for the exam.
It's a multiple-choice test.
A drug test.
A negative result will add two points
to your grade point average.
Get a positive result…
and you'll be expelled.
-He can't.
-Questions?
This is stupid.
Just wonderful, dude. Just wonderful.
So, with the little prince, what happens
in Triesen stays in Triesen.
But you're gonna screw us plebs over
for what we do in our private lives?
You got the wrong bitch, partner.
I'm in this class too.
And I was at the party,
so I also refuse to take it.
Come on.
Patrick.
Let's go.
-This isn't fair.
-I'm not taking it, either.
Otherwise, what?
Are you gonna expel the entire school?
If necessary, then yes.
Come on. Chill out. He's totally bluffing.
Hey, Omar, can you not?
Let him do the test.
You really think he'll kick you all out?
You think he'll get rid of his cash cows
who pay for his screens in the hallways,
little cameras, and metal detectors?
Come on. I'm the only one who didn't go,
and I'm on scholarship.
So, go ahead, Benjamín. Do the test.
Dude, seriously. Shut up.
Okay.
Since it seems the class
who rebels together stays together,
I'm going to ask you to stick together
once more to make a decision.
Now we're gonna vote
via the school intranet,
and voting will be compulsory.
You'll have to choose a student,
someone from within your class,
and whoever's elected…
Well, that student will be expelled
on the remainder's behalf.
-Seriously?
-Because somebody has to pay.
Is this guy for real?
-Why is he doing this?
-What the fuck?
Everyone, shh. Please calm down!
You're the ones
who will be making the final decision.
Oh, and, uh, García,
congratulations on sticking to your guns
against the peer pressure
and not being emotionally manipulated
into standing up with the others.
It would be a shame if a student
like García were expelled, while others,
who have zero interest in the common good
and no viable plans for the future,
were to remain.
Son of a bitch.
-Why rile him up like that?
-Someone needed to take a stand.
'Cause, clearly, you're not going to.
What?
-Nothing.
-What's the matter?
You agree with him, don't you?
You think I should go.
I think it wouldn't hurt you
as much as the others.
That's what I think.
My father has that power.
He pushes you. He's demanding.
And he's never quite satisfied with you.
You get to the point where you try…
anything to gain his approval.
I think wanting to be his friend
is just a convenient
and easy way for you to…
to stay close to him
while telling yourself
and the rest of the world
that you're not into him at all.
No, I don't think so.
Well, you don't have to agree with me.
Just with yourself.
-Talk to you soon?
-Sure.
Mm-hmm?
Good morning.
Hey, I'm honestly sorry about last night.
Apology accepted.
Caye, come on.
Hello, fellow goddesses.
Sorority call.
I want-- No.
I need to
make you reflect on your excuses
for kicking a classmate out of school.
-You hear everything in bathrooms.
-What the hell?
And I know
that some of you ladies
intend to vote for Phillipe
to kick him out of school
based on wild accusations
that are totally unfounded.
That's wrong.
And, you know, that's despite him
standing up to authority
like everyone else did.
Okay?
I, as a very special friend of Phillipe's…
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
…I have to say that he is simply
a gentleman from head to toe.
Cayetana? She's supporting him.
Guys, come on.
So, that makes not one but now two women
who know him intimately
and who believe in
his right to redeem himself.
And, babes, if you thought
the whole monarchy thing is medieval,
let me tell you
that retro is very much in.
But burning someone at the stake
without evidence isn't exactly chic.
Right?
Okay, bye.
Hey, uh, what'd you mean
by "special friend"?
-You're welcome.
-But you and I barely know each other.
Baby, I told you,
if they think there's something going on,
you'll stop being a rapist
and go back to being a prince.
The darling of Spain and Triesen.
The public eats it up
when they see a couple
that's young, rich, famous, good-looking.
And I swear to you,
these kids will forget everything
to buy into that fairy tale.
ALMODÓVAR FILM SEASON
You're into that director, aren't you?
-You know who Almodóvar is?
-No idea. I just saw it on your Insta.
It's so you'll forgive me.
I was trying not to hurt you,
but I hurt you three times as much.
So, what is this? A date?
No, man.
It's me making plans with friends.
I'm inviting people from my class
and from your class as well.
Just to get everything clear up front.
So no drama.
Come on, give me a hug.
I know you're dying to.
Who are your plans with?
People.
None of your damn business.
The girl from last night?
Yeah, I went to the party.
-And I saw you with her.
-Okay, fine.
Her name's Jess.
You could say she's my first dyke friend…
and invited me to my first dyke party.
A lot of pretty dykey firsts to be honest.
Well, let's go to the drive-in.
And
then I'll go with you
to that dykey party
with this so-called Jess.
Only if you wanna.
You serious?
BABE, WHAT'S THE PLAN FOR THE DRIVE-IN?
Hey, Omar.
I'm sorry I assumed
you didn't care about anything.
We don't really shoot the shit anymore.
We're spending more time together
than ever.
At the house,
at the restaurant, and at school, but
we don't talk anymore.
Oh my God.
Why am I getting so intense? Jesus.
Omar, I'm stopping by the house
to change for the drive-in.
You maybe wanna…
Maybe just hang out in the plaza?
Have some beers
and sunflower seeds like we used to?
Sorry. I didn't know where to go.
BABE, WHAT'S THE PLAN FOR THE DRIVE-IN?
-Ari, come help me a sec.
-Coming.
What do you think?
-A tracksuit?
-It's very '80s.
Yeah, vintage '87 junkie.
Trap music's screwed you up.
Guys, the cars.
Could you go down?
-Yeah, I can go.
-Tell 'em we'll be right there.
Let's see.
Alone, even for just a minute.
-Should I reveal his weaknesses?
-Jesus Christ.
Why does everyone
assume that I'm gay?
Oh, honey. You can like whoever.
You don't need to put a label on it.
But I saw how hard you got.
Maybe it's not for him.
No, of course not.
Because you're a macho alpha male.
Look, I mean, I get that your dad
plays soccer and all that and--
Let's stop putting a label on it.
What matters is that I like who I like.
Ah.
That's all.
Uh, guys. The cars are here.
-Shall we?
-Let's go.
LEAVING NOW. WE'LL PICK YOU UP.
IT'LL TAKE ABOUT 20 MINUTES.
What's wrong?
Don't make that face, dude.
Look at him.
He's all beat up with nowhere to go.
-Hey, I'm gonna go.
-You're not gonna go anywhere.
Now, relax.
Stings, doesn't it?
ALMODÓVAR FILM SEASON
ALL ABOUT MY MOTHER
LAW OF DESIRE
TIE ME UP, TIE ME DOWN
-Hi. How are you? Two orange juices.
-Hi there.
Do you have any vodka?
How come I'm sick of the '80s and '90s
when I was born in the 2000s?
Baby, can we go to the car
and listen to music from this century?
Wait. No, I like this song.
HIGH HEELS
ALL ABOUT MY MOTHER
But if you don't wanna go out with her,
why did you say yes?
Well, that's exactly why, Cayetana.
Right there.
So she knows
she doesn't have any power over me.
I mean, none.
Selfie?
-As friends?
-As good friends, you mean?
Sure, you mean as BFFs.
Of course.
Smile.
That's it.
EXPULSION VOTING
Come on.
Can't we have a little bit of fun?
How?
It's too much.
First, Omar lied to me
and then left me hanging.
Now there's this whole voting thing.
And I also feel like
I'm letting your dad down, you know?
I was wondering
when you'd mention my father.
Samuel, do you think Iván and Patrick
are thinking about my dad in this moment?
BAD EDUCATION
Look, just never mind.
I'm gonna go and get some food.
TALK TO HER
-Thanks.
-You and I need to talk.
Come here.
-So, what happened this afternoon--
-I'm sorry.
I didn't realize you were one of those.
Those what?
One of those girls
who go for guys like their dad.
Daddy issues?
I'm sorry, what?
I'm messing with you.
I just don't think
Samuel's a good match for you.
Yeah, the way he kisses
is fuckin' awesome.
-But you kiss much better.
-Here's what we're gonna do about this.
You're gonna stay away
from Samuel, from me,
and most importantly,
you'll stay away from Patrick.
And what happened
this afternoon never happened, okay?
Ari, did you smell me?
You know what I'm smelling?
Your little game here.
So, if you fuck with my brother
even the slightest bit,
I'll smack that grin
right off of your mouth.
Is that what you think of me?
Look, your brother
makes me feel fucking great.
-Mm-hmm.
-I hope to make him feel just the same.
But just as friends. That's all.
You can't ask me to feel the same
for him that I feel--
Shh.
That's enough.
So, can't your parents help you?
Or anyone?
But you're a minor.
They could help you find a place
or something, couldn't they?
There are more kids
than beds in that facility.
Do you think they care
if we spend a night on the street?
I mean, someone must care.
I'm telling you, they don't.
You got me. I care about you.
It's the first time
I've heard that since I got here.
Thank you.
I'm gonna get more water.
Omar.
You have a boner right now?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what happened.
-I didn't mean to.
-Are you a queer?
Yeah. I'm queer.
I turn you on?
No, no. Not at all. It was the situation.
-I'll put the tabbouleh in a Tupperware.
-No, don't kick me out.
I'm not kicking you out,
but I assume you don't wanna stay.
But I have nowhere else to go.
What are you doing, Bilal?
What's the matter?
-No, what's the matter with you?
-Don't you like it?
You don't wanna do this.
-Yes, I do.
-Stop!
You're doing it because you think
it's the only way I'll let you stay.
What kind of life have you had
that you think you only deserve help
if you sleep with someone?
We're gonna find a roof
to put over your head,
and we're gonna find you a job, okay?
-What?
-Nothing.
Wow.
-I'm gonna go get popcorn.
-Uh, no. Don't, Caye. They'll bring it.
-It's okay. Let her go if she wants.
-Yeah, I'm gonna get some air.
But, Caye. Hey, Caye, girl.
What's wrong, huh?
Nothing. Nothing's wrong.
Okay. It feels like you're afraid
to be left alone with me.
Who, me? Afraid?
No, no, I'm not scared.
-Because we're friends, right?
-Exactly. We're just friends.
Yeah.
And friends, well…
Friends sometimes do things.
Ah, uh, no, Mencía.
No, no, no, no.
-No, what?
-I said no.
It's just, this place is packed.
-And?
-Well, um, everyone can see us.
Well, you know what?
I don't really give a shit.
Uh,
what if Caye comes back?
I don't care.
-No, kid. We shouldn't. I mean--
-I told you, I don't give a shit.
Well, well, well.
Look who's here. Thanks for saving a spot.
Hey! You look totally gorge, babe.
Yeah, thank you.
Why don't you take my spot?
I'm not hungry anymore.
Wonderful.
Hey, how are you?
Super great, and you?
I'm great too.
-That's great.
-What?
Have you given up on me already?
Look, Caye. I wanna do my part too, okay?
But it's gonna be really hard
for me if you're judging me 24/7
and telling me that…
that what I do is wrong or…
or that it's not enough, you know?
Yeah.
Meanwhile, she's a yes-girl
and tells you everything is okay, right?
She makes my life a lot easier.
Here. Baby, my treat.
-No, thank you.
-No, please. Take it. I bought it for you.
I said I don't want it, okay?
-Seriously? Are you kidding me right now?
-Ah.
Uh… I'll ask for a broom.
You clean here too, don't you?
Isadora, Jesus.
Yeah, fuck it.
Um,
can I borrow this real quick?
Fucking clown.
And you? You're a dumbass.
That fucking little cunt.
What a total fucking bitch!
I mean, did you see
what she just did to me?
Did you see?
Here. You can wear this.
Yeah.
Now that I finally managed
to get naked in front of you?
No way.
I'm all yours.
Okay?
Psst. My favorite scene is coming soon.
Hmm.
Can we go to your place?
Didn't we say
we'd go to the party after this?
Yeah, but I mean, don't you prefer
this party right here?
I was looking forward to going, kid.
I just don't want
any more problems with my dad.
You know what he's been like.
Yeah, so then tell him
you're sleeping over at my house.
I think I'd better not.
How's this go, Mencía?
How does it go?
I come out of the closet,
and you get in, so we never meet outside?
That it? Huh? Tell me.
Please tell me. What are we?
What the fuck are we, dude?
Tell me!
Never mind.
We're done.
I really tried, kid, you know.
I tried so hard.
But I'm done. It's over.
It's over, Mencía.
-No, what's over? Wait.
-It's over.
Wait here.
If I let you loose, will you escape?
I don't know.
You'd better tie me up.
Tie me up.
Samuel,
tie me up.
Tie me up.
How'd it go?
Not good.
Worse for you?
-Well…
-Wanna leave?
Yeah.
I told you. Don't you dare hold back.
Okay?
Please, Phillipe. Please, stop.
Stop! Please, don't, Phillipe!
I'm begging you. Stop!
Stop, stop. Stop, stop, stop.
Let's go. Let's leave.
-Stop what?
-I said we're leaving now.
I don't get it.
I thought you were into this.
I really love this film so much.
Wanna knock one more back?
No, man. I'm wiped. Gonna get some sleep.
What? One little drink.
Then we go to your place.
No, seriously. Let's go home.
But to our own houses.
-What's wrong?
-No, nothing.
I just don't think it's smart
for us to sleep together again.
That's all.
Hey, I meant just as friends. Chill out.
Well, that's why.
Since we're friends,
we can't keep doing that, can we?
-Of course we can.
-No, we can't.
We can't, because you can't get your head
around the fact
that nothing's ever gonna happen
between us.
Look, Patrick. I am the way I am,
and I'm open with people I care about.
But you come up
with these fantasies. They hurt you.
That's why it's better
if we just have some space for now.
Fucking great.
Hey.
THE PERFECT ENDING
TO A PERFECT NIGHT WITH YOU.
Babe, hey. Babe, let's stop. Okay?
Okay?
Sorry.
I've been neglecting you all day,
just thinking about the same shit.
What are you thinking about?
About how I don't want to disappoint you.
I see.
Like you've disappointed
my father?
I'm fucking with you.
Why are you obsessed
with disappointing us?
You're not disappointing anyone.
Do you know
why I'm like that with your dad?
No.
Because I have no idea
what it's like to have a father.
And seeing the way yours worries about me,
asks me what I want to be
or how I'm doing.
He believes in me and is betting on me.
That's such a new feeling.
And I like it.
It gives me peace.
Come here.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR LISTENING TO ME.
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR DOING THE RIGHT THING WITH PATRICK.
Man, with this whole Bilal thing
and learning his life story,
I think I finally know my calling.
Social work.
It's a good fit, right?
What's wrong? What are you looking for?
My computer.
I left it right over here.
Where? Here where?
After school,
I'll go to Bilal's facility and ask him.
But with all the computers at school,
I'm sure you need it less than he does.
What?
It's not an urgent need.
And for someone like Bilal, he can live
on that money for a whole month.
But don't worry.
If you need it, I'll buy you one.
I'm coming!
All right, I'm coming. Jesus.
Hey, baby. Hello.
What is this?
Huh?
Isadora, what is this?
"Hi. How's it going, Isadora?
Good morning! How are you? Okay. You?"
-"Good."
-Can you explain what this is?
-Isadora, what the fuck is this? Huh?
-Yeah. What the fuck is what?
-Was it or was it not a perfect evening?
-No. It was a fucking disaster, okay?
And I didn't come here
to have drinks and chat.
Shh! Lower your voice,
or the hotel staff will hear you,
and I want a supportive,
nontoxic work environment. Understood?
I told you already, baby.
As long as people buy the story
about the prince and the empress,
they'll forget all your sins.
And more importantly, so will you.
Yeah, but I'm not your trophy.
Or anyone's.
Trophy?
You? Honestly?
You're a broken trophy.
Baby, you're radioactive.
You don't gain me followers.
You lose them. Today I lost 2,000.
-Why are you helping me then?
-Because I can't anymore.
I can't stand seeing you
keep punishing yourself
and how they keep punishing you
for something in your past.
It's done.
You need to get over it.
You need to be
with someone who is good for you,
not someone who's constantly reminding you
that you made a mistake.
If you take a small child
and say that he's bad,
that he's bad, that he's bad, what then?
The kid ends up believing
he's actually bad.
I know what I am talking about.
We are not bad. Not me or you.
And I won't allow anyone
to convince us otherwise.
Okay?
And here's a little tip, baby.
If life offers you the opportunity
to lay eyes on the body and face
of an empress of Ibiza,
then what do you do?
You say yes. Yes and yes.
And if you hesitate,
you say yes again. Hmm?
But don't go around posting pics.
Especially not fake ones, okay?
I promise you, it won't happen again.
Although maybe it wasn't such a bad idea.
How are you doing in the voting?
Shanaa.
You didn't vote, and it's mandatory.
What happens if there's a tie?
In that case,
both students would be expelled.
Fuckin' A.
Whenever you're ready.
Samuel, he won't expel you. Don't worry.
My vote's for Samuel.
Omar, bro. What you doin'?
Samuel García Domínguez,
you are expelled for three days,
courtesy of your classmates.
-I thought he was gonna be expelled.
-And he is… for three days.
See that?
Coulda let us know sooner,
don't you think, Benji?
Hold on, hold on.
Wait a minute. What? What's the matter?
Now you're disappointed
because I didn't permanently expel one?
So much for
that whole unite and stick together thing.
In the end, it's every man for himself.
Hmm.
Gonna go to class, Samuel. Ciao.
Remember the time
when you came to talk to me,
and you defended Omar?
Remember that I told you
to focus on your own battles
and stop fighting everyone else's?
Well, it looks like that's a lesson
Omar appears to have learned very well.
Dude, hear me out.
I knew he wasn't gonna let you go.
If it had been me, then forget
that three-day shit. I'd be on the street.
Get outta my house.
-What?
-You heard me.
You gotta be outta here by tomorrow.
Please. I need to understand.
I need to know why you did it.
Did my dad make you that crazy?