I'M AT THE CLUB.
Rebe's at the club.
Perfect. The fewer people around,
the more credible.
Look, dude.
If Benjamín said
the police were going after him,
let them do it.
-We just need to keep our mouths shut.
-Benjamín didn't kill him.
Well, it's either him or Guzmán.
You want them to get Guzmán?
Obviously not.
It's your call.
I mean, we could always
pin it on Phillipe.
He'll pay two for one.
First rape, and now murder.
-He always gets away with it.
-Enough, dude.
Samuel, who will it be?
POLICE LINE, DO NOT CROSS
This never happened.
-Can we just talk about it?
-No.
It's just that
the truth is, I…
Iván, you're never gonna come near me
ever again.
Okay?
Hey. What you doin'?
Tell the lieutenant I'm taking
all them to the club to send them home.
CHARITY AUCTION
Okay. Now
we each go our separate ways.
-Go with the others, please.
-Yeah, sure.
Are you okay?
What's the matter? Why are you soaked?
All of you are free to go home now.
Are you okay?
Yeah, Dad. I'm fine.
What if he did it?
Murderer? Our father?
Well, look. Armando nearly killed Ari.
And after everything that he did to me--
Mencía, what's the matter?
Are you just tired of
getting along with Dad?
-Is that it?
-No.
I mean, we're a family.
If we don't support each other, who will?
Well, we also shouldn't betray each other,
but here we are.
What are you inferring?
Chill out.
I also don't think Dad's capable.
As for the rest, don't worry.
We're still the same shitty family.
What's his deal? What's wrong?
Ari.
Can we talk?
I mean, um… Mm, no.
Hey.
What's up, man?
-Can I have a seat?
-Yeah, sure.
-Sit down.
-You sure?
Iván, if you want to talk
about anything, you know I'm always here.
As your friend.
I'm so stupid, crying.
All good. Cry it out.
I never meant to hurt you.
I want you to know that.
Save that for later, okay?
Now, tell me what's the matter. Go on.
It's Ari, right?
Let's go. Come on.
We'll lay on the lawn for a while, okay?
I'm sick of
leaving people I care about behind
every time my father changes teams.
Ari and you mean a lot.
I've lost you without goin' anywhere.
Except I'm right here, so chill out.
Seriously, why should I even bother
finding someone,
when maybe next week,
I'll end up in… Dubai
or… or who knows where, man?
Right.
I have the opposite problem.
My entire life,
I've been fiercely searching for
anything that's worth my while.
And nothing.
But at least along the way,
you got to fuck all those dudes, right?
But really, I don't get it.
Well, because we're all out of sync.
We're looking in different directions.
Take us, for example.
I'm crazy about you.
You're into my sister,
who has a boyfriend.
And Ari, I mean…
Ari looks many places at once.
What are you lookin' for?
In a guy?
Loves me like I deserve.
Someone who loves me the way I'd love him.
I wanna feel like his priority
and have him feel he's mine.
I'd give him my all.
And you… in a girl?
What you and I have here.
Connection.
We could talk about anything… or be quiet.
Serenity.
Intimacy.
How about we skip class?
A little quality time together?
All right.
Come on.
Could you be a little more discreet?
Just a little.
Mm, sure.
You don't have a life,
so you look through ours in the trash.
Know why I do drugs? I can.
And 'cause it makes me
sharper and stronger.
Does Phillipe know about it?
Wanna ask him yourself?
Do you really wanna know
what his answer is?
No, I just don't want you
dragging him with you.
Aw, how cute.
Don't you worry, baby. He's happy with me.
Very happy.
And you know why?
Because I offer him
only the best version of myself.
No cap.
We found a cell phone in the lake.
Near the spot where the body showed up.
We think the phone belonged
to Armando de La Ossa.
We started recovering
some data, phone calls, messages.
And I have to ask you for your cell phone.
Mine? But why?
To compare the data in your phone
with that of Armando de La Ossa's.
Why do you have it in for me, Lieutenant?
We're just cross-checking data.
Yours, the school's, the data from
the association De La Ossa presided over.
I've done nothing.
Then you should be
the first one interested in collaborating.
Sure.
Thank you.
Do you have any other phones?
A work phone, for instance?
No, it's the only one.
Um, Dad?
Ari, it's all right. Don't worry.
Could I speak to her outside for a second?
Sure. Go ahead.
What's happening, Dad?
Nothing. It's nothing.
I have nothing to hide.
Just relax. Trust me.
They can search what they want.
Come to my office
with Samuel after your classes.
With Samuel? Why?
Just do as I say.
Come on. Go to class.
Mencía, no. Not you.
Why me?
If you want, I can stay. I don't mind
skipping classes or anything like that.
No, it's just
that I have to tell her something.
What have I done now?
Support me.
I don't know. You got the wrong daughter.
Right, Benjamín?
No. Ari always supports me, but
I'm just gonna need a favor
that… that she can't do for me.
I lied to the lieutenant.
I told him I only had one phone.
I have another
in the right-hand pocket of my jacket.
Take it and hide it really well.
You know I didn't do it, right?
Who would ever want
to put a murder suspect
in charge of a holding company?
Or in this office,
to supervise their children's education?
There are a lot of ways to condemn a man.
Not just jail.
Samuel, you once said that…
…that Armando wasn't coming back,
with surprising confidence.
Did you know he couldn't come back?
I wanted you to feel better.
I hated seeing Ari afraid.
Armando died on New Year's Eve.
Why did Guzmán leave a few days later?
-Come on.
-No, no.
I'm not criticizing him. I admire him.
But I think
that covering up for the culprit
has gone from a heroic gesture
to becoming something unjust.
Samuel, was it Guzmán?
Don't know anything.
I'm sorry.
I have to go to work.
No, I'm serious.
How do people do it?
I mean, how do you manage
to meet guys who are worth a damn?
-I'm clueless.
-Easy.
I go to bars in hotels,
gyms for rich guys,
and practice extreme sports.
You serious?
Sweetie.
Tinder, like the rest of the world.
-Oh.
-As a therapist, that's your homework.
Yeah, so, you're not my therapist.
All right. Well, as a friend.
As a friend, I'm telling you,
"Move on, Cayetana.
Evolve. I don't know. Try things."
Yeah, but by going on Tinder? You think?
Just… I don't know.
Meeting with a ton of Internet randos?
No, c'mon. I mean,
you talk to one guy, then another guy.
And if you don't feel a spark,
you can manifest someone.
Manifest?
How do I manifest someone?
Just think really hard about a person
and a song that reminds you of them.
Play it on a loop,
nonstop, and they'll appear.
-What do you mean? Appear, how?
-It's not scientific at all.
Honestly.
But… But you have to trust.
It's life. It's energy.
It's… I'm telling you,
the law of attraction.
Don't ask why, but it works. I'm leaving.
'Cause if I keep drinking,
I'll end up rambling about ayahuasca.
-Give it here.
-Are you paying?
-Yeah, I got it.
-Thanks.
-Talk soon.
-Ciao.
Omar? I'll take the check, please.
-The check?
-Yes, please.
Sure. Let's ask Omar.
Hello?
-What are you doing here?
-What's up?
-Felipe?
-Can I come in, Omar?
Yeah, sure. You know each other?
-Yes.
-Yeah, yeah.
We know each other, for sure.
-God.
-Oh man.
-It's so exciting to see you.
-How are you?
What are you doing here?
Nothing. Picking up some food
that the Lake Club's
donating to the center.
-That's random.
-Yeah, well, you know.
Me and my causes,
we can't stop. It's… How are you?
-Great.
-Yeah?
-You look so handsome.
-Ah, shit, Caye.
Hey, uh, wanna have a drink, or…?
Mm… yeah.
-How about right here? Does that work?
-Yeah.
This place is perfect.
I mean, it brings back great memories.
-For me too.
-Yeah? For you too?
Yeah.
Can you hold off until I'm done loading
my gazillion boxes into the van?
-Sure. I'll wait as long as it takes you.
-Perfect.
-It's freezing, isn't it?
-Yeah, a little bit.
What are you doing?
Did you skip class?
Having some beers, chilling.
Beer, this early?
Dad, join us or leave us alone.
Fine.
You can drink…
…but only under my supervision.
I mean, look.
I have nothing against gays. Nothing.
Idiot!
-Let him.
-What?
Let's see, Cruz.
You have nothing against gays, but…?
There's no but.
Not half a but.
I just don't understand why
you get more excited
about a man than a woman.
Because women are, like, you know,
like gifts straight from Heaven.
Yeah. And men are from hell,
which is a lot more fun.
I'm gonna get some ice.
And get out of the way a bit
'cause this is just…
-What?
-You're such a dick.
-Go and apologize.
-Why?
-Dad, go!
Okay.
Let me. I'll do it.
Oops.
Patrick.
I'm sorry about what I said earlier.
I acted like a dumbass.
Look, Cruz.
I don't care about
your hetero hang-ups and bullshit.
The fact you treated me
like fucking shit upset me more.
Yeah, it was a mistake.
What was?
Treating me like shit or kissing me?
Both, I guess.
-Both?
-Yeah.
Look, let's do this.
For every lie you tell me,
I'm gonna come closer.
Two steps for each one.
Until we're so close, I can see
if you have the balls to lie to my face.
If you tell the truth,
then… I'll walk away, just like you want.
I'm not in the mood
for this kid shit, all right?
Then don't hook up with kids.
But I already apologized, okay?
Now we each go our own way, right?
Right?
-Each go our own way?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
You don't want me to go.
Look, Patrick, I'm not gay.
Bi.
Or bi or tri.
I'm a soccer player.
Look, insist all you want.
Soccer player isn't a sexual orientation.
I mean, Patrick, I…
I'd rather not get involved with people
in my son's social circle, you understand?
That's not something
someone like me can afford to do.
I hear you loud and clear.
All you had to do was be honest with me.
It's okay.
Really.
We'll just leave it at that,
as if nothing ever happened.
Patrick, wait.
Hey, come here.
Why?
Don't make me keep lying.
Hey! What's up with that ice?
The ice. Cruz.
-Has it melted already, or what?
-Please come to my room tonight.
-Cayetana!
-You scared me.
Hey, question. Do I smell bad?
-I shoulda gone home first.
-What?
-Smell.
-Ah! A little. Just a bit, yeah.
-Seriously?
-No. No, messing around.
Okay.
-Want a beer?
-Yeah.
-Yep? Um…
-Yeah, I'd love one.
Two Mahous, please.
So? How'd it go?
All these places, and of course,
we run into kids from school.
-This is a bit much, right?
-Mm.
I mean, a gazillion boxes, right?
That's…
We should at least go say hi.
Hey! I can't believe it.
-How are you?
-Hey, man.
Look who we have here.
-What's up? How are you?
-Uh…
Felipe. Felipe, like you,
but in Castilian.
Nice to see you, man. Yeah.
We're the same,
all except for… the wardrobe.
-Phillipe…
-Oof.
That's a good joke.
Phillipe, he just got off work.
Do you even know what that is?
-I just came over to say hello.
-Great.
Actually, it seems
like the stars have lined up.
You're with him. I'm with Isadora.
-Hmm, sure.
-Meet my girlfriend.
Hi. How are you?
-How are you?
-I'm great.
You two look a lot alike,
you know that? You do.
You'd make a great couple.
You do make a great couple.
You know, the four of us
could have dinner together.
What?
It'd be fun. Like a double date.
Well, technically, we're not a couple, so…
-Ah. Hmm.
-Mm.
Yeah, but I don't know.
Maybe it could still be kinda fun.
-Are you treating?
-Sure.
I thought you two
lost touch over Christmas.
Mm. Well, obviously not.
So, I actually met him at an NGO.
-He works there.
-Mm.
With little Black kids starving to death
and sick with AIDS and all that?
You're kidding, right?
No, no, no.
This is essentially just Isadora.
Ah, no. Hey.
Don't be mean. I'm exaggerating a bit.
Hey, listen a minute.
No, so I also have friends
who spend summers
on boats saving the whales.
I personally think
the world's going to shit anyway,
but if you enjoy that, be my guest.
I don't exactly do this
because I enjoy it.
No? Then why do you do it? Oh. Shh!
You're passionate.
You have passion
that is visible 300 kilometers away.
You can't imagine.
I mean, I want to imagine.
I want the image in my head,
but, no, it's not happening.
Yeah, passion's something else.
Isn't that right, honey?
Look how happy he is.
Look how happy I make him. Look at him.
-Mm. He's entertained, for sure.
-Your guy's entertained. Mine's happy.
-Hmm?
-Uh, question.
Are you rich kids always like this?
We're not rich.
Aristocracy, sweetheart.
The waiter's a rich kid.
Hello?
Ah. Oh. He's too far.
Okay, listen. I'm going to go
to the bathroom.
-Order me another drink, please.
-Mm-hmm.
I'll be right back.
Shit.
She's like an earthquake, isn't she?
Yeah.
Just wait till she gets back
from the bathroom. She'll be a tsunami.
COME HOME. DAD NEEDS US.
HE'LL BE FINE.
THE ONLY THING HE'S GUILTY OF
IS SMASHING MY FACE IN.
What movie did you pick?
And, uh, what is this?
-I was feeling it.
-Oh.
Honestly, doesn't this turn you on,
even a little?
You're gonna talk like your dad now?
-No, no. Not at all.
-Yeah.
I'm asking you because
I really want to know what turns you on.
Yeah? Why?
Just to know.
Yeah.
Mm.
Well, yeah. Of course it turns me on.
Why wouldn't it?
But he turns me on more than her.
It would turn me on even more
if she were another him.
Oh shit.
Apparently,
this really turns me on.
I want to suck cock.
Mm.
It turns me on
seeing how much it turns you on.
You and your fucking ambiguous games, huh?
But I'm not playing.
-You're not?
-No.
Wait, you're telling me that,
the two of us here, like this,
that turns you on?
Of course.
-Yeah? Why?
-You're really hot.
I feel great when I'm with you, and…
this really turns me on.
Why don't you try it?
Because if I did try,
it would be with you.
And I'm really scared of hurting you
as much as your sister hurt me.
Fuck. I don't know. Wait.
Listen,
stop jerking me around, okay?
It's just that…
-It's--
-No, Iván. I said no.
We can be friends if you want.
But stop messing with my shit.
But-- It's just-- Patrick.
Where are you goin'?
-To sleep in the guest room.
-But, Patrick. Sleep--
I said fucking stop it! Seriously, you…
Sleep here with me.
You're crazy, dude.
-Got me that drink?
-You sure?
Well, yeah.
What a sweetheart.
That guy's divine.
Hey. Hello.
Well, you're all suddenly super quiet.
What happened?
Mm.
This red wine is good,
but today it's… especially good.
Well, hold up. What's up?
Why aren't you drinking?
Baby doll? Sweetheart! Hello? Baby doll!
Four margaritas, please, honey.
-Thank you.
-No, some of us have to work tomorrow.
Let me explain something.
Our whole life is just work, right?
From the first drink
in the morning to the last at night.
And it's forced labor. Very forced.
That's why we have to live life
the best we possibly can.
Oh! There it is.
It's here. Come here. Come on.
Whoo-hoo. Amazing.
Uh, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I really am.
I'll bring something
so you can clean yourself up.
Run 'cause I don't wanna see
your face right now.
-Isadora--
-Everyone's looking.
Maybe we-- Let's get you cleaned up.
-No. There's no real need. You can't tell.
-Yeah. Yes, there is.
No, you look perfect.
Can you come out with me?
Get some fresh air? I need some.
-Whatever.
-Okay? We'll be back.
-I'll leave this.
-Great.
I was pretending not--
Look how pretty the full moon is!
-It's beautiful.
-Look--
You're fucking kidding.
-Are you okay?
-Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Caye, what's wrong? Is she high?
No. No, she's drunk.
You saw how much she had earlier.
-Go inside. We'll be right back.
-Okay.
What was that?
If Phillipe has to hear about
your problem, it should be from you.
I don't have a problem.
Yeah. And I mop floors 'cause I find it
professionally fulfilling.
Oh no.
How awful. No way, no way, no way.
Come on. Get up. I'll take you home.
Uh, yeah.
So I think we're gonna head home now
because she's a little under the weather,
so I'm taking her.
-Should I take you?
-No, no.
I'm not very good company
for anyone right now.
Let's go.
But are you seriously leaving?
Pfft. I'm really sorry. I wouldn't,
but I can't leave her in this state.
But I want to meet up with you.
Will you call me?
-You wanna see me?
-Yes.
-Okay. I'll hit you up. Call you soon.
-Okay. I'm sorry.
No problem.
-We're leaving. C'mon, Isadora.
-I'm coming.
-Enjoy dinner.
-I'm sorry.
-Get some rest.
-Good night.
-Ciao.
-Bye. Ciao.
HAS IVÁN GONE TO BED? I'M WAITING FOR YOU.
Fuck.
Uh, please.
Um… I… I can't sleep.
Then count sheep or something.
It's just that… I can't stop…
…goin' over and over it in my head.
What if because my prejudices or fears or…
or……I don't know what,
I might miss out on
something fucking great?
With someone who is fucking great.
And who makes me feel fucking great.
Dude, stop.
You're gonna make me really angry.
For the last time, Iván. Stop.
No.
I don't want to.
What? I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-What are you doing?
-I'm nervous. Sorry.
-Hey.
-Calm down. Chill out. Chill out.
-Okay.
-Yeah, I should chill out.
-It's okay.
Yeah. Oh, fuck.
It's okay. It's okay. You're good.
It's okay. Let me.
Yeah?
Okay.
Good?
Really good.
Should I try it?
If you want to.
You want me to?
What do you think?
Of course.
Iván, Iván, Iván.
-What?
-Be careful with your teeth.
-I'm sorry.
-You're good.
-No, don't worry, okay?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Do you want me to keep going?
-Yeah.
Ah.
-Oh. Stop, stop, stop, stop.
-Sorry. I'm sorry.
-No, no. Don't worry.
-Is it okay?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
-It's good.
-I just want you to enjoy it.
-Oh, I am.
-Are you?
-Turn around.
-What? What?
-No, no, no. Not that.
-I'm not going to do that.
Patrick, not that. Patrick, no.
-Iván, I won't do that.
-I'm not ready.
-Dude, I swear.
-I'm not ready for that.
-Okay?
-I won't do that, but turn around.
Turn around.
Did that tickle?
-Yeah. But I like it.
-Yeah?
-Do you like it?
-Yeah, yeah.
I don't mind you
doing it to me if you want.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Okay.
What are you doing?
What? Isadora, what are you gonna do?
Swim some laps, high as a kite?
Maybe. You have so little experience.
You get in the water, and bam!
All your troubles disappear.
It's super normal
to be living in the Four Seasons Madrid.
Baby, I'm the Empress of Ibiza.
Any less wouldn't do.
Yeah, okay. Well, I'm off. Ciao.
Isadora!
Isadora, come on.
Get out. You're gonna drown.
Isadora?
Oh, you're fucking kidding me, girl.
Yeah, FYI,
that wasn't funny at all.
It's over now.
Okay. Ciao.
Isadora, oh my God.
You, wake up.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
I thought you'd left. Stop, okay?
No. No, I haven't left.
No one should live in a hotel.
I've lived in hotels all my fucking life.
In my parents' hotels
or the hotels where they left me
when they went off to live the high life,
touring the world.
And I discovered the nightlife.
The people of the nightlife,
the partying, and the drugs.
I got hooked.
And I got hooked on the rush and…
…I don't know.
But suddenly, I was no longer alone.
Are you sure
this is stuff you wanna be telling me?
Can you just shut up
and enjoy seeing me this way?
Now I met Phillipe.
And he's a guy that I like a whole lot.
I like him.
He's someone who… I don't know.
He makes me wanna be better
and leave all this crap behind.
But he's obsessed with you.
And you know it.
So as long as you exist, there's no way
I'll ever be able to compete.
All that stuff you found is gonna continue
to be part of my diet for a bit longer.
Uh, okay. So now it's my fault
that you're an addict?
I think it's easier to blame you
than it is to get over my addiction.
I've had enough of you, Cayetana.
Ah.
You just told me you were all alone,
yet now you say you've had enough of me?
Maybe you're alone
because you push people away, huh?
I don't know.
Phillipe…
Maybe you chose him because you knew that,
deep down, you couldn't actually have him.
Don't offer an Argentinian
cheap therapy, baby.
I think you know where the door is.
Just so you know,
I also used to think that…
that I didn't deserve anyone's love.
And that can be overcome, just like drugs.
Psst. You got up early.
-Hey.
-Hi.
You left in quite a hurry this morning.
Yeah. I wanted to shower
and change at my place.
Uh-huh.
Why are you here?
Your father wants
to give me a special thanks
for the thing with the auction item.
Show me to his office?
Uh, yeah.
This way.
-I waited.
-Huh?
-I waited for you.
-Right.
I passed out.
What's the matter?
-What?
-What's wrong?
I'm not in the headspace
for stuff like this.
I have a bunch of problems, and… and you,
being who you are,
you can't be put at risk.
We should just forget it, okay?
This office right here is my father's.
Move aside, sir.
Excuse me. We have orders
to come and search your office again.
Wait. Uh, what? Again?
-I don't know what you're trying to find.
-Excuse me.
-Please. You have to leave.
-But how long?
Please, don't… don't touch me.
I can do it.
This is incredible.
Well, there goes the Nazi, guys.
WE'RE BOTH GONNA BE CAUGHT WITH OUR CELLS.
Ari?
TYPING…
FORGIVE ME FOR BEING SO ON EDGE.
IT WASN'T YOU. IT'S EVERYTHING.
TYPING…
NO, FORGIVE ME. THIS IS TOO MUCH.
I GUESS IT'S HARD TO SAY OUT LOUD
WHAT HAPPENED TO ARMANDO.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO. TELL ME IN A MESSAGE.
WHAT'S GOING ON BETWEEN YOU AND IVÁN?
What's that about?
You said it.
There are things better not said out loud.
Ari, not long ago, I was Iván.
I recognize your behavior.
Answer me, and I'll answer you.
But won't my answer determine
what yours will be?
So there is something.
No.
I'm helping him
with some Patrick problems.
And I don't know what happened to Armando.
Hey. Do you have a minute?
What are you doing here, Mencía?
You gonna practice Olympic phone throwing?
If I practiced a little more,
I would have hit your clingy girlfriend
on the head like she deserved.
Wow. I thought
you were comin' in peace.
I'm sorry.
I'm a dumpster fire.
I'm a mess,
and I have no idea what to do right now.
I think that you're the best person
to give me some good advice.
Well, I think you're right, there. Mm-hmm.
There's this method that never fails me.
Basically, throwin' a coin.
Heads, one thing. Tails, the other thing.
I don't know if I should tell on my dad.
What are you saying?
I think my father did it.
I think he's the one who murdered Armando.
-There's all this weird stuff going on--
-Hey, no. Okay? No. No, Mencía. Okay?
-Don't be thinking that about your dad.
-But you think the same thing.
'Cause he's not my dad.
Look, for you to be strong, you don't have
to reject your father, you know?
The opposite.
It's brave to stand by your family,
even when you don't fuckin' like it.
I mean, my mother did a bunch of stuff
that seriously fucked me up good.
But in the end,
well, she's still my old lady.
And your father's your father.
So then, what?
Stay quiet?
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you.
Aren't you worried about Mencía?
I am about Ari.
Okay, listen to me, kids.
Everyone's gotta save
their own asses, you know?
Let Mencía save her dad's.
Meanwhile, we gotta try and save our own.
The cops have been swarming
this place for days, right?
Maybe today they'll arrest Benjamín.
And if he didn't do anything,
well, then I guess… they'll release him.
Yeah, man. They will.
Right?
Are you looking for this?
I…
I don't know what I'd do if someone did
to my kids what they did to you.
And trust me, I totally understand
that you want to help your father.
But right now,
you'll help him out a lot more
by talking than keeping quiet.
Mencía.
Help us understand your father.
-Lieutenant!
-Not now.
-I need to talk.
-I said not right now.
It was me.
I murdered De La Ossa.
Report Guzmán
and put an end to this.
Look, Guzmán didn't do it.
Well, me neither.
Of course…
there might be a third possibility.
I would put all my best lawyers
to work exclusively with you on your case.
And we'd get you out as soon as possible.
And I give you my word of honor
that from that moment on,
you will never ever
have to worry about your future again.
Or about money or about anything… ever.
Standing up for me
can set you up for life.
How many 18-year-olds can say
that their life is sorted out?
You could even come live with us.
And my family would be your family.
Rebe! Rebe, Rebe!
Not here. Not in here.
You need to calm down.
What the fuck has he done, Omar?
Huh? Was it an honor thing?
To save the fucking Nazi or Guzmán or who?
Maybe he did it to save you too.