Don't listen to him.
That's just his bullshit honor talking.
Samuel didn't kill him.
Rebeka, how do you know that?
-Because he didn't do it.
-Aha.
So, you know he didn't do it, hmm?
All right.
Then who did?
Yeah. See you later. Hey. Phillipe.
How are you?
Good. It is what it is. And you?
Good. Have you given it any more thought?
You know? Greta, the counselor.
She's really cool.
I think she's a good option, right?
I don't know. I think I'll pass.
But thanks. I mean it.
Phillipe.
You won't get any better at this rate.
And if you don't do the work,
I'm not waiting around for you.
I mean, I'll go with you…
…but I need you
to make a little effort on your part.
-I'm serious.
-All right, yeah. Okay.
-I'll go.
-You will?
I'll go with you.
I promise you'll love Greta.
-This is illegal, man.
-He's such a dictator!
This can't be.
-What's with them?
-No idea.
What's going on here?
Gatherings of more
than three people are prohibited.
You know that. So, what's going on?
When we load the school's app,
it activates geolocation,
and we can't deactivate it.
Well, that information's being gathered
for the sole purpose of keeping you safe.
The thing is,
we're not a bunch of lost puppies.
We don't need you to find us.
Yeah, exactly. And let's be honest.
You're kind of a nobody.
But I own businesses and half of Ibiza.
You want me to get kidnapped?
You won't be. The location's encrypted.
In other words, you're gonna know
where we are at all times, right?
No one can access it except your families.
They can deactivate it if they wish.
Oh, really?
Then, why don't you deactivate mine?
If it's for our safety, I understand.
In any case, you all have
far more important things to think about,
such as an exam in two days
that could make or break your GPA.
-And most of you are falling behind.
-You took away points for no reason.
And you'll lose even more
before the exam, Shanaa.
Why don't you prove
you can do something other than complain?
The highest grades will have access
to the best internships
in any field they want to go into.
Oh, that's fucking rad.
-You're not even close.
-Not too far.
-Disperse them, please.
-What?
Come on, kids. Go to class.
Please. Come on.
Guys, come on. Let's go. Let's go.
Keep moving. Hurry up, kids!
Mencía.
Don't give up everything you had
just to get brownie points
with our old man.
Because don't forget that,
for him, it'll never be enough.
-Yeah, I saw him.
-Girl, that's fire. See ya. Yeah.
You may already be losing her.
Listen, all of you!
My father may be in charge here,
but out there,
we're the ones who are in charge!
-Damn straight!
-A huge party's in order.
No damn rules or regulations
because we set the rules.
Rule number one. No geolocation.
Anyone at the party will have to put
their phones in airplane mode. Got it?
And now that I'm thinking about it,
no official uniforms or attire allowed.
You know what?
Let's skip attire altogether!
Watch out,
Sauna Ken's makin' a comeback, huh?
So, wait. Hold on.
It's a party where everyone's naked?
A party where everyone goes
as far as they want to.
-Yeah.
-Rule two.
None of this social distancing.
Let's be all up in and on each other.
Well, damn. Fuckin' A.
I mean, I'm single and need some action.
-Let's slut it up!
-Get it, girl.
No. This is even if you're not single.
It'll be everyone with everyone.
Rule number three.
Our main purpose here is to experiment,
which means no prejudices,
complexes, or other things.
You better leave
your sexual orientation by the door
or don't come in.
Is this negotiable, or…?
Samuel, I'm the son of a dictator.
What do you think?
Okay. You do you, but…
-Ah.
-…I'm not risking it.
How about you, sis? You in?
I'm practically dying to go.
-It might be fun, right?
-You can't if you have doubts.
Ari, come by yourself, okay?
It'll be way more fun.
Trust me.
-All right, count me in too.
-Yeah?
-Oh shit!
-Perfect, guys. Let's do this.
So, I'll ask Isadora
to reserve the VIP area and get her to DJ.
Tomorrow night, anything goes!
Do whatever we fucking want! Whoo!
My background's in academic counseling.
Not the kind of thing
you're asking me for.
Yeah. Yeah, we know.
Very well.
Then, I'll do what I can to help.
Are you two having sexual intercourse?
Shit.
You can rest assured,
everything we talk about is confidential.
And I'm pretty sure
Benjamín hasn't set up cameras
or microphones or anything.
Well, no. We're not together.
Any other partners?
No.
Not with her or anyone.
Why not?
Why what?
Why haven't you been having
sexual intercourse?
Because
I haven't felt like it.
Isn't there any girl out there that,
I don't know, that you've liked, or…
Not like her.
This profile
you sometimes display--
-What profile?
-Your pattern.
The one that emerged
with Elodie and now with Cayetana.
I don't know. We might call it
"overly impetuous," maybe.
It's predatory.
What do they have in common?
-Those two?
-Them, the situation, everything.
Um…
That we both said no.
That I liked both of you a lot.
And with both of them,
you'd had a little too much to drink.
Right?
So, how was that? Okay?
I think it went well, no?
Sure.
What's the matter?
No, nothing.
It went well, no?
-Phillipe.
-At least you think so, right?
Is it the alcohol?
Are you upset
that she banned you from drinking?
No, no. It's not the alcohol.
It's, uh…
I don't know. It's the fact that…
that you called me a predator back there.
Because that's what I am to you?
A predator?
No.
It's just, no.
What I wanted to say was that,
when you drink, sometimes I think that…
when you're not conscious of your actions,
that side of you can come out.
But it's not who you are.
Caye…
…have you ever really had
the intention of forgiving me?
But for real?
Phillipe, this is a bit of,
well, a journey.
I have no idea how all of this will end,
to be honest with you.
But for the moment,
I'm gonna be there by your side.
Go a little faster.
Come on, guys! Let's go!
Rebeka, go!
You're near ready
for the Olympics.
Oh shit, you can still speak?
I thought you'd lost your voice.
And your hand
since you don't ever call or text me back.
-There's the Rebeka I knew.
-And what's that mean?
-Good form. I like it. Go.
-Forget it.
Keep it up.
-One, two, three, four…
-Oh yeah, sure. I'll forget it.
'Cause we only talk when you want to.
You tryin' to drive me crazy?
No, you don't need to get crazier.
I got my fill with the 20 voice messages
you sent me in an hour yesterday.
Don't you think?
Well, don't you worry. All right?
I won't send you any more.
I can be loyal, intense, and clingy,
even when someone treats me like shit.
Watch out.
'Cause when I flip the switch, I'm out.
Good job.
And I flipped it.
So, make sure you save those messages.
Because when you decide
to change your mind and call me,
your ass will be blocked.
And those 20 messages will be
the one place you can hear my voice.
Girls, let's go.
You going or should I?
I will.
Hey there.
What are you doing here?
What would you like me to be doing?
-Hey, are you trying to get us kicked out?
-There are no cameras.
Are you sure?
I made sure.
Okay, stop it.
What's the matter? Just relax.
-Lately, you've been very Ira.
-And you've been very my father.
Are you sure this party's gonna be
something you can handle?
Shh!
No, no. Don't cover her mouth.
-Oh shit! Fuck!
-How long has he been there?
-Perhaps my daughter has something to say.
-Dad, please leave! Get out!
I want to see you both
in my office. Separately.
Fuck. Didn't you say
there weren't cameras?
Don't be an idiot.
You think I didn't look?
Fuck. Shit. Ah, fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck. Fuck.
Fucking, fucking fuck. Dude, I--
You aren't even going to bother
explaining yourselves?
I can apologize,
but there isn't much to explain.
You honestly don't know
how sorry we are.
I won't even begin to go down
the laundry list of rules you just broke.
-Dad, I know I broke 'em.
-It's "Benjamín" here.
-I got it.
-I'm not the principal right now.
I'm speaking as Ariadna's father.
But I'm the one who egged Samuel on.
What's gotten into you?
Why have you turned into this tramp?
What can I expect from your relationship
with my daughter, Samuel?
What?
Since you've been together,
Ari is running wild.
She's uncontrollable.
One day, everything's fine, and the next,
someone bashes you in the skull.
We lost Mom and almost Patrick and me.
Life's so random!
Do you get it? I'm doing what I want now.
Whatever I want.
Dad, you're not gonna get
a better explanation.
Benjamín.
Get to class.
Regardless, I still have high hopes
for you, Samuel.
You're hardworking, ambitious.
But you need to focus.
Both of you need to focus.
Because I need Ari
to go back to how she was.
But if I try to talk to her, if I attempt
to get strict with Ari right now,
I'm gonna get the opposite effect.
She'll rebel even more.
-But if you reined her in…
-No way. She's the one holding the reins.
Make her think she still is, then.
But don't disappoint me
once again.
Hello?
Bro, you can't be here. Sorry.
Sorry.
I'm just looking for food.
Please, sir.
Bilal, right?
Nice to meet you. I'm Omar.
Where are you from?
Comores.
-Where?
-Comores.
I've never heard of it.
I'm from Palestine.
Is it cool with your facility
you're wandering around?
There's too many of us.
They won't miss me.
I'm not looking for trouble.
Just for work.
I can maybe help with that part.
I assume you can wash dishes
and mop floors?
-Yeah, sure.
-Hop to it.
Okay, your lunch break's over.
Thank you.
Merci beaucoup. Thank you.
Don't say thank you. Get to work. Come on.
Let's go. Allez, allez.
Let's see if I understood you.
You're giving away your wine collection,
but you're not coming to the party?
No alcohol.
I made a promise.
To who? Little Ash Girl?
What?
-The janitor, the cleaning lady, the maid…
-Okay, okay, okay. I got it.
And she's a witch too. Who knew?
How does she wield
so much power in her broom?
Well, I'm out. Have fun.
You're trying too hard for the wrong girl.
That's enough, all right?
-Cayetana is--
-Yes, she is.
She's the person
who abandoned you when you need her most.
She didn't abandon me, though.
She's made things clear.
Her path's hers,
and she wants to walk by my side.
Mm-hmm. By your side.
Not with you.
Aren't you happy?
You get ten an hour.
Sure. Thank you.
De rien.
But you're sure you're cool with it?
More tomorrow?
Tomorrow, mm…
No, it's my day off.
But I'll call you, okay?
It'll just be here and there at first.
You wanna take some food with you?
There's always leftovers,
I mean, and they'll just throw it out.
It's not much. A little pasta, bread.
But, hey, it's something.
What do you prefer,
pasta or hamburger?
I'm sorry.
I needed the cash.
Get out.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to steal. I was forced to.
-Get out now.
-I'm so sorry.
Some gangsters--
Dude, I said, get out.
Fuck.
You won't do it again.
Do what?
Well, I mean, trusting someone blindly
just 'cause.
I don't get it. Why do people just go
and throw away opportunities? Y'know?
I don't know.
You tell me.
What's with your tone?
We have an important exam tomorrow,
and you're determined to go to that party.
That's all.
-Yeah, but Samuel, dude, that's not fair.
-Come on. I need to study.
And close the door when you--
-Hmm. Nah.
-Let's see.
Oh, okay. Yeah.
These aren't a bad option for tonight.
Tonight?
For the party.
-May be a bit short, I think.
-You think?
I love them like this.
But Patrick likes everything
to be a bit more, well, elegant.
After all, it's his party. Right?
-Oh, Patrick's party.
-Ari.
-Coming?
-Sure.
Patrick.
I'll catch up to you.
So, you're having a party, huh?
I'm not invited?
-Hmm. It's not your thing.
-Why not?
This party is so we can be free to…
to, um… mingle,
make out, get high, grind.
To experiment a bit,
without fear, prejudice, or rules.
Only for the brave.
Then I'll be there.
Well, you might have to try
a thing or two.
Then I'll try it.
That right?
Your legs are trembling.
I'm just nervous
about seeing you chicken out.
Guess I'll see you tonight.
The decision to get rid of
all the alcohol in your collection
is very responsible of you.
Phillipe?
-Hmm?
-Are you here with us?
Mm-hmm.
Something you'd like to share?
Well, uh, the fact is…
I have doubts, Greta and Cayetana.
Uh, let's see.
For starters, this thing we're doing--
By "this thing,"
you're referring to our meetings?
Yes, this. Coming here
so you can tell me all the ways I'm wrong.
Well, I don't think-- I don't believe
I've used the term "wrong" or "right."
Well, okay. Either way, though,
if you're gonna tell me how to change,
uh, and she's not really gonna do
much more than listen and nod,
I mean, I think you could just e-mail me
the instructions in a PDF,
and I'll do it at home on my own.
What's with all this?
You don't wanna be with me, do you?
What?
I mean, are… are you gonna be with me,
really supporting me?
Right there, holding my hand
through all this?
Wait, hold on.
You see me sitting here, don't you?
Yeah, but… but I mean
like the way we were before.
Together, me and you.
Phillipe, you need to do this
for yourself.
Not for me
or to make me get back together with you.
Well, that's really all I needed to hear.
Thanks a lot, Greta.
Thank you both.
What the hell?
You're going to the party?
'Cause I thought maybe you'd like
to come over to my house to study.
I mean, I'm the one
who'd like you to come over.
What's this about?
Um, when I study without you,
I'm less productive.
Even though we tended to get distracted.
Mencía, what do you want?
I want to…
to give it another go.
I'm sorry. I was selfish.
I never thought about what I was doing
or the consequences of any of my actions,
and I really miss you.
Don't you kinda miss me too?
Even a teensy bit?
Whoa, okay. No need to flip out.
I don't miss you that much. It's just--
Cut to the chase.
Please just come over tonight.
Look, Mencía. I actually really need you
to come over for once.
To the party.
Mencía, I also wanna try again.
But I can't jump every time you call.
I can't, kid.
So, if you're serious, then come.
If you really care about me,
that's all I'm asking from you.
Come.
Okay.
Oh my God.
Yeah, "Oh my God."
But we're not staying long.
-It's spectacular.
-Huh?
All right! Everyone, over here, please.
Listen up.
I'm here to remind you that this evening,
there are no goddamn rules!
And there's no curfew tonight!
There is no… social distancing.
Discipline can get fucked!
Get crazy, go!
Take photos!
Make videos! But don't send them tonight.
Don't switch out of airplane mode.
I mean, ever.
Don't let anyone know where we are.
Fuck adults!
Tomorrow, everyone will see
that we're goddamn free!
Don't forget out there!
Tonight, anything goes!
Whoo!
AIRPLANE MODE
DAD
PATRICK
Pink essence of Ibiza for everyone.
You really know how to party, baby.
Ah?
Mencía!
So, now your brother's
completely lost his mind too?
Where is he?
No idea.
No, of course.
NO STUDENTS CONNECTED
Do you want your dose of Ibiza, baby?
It's not alcohol.
There you go.
Go all out. Very good. Nice work.
Where's Mencía?
Kill the flash. Jesus.
You're gonna make me blind, kid.
Studying.
She's not comin'.
Okay, great. Slutting it up.
Soccer player's
fuckin' hot, right?
Damn, I need a drink, boo.
Oh, you came after all.
Where'd you leave your hang-ups?
In the coatroom.
And your absolutely
unbreakable heterosexuality?
Parked outside.
Someone might steal it.
These are too tight.
Come with me.
How many times have you jerked off,
thinking about this moment, huh?
What's this?
Now you're playing hard to get?
Wait for me. I'm in charge here.
If I didn't know better,
I'd think you were gay.
I'm just playing.
Anything goes, you know?
I don't know.
I don't know. I have my doubts.
Help me get rid of them?
And is this mine,
or did Patrick leave it behind?
Figure it out.
Whoo-hoo!
There you go.
Go all out. Very good. Nice work.
Kill the flash. Jesus.
You're gonna make me blind.
What's the matter? Wasn't that convincing?
-Ari, are you serious?
-What?
Don't let anyone control you
or tell you what you're allowed to do
or what you can try or not.
Our chemistry's fucking great.
What did you say?
-Hey. Whoa, whoa there, partner.
-What?
You're not sinking one
in this net tonight.
Fuck, but you really, really turn me on.
-And you wanted to also?
-Yes, I wanted to. I wanted to want to.
But I don't want to, and I won't.
Even drunk, I can't kid myself.
Turns out, I'm an even bigger dyke
than I thought I was.
Uh-uh. But our chemistry.
Hey, come on.
We need to get outta here soon.
Well then, we'll have to speed things up
if we wanna experiment a bit, y'know?
Will you do whatever I want?
Samuel, I know perfectly well
when we have to leave,
and that is not right now.
So, shake off this little mood you're in,
and let's make the most of our time
and do things.
That's what we came here for.
Isn't that right?
You gonna do what I want? Yes or no?
Come on, babe.
Only if you do whatever I ask you to do.
Ask away.
I want to see you with another girl.
C'mon.
Hi.
-I really like your glasses.
-Thank you.
And I really like your dress.
-Hey, wanna make out?
-Obviously.
Hey, yo! What's the matter, man?
Why are you so upset?
-It's nothing.
-What's the matter?
-I let people hurt me because I'm stupid.
-Huh?
Then us damaged goods
can hang out here together, okay?
We'll show them they can't take us down.
What the hell? What?
Does this seem normal to you?
Well, yeah. I mean,
Patrick is just super hot.
Huh? No, Omar. I mean,
he promised he would quit drinking.
-Cayetana.
-Hey.
It's his life.
His choice.
-But his choices affect people who--
-Who what?
Who care about him?
-Yeah.
-Who worry about him?
Who love him?
-Omar.
-Come on, say it. It's no big deal.
No. That's not it.
It's just, he doesn't love himself, okay?
Look, Caye.
Your turn.
-What? No, Ari. We're about to leave.
-Don't waste the time we have left.
Samuel, so I did what you told me,
and now it's your turn.
I wanna try.
You'll get to try death if your father
catches us getting home late.
No. He won't kill me today
because I'm staying here.
Jesus Christ.
Am I even the one
that you're worried about?
You're more worried
about my dad's reaction?
Who are you dating? My dad or me?
-The guy who holds the scholarships?
-Ari, no. That's not why I'm with you.
-But your father's betting on me.
-I'm betting on you too.
Who are you betting on?
Which of us are you trying to please?
Is it clear now?
Whoo!
Hey!
Is it me you were looking for?
Oh, yeah. There's something I owe you.
Are you pissed off at me?
What for?
Because of Rebe?
Please, the chick left me
with a case of blue balls.
She's super hot, though.
Plus, I mean, makin' out with a lesbian
is also a way to experiment, right?
You're pissed off? Seriously?
I'm always fucking serious.
I'm not an in-the-closet cocktease
who's super fucking repressed.
Not again, man.
I've told you a million times. I'm hetero.
Yeah, sure you are. In your words.
What about your eyes?
What about your hands?
I mean, you gladly touched my dick
in the shower, then my ass in your bed.
Bullshit, you're hetero.
You gotta be fucking kidding.
-What?
-You're hooked on me.
Super hooked.
Really? No fucking way.
Hey, I haven't done anything with you
that I wouldn't do with any friend, okay?
What I'd do with any friend. But with her?
I'd do a lot with her.
Yeah, all right. Sure.
But you haven't kissed me.
And I'm not going to.
Because you're scared
to make out with a dude, right?
If you are,
why don't you go the fuck home?
I'm not scared.
-Ah, yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
Let's see.
Okay, watch me.
Hey, where are you going?
Sorry, guys.
-Anything goes, right?
-Yeah.
Fucking delicious, Samuel.
Who do you taste like?
What are you doing?
-What am I doing?
-Yeah. What the fuck are you doing?
-What are you doing here?
-I just--
You're breaking the dress code.
-Why's she wearing so many clothes?
-Stop. Leave me alone, all right?
-Stop now. For real.
-God.
Listen to me. Don't just throw away
all the progress you've made.
-The first step's hardest. You took it.
-No. Leave me alone.
Leave me alone, Caye! Okay?
You want me to…
Okay. Just wow.
-Can you please stop?
-Fuck! Let me live my life!
-Hey!
-What?
-Stop it. Just chill out.
For a cleaning lady, you're pretty good
at messing everything up. Huh?
Ah!
Hey, Mencía!
I'm excited you're here.
You're gonna have a blast!
-Ari, let's go. We have to go home.
-What?
Dad told me to get you.
-We have to go home, now.
-No. I'm staying right here.
-You're staying.
-Let's go. I'm telling you.
-We have to go home.
-I said no!
Hello?
Fuck.
Hey, man.
No. No, no, no.
Get outta here.
Sorry.
-I said no. Get out.
-I needed money was all.
Sure. I fucking need money too. So?
Listen to me.
-They're threatening me.
-Don't care.
If you were trustworthy,
no one would threaten you, okay?
I'm sorry. Really.
They're coming for me,
and I don't know where to go.
Please.
Fuck.
Don't feel guilty for a second.
Honestly.
This whole life thing
is about having a bomb-ass time,
about relaxing, about being happy.
And are you happy, or are you not?
-Mm.
-Exactly. Right.
So, then, who is some cleaning lady
or anyone to tell you what's right?
She your mama? Your mama? No.
On top of that, you're nailing it all.
Like, you know,
if anyone were to do for me even half
of what you're doing for her,
then I would never let him go.
Never.
Honestly.
I mean, just thinking about it
makes me wet.
But you don't know me at all.
See?
I wasn't lying.
I'm here for you, whenever you want.
Got it? Hmm?
Dad?
Why are you here?
Who did it?
Not Samuel.
Then what is Samuel doing, Rebeka?
Is he protecting someone?
Or is it you
who's trying to protect Samuel?
Rebeka,
what do you know?