Benjamín and Armando
were running a network
that trafficked the data of people
who are powerful and influential.
And? Why ask me about it?
Do you know anything?
No. Of course I don't.
Okay, then.
Could you obtain evidence
that might implicate Benjamín in this?
What?
You have a rapport with Benjamín.
He places a great deal of trust in you.
Maybe you can think of
a way to obtain information.
I no longer make deals with the police…
considering last time I got burned by it.
Right.
You know, the prosecutor has agreed
to close your case if you collaborate.
You help us,
Benjamín goes to jail, and you don't.
Was your strategy
to let me rot in there?
Because mine was to rely on you.
And you will still be able to rely on me.
I promised you that
you wouldn't have to worry about anything
for the rest of your life.
You attack me for liking guys,
and it turns out you're gay?
Calm down, dammit!
We were drunk.
You guys also mess around
when you're drinking.
We drank, we let ourselves go,
and it happened. End of story.
End of story, my ass!
I opened my heart to you.
I told you I had feelings for him.
You wanted me to forget him
because you were jealous?
Iván, that's not the point!
You've been after me
since we met.
You didn't get me, so you went all crazy?
And believed it was a good idea
to go after my dad?
What for? To get revenge on me?
-You're not the center of my life.
-Yeah. Yeah, I am.
You'll drive everyone around you crazy
to get whatever you want.
You lie, and you manipulate.
You can be so poisonous, Patrick.
So, I manipulated you, huh?
Did I also poison you
so you'd come looking for me?
Listen.
Man, I swear to you,
you better not come near me
or near my dad or near anything
that has to do with my life again.
I don't want you around, Patrick.
Samuel?
Samuel? Samuel, hold on!
Well, at least now you finally realized
you can't trust the Nazi, can you?
I don't know
if I can trust the police.
Plus, I have no idea what the fuck
they even want me to find on Benjamín.
A computer file labeled
"my shady dealings with Armando," or what?
-Holy shit.
-What?
Mencía.
What about Mencía?
Mencía said she found a SIM card
in the phone Armando gave her
that implicated Benjamín
in some suspicious shit.
Wait, hold on. What?
Here's the deal.
That SIM card's at his house somewhere,
or it's here at the school.
So, it's up to you.
You have to make up with
the wannabe marquis, partner.
Just to sneak into her house?
Not to dredge up shit,
but that's exactly what you did to me
when you played me. Or pretty much.
I'll make up with her,
sneak into her house,
and who will search here?
I know someone.
Where are you going?
Is this an apology or…?
Yeah. I acted like an arrogant asshole.
You've done a lot for me.
And, I don't know,
this whole thing's been such a big mess.
Can we maybe start over?
Tonight, you're gonna sneak into
Benjamín's office
and look for that SIM card.
What?
Cayetana, you have access to everything.
Especially the security guards' uniforms.
It's for Samuel, to get justice.
Please.
Phillipe?
You have less than a minute to reply back
to one of my 700 messages that I sent you
before you'll be looking me in my eyes
and having to explain yourself
to me in person.
Isadora. Hi, uh, well,
we just wanted to ask you a favor.
Sure. What is it?
We're planning a getaway
to, uh, to Ibiza this weekend,
and we're lookin' for VIP passes
to your club.
Okay, sure. I'll arrange it.
-Thank you so much.
-Mm-hmm.
-Hi, Isa.
-Hello.
I was just buying something.
What's up with
all this ghosting all of a sudden?
What ghosting? No, I'm just really busy.
Talk later, okay?
No, no, no, honey.
We'll do this right here.
What's the matter, Phillipe?
I thought you'd fight
for me like I fought for you.
First, let's see if you can stay clean.
I mean, one day's fine,
but it means nothing.
What? Hold on.
Do you remember the person
that defended you against the whole world,
when the school was screaming
that you were a rapist? Remember her?
I'm that girl, Phillipe.
I decided to believe you.
You "decided"? What do you mean by that?
What are you telling me?
You don't believe me?
So, first, you lie to me,
convincing me that you trust me.
Now I should simply trust you back?
I'm not gonna fight for a junkie
who's plastered in makeup and glitter
to cover the aching void she's got inside.
Look at you.
You have no one.
It's pathetic.
Try not to die of an overdose.
Please have some class, Isa.
Good morning.
How are you?
Look, I know I really blew it
during our night together.
I think you mean our last night.
But…
…is there any way I can make it better?
I feel like… I feel like I didn't make
the best out of our final opportunity.
Yeah.
Um, Iván, the thing is,
Samuel's come back.
He's talking to my dad.
So, no, it's impossible.
We're gonna go back to normal. All right?
We're planning another meeting
with the lawyers next week.
They're gonna try to get you
a good deal, but I won't lie to you.
-It'll be hard.
-I'm aware.
But I want you to know…
…in case it's not clear,
that I am tremendously grateful.
I know that.
Benjamín, what do you say
we talk more about this
tonight at your house?
My house? Why?
Figured we'd be more relaxed there.
We can talk about it over dinner
with Ari.
And with Mencía and Patrick, of course.
We can hang out together
as if things were really… back to normal.
If that'd be all right.
Of course. That sounds perfect.
Great.
Aren't you worried that…
that what we have now
might just be a kind of mirage?
I don't know.
Just, sometimes I feel
like our relationship will never work,
no matter how hard we try.
Well, I don't know. I have no idea.
But I mean, if it's just a mirage,
we'll have to enjoy it while it lasts.
-Mencía.
-Hmm?
And
Rebeka.
Both of you.
Uh, Samuel's coming over
for dinner tonight, and, um,
I was thinking that,
if it's okay with you,
I'd extend the invitation to Rebeka.
Sorry, what?
I don't think I've thanked you enough
for what you've done for me and, well,
and for your family.
So, I think it's only natural
that your significant others
feel as much at home
at our place as at their own.
Uh, Patrick seeing anyone now, or…
What am I saying?
No, no. Of course not.
Okay, well, let me know what you decide.
What just happened there?
Hello.
Hi.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
As good as you, judging from your face.
Oh, really? Great. Is it that obvious?
Phillipe?
Yeah, I guess.
Kind of. Maybe a little.
Don't know.
And you?
I don't know.
It's complicated.
Painful.
Complicated and painful. I don't know.
Right now,
all I want is to get outta here.
Leave this school, Madrid, everything.
Hmm, trust me.
I understand you perfectly, babe.
Know what?
Let's bounce.
-Wait, what?
-Let's go.
Far, far away.
From Madrid, from this school,
from all these mediocre losers.
I mean, look at us.
We deserve to be so much more.
That is what we're gonna make happen.
-Let's go.
-What? Where to?
Do you trust me?
-Yeah, but--
-Let's go.
Hey, guys.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Uh, did you manage to,
uh, get the passes for us?
Mm, no. No. I got something much better.
Let's go.
Come on!
Attention, my dear passengers.
You better make sure
you buckle up super tight
because we're gonna be in for
a bumpy little ride to my empire.
'Cause, babes, we're going to Ibiza.
Hello!
Hi, my babies.
Hello. It's so nice, so nice, honestly.
It's so nice to be home again.
And tonight, we'll take flight
like we always do.
I missed you guys like crazy.
I love you so much, everyone!
Shit.
Hello?
Hi.
I need to fly to Ibiza.
Jet or helicopter.
Immediately. Understood?
Go, go!
Yeah!
Tonight is ours. Just you and me, okay?
Let's go, Ibiza!
When we come back after Easter,
we could maybe expand the debate team.
That way, we could participate
in international competitions,
and not just within Europe.
-What do you think?
-That's cool.
Patrick, mind being present with us?
Benjamín, why don't you just pretend
I'm not here and look after your guests?
Okay, I think that's enough now.
Hey, hey, hey.
I said leave me the hell alone!
Dude!
Oh my God, Patrick!
-What's wrong with you?
-Patrick.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, thanks. Uh, um, I'm sorry.
-Get out of my face!
-Patrick!
-What is the matter?
-Let's talk about it.
-I said no.
I don't know what's goin' on with my son,
but a father is allowed to be worried.
I mean, isn't he?
Go downstairs.
That's awesome, dude.
The office was upstairs, right?
Hurry. You get the card,
and I'm gonna say--
I just hate to see them like this.
Samuel,
are you starting to puss out?
A stomachache. That's what you have.
That's what I'm gonna say. So--
They're broken. I don't want them
to have to suffer anymore. Got it?
Oh, great. Would you rather go to prison?
No. But I also don't want to destroy
his life and tear apart his family.
Relax, man. I'll go.
You keep drinking and sitting on your ass.
Leave it. Hey, Rebe.
Stop it. Get back here.
You think that's normal?
These violent outbursts,
just because of some boy?
Actually, I do. It's called being in love.
It's called hyperesthesia.
I could use
a little bit of empathy from my father
because I need someone to listen to me!
Is that too much to ask?
Okay, well…
tell me what…
So what is up with this boy? Who is he?
Is it Carvalho?
He hates me right now.
And why is that? What'd you do?
So, you're just assuming
that I'm the one to blame here?
Patrick, no one hates anyone
for absolutely no reason.
What did you do to him?
Nothing.
I went all out to meet him, and
we connected.
He toyed with my heart, jerked me around.
We hooked up,
and now he's over me.
I still don't see
any reason for him to hate you.
Because now he's over you?
Because I'm an idiot.
I fall in love
and give it my all, and they run.
You scare them off,
which isn't surprising,
given your obsessive-compulsive nature.
So, he ignored you,
and you threw a tantrum
and did something impulsive
to get back at him and get him
to pay attention to you. Right?
What'd you do to him?
I slept with
someone very important to him.
But it was 'cause I was really feeling it…
and 'cause he was over me.
What?
You realize this
is self-inflicted, don't you?
You're surrounded by people
who would do absolutely anything for you,
and you,
with your… your narcissistic ego,
all you do is hurt them.
I mean, hurt us because I'm including
myself and your sisters in that.
Patrick,
whenever you need me, I'll be here.
I do hope that at least you realize that.
But, son, you have to grow up.
I'll sort it out by myself.
But thanks.
-Thank you!
-Having fun? You're welcome, sweetie.
This is so sick!
I mean, it's legit. Seriously, dude.
Hey, everyone!
Let's move the party over to my suite.
-Let's go!
-Is… Is there a hotel here?
Honey, this place has everything.
It's Ibiza, baby! Let's go!
Go, go, Ibiza!
Oh shit.
Looking for this?
Did you get back together with me
so you could sneak into my house?
No.
I got back together with you
'cause I love you.
Oh, yeah?
But that has nothing to do
with wanting to help Samuel.
And to help Samuel avoid jail,
I need that card.
Are you seriously asking me
to betray my family for you?
Or for Samuel?
Fucking hell, Mencía.
-You're jealous of Samuel?
-This isn't about jealousy.
No. It's because you all lie.
Now I have no idea who to believe.
That's the problem here.
Because I just keep getting
slapped in the face over and over again.
-Menci--
-No.
Don't you dare call me Menci now, okay?
Don't you dare.
I just want my friend to get justice.
Because Samuel could wrongfully go to jail
for helping your family.
If you love me, you'll hand it over.
You wouldn't ask me for it
if you loved me, Rebeka.
I love you. I do.
You know that.
It's so hot here.
Okay, let's…
let's take all our clothes off.
Come on. Ciao.
-Baby, baby, baby.
-Huh?
Look at me. Look. Are you all right?
Don't worry.
-Just…
-What?
I'm just coming down. Comin' down.
Mm'kay. That means
you have to take some more.
-Okay.
-Yeah?
-All right.
-Mm.
-I'm going to the bathroom.
-Mm-hmm. Okay, okay.
Whoo!
Just get…
…get outta my head.
Okay, well,
your brother went to take a little walk.
The fresh air will do him good.
-Something wrong?
-No.
Where's Mencía?
Mencía? Uh, no idea.
So, I'm actually really not feeling well.
I just got my period,
and I'm gonna make a giant mess here.
-Samuel, we'd better leave.
-Let's go.
No, please. Don't just leave.
I'll give you ibuprofen.
No, really. Don't worry. Honestly,
it wouldn't help. We should leave.
-Let's go.
-I'm sure there's nothing wrong with you.
Did you have a fight with Mencía?
No, we didn't. I told you,
I don't even know where she is. Samuel?
We're leaving.
Hi.
Excuse me?
Hold on, Samuel.
I'll be right there.
What's the matter now?
They just caught Cayetana
rifling through my office at the school.
What?
Okay, we have to go. Thank you.
-Everything was delicious, Benjamín. But--
-Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
-Did you two know anything about this?
-No.
No, we didn't know a thing.
Why would we know?
-Thank you again, seriously. See you.
-I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Isa, the doorbell!
Are they kickin' us out?
No, no. 'Cause I'm the owner.
No one's gonna kick you out of here.
No one, so just chill out.
I'm going to see who it is. Okay?
Hey, what's the matter?
What's the problem?
Oh, sweetie.
You came! Come, come in here. Come on.
Does this seem normal to you?
What'd you say?
No. No, baby.
Honey, listen to me. Stop!
Baby. Wait. Baby, whoa.
I'm talking to you. Stop.
Not interested. Why'd I come here?
Because you care.
You care about me.
Love me?
Don't get cocky, all right?
I came here because
I can't watch you destroy yourself
and just stand by.
Right. I'll tell you what we'll do.
If you follow me in there,
then I swear…
Look at me.
I swear,
I will never do it again.
You know damn well
you won't keep that promise, Isadora.
Look at you.
Well,
if you really want me to quit,
then go in there and come get me.
EMPRESS SUITE
I don't know
what the fuck…
…you did to me…
but this has never happened
in my fuckin' life.
I…
Fuck.
I need you to disappear.
I need to fucking erase you,
once and for all, from my mind,
Patrick.
Shit. Just what I needed.
Iván isn't here.
I thought you knew.
I know.
That's why I came to see you.
That's a bad idea.
Cruz, I ran away from home.
Please.
Okay, come in.
I'm sick of having the people
I care about end up hating me.
Iván adores you.
You know that.
Now, put yourself in his shoes.
He saw us together.
The best thing we can do is give him
some space until he clears his head.
-I'll give him space, then.
-You do that.
And you?
What about me?
Do you hate me?
Not at all.
What are you doing?
Well, then, since you don't hate me,
I don't wanna mess things up with you.
This is how you mess things up.
Stay away from me and Iván.
Please back off.
What's the matter?
Are you confused too now?
Or now you're thinking clearly
and want to push me away.
Honestly, I'm so disgusted with myself
that I can't look at myself in the mirror.
Why?
'Cause this can't happen again.
Understand?
Why can't it happen again?
What if it does?
I should stay away from you, Isadora.
You're more dangerous
than the drugs you take.
In the end,
you'll get addicted to me too.
I think she's unconscious.
Guys,
I think Isadora's passed out.
Come on, dude. Join us.