Thanks for dropping us off.
What about you?
Do you want me to say it that much?
I want it…
this way.
I will do everything for you to forgive me.
I really like you.
Let's talk about that later.
Techno!
Give me more time, Kla.
How come you're here?
Thanks for dropping me off.
Why are you still here?
I told you.
I don't want just a simple “thank you.”
What do you want?
Hit on you.
Why are you still here?
I told you.
I don't want just a simple “thank you.”
This time, I won't let you kiss me.
Now I know.
You're teasing me.
I’m not.
Well...
What do you want?
Hit on you.
♪I used to tell you♪
♪That we could never be more than friends♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪This time, you won't be sad♪
♪We will get through it together♪
♪From now on, let me take care of you♪
♪Tomorrow or whenever, our love will be everlasting♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
Where is it?
Can, what are you finding?
When did I lose it?
It’s not here.
What’s wrong with you?
I’m so dead.
What? Are you going to die soon?
My only property.
I don’t think you have to worry about that.
You’ve got nothing.
Job!
I do! It’s my phone!
But right now, I don’t know where it is
I couldn’t find it in my bag either!
I haven't completed making all the payments with my mom.
How can I play games now?
Have you tried to call your phone yet?
You’re so smart.
Someone picks up.
What is she saying?
She says…
Sorry, there is no acknowledgment from your requested number.
Just let it go
If your phone is turned off like this,
then someone probably stole it already.
Job!
Calm down.
I’m thinking of a way to help you now.
Can you remember where you've been today?
I still used it when I came out of the house.
And then…
Tin!
I’m going to the international college building now.
Hey!
Can!
What about your bag?
I have to keep it for him, right?
Why there’re so many things?
Excuse me.
Do you know Tin?
He’s tall.
He has fair skin
and tall.
Hey guys.
Do you know Tin?
He’s tall and he walks like this.
You don’t know him?
He’s fair-skinned and tall.
His eyes are like this.
He’s quite arrogant.
He has class in this building.
He’s very tall and fair-skinned.
Why can’t you guys help me?
Excuse me.
Do you know a guy named Tin?
He’s tall, handsome, and arrogant. Is that right?
You know him?
Of course.
Where is he now?
We don’t know.
Don’t be sad.
I’ll ask someone in the group chat.
What group chat?
A handsome guy like him definitely has a fan club group.
Fan club.
He left already.
That means I won’t see him today.
Don’t be sad.
He has class in the afternoon.
He’ll come back.
You’re the cutest!
Thank you so much!
He’s so cute!
Where is he?
I should have asked for his number.
What are you doing here?
Tin!
Clumsy.
Where were you?
Do you know that I’ve been looking for you?
I waited for so long. They said you will come back in the afternoon.
Do you know what time is it now? It’s already 3 PM.
You were looking for me?
Why are you smiling?
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
Dirty.
What’s wrong with you?
I’m not dirty.
I take a shower every day.
But…
I’m just not that clean.
See?
I’m clean now.
Why were you looking for me?
Oh right!
Have you seen my phone?
Your phone.
Huh?
You forgot it in my car.
I didn’t see it.
It dropped when I opened the door.
It just dropped from the car.
How come it looks badly damaged?
It was crushed by a ten-wheeled truck.
A ten-wheeled truck!
My son…
I never thought you'd leave so soon.
I never thought that we’d spent only eight months,
ten days, and twenty-eight hours together.
There’re only twenty-four hours in a day.
Be quiet!
For you.
Don’t bother me!
I’m in mourning for my son.
This is for you.
A new phone.
I bought it for you.
Tin!
I told you before.
You can’t buy me with money.
Just keep it.
I don’t want it.
Can!
Wait!
Can.
Wait.
What did I do wrong?
Let me go.
No.
We need to talk.
I don’t want to talk to a guy who throws money at other people.
When did I do that to you?
You just bought me a new phone.
That’s how you solve the problem?
Huh?
Are you not going to say sorry to me at all?
Do you think money can solve every problem?
I want to repay for what I did.
I don’t want it.
I broke your phone,
so I have to repay you with a new one.
But you didn't mean to drop it.
I don’t know how you’re raised.
But all I want from you is to say sorry.
You can’t say that?
Just say sorry!
Just that?
Yes.
That’s all.
Sorry.
Say it again.
I’m sorry.
That’s it.
Keep in mind that
if you do something wrong, you have to say sorry.
That’s what my mom taught me.
I forgive you
for breaking my phone
and throwing money at me.
I didn’t mean to do that.
But you bought…
I just want your number.
I want your phone number.
So, I broke your phone.
Your new phone already has my number.
As for your new number,
I already saved it.
Did you buy me a new phone
just because of that?
I told you.
What did you tell me?
I can’t remember.
I’m stupid.
Can you tell me again?
I will hit on you.
That’s why I want your number.
An arrogant guy like you
bought me a phone
because you want my number?
That’s the only way I can think of.
Fine.
I’ll take it.
Are you giving it to me or not?
Give it to me.
But
I'll pay you back.
I don’t want to owe you anything.
Why are you smiling?
Let’s go back inside the café.
I haven’t finished my iced cocoa.
Why is he not picking up?
Let me have some.
Bro,
you can eat it but don’t steal the code.
It's under the tray.
I won’t.
What’s the matter?
Why you serious?
Can won’t pick up the phone.
Oh!
Can just changed his phone.
That’s right.
He told me that he wanted to change a new phone.
But he doesn’t have enough money.
He has enough money now?
And why did he have to change his number too?
You're right.
Maybe someone bought him a new phone.
Just like me.
I just bought a new phone for that pretty nurse.
Okay…
Techno!
About that conversation.
Who’s the guy that wants you again?
We're talking about Can.
How come it's about me now?
Come on.
You have to tell me about this.
Tell me now.
I can’t talk.
I’m chewing.
I can’t talk right now.
Damn.
Why can’t he share his secret with me?
Damn, I ran out of items in the game.
But I can redeem code and claim it right now.
Can.
Why are you here so early?
Techno.
What?
Help me.
What is it?
I can’t figure it out.
I’m serious. The nurse that I met has such fair skin.
Job
Her eyes are so big like she’s wearing big-eye contact lenses.
Champ, don’t just listen to him. Look at me here.
Can!
The reason I join the team because she likes an athlete.
Dude, look at me.
Help me first.
I’m dying.
What’s wrong with you?
Techno.
What?
What if someone hits on you?
What are you going to do?
How am I supposed to know?
He never hits on me.
Before I realized that, we already did it.
Dude,
I saw a guy from the English program.
He’s waiting at the entrance.
Who is he?
I don’t know.
But I know he’s from the English program.
He seems arrogant.
He’s fair-skinned.
He doesn’t talk to anyone.
Can!
Why is he in such a hurry?
Wait a minute, bro.
Huh?
Who did you...
sleep with again?
Something fishy.
Well...
I think...
It’s time to practice now. I’ll go get changed.
See you!
Techno, why are you running away?
Since when did he become like this?
That was quick.
Let’s go to practice.
Let's go.
What are you doing here?
I’m here to score some points.
What points?
Football?
But you don't play football.
I know!
You’re here to score points with my captain.
Our team is full already.
We don’t want more member.
You know what I mean.
I don’t know.
I'm stupid. I don’t understand what you mean.
You’re blushing.
Who’s blushing?
I’m not shy at all.
If you say so.
I bought this for you.
I know
that money can’t buy you.
But this is just snacks.
You can accept it, right?
If just snacks…
They all look so yummy!
Look at this.
Lucky me.
Can.
Your payment.
I told you already.
I’m here to score points with you.
He kissed me again!
And why is my heart beating so fast?
But this looks yummy!
Look at this!
Which one should I eat first?
There're so many things.
I choose everything by myself.
I hope that you will like it, Techno.
If you like hot and spicy, then eat Bento.
But if you like it mild, then drink Jele Vita Bead.
I miss you.
I know that you don’t want to see me right now.
But I do miss you.
Crazy kid!
(Thanks for the phone. I’ll definitely pay you back.)
Hello.
Why are you calling me?
It’s easier to talk.
Texting is not hard, either.
I almost finished typing.
Do you like your new phone?
I like it so much! It’s much faster than my old one.
It’s so good for gaming too.
I don’t know if it’s good luck or bad luck
that you accidentally dropped my phone.
Right.
What a good accident.
Lucky me that you let me pay in installments.
I don’t have that much money to pay in one go.
Actually, you're a good person.
Am I good enough to hit on you?
Can.
I don’t know.
Just tell me yes or no.
I said I don’t know.
All I know is that…
I don’t get goosebumps when you hit on me.
I'm really going to win you over then.
I don’t know!
I’m sleepy. I will hang up now.
I'm really going to win him over now.
Ae
I’m going to a convenient store. You want to come?
I’ll go too.
Hello, Tar.
Hello, Tum.
How are you?
Well...
I’m doing well. My school just started,
so I’m a little busy these days.
How about you?
I'm fine.
I’ve been thinking about...
what kinds of songs I should write.
Writing songs?
You become an artist now?
About your song, any progress on that?
I still don’t know what I should write.
I have no idea.
What about love song? I think many people will like it.
Love song?
I don’t know.
What are you doing now?
I’m working on my project.
I've been reading papers and articles for this project.
I'll go to take a shower after I finish.
How about you?
Is it getting colder over there?
It’s Thailand.
It’s as hot as ever.
If you have time,
please come to visit me.
By the way,
when are you coming back?
I’m not sure either.
But if I have a long holiday,
I will definitely go back to see you.
Tell our parents that I miss them so much.
You come back this time,
will I get to try your desserts?
Definitely!
This year, I already learn how to make desserts.
I think my skill probably has improved.
It's your holiday, right?
Yes.
Well...
I won’t bother you then.
Okay. I'll take a shower and go to bed.
Good night.
Okay.
Well then,
good night.
Dad.
I'm bored.
I told you to go with mom.
No, I don’t want to go.
Grandma’s always nagging.
I don’t like it.
I want to stay here with you.
But you just said you’re bored.
Can you tell me a bedtime story?
I’m still working.
It’s already late. You should take a break.
You should stop working.
Break?
Does that mean I don’t have to tell you a story either?
No. You have to tell me a story.
Well…
How about...
a story of two brothers?
No. It doesn’t sound exciting.
How about...
a story of two brothers and a servant?
It doesn't seem fun.
Once upon a time,
there were two brothers.
The older one was a jealous kid
who wanted to revenge on everyone.
The younger one was a naughty kid
who was spoiled since young.
Actually, it's the older brother
who raised him that way.
So, no one would love him.
Until one day...
How dare you tell me what to do!
You're just a servant.
I can do what I want.
Tin.
That's not nice to say.
Tul won't like it if he hears you say that.
I'm not saying it to Tul.
I talk like this
to only a servant like you.
You have no right to tell me what I can and can't do.
Do you understand?
Yes. I understand that I have no right.
Good. Now get out.
Rasa told me not to let you go out.
Get out!
I can't. Please wait for Tul to come back first.
Move!
I'll make them pay for what they did to Tul.
You can't do that.
Rasa told me to keep you out of trouble.
But those people insulted my brother.
I still can't let you go.
You should follow only Tul's orders,
not my mom's.
I will tell Tul about this.
Sure.
You can tell him whatever pleases you.
I didn't mean to do that.
What happened?
He...
He put himself in front of me.
I didn't do anything.
Shut up, Tin!
The older brother couldn't stand his spoiled brother anymore.
What happened after that?
Did the younger brother get punished?
Of course, he did.
Remember this.
Don't be naughty like that boy.
I'm a good boy.
I swear that I'm a good boy.
I'm not naughty like that younger brother.
That's right.
A naughty child will be punished.
A naughty child...
that no one wants.
Why don't you tell him
who made him become like that?
Who made that younger brother to lose all his friends?
Tell him that.
Dad.
Uncle Tin, don't hurt my dad.
Listen to me.
Don't be like an older or younger brother.
Don't be a devil in disguise.
And don't be a stupid person
who gets fooled easily.
Do you understand that?
Yes.
Dad, Uncle Tin is so scary.
It's okay.
Uncle Tin is just tired.
Sit here.
Remember this.
Don't be like the two brothers.
Especially the older one.
There's a price he has to pay.
He's paying for it now.
Tul...
Did anything happen to you?
(Thanks for the snacks. So yummy!)
You call me again.
I haven't finished texting yet.
If I tell you something,
will you believe me?
Of course.
You're my friend.
I believe in everything you say.
I used to think that my brother
was everything to me.
He was all I got.
Whatever he said,
I would believe him.
He told me that
my parents hate me.
And I believed every word he said.
I believed all the lies he made.
He said he would help me
when I was accused of abusing drugs.
Huh? What?
I grew up to be a spoiled child,
a bad person.
And that spoiled child
was sent to study abroad.
I always went to the party
and hangout.
And then I was arrested
for abusing drugs.
But I didn't know before that it was a drug-fulled party.
I was all over the news.
I was on newspaper front pages.
"A rich kid who turns into drug addict
was arrested abroad."
My brother said that he would help me.
But it was him who was behind all this.
He hates me.
He wants me dead.
He wants to take everything away from me.
He hates me.
Tin, where are you?
What?
I'm asking, where's your house? I will go to you now.
I'll punch your brother in the face.
Where are you? Tell me!
Can.
Can I go to see you?
Why not?
Gucci.
Do you think he will be okay?
You actually believe me, right?
Yes.
I believe you.
I despise your brother now.
I'll hit him in the face when I meet him.
So, this is his son.
What's up?
Are you a bad person like your dad?
Don't insult my dad. He's a good person.
He has a great personality.
Maybe he's evil.
My good boy, what did you do today?
I was fighting with Uncle Tin's friend and I won.
He said you're a bad person.
Search about Tin's friend, Can, for me.
I want to know who is Tin's important person.
I hope you won't be angry.
♪Do you hear the sound outside the window?
The sound of thunder scares me♪
♪Can I hold your hands to calm my heart?♪
♪Stay with me until the rain stops♪
♪I don't know what to do if you walk away♪
♪Let me please you forever♪
♪I will do everything to make you stay by my side♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night without you?♪
♪You know that I like the way you hug and the way you say I love you♪
♪Just whisper the words in my ears♪
♪I can't barely stand the thought of you leaving me♪
♪Can you stay with me a little longer?♪
♪Stay with me until the rain stops♪
♪I don't know what to do if you walk away♪
♪Let me please you forever♪
♪I will do everything to make you stay by my side♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night without you?♪
♪Can you see the rain?♪
♪I can feel the pain♪
♪Stay with me until the rain stops♪
♪How do I get through the night without you?♪
♪Can you see the rain?♪
♪Let me please you forever♪
♪I can feel the pain♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night without you?♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night without you?♪