Hello, Ae.
Can I talk to you?
What do you want from me?
I want to tell your story through a song.
I just want you think about it.
I'm sorry that I disappoint you.
But I never said that
I'd be against in your relationship.
But I'm okay now
because my sister won't kill me.
It's time for your brother to meet him.
My name is Tul.
I'm his brother.
I'm glad that I'm finally get to meet
my brother's important person.
You're such a douche-bag.
Don't mess with him.
Dust is everywhere.
I'm angry.
What's wrong?
That asshole.
Why are you making that face?
I don't know why I'm angry.
It's because of your brother.
I thought your brother came
looking for a fight,
but turns out he played nice instead.
I was going to deal with him,
but you told me to get inside first.
If you didn't stop me,
I'd curse him so bad he wouldn't be able
to find a way back home.
Wait. This is his house...
But I'm so angry!
He's pretending to be a good person.
Does he think he can deceive me?
If you tell me he's bad,
of course I'd believe you.
What are you thinking about?
Promise me one thing.
Don't involve yourself
with my brother again.
Are you scared?
I am.
I'm scared that he'll take it out on you.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
I won't let anyone hurt you too.
Come on.
Stop ruining the moment.
Of course.
I'll recreate the atmosphere for you.
Can!
Stop it.
I know you want to do it.
Because I've already fallen for you.
Good answer. I'll make you feel good.
Tin!
♪I want you to be my sky when I fly♪
♪Be my guiding star when I'm lost♪
♪I only beg for you to embrace me
in the deeply cold night♪
♪I only beg for you to be my eternal love♪
♪I used to tell you♪
♪That we could never be♪
♪more than friends♪
♪When I said that I don't love you,
I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends,
I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us
to be just friends anymore♪
♪This time, you won't be sad♪
♪We will get through it together♪
♪From now on, let me take care of you♪
♪Tomorrow or whenever,
our love will be everlasting♪
♪When I said that I don't love you,
I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends,
I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us
to be just friends anymore♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true
and honest to you♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true
and honest to you♪
=A Chance To Love=
Oh, nice guess.
Even if mom taught me to behave myself
when I go to someone else's house.
I'm frigging' hungry.
Where did everyone go?
There were so many people here
in the morning,
now it's so quiet.
The worker's rooms are at the back.
Everyone's probably asleep now.
You don't have to be that wary of me.
Where's my brother?
Already asleep!
Then why are you down here?
Do you need anything?
I don't need anything
from someone like you!
Stupid stomach...
The hell are you laughing at?
Come with me me,
I'll cook you something to eat.
Who says I'm hungry?
I'm not!
Spaghetti with chili and bacon.
Looks simple,
but I'm sure it'll taste good.
Give it a try.
You can't believe I can cook?
Just because Tin doesn't like cooking...
doesn't mean that I'd also hate it.
I'm not gonna eat it.
You're a funny kid.
Just eat it, so it won't go to waste.
This is because
I don't want to waste any food...
It's good, right?
This is Phu's favourite menu.
But he can't have spicy food,
so I'd only put in bacon for him.
Phu said he met Tin's friend
who says that I'm a bad guy.
That's you right, Can?
What did Tin tell you?
All the bad things you've done, obviously.
And you believed him?
Yeah. Whatever Tin says,
I'll always believe him.
I also don't understand why
Tin loves to make up stories...
about how I like to hurt him
and other people.
Even if I might not seem like it,
I do love my brother.
I really don't understand
what Tin is thinking.
Don't you dare insult Tin.
I won't believe anyone other than Tin.
Remember that.
What a waste.
He acts just like Phu.
Frigging' Champ, why don't you
just say that I already lost...
Techno!
Speaking of the devil
and the devil appears...
I won't be here anymore.
-Are you okay?
-Stop!
Don't say anything.
But...
I said shut up!
If you say one more word,
I won't talk to you anymore.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't touch me.
You're still cute even when you're angry.
Come on Tin,
I'm just here to buy something with Ae.
And since exams are finished,
I just want to go shopping and relax.
I'm not angry about that.
Then you're angry that I'm here with Ae?
Tin... It's just Ae.
My spoiled prince,
you know fully well who Ae likes.
But I guess I can't really say much,
since you also like me.
Sorry that I'm very charming.
I'm not surprised
if you get jealous over me.
I'll make it up to you when I get back.
I gotta go, see you later.
I have an hour left...
What should I do?
Let's find something to eat.
I'm not scared of you.
What a coincidence.
What a coincidence my ass!
Your house is in the opposite direction!
Why are you here?
Fine, fine.
I'm here to see you, Can.
Why?
If you wanna know, let's talk for a bit.
What are you looking at?
You act just like a child.
I didn't think
Tin would like someone like you.
What's wrong with being like this?
Nothing.
I didn't mean anything bad.
I'm just surprised
Tin is dating someone so innocent.
Because in the past,
he didn't date people like this.
Are you...
trying to make me suspicious of Tin?
Keep dreaming.
The past doesn't mean anything.
I'm the present.
I'm not here to do that.
I'm just here
to correct a misunderstanding.
To correct...
a misunderstanding?
Tin said
I accused him of taking drugs, right?
It's not accusing
if he's telling the truth.
What...
is this?
Tin didn't tell you
that he did drugs before?
Ae.
I can't meet up with you today anymore.
Sorry.
About what you said.
What did you mean?
Here's your order.
Thank you.
So? Why did Can call?
Don't be so nosy.
Fine.
Insult me as much as you want.
It's all you do anyway.
If you're not nosy,
why would you follow me then?
Sorry for the interruption.
Let's talk.
This is Ae
from the Faculty of Engineering.
The one that I told you about before.
And this is my friend.
Tum.
The one who wants an inspiration
for writing a song.
That's why we're interested in your story.
It's just you who's interested.
Try talking to him first.
Maybe you'll get some inspiration
for multiple songs.
Not just one.
Keen said your story is interesting.
Actually...
If you're not interested in my friend,
you don't need to talk to him.
It seems that you don't want to be here.
Stop it.
I'm just stating the truth.
Then let me ask you something.
How interesting
do you think your story is?
I don't know.
I just...
know that I'm willing to do anything
to tell him that I love him.
And I'll always be waiting.
And what did he say?
Have you ever loved someone so much?
But there's something that
makes you unable to be together?
Of course.
See?
I told you that Ae's story is interesting.
Yeah.
I think it's already worth it
that we skipped practice to come here.
-Hey, Ae.
-Shut up.
I don't want to hear it.
Fuck you.
Why are you so rude?
If you stop prying
into other people's businesses,
maybe your life would be better.
It's not like I can help it!
Like that couple back there.
Something smells fishy.
Trust me.
I can feel it.
Keen likes Tum,
but Tum likes someone else.
For sure!
Oh, yeah.
Should I just ask Type about this?
Maybe I'll get some extra information.
Stop right there.
It's their business, not yours.
Are you going to hit my head
until my brain explodes out of my skull?
Fine.
I'll stop thinking about them.
Instead, I'll wait to hear
how your song will turn out.
It's not my song.
Then let's refer to it as the song...
that will be born
from the story of you and...
Shit. I shouldn't have said anything.
What should I do?
Oh, yeah! Where is Can?
He texted me
saying something came up suddenly.
But I think he must be lying.
I bet he got up late this morning.
Why are you sighing at me?
Hey, Ae! Wait for me!
If you ditch me,
no one's gonna help me carry my stuff!
Ae!
What is this?
I saw you updated your
status on Facebook yesterday...
that you got wet in the rain.
And?
You should start looking after yourself.
Here. Eat this.
I bought it for you.
If you got soaked in the rain,
you should take a lot of vitamins
so you won't get sick.
Why didn't you tell me
as soon as you got here?
I would've hurried to come.
What are you looking at?
Aren't your eyes already small enough?
Stop squinting.
Tin.
Let me ask you something.
What?
Have you taken drugs before?
Why are you asking me something like that?
Take a look at this.
Where did you get this picture from?
Well..
Your brother sent it to me.
You talked to my brother?
Yeah...
I did.
Okay.
Then we're done here.
In the end, you chose to believe him.
Tin!
Wait!
Tin...
Tin. Listen to me.
You believed him, right?
You hate me now, don't you?
Can you stop for a second
and just listen to me first?
How can you think that
I would believe him more than you?
If I believed him,
why would I even bother to ask you?
Seriously.
Do you really think that
I would choose your brother over you?
How many times...
do I have to tell you that
you're the only one I'll listen to?
Even if I'm stupid
and you end up deceiving me,
I will still only believe you.
So stop being a fool
and imagining things all on your own.
Tin!
Just tell me!
Just tell me what's wrong.
I'm your boyfriend.
You told me before that I'm stupid, right?
Then start telling me things
so I know what's going on.
Just tell me already.
Why are you quiet?
Come on, answer me.
I'm sorry.
I'm just scared.
I thought you believed my brother.
And you've already hated me
like everyone else.
I'm sorry, Can.
You're my boyfriend.
♪Let love and our hearts guide us♪
How can I believe anyone more than you?
♪You​ will never ever have to feel sad♪
♪We will always be together♪
♪This time,
let me take care of you forever♪
♪Our love will last until the end of time♪
At first,
I really thought you'd believe my brother.
Tin.
I will seriously hit you on the head.
What are you saying?
Everyone who's talked
to my brother before,
all believed him.
In the end, they all left me.
Did I ever say I believed him?
I just wanted to know what that clip is.
I didn't intend to show you that clip
and start crying.
I just wanted an explanation.
After that event,
I acted like a fool.
But I didn't do drugs.
Yes.
I could sleep with anyone,
but I am not like
what my brother told you.
That's all I needed to hear.
See?
As soon as you explained it to me,
I understood immediately.
I'm really sorry.
Why are you saying sorry?
The one who should apologize
is your brother, not you.
How can he do that to you?
I'm so furious.
Why are you staring at me?
I love you.
Please don't leave me.
Can.
Tin!
Why are you pulling my hand away?
Can't you see I'm embarrassed?
Of course, I'm not gonna go anywhere.
I'll stay with you like this.
I'm so embarrassed I feel like dying.
Can.
Tin.
We're in the middle of the campus!
Stop it!
I really feel like dying.
That's enough.
You've thought about it carefully, right?
Yes.
I've made my decision.
Even if in the end,
you'll have no one left?
Yes.
Even if I'll have no one left...
If it's your final decision, then fine.
Thank you.
Tul.
Never mind, nothing.
You can go.
Gonhin.
I'm sorry...
for not being able to help anyone.
Why are you at Bangna anyway?
Family gathering.
I can't go.
Everybody already thinks
my family only has my brother.
I see.
Then go on.
I'll keep sleeping while missing you.
If I just tell him I miss him,
he'll hurry to come see me tonight.
I should just get more sleep.
Tin...
What?
Calm down...
Can... Calm down...
Fuck it! I'm not staying calm anymore!
Where are you going, Can?
I'm gonna murder someone at Tin's house.
I'm not coming home tonight.
And if I go to jail,
don't forget to come bail me out.
What is wrong with him?
Did you bite my son?
Why is he acting so crazy?
Coming, coming!
-Oh, Tin!
-Hello.
Hello.
Did Can know you were coming?
Oh, no.
I was just around
so I came to give you some snacks.
Thank you, Tin, you're always so nice!
But next time,
you don't need to bring us anything.
Okay.
And is Can home?
Oh, right! Since you mentioned it...
He went out around an hour ago.
Saying he was going to your house.
You didn't see him?
Maybe you passed each other
on the way here.
What did he say again...
He said he was going to murder someone
at your house!
My son seems to become more silly
with each passing day, don't you think?
He has someone as cute as you as his
friend, why would he want to kill you?
Please excuse me.
Oh, Tin.
You're already going back?
What's wrong with everyone today?
Here's your jacket.
I'm coming home a bit late tonight.
Auntie, you can sleep first.
I'll lock up the house when I come home.
It's okay, I can wait for you.
Tul!
Can. Tin's not here today.
-Tul!
-Fuck you! Why would you do this?
You are such a fucker, do you know that?
Let go of me!
You think I'll believe you?
-What did I do?
-Everything!
Leave Tin alone, you fucker!
-Please stop, Can.
-Let go of me!
I beg you.
What's going on here?
Who can tell me what's going on?
Where's Can?
Can punched Tul's face.
Do you think it'll end here?
Doesn't matter how it's gonna end.
I won't let you lay a finger on Can.
Look after him carefully.
The best kind of revenge is to be happy.
Tin!
You've thought this through
carefully, right?
Yes.
♪I never understand the meaning of love.♪
♪What is it?♪
♪Why do we need it?♪
♪I don't understand why.♪
♪Maybe it's just me♪
♪Who don't understand my own heart.♪
♪I don't realize that
my heart is missing someone.♪
♪All I know that
it is not the same as before.♪
♪Every time I sit next to you,♪
♪my heart starts beating fast.♪
♪It starts racing out of the blue♪
♪and now I'm getting tired.♪
♪Is this what you call love?♪
♪My heart won't listen to me anymore.♪
♪I tell myself to stop thinking about you♪
♪but my heart keeps calling out for you.♪
♪It's just you and there's only you♪
♪that my heart is yearning for.♪
♪I don't know since when,
but now I love you with all my heart.♪
♪Is this what you call love?♪
♪My heart won't listen to me anymore.♪
♪I tell myself to stop thinking about you♪
♪but my heart keeps calling out for you.♪
♪It's just you and there's only you♪
♪that my heart is yearning for.♪
♪I don't know since when,
but now I love you with all my heart.♪
♪Is this what you call love?♪
♪My heart won't listen to me anymore.♪
♪I tell myself to stop thinking about you♪
♪but my heart keeps calling out for you.♪
♪It's just you and there's only you♪
♪that my heart is yearning for.♪
♪I don't know since when,
but now I love you with all my heart.♪