Why do we have to be in a relationship?
Because you're the air I breathe.
Can't we be friends?
I want only you.
Can.
Give him some time.
If he doesn't understand,
it doesn't mean he has no feelings.
We practiced so hard.
We practiced every day.
I'm right here.
I'm always right beside you.
I like you.
I like you too.
Get home safe, guys.
It's okay that we lost this time.
You guys still have another chance.
Let's go back.
You should go back too, captain.
You did your best today.
I'm so proud of you.
Stop it, Champ.
You'll make me cry.
Techno! Technic told me that...
Can I comfort you?
I lost, Kla.
I lost.
Don't cry.
I'm right here.
I love you.
That's another story.
I'm still mad at you.
Thank you for comforting me.
Techno!
♪I used to tell you♪
♪That we could never be♪
♪more than friends♪
♪When I said that I don't love you,
I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends,
I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us
to be just friends anymore♪
♪This time, you won't be sad♪
♪We will get through it together♪
♪From now on, let me take care of you♪
♪Tomorrow or whenever♪
♪Our love will be everlasting♪
♪When I said that I don't love you,
I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends,
I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us
to be just friends anymore♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪And you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true
and honest to you♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪And you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true
and honest to you♪
=A Chance To Love=
Tin.
I'm upset.
Do you hear me that I'm upset?
I know.
But first, here.
You should eat.
I'm still upset.
You're so messy.
Can.
Enough.
I'm still sad.
But before that,
swallow the food first.
You told me to do my best.
But I still lost.
You came to cheer me on, but I still lost.
I don't want to disappoint my team.
Also...
I don't want to disappoint you.
You never disappoint me.
Tin.
I don't want to eat anymore.
I'll pay the bill and send you home.
I don't want to go home.
I don't want Lay to tease me.
Okay.
Where do you want to go?
Your house.
Tin.
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
Can I sleep with you tonight?
Well...
I read it.
Men having sex together for the first time
will be painful.
It's going to hurt so much.
The pain will make me forget.
Well...
It might help me to forget
that I lost the match today.
You have to help me,
or I'll have a nightmare.
That's totally nonsense.
Why would you say that?
You want to sleep with me
just because you want to forget?
Are you saying that
you won't sleep with me?
I won't.
I don't want to just have sex with you.
Fine. I'll sleep with someone else.
Fine.
You'll probably find
a few man around here.
Tin!
I might be stupid,
but I won't have sex with random people.
Also, I hate it when you ignore me.
You won't pick up my call.
You won't text me back.
You're also with other girls.
I hate it all.
Anyway,
if I'm going to sleep with someone,
it has to be you only.
Are you done talking?
Then let's go.
Go where?
Get in the car.
Come on.
One.
Two.
-Three.
-Tin!
Can I buy something first?
What are you going to buy?
Well...
Some protection.
Wait for me here. I'll be right back.
Can.
Take a shower first.
I don't mind.
But I do.
-We'll be dirty anyway.
-Can.
I know.
Why do you have to scold me?
I'll take a shower now.
I'll clean up nicely.
Wait for me.
Auntie Klin.
-Yes?
-Where's Phu?
He went to his grandmother's house
with Vadee.
I see.
Have you eaten yet?
Do you want me to cook anything for you?
I ate already.
You should take a rest.
I come back home quite late these days.
You don't have to wait for me.
It's my duty to take care of you.
If Gonhin is still here,
he will do the same thing.
Auntie.
How's Gonhin doing?
Tul.
Why did you come home so late?
I wanted to finish all the work first.
I didn't notice the time.
Really?
I feel like you always
come back home late these days.
Well...
Is there something wrong
between you and Vadee?
Nothing's wrong.
I should be the one who's worried.
Why are you still awake at this time?
I'm worried that you'll get sick.
My dear Tul.
You're always such a good boy.
Unlike Tin.
He brought someone home today.
I don't know his family background at all.
I don't know what kind of friend he has.
I hope that
he won't make the same mistake again.
I'm so lucky that I still have you.
I can pin my hopes on you, right?
Yes, mom.
You can trust me.
He's stupid. He's crazy.
But he's so cute.
Tin.
I finished taking a shower.
Can I get into bed now?
I'm already clean.
I feel cold now.
Can I?
Sleep with me.
Just sleep, right?
Don't go back on your words.
You already made a promise
that we won't just sleep.
You're not afraid?
Why would I be afraid of you?
You said you want to feel the pain
so you can forget, right?
I'll make you happy
and forget about everything else instead.
Then do it.
What's wrong?
I'm upset.
I know.
I'm upset that
I don't understand my feelings...
...until I saw you with another girl.
Tin.
If you sleep with me,
don't sleep with someone else.
I promise.
You'll be the only one.
You can trust me.
But that doesn't mean
you'll get what you want.
There's nothing going on
between that girl and me.
But...
...I saw you two walked arm in arm.
I chased her away after that
because she annoyed me.
Dude.
You can't do that to a girl.
You will hurt her feelings.
What do you want me to do?
Why didn't you talk to her nicely?
Maybe she will understand.
What if I did,
but she wouldn't understand anyway?
What if she still bothers me?
No, I don't want that.
What I did is the best way out.
Whatever.
I don't want to think anymore.
It gives me headaches.
Anyway,
there's nothing going on
between you two, right?
I'm glad...
...that you get jealous.
I...
Trust me.
There's only you.
I trust you.
By the way...
Tin.
Can we do it again?
Tin!
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm asking for one more time.
Why are you pretending to be sleepy?
Please.
Cheers!
Come on, guys.
Let's celebrate for our loss.
But we'll never give up.
My energy is back.
I thought
you'd be sadder than this, Techno.
Come on.
We didn't win this year,
but there's still a chance next year.
But you won't be here next year.
Stop it.
It's not like I'm going to die.
I'll be around here.
I might not be with you all next year,
but you guys are still here together.
Ae.
Next year,
you have to win the championship.
It's not just you who will be happy.
A senior like me will be very happy too.
I won't let you down.
I'm passing on the baton to you.
By the way, where's Can?
I haven't seen him.
Don't worry.
Tin won't hurt him.
That's good to hear.
Here's to us.
Cheers, guys!
Take a photo for me.
I'm leaving soon.
Let's take a photo.
Your camera is good.
-Great.
-You guys can do it.
You'll wait to see me
become successful, right?
Good morning.
What am I doing here?
Go take a shower.
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
Then go take a shower.
You were so sweet last night.
Why are you so mean now?
It's called making love.
Huh?
What we did last night.
It wasn't just having sex.
It's called making love.
You should know that.
What's the difference?
For me,
I only make love to my lover.
It's time to take a shower.
I'll cook something for you.
What lover?
It gives me goosebumps.
Why do I feel like
there are spiders in my stomach?
About last night...
Last night didn't give me goosebumps
like when he called me his lover.
Why did I bring the blanket with me?
I'll take a shower now.
Tin.
You called me lover, right?
I can call you a lover,
boyfriend,
or wife.
Anything is fine.
Dude.
Can you not call me your wife?
It gives me goosebumps.
When will you be my boyfriend?
I'm sorry about that day.
Let's forget about it.
What about this time?
Dude.
I'm not handsome.
I can see that.
I'm not rich.
I know that.
You can just nod.
You don't have to say anything.
One more thing. I'm stupid.
There's nothing that I can compare
to a prince like you.
You should know that...
...I don't care about what you just said.
If I did,
I wouldn't approach you
since the beginning.
Well, then...
Well, then...?
Well...
Be my boyfriend, my spoiled prince.
Be my boyfriend, Cantaloupe.
Here.
Tin.
I'm hungry.
Let's make a deal.
What kind of deal?
I don't like it when you use swear words.
I don't like it
when you call me by my full name.
Cantaloupe.
Fine. Okay.
Do you want me to address you as "Mister"?
No.
But shit,
fuck,
asshole,
or any other rude words
that you like to say.
I don't like it.
I know.
I'm used to saying those words,
but I'll try not to say them anymore.
That's it. Here.
You don't like it when I swear, right?
How about...
"Mr Tin!"
Again.
What?
Don't be stupid.
Why can't you just say that you like it?
Mr Tin.
Can is hungry now. Can wants to eat.
Stop it.
Or I won't be able to resist myself.
I'm crazy in love with you too.
Are you crazy now after losing the match?
My lovely sister.
I miss you so much.
Are you drunk?
Go away. You stink.
I'm not drunk.
I didn't even drink.
I went to Tin's house.
Really?
What is it like? Tell me about it.
His TV is so big.
It's much bigger than this.
His bathtub is so big
that you can swim in it.
His bed is so soft and comfy.
There's a swimming pool too.
Air conditioner is on all day.
It's cold everywhere, unlike our house.
Also, the food!
Everything is so delicious.
You won't feel full
no matter how much you eat.
That sounds great.
Tin is amazing.
Imagine a cute boy who has a tiny body
and pink lips by his side.
It must be perfect.
I don't understand
how he can be your friend.
Tin likes me.
He just feels sorry for you.
Whatever.
You can ship him with whoever you like.
I'm going to take a shower and sleep.
I didn't sleep much last night.
Don't touch me!
Can!
Tell me more about Tin!
What was he doing last night?
Why does she like to ship Tin
with someone else?
Tin is my boyfriend.
I can call him my husband now.
But that word got stuck in my throat.
"Imagine if he has a cute boy
by his side..."
He's my boyfriend.
I'm serious, Can. Someone likes Tin.
If he has a cute boy with fair skin...
...and red lips by his side,
it must be so adorable.
Did I say something wrong?
I'm serious, mom.
Tin is so handsome.
He's like an incarnated angel.
Imagine two male angels together.
It must be perfect.
A handsome angel
should be with a pretty angel.
Not always.
A male angel
can be with another male angel.
But I can't imagine Can with Tin at all.
It gives me the creeps.
That's right. That's creepy.
Can.
Can I ask you a favor?
Can you ask Tin for me
if he's dating someone?
No. I won't ask.
Why not? Please.
Just ask him
if he has a girlfriend or a boyfriend.
If he has a boyfriend,
it will be perfect.
Can!
Can you ask him for me
if he has a boyfriend or not?
Why can't he do that for me?
I can't figure it out!
What's wrong with you again?
Are you still upset
about losing the match?
Job.
Does a handsome guy
have to be with another handsome guy?
Are you crazy?
A handsome guy
should be with a pretty girl.
Look at me.
I should be with that pretty nurse.
There should be a limit to your craziness.
It's so tiring
to have such a stupid friend.
Damn you. You're talking nonsense.
I'm not talking to you anymore.
The exam is coming soon.
You're still going to skip class?
What took you so long?
What are you doing here?
English program students
are already on holiday.
I'm here to pick up my boyfriend
for lunch.
You say that word so often.
"I'm here to pick up my boyfriend
for lunch."
Can't you say another word?
Well, you are my boyfriend.
What are you thinking?
Well, I feel like I'm your sugar baby.
Huh?
Who's sugar baby? Who's sugar daddy?
Look at you.
You always treat me well
like a sugar daddy.
Should I call you daddy?
Like this. Daddy.
Other couples call each other like babe,
bae, or boo.
Should I call you daddy?
My daddy.
Let's go.
To where?
Eat lunch.
See!
You're acting like a sugar daddy.
Then let's go, my sugar baby.
You can start
pleasing your sugar daddy now.
Daddy, wait for me!
Come on, Tin.
Don't be grumpy.
It won't be too long.
I already made an appointment with you.
When did you do that?
You came to pick me up by yourself.
Also, I'm not here to play football.
I'm here to get my comics back from Pond.
Come on. It'll be quick.
I'll let you treat me a meal in return.
By the way.
My sister, Lay...
She likes to ship you
with other handsome guys.
So what?
I don't understand.
Why do all the girls think that
good looking people should be together?
Exactly.
Even a guy like me
can date a guy like you.
Why? What's wrong with a guy like me?
You're not handsome.
You're not rich.
You're also stupid.
I didn't say all these words.
You said it yourself.
Then leave me and find someone else!
I won't go,
no matter how hard you push me away.
You're the only one for me.
You're crazy!
Lay.
I'm here to do a sister's duty.
Are you okay now?
Thank you.
I'm okay now.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
Lay.
Come here.
Can.
What are you doing here?
I'm here with Chompoo.
Just that?
That's right.
Hello.
Tin is so handsome.
If Pete is still here,
he and Tin will be a perfect match.
They won't!
Why are you so angry?
I don't know.
I'm off.
Tin, let's go.
Wait.
If you want to go, just go by yourself.
Why do you have to take Tin with you?
He just came here.
Well...
Well.
What is it?
Can and I...
We are...
What's going between you two?
Nothing.
Can!
Spill your secrets to me right now!
I told you there's nothing to say!
I can tell from your voice
that you're lying.
What's going on?
Can!
Tell me now or open his mouth.
There's nothing going on.
-Can!
-I told you there's nothing!
Can!
You want to know, right?
Fine.
Watch this.
Do you know now who his boyfriend is?
♪I'll let you be my sky when I'm flying♪
♪I'll let you be my guiding star
when I lost my way♪
♪I wish you were here to hold me
through these cold nights♪
♪I wish that
you will be my everlasting love♪
Why Tul can do it but I can't?
Because he will be responsible
for everything after me.
What if I ask to live somewhere else?
Are you sure that you will buy a room
just because of that reason?
I also want freedom.
Don't forget to introduce me
to your friend.
Hey.
That's your asshole brother.
I'm glad that I finally get to meet
my brother's important person.
You're such a...
I want to know your master's weakness.
I can't tell you that.
♪Finally, I realised how it feels
to lose someone special♪
♪It is way to late for me to realise♪
♪You are now only lives in my past♪
♪I had never really loved someone
until I found you♪
♪You​ will never ever have to feel sad♪
♪We will always be together♪
♪This time,
let me take care of you forever♪
♪Our love will last until the end of time♪
♪I just realised
what my heart truly wants♪
♪Can you give me a chance to start again?♪
♪Can you come back
so that I will never let you go♪
♪I will never disappoint you
like I did before♪
♪You​ will never ever have to feel sad♪
♪We will always be together♪
♪This time,
let me take care of you forever♪
♪Our love will last until the end of time♪
♪Let the past be the past♪
♪Begin again with just the two of us♪
♪Let love and our hearts guide us♪
♪I am not afraid if I have you♪
♪You​ will never ever have to feel sad♪
♪We will always be together♪
♪This time,
let me take care of you forever♪
♪Our love will last until the end of time♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true
and honest to you♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true♪
♪Our love will last until the end of time♪