Ae.
What did you tell us what friends are for?
Huh?
You like to help other people, right?
Then why don’t you care about us?
We are very worried about you.
Where's the guy named Ae?
You're his friend?
No.
Hey!
Are you here to mess with my friend?
If you’re here to mess with him, I’ll punch you in the face first.
You’re all pathetic.
Why?
Do you think someone like me doesn't have a girlfriend?
You should go back where you came from.
Can!
Where were you? I called you but you didn’t pick up the phone.
Hello.
You are Can's friend?
I’m Lay.
I am Can’s sister.
Sister?
Not girlfriend?
No!
Of course not!
Just sister.
A guy like him cannot find any girlfriend.
Give me that.
♪I used to tell you♪
♪That we could never be more than friends♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪This time, you won't be sad♪
♪We will get through it together♪
♪From now on, let me take care of you♪
♪Tomorrow or whenever, our love will be everlasting♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
Lay.
Let's go back home.
Just sit still.
Lay!
Be quiet!
Thank you for inviting us to lunch.
It's okay.
I've got time today.
But you said you've got some errands to run.
There's still so much time left.
Your name is Lay, right?
You can order anything you like.
Are you treating us?
Yes, feel free to order.
Are you deceiving my little sister?
I will start to order then.
Sure.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Lay.
Why do you call Can...
Cantaloupe?
Well.
Can comes from...
Ouch!
Let's just ignore him.
He's always acting crazy.
His name, Can, comes from Cantaloupe.
And my name Lay, comes from Lemon.
Because when our mom was pregnant, she wanted to eat it.
That's nice.
How is that nice?
The name is too cute.
Not all mothers care enough to think of their children's names.
I want to go home now.
Lay won't stop talking about me.
This dude too.
Speak of the devil.
Why are you following me around?
I didn't follow you.
I just want to go to the toilet.
Just go. It's over there.
Go!
There's big question mark on your face.
Am I that obvious?
I just want to ask you a few questions.
Ask then.
Well...
About what you said...
Not all mothers care enough to think of their children's names.
What do you mean?
My name is Tin.
I know that.
Tin and your surname is something with Nan.
But...
I just want to know why you said that.
My brother's name is Tul.
Tin and Tul.
Both of your names are much cooler than ours.
The reason that my mom gave me that name
is because she wanted it to match with my brother's.
She wants me to be good
and smart
like my brother.
I'm the son that she doesn't want.
I'm just Tin
who will always live in my brother's shadow.
Tin...
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what you've been through.
I'm curious because I saw you're making weird face.
You believe me?
What do you mean?
Just a little bit of acting, and you already fall for that?
You're stupid.
You asshole!
I was worried about you. You're an asshole.
Thank you.
For what?
For worrying.
Who's worried?
That person must be crazy.
What if I tell you the truth.
Will you believe me?
I have to pee. I'll be right back.
Tin.
You're his good friend, right?
Yes.
Can you look after him for me?
He is a little bit foolish and naive.
People often trick him.
Is it that often?
Very often.
When he was young,
he was fooled into believing that he would get an extra point
if he could open a girl's skirt.
Can believed that!
He opened my skirt.
I was crying so hard back then.
That's not it.
He was tricked to get rid of ant's nest.
He also went into a house because someone told him that the dog was abused.
He almost died.
Imagine a Thai Bangkaew dog attacking a ten-year-old kid.
I don't want to think about it anymore.
What did Can do then?
What can he do?
It doesn't matter how many times he got hurt.
He's always optimistic.
He never gets angry at anyone.
He truly believes in his friends.
Why are you telling me all this?
Because you're smart.
I want you to teach him.
Thank you for telling me this.
Can I trust you?
Type, are you there already?
Wait for me. I'm coming.
Come on. Wait for me.
Alright.
What are you doing here?
Keng has been waiting for you for two hours already.
Techno.
Can I talk to you about...
that night?
Shut up! Technic is still here!
Come on.
Brother.
Actually,
I know everything.
Huh?
I'm not joking.
But I don't want to interfere with this matter.
You two should talk.
Techno.
What can I do
for you to forgive me?
No...
I'm not mad at you.
Then why are you avoiding me?
I'm not avoiding you.
Techno.
I will do everything for you to forgive me.
I really like you.
Let's talk about that later.
Type is waiting for me.
I have to go now.
Techno!
My brother...
He's so good at running away.
He's avoiding you again.
I did wrong this time.
It's everyone's fault.
I sold my brother for free gifts.
Shit!
Why is he so handsome?
My damn heart, calm down. I will have a heart attack.
Give me more time, Kla.
I never thought of having a boyfriend before.
Shorty, wake up!
What the hell?
It's not time for sleeping.
It's so late already.
Usually, you wake up at 5 a.m.
Get up!
Shit!
I don't know anything.
I didn't see anything.
My two best friends are getting together?
Shorty.
Are you going crazy?
I understand if you want to have a boyfriend.
But I cannot accept the fact that...
Mai is your wife.
Pond!
What?
Are you crazy?
That's right.
I get it.
You have a new buddy now.
You already forget about your old friend.
Damn you.
Where are you taking me?
Just come.
I take you here to do something that is suitable for you.
Stop making a pit bull face.
Here it is.
You should join this.
What is it?
A volunteer camp?
That's right.
Instead of feeling sad.
You should do something more useful.
You should use your time thinking about your boyfriend
to do something that you're good at.
Register this.
It's better than overthinking.
Mai is amazing.
He doesn't study here,
but he knows about this camp.
It seems like you'll enjoy it though.
You told me that you want to go if you have a chance.
Ae.
Ae!
Are you listening?
Can you take a picture for me?
Huh?
Since when do you like to take pictures?
Just take it.
Fine.
One. Two...
You're not going to smile or pose anything?
This is good enough.
Can you tell me what's going on?
You said I don't like to update about my life.
I want to try to do it.
It's better than doing nothing.
Ae.
I'm okay. Thanks.
Are you sure?
He doesn't look okay to me.
Thank you for dropping us off.
Lucky us that we don't have to carry heavy stuff back home.
It's me who carry everything. You didn't help me at all.
Lay, I'm your brother!
What are you laughing at?
I have to thank you anyway.
What about you?
What?
Did you forget something?
Forget what?
I came out of the house with just a phone and a wallet.
It's probably Lay who forgets it.
He asks you, did you forget to say thank you?
I will tell mom if you still behave like this.
Lay.
I'm your big brother.
What are you laughing at?
For you.
Thank you.
Lay.
We cannot accept things from strangers.
Mom also taught us that we can't be bought with money.
Who is the stranger?
He's your friend.
Your friend gives me this so I can accept it.
I will go inside first.
Okay.
What else do you want?
Did you forget something?
Do you want me to say it that much?
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Are you satisfied now?
I want it...
this way.
You're so much cuter than those girls.
He kissed me again!
Why...
Why do I feel this way?
It feels like
dragonflies in stomach.
I get it now.
This is how you solve it.
What's wrong with you?
He's stressed.
Then you should eat this. It will help to relieve stress.
Stop playing around.
You're not helping me to do the work at all.
Give it to me.
I'll eat it for you.
Come on, dude.
It's mine.
Seeing you enjoy eating can help me to relieve stress.
What makes you stressed?
About Ae.
Just give him more time.
It seems like he doesn't have anyone beside him.
You should stop feeling sorry for him.
Why?
Because he still has us by his side.
Let's continue with our work.
We have to finish Ae's part too.
After we finish, we can go and look after him.
That's right.
What do we have to do again?
Pick it up.
Pick it.
Let's get it.
What?
Cheers!
Fight for Ae!
Fight for Ae.
Start working now.
Keen.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
I'm here for a while already.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It should be me who ask that.
It's like there's something going on in your mind.
Is it about Tar?
No.
Tar is doing fine.
He called me yesterday about his friends and study.
There's nothing to worry about.
I just feel like...
I don't have any inspiration these days.
Inspiration to write songs?
That's right.
I want to write a love song.
But...
I have no idea.
I don't know how to write a song but I have an idea.
Someone told me that
if you want to write a love song,
you must learn how to love first.
Who will love someone like me?
How can you know if you haven't looked around?
What do you mean?
Just forget about it.
Let's practice.
Okay.
Did you figure out how to play yet?
I did.
I added solo part into this.
You finally come back.
It's late already.
You should come back earlier.
You will make our parents worry.
You're just a student.
Are you done?
Why are you so against me?
I cannot say anything to you at all?
I don't need to listen to you.
You were always calling for me before.
I told you.
Stop pretending.
You can be a good son,
a perfect husband,
or a caring father.
But don't pretend that you're my brother.
He's long gone.
I'm sitting right here.
He's dead!
He's dead a long time ago, along with my stupidity.
I'm smarter now.
When will you take off your mask?
You can't do it, right?
Because if you do and people know the real you,
no one can stand you.
I'm off.
My little brother is too straightforward.
You can't stand to be with me either, right?
Gonhin.
Hin, where's Tul?
He goes to talk with the teacher.
I will wait for him here then. I want to see his face first.
He makes my day brighter with his handsome face.
Have you heard that Tul already has a girlfriend?
Is she the one that waited for him that day?
She is so pretty, but I hope they're not together. What a waste.
Hin, Tul already has a girlfriend?
Well...
I...
Hi, girls.
What are you guys doing here?
We're here to chill in this room.
I thought you guys come to see me.
Well yes.
You probably know already that we're waiting here to see you.
I won't know that if you guys don't tell me.
You guys almost made me cry.
Hin, are you free?
I want to discuss with you about what the teacher just told me.
Will you excuse me? You guys can stay here.
I'll be right back.
Come.
Hin.
Look up and look into my eyes.
Look up!
Who made you cry?
No one.
You know that I hate it, right?
I hate it when someone makes you cry.
You can only cry because of me.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I belong to you.
That's right.
Remember that.
You belong to me.
You wouldn't get it when I give it to you.
Now you're dragging me all the way here to buy it.
It's you who drank all of mine.
Coming with me to buy it is the right thing to do.
It's you who drank all of them.
What are you talking about?
What did you do that makes you so hungry?
Well...
My heart was beating too fast because of Tin.
Huh? What did you say?
Oh!
I was going to say that
you eat too much,
but you also talk a lot.
That's why you never get fat.
Of course not. It's because I stop eating junk food.
You should drink Jele. It's the best.
Easy to drink and it won't make you fat.
This one.
It helps you to grow.
You should drink a lot of this.
So you will be more mature.
It's yummy.
Lay!
Where are you?
Go home!
That's right. I have to hurry.
I'm late again!
Why didn't you wake me up?
Where's the motorcycle?
How come you're here?
When will you stop greeting me with that sentence?
Thank you for dropping me off.
You can leave now.
Why are you still here?
I told you.
I don't want just a simple 'thank you.'
I know what you're going to do.
This time, I won't let you kiss me.
You're teasing me.
I'm not.
You are.
You kiss me because you want to make me lose my mind.
I won't let you do it for a second time.
I'm not teasing you.
Well...
What do you want?
Hit on you.
I never hit on anyone like you.
I don't know how.
But I will hit on you.
You
hit on
me...
You're hitting on me.
Hit on me...
If I tell you something,
will you believe me?
Can I go to see you now?
♪Do you hear the sound outside the window?
The sound of thunder scares me♪
♪Can I hold your hands to calm my heart?♪
♪Stay with me until the rain stops♪
♪I don't know what to do if you walk away♪
♪Let me please you forever♪
♪I will do everything to make you stay by my side♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night without you?♪
♪You know that I like the way you hug
and the way you say I love you♪
♪Just whisper the words in my ears♪
♪I can't barely stand the thought of you leaving me♪
♪Can you stay with me a little longer?♪
♪Stay with me until the rain stops♪
♪I don't know what to do if you walk away♪
♪Let me please you forever♪
♪I will do everything to make you stay by my side♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night without you?♪
♪Can you see the rain?♪
♪I can feel the pain♪
♪Stay with me until the rain stops♪
♪How do I get through the night without you?♪
♪Can you see the rain?♪
♪Let me please you forever♪
♪I can feel the pain♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night without you?♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night without you?♪