Tin said I accused him
of taking drugs, right?
Tin...
Let me ask you something.
Have you taken drugs before?
You believed him right?
How many times do I have to tell you...
that you're the only one I'll listen to!
Sorry.
What...
I can't stay calm anymore!
Do you think I'll believe you?
Who can tell me what's going on here?
Is Can home?
He said he was going to murder someone
at your house!
I need to go.
Tin!
Don't do something stupid, Can.
♪I used to tell you♪
♪That we could never be♪
♪more than friends♪
♪When I said that I don't love you,
I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends,
I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us
to be just friends anymore♪
♪This time, you won't be sad♪
♪We will get through it together♪
♪From now on, let me take care of you♪
♪Tomorrow or whenever,
our love will be everlasting♪
♪When I said that I don't love you,
I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends,
I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us
to be just friends anymore♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true
and honest to you♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true
and honest to you♪
=A Chance To Love=
Where is Can?
Can is in Mister's room.
He didn't do something stupid, right?
Can punched Tul's face.
You're finally here.
This?
It's nothing.
I only got punched a few times.
Your friend packed quite a punch.
Where is Can?
Talking to dad.
Do you think it'll end here?
It doesn't matter how it's gonna end.
I won't let you lay a finger on Can.
In the end,
you are the one who is the happiest.
I wish you luck.
Why are you so biased?
Tin is also your son.
Why did you do this to him?
Do you know what your eldest son
has done to him?
All you do is work, work, work.
Do you have any idea how sad he feels?
How much he got hurt?
Do you know anything at all? Do you know?
Do you know what Tul sent me?
He sent me a video of someone
who looks like Tin having sex with a girl,
and taking drugs.
Do you think I won't be able
to remember my own boyfriend?
How can he do this?
Tin,
let's have a talk.
Tin, why are you so late?
I arrived a long time ago.
I only managed to get a few punches in.
Someone like him
deserves even more of a beating.
Too bad someone stopped me.
Why?
Does nobody know that
he's such a son of a bitch?
Stop it, Can.
I won't stop.
I will let everyone know
what your brother has done.
Can.
Tin!
Why didn't you tell your father
about what Tul's done to you?
That's enough.
I'll drive you home.
I'm not going anywhere.
Not until we've cleared this up.
Cantaloupe.
Let him go, son.
Go on.
I also want to know
about the things my eldest son...
has done.
Dad...
I've never gotten the chance
to talk to you...
or to your brother.
This time...
Maybe it's time I listen.
Yes.
You should listen.
Stop being one of those stupid adults...
that are only biased
towards one of your own son.
Go on.
Tell me, an adult that
doesn't equally love his own children,
about what happened.
Tul sent a clip of someone
who looks similar to Tin...
doing drugs, having sex,
and he also back-stabbed Tin.
Give it to me. I'll do it for you.
It's okay.
Tul, I don't understand at all.
Why do you purposefully do
all these things to make Tin hate you?
I've never done anything like that at all.
Tul...
I've looked after you
since you were just a baby.
Why won't I know?
The reason why you're doing this
is to make Tin hate you, right?
I have to do this.
And everyone should know the truth.
I shouldn't get all these praises
that I didn't deserve...
from my little brother.
Come on, Tul.
And that's the reason
why you punched Tul, right?
Obviously.
How can I not get angry?
He's sneaking around and doing things
behind Tin's back..
Is this true, Tin?
Even if I tell you,
you wouldn't believe me.
Why didn't you give it a try first?
If I told you that he's hurt me
since I was young.
I'm sorry...
for hurting you without knowing it.
I'm sorry
for staying silent all this time.
Even though all this time,
I thought that
I was doing what you needed me to do.
I am indebted to you...
and Tul, aren't I?
What does that bastard
have to do with anything?
What do you mean by what I needed?
Freedom.
Freedom?
That's right.
The freedom to do anything you want.
The freedom
to choose how to live your own life.
The freedom...
that your brother and I would never have.
I've never told you before, right?
That's right.
I've never told you.
Freedom...
that I've had before
when I married Tul's mom.
The only freedom that I chose.
Even if people were against me,
I didn't care.
And it ended in a failure.
It left me with only a boy
who had to receive all the misfortune.
Tin.
I admit...
that I didn't try to stop your mom
and your brother...
sent you overseas.
I am even thankful that that happened.
How can you say that?
Tin.
For me,
having no one
placing any expectations on you...
is the best thing.
You'll have your own life.
You can choose anything.
Everyone
will not place expectations on you.
Because that will slowly kill you.
That's why I said...
that I've given you
the best thing I could.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand anything.
Explain it to me.
That child has gone through more things
than everyone can imagine.
Your brother
has faced many things through his life.
He's never been happy.
And you...
who I thought
I've given the best thing possible to.
Who would've already find
his own happiness.
Tin.
I beg you.
You can hate me however you want.
You can be angry at me however you want.
But please, forgive your brother.
You are so biased.
Okay.
Tin!
Your brother has caused you pain
for so many years.
I will forgive him.
But you have to promise me first...
that you will give me the freedom...
to love whoever I want.
I promise.
No one will be able to stop you
from walking on the path you chose.
Even if that person is your mom.
Please take care of my son.
Please look after him...
in place of this old uncle
who never got the chance to do it.
Oh, right.
Tul is going to get a divorce.
Does this make you happier?
You've always been a good child, Tin.
Where are you going?
I'm still going to prove...
that I am also capable of doing things.
That's good.
If I have another talented son
who can help me,
I'd be very happy.
Tin, we haven't finished talking yet!
Tin, why did you drag me out?
We still haven't cleared up everything.
I despise your brother so much, I still...
Let go of me, Tin.
I still haven't finished
talking to your dad.
It's already finished.
You're the one with a slow brain.
How is it finished?
I still haven't finished telling your dad
about your brother.
Whatever, I will take revenge for you!
Don't you realize that you already did?
Huh? How?
Can you explain it to me? I'm stupid.
Promise me first,
then I'll tell you the best way
to take revenge.
Okay, I promise.
Tin, it hurts!
Stay by my side.
Make me the happiest man alive on earth.
The kind of happiness
that my brother can never have.
That...
is the best kind of revenge.
Sure.
I'll make you the luckiest man on earth.
So lucky that your brother
will be jealous of you.
♪I'm not asking anyone to understand.♪
Tin.
♪I'm not asking
for any other precious things.♪
♪I'm not asking for anything else
that everyone is seeking for.♪
I love you.
You can cry and let it out.
Who cares about anyone else.
You don't have to act so strong
in front of me.
I will never leave you.
Don't ever leave me.
Yes.
I already promised
that I won't go anywhere.
♪Hold me tighter than yesterday.♪
♪I want you. Only you.♪
♪I want you to be my everlasting love.♪
What's up, Type?
Yeah, I'm about to leave.
I won't take long.
Gotta go.
Techno.
I know that you don't want to see my face.
You don't want to pick up my calls.
But I have many things I want to tell you.
I know that I was wrong to make a move
on you while you were drunk.
But it's because I've liked you
for a long time.
For many years.
From the first time we met,
you're one of the few
that didn't care about my looks.
You didn't care
about my family background.
You make me feel good
every time we are together.
Shit!
He wrote me a whole letter?
Doesn't he know I also get embarrassed?
No! I shouldn't be soft-hearted now.
Techno.
I...
Shit.
He wrote me a letter...
and wait for me in front of my house.
Also, he became more handsome.
No! I can't go feeling soft-hearted now!!
How long are you gonna stand there?
Come take a seat.
No.
Cantaloupe is waiting for me.
He's probably screaming
about how hungry he is right now.
You guys played pretty hard, huh?
In the end,
you're the one who is happy.
No matter what I do,
you'll still be happy.
Dad told you, right?
That I will get a divorce.
Why?
Why what?
Why would someone like you,
who needs success,
decide to get a divorce?
When Vadee and Phupha went to France
a few months ago,
Vadee met someone new there.
But I won't blame her.
Since I was the one
who never spent time with her.
But Vadee and I talked about it
for a while.
It's time to give each other freedom.
What about Phupha?
Phupha will stay here.
As soon as we get a divorce,
Vadee will go to France.
Go on and mock me.
In the end,
your brother is just another failure.
Everyone leaves me in the end.
Even my own mother.
In the end,
like dad said, you're such a good child.
Never mocking anyone else's failure.
Even if that person is someone like me.
Why are you stopping now?
Even though
there's so much more you could do.
You could make Can hate me.
So why did you only send one clip?
Like a silly child's game.
I already promised him.
I just...
wanted to know if he really loves you.
But I'm stopping now.
Since I already lost.
Look after him carefully.
Don't make a mistake like me.
What took you so long!
If not because I hurt...
What are you laughing at?
I know now,
why your cheeks are so soft.
It's because you love eating this.
Tin.
Even if my cheeks are soft,
it still hurts.
You pinched so hard.
Do you want some?
Are you finished?
Go get a new one!
Won't you feel shy at all?
Shy about what?
An indirect kiss through the straw?
We're already past that point!
You...
What?
Fine, take it if you want.
I'll give it to you.
Really?
Yeah.
You are...
so cute.
How cute?
So cute.
Eat slowly.
I love my dad, and I love my name.
Because my name means...
The love that I gave to someone.
Why did I just figure it out?
Gonhin.
You thought this through carefully, right?
About this decision.
Yes.
I know this might seem ungrateful,
-But I...
-No.
It's not like that.
When I hired your family to work for me,
I've never thought...
that you are indebted to me.
Your family...
is the one who has been helping me
for many years.
But if you've already decided,
I won't hold a grudge against you.
Yes.
I've already made my decision.
Does Tul know yet?
Tul already has Vadee...
and their child
who is going to be born soon.
And what about you? Who do you have?
I have memories...
of the last 10 years.
I am sorry.
I am sorry that I won't be able to stay
and protect Tul anymore.
I can no longer do that.
I want to keep protecting Tul,
but I can't stay any longer.
I can't destroy the family
that Tul has wanted for so long.
Gonhin.
Just calm down first.
I have to get out of this house.
You know, right?
That you can always...
come back to this house.
You know it, right?
That Tul will always need you.
Yes.
But not now.
Not now.
I really cannot help any of my sons.
Tul.
I don't want to hear it.
I have something I need to tell you.
I said I don't want to hear it!
Please.
Listen to me.
I don't want to hear it.
I won't listen to it!
I'm leaving tomorrow morning.
I told you that I'm not letting you leave.
But I have to go.
Tul.
We both know that
there's no better solution than this.
Vadee is pregnant with your baby.
The baby that I don't want.
Of course, you do.
You want him.
You've always wanted a family.
Someone who will love you.
And Vadee is going to give birth
to that person for you.
Something which I cannot give you.
Please don't say that you don't need her.
Because you know it best that you do.
No.
The one that I need is you.
I can no longer stay by your side.
I have to go...
so your world will be complete.
You are my world.
I am just another rock.
Please just throw me away.
I am not worthy to be your whole world.
But you promised me
that you won't ever leave me.
After this,
you probably won't need me anymore.
I love you, Hin.
I love you.
But your child needs a father.
That child...
Please give him a lot of love.
Don't let him grow up to be like you...
or Tin.
If you have no reason to keep on living,
think of it as a request from me.
Please keep on living for your child.
This is my last request.
Can you promise me?
That you'll be happy.
You're asking me the impossible.
I hope you'll be happy.
Hin.
Hin!
♪I still have hope
even I know that it's hopeless♪
♪I've been hopelessly
wishing for the impossible.♪
♪I'm asking just for once♪
♪Just for once♪
♪Give me just a few seconds♪
♪So that I will no longer be lonely♪
I am repenting my own sins now,
right, Gonhin?
In the end, I'm left with nobody.
And then,
I punched Tin's brother
until he flew into the wall.
-Is that so?
-Of course!
He dares to mess with my Tin.
He doesn't know me well enough.
Now you can say, "my Tin"
without feeling shy, huh?
You're the one who taught me...
that we need to have confidence
in what we do.
So now, I'm brave enough to say
that Tin is my boyfriend.
Wow.
That's so brave of you.
Now, I'm gonna go sell this video
to your boyfriend...
and see how much money
I can get from this.
Fuck you, Pond!
What's the matter?
Don't send it to Tin.
I can also get embarrassed.
Don't be so touchy.
Is there a whole watermelon in your mouth?
Your cheeks are so puffy.
Ever since you've got a boyfriend,
and have been kissing each other
in the middle of campus,
You've become a lot more showy.
Stop it! Give me the phone!!
No, I won't give it to you.
What are you doing here?
What's up, shorty.
That loud mouth over there told me
you're going to release your own song.
Hey!
I didn't go around telling everyone
about that.
It's not my song.
A senior is going to write a song,
so I'm just helping him out.
Same thing.
So when will I get to hear it?
Next month,
at the university's music festival!
He really knows every little detail,
that bastard.
Ouch! Can!
Stop taking out your embarrassment on me!
Ouch!
That's enough!
Look, your boyfriend's here
to pick you up.
You should get going!
Okay, then I'll be leaving first.
Ae, I'm going first!
-See you!
-Bye.
You're such a nuisance...
Who said he's a monkey?
He's clearly a dog.
Am I gonna catch rabies?
Then next month
I'll come and listen to your song.
Hey! Listen to me first!
Do I have to?
Do you think you're worth my attention?
Ouch, that's pretty harsh.
Tin, what's wrong?
Tin.
Are you mad at me
because I was fooling around with Pond?
Here.
Stop being mad.
I'm making up with you, so smile!
Why do I have to smile for you?
Because you have such a cute
and handsome boyfriend!
Also, me and Pond? Together? No way.
I get the chills just thinking about it.
I'm not mad at you anymore.
Good!
That's the right decision, very good!
I'm planning to go overseas
for about a week.
What?
Where are you going?
Tin, I'm talking to you right now.
What are you looking at
while smiling like that?
Hey!
That we need to have confidence
in what we do.
-So now I'm brave enough to say...
-You're kind of cute.
-that Tin is my boyfriend.
-Pond, that asshole!
That's so brave of you.
Now I'm gonna go sell this video
to your boyfriend...
Give that back.
I'm not giving it to you anymore.
You already kissed it, so it's mine now.
Fine, take it back.
Tin!
I'm returning the kiss too.
Stop making me embarrassed!
But in the video, you said...
you're not the shy person
you used to be anymore.
That's right!
I'm not embarrassed at all.
Because you're mine.
I just said the truth.
That's right.
I'm yours.
What are you doing?
Hang on.
Slow down.
Calm down!
Here, have some.
You'll get hungry later.
Are you okay?
It'll come to you soon.
Eat this first.
Great!
Have some first,
and then you can continue working.
You can do it!
Thanks.
Where are you up to now?
Nowhere.
You got it?
Let me see.
See? You can do it if you try.
How is it?
I think this part is okay.
No matter where, you are...
Like this?
Yeah, this part is good.
Why are you hugging me?
Keen.
Look, I've finished writing this song.
Look!
I've never felt this confident before.
Do you like it?
Hurry! Tell me, do you like it?
Of course.
Right?
I like it too.
I've never felt this good
about a song before.
Tin, wait!
So tiring.
Good thing I have this drink.
-Why are you here?
-You're asking me why!
You forgot something.
What?
This!
I love this. It's so good.
It's that good?
Of course.
I'm still chewing on the coconut jelly
with vitamin C in it.
Wanna have a try?
Okay, then let me try some.
Here, you can try mine.
Are you crazy?
I'm talking about this drink.
I want to taste it from your lips.
You should go.
See you later.
I'll send you off.
Who is this?
Tum's friend?
Tin!
How did you come here?
Who said I miss you?
We haven't seen each other
for only a few days.
You're too obsessed with me.
Tin!
I'm done here.
I already know what I should know.
Tar!
Since when did you come back?
Mom didn't tell me anything.
I asked her not to tell you.
I want to surprise you.
♪This song is still beautiful♪
♪every time I listen to it.♪
It's so lonely
to listen to a love song alone.
♪Finally, I realised
how it feels to lose someone special♪
♪It is way to late for me to realise♪
♪You are now only lives in my past♪
♪I had never really loved someone
until I found you♪
♪You​ will never ever have to feel sad♪
♪We will always be together♪
♪This time,
let me take care of you forever♪
♪Our love will last until the end of time♪
♪I just realised
what my heart truly wants♪
♪Can you give me a chance to start again?♪
♪Can you come back
so that I will never let you go♪
♪I will never disappoint you
like I did before♪
♪You​ will never ever have to feel sad♪
♪We will always be together♪
♪This time,
let me take care of you forever♪
♪Our love will last until the end of time♪
♪Let the past be the past♪
♪Begin again with just the two of us♪
♪Let love and our hearts guide us♪
♪I am not afraid if I have you♪
♪You​ will never ever have to feel sad♪
♪We will always be together♪
♪This time,
let me take care of you forever♪
♪Our love will last until the end of time♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true
and honest to you♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true♪
♪Our love will last until the end of time♪