I like you.
I know that.
I'm hitting on you.
You can hit on me.
You can like me.
I just...
I still don't know
if I'm okay with you or not.
What is love?
It means Pete.
Why all I can see is pain?
I don't want to be like you, Ae.
-Why are you avoiding me?
-Who's avoiding you?
-You're over-thinking.
-You do.
But I'm glad.
Because that means
you're actually thinking about me.
What is it?
Will you be boyfriend, Can?
What's wrong?
I don't understand.
Which part don't you understand?
I don't know.
I don't know if I like you or not.
We can go out and eat
and watch movies together.
Isn't that enough?
Why do we have to be in a relationship?
Because you're the air I breathe.
When I'm with my family,
I feel like I'm drowning.
I can't breathe.
I'm suffocating.
But when I'm with you,
I feel like I can breathe again.
I still don't understand.
Look at Ae.
Ae is still sad.
I don't want to be like him.
If we...
If we're not together,
then we won't be sad later.
Can't we be friends?
I don't want to be just friends.
♪Can I change it? I don't want us
to be just friends anymore♪
But...
I want to be your friend.
I have an appointment at home.
See you later, Tin.
♪I used to tell you♪
♪That we could never be♪
♪More than friends♪
♪When I said that I don't love you,
I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends,
I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us
to be just friends anymore♪
♪This time, you won't be sad♪
♪We will get through it together♪
♪From now on, let me take care of you♪
♪Tomorrow or whenever,
our love will be everlasting♪
♪When I said that I don't love you,
I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends,
I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us
to be just friends anymore♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true
and honest to you♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true
and honest to you♪
=A Chance To Love=
Lay! I told you not to eat first.
It's not a big deal.
No means no.
Here.
Your brother is coming back soon.
Let's start eating together.
We'll never eat together.
Dad will be home late today.
Are you talking back to me?
Can is finally home.
Let's eat dinner.
I didn't eat first.
You don't have to scold me.
I'm tired to listen.
You guys can eat.
I'm not hungry.
Are you sick?
Is he sick?
Did you do anything to him?
Mom.
Why are you accusing me?
I didn't do anything.
What's wrong with him?
Lay! I told you not to eat first.
Not before me.
-I'm hungry.
-Let your mother eat first.
Do you know manners?
Do you want a bigger spoon
if you're going to eat that much?
Can I have an omelet too?
We already have four dishes.
Still not enough?
I don't understand.
I still don't understand.
I don't want to be sad.
I also don't want you to be sad like Ae.
I like to see you smile.
So, let's be friends.
You're the only one I want.
Nobody else.
I want only you.
Can.
You're so much cuter than those girls.
♪I still have hope even I know
that it's hopeless♪
I never hit on anyone like you.
I don't know how.
But I will hit on you.
♪I still hope and wait
for the lonely nights to pass♪
♪In the pain and torment♪
♪It might take a lot of time
that all the stars fall down from the sky♪
Tin.
♪I still have hope
even I know that it's hopeless♪
♪I've been hopelessly wishing for
the impossible. I'm asking just for once♪
What is it?
Will you be boyfriend, Can?
If we're not together,
then we won't be sad later.
♪Give me just a few seconds♪
Can't we be friends?
♪So that I will no longer be lonely♪
I want you.
Just you.
♪Why am I still hoping
when there is no hope?♪
♪I still hope and wait
for the lonely nights♪
♪To pass♪
♪In the pain and torment♪
♪It might take a lot of time
that all the stars fall down from the sky♪
♪I still have hope
even I know that it's hopeless♪
♪I've been hopelessly
wishing for the impossible♪
♪I'm asking just for once♪
♪Just for once♪
♪Give me just a few seconds♪
♪So that I...♪
♪Will no longer be lonely...♪
Job.
Your inspiration to play football
impresses me.
If Ae weren't always drunk
these few months,
we'd be friends a long time ago.
Come on.
It's not too late.
My friend,
join me to flirt with nursing students.
Girls from the Faculty of Nursing?
All the fair-skinned girls.
Girls in white uniform.
They come with a bright smile
on their faces.
And then...
"Excuse me,"
"it's time to take your medicine."
Dude.
I want to be sick now.
Me too.
What should be my excuse
to go to the hospital?
How about getting stabbed by ChaAim?
Oh, right!
Who cares about those nurses?
I'm not interested.
I'm into a Liberal Arts girl.
I already have a girlfriend.
She's very cute.
You can flirt with other girls
by yourself.
What are you looking at?
Nothing. You're just an asshole.
You dare to say that to me?
I'm your lifesaver.
Yummy?
You should try.
Smells good.
Don't steal it from me.
I bought all this for myself.
All the yummy stuff for me only.
I'm not hungry.
You're not hungry?
What's wrong?
I don't understand.
Whatever I eat no longer tastes good.
I feel like I'm constipated.
I can't stop thinking about him.
I think I'm going crazy.
I think you've always been crazy.
(How are you?)
Can I sit here with you?
You can sit wherever you like.
I'm not the owner of this university.
The University Football Tournament
is coming soon.
You guys have to work harder.
Do you remember
the pain of losing last time?
We won't lose again this time.
But I'm not sad at all.
Because I just joined the team this year.
You and Can are the same.
Come on.
You shouldn't spoil them too much.
Type ditched me to be with his husband
is already bad enough.
Damn you.
Whatever. Just do what you want.
Where is the little monkey?
Where did he go?
Shit!
Since when did you come?
Why are you sneaking up on me?
You scared me.
What's wrong with you?
You look so gloomy
like someone uses black magic on you.
Can you help me eat this?
I bought it but I've lost my appetite now.
Someone like you has that feeling?
How can someone like him lose appetite?
You guys can go to practice now.
Hey.
Ae.
You're not going back yet?
It's already late.
What time is it now?
It's already 9:30 PM.
Techno is so harsh.
I want to know between going
into the final match or dying,
which one will come first.
I'm so tired today.
Tin.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you suddenly say his name?
You've become like this...
...because of him, right?
Is it because
my answer wasn't clear enough?
What question?
I didn't ask you any questions.
You're going crazy
because you're missing Pete too much.
Do you even look at yourself?
You're sad about Tin.
You're going crazy as well.
Listen to me, Can.
I told you that my love means Pete.
If he stands right here in front of me,
I won't hesitate to pull him in for a hug.
I'll protect him.
I'll always be by his side.
Even if your brain can't understand that,
but your heart should know.
You should talk to him.
Trust me.
Okay.
I'll talk to him.
Thank you so much.
You're my best friend.
I've got your back.
I'll get changed then.
I wish you're here with me.
Techno.
Don't run away from me.
I'm not.
I'm not running away.
You're over-thinking, Kla.
You're never home when I go to see you.
You also jumped out of the window
to avoid me.
That doesn't mean
you're running away from me?
I jumped off the balcony not window...
Is there anything else you want to say?
I want to go home and rest now.
I really like you, Techno.
I admitted that I lied to you.
I lied that you're the one
who started it first.
But there's one thing
that I never lie to you.
It's that I really like you.
I like you for such a long time.
I like you since the first day we met.
But you did lie to me.
That's still the truth.
I've told you.
I have nothing to say to you right now.
I've got to go.
Techno.
What else do you want?
At least, please let me take you home.
Please.
Is this his car?
He's not going home yet?
How should I start a conversation?
It's so late now.
I'd get into trouble
if you didn't help me.
You also give me a ride.
Thank you so much.
I shouldn't hide behind his car.
Tum.
Look at this.
This guy that I told you about.
He posted it again.
I told you about him before.
He always posts a photo every day.
His caption is like,
he's talking to someone.
But he never tags anyone.
I was going through his FB.
He actually posts like this every day.
It's like his diary.
He posts where he goes, what he does,
and who he hangs out with.
You should take a look.
I don't think that's weird.
People who use FB always do that.
Then...
Why do you think he's interesting?
I don't know. You should go through it.
It's like he wants to say something.
He's telling what's going on in his life.
But if you're not interested...
Who told you I'm not?
-You said...
-I'm just asking.
I believe in you.
Should we go to meet him?
How?
He's an engineering student
from our university.
It won't be hard to find him.
Okay.
If you think that's a good idea,
then I think so too.
Great.
Dude.
I think I got it.
I think this plan is okay.
This strategy will work.
I agree with whatever you say.
Thanks, bro.
I believe that if we win this match,
we'll have a chance to become a champion.
This one is hot and spicy.
Tin.
Why are you walking so fast? Wait for me.
Thank you for dropping me off last night
in front of the university.
My friends are terrible.
They wouldn't wait for me.
That's why I have to bother you.
Thank you so much.
Calm down, Can. Quit imagining things.
I have to talk to Tin first.
Tin.
Can I ask you something?
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't.
Well...
Do you want to be my boyfriend?
I'll never choose you to be my girlfriend.
Now stop bothering me.
It's annoying.
Damn it!
Give me a ball!
You're pretentious! What a show-off!
Give it to me!
You said that I'm the air you breathe!
Then why are you breathing in
from someone else?
Give me a ball!
I don't have it!
How come? I have to practice!
Damn it!
I've been collecting balls for you
for half an hour already.
Look around!
You should collect them by yourself.
I'm off.
Didn't you say you like me?
Job.
Come here.
Dude.
What's wrong with Can?
I wonder too.
He's been like this for a week.
I told him to rest but he wouldn't listen.
Is he okay?
How can he be okay?
He practices too hard.
I think he wants to win
the World Championship.
Well...
You should stop him.
Do you think he will listen?
I know that I'm handsome and cool,
but I can't do everything you say.
Why don't you ask Ae to stop him?
He listens to Ae more than me.
Ae, you should stop him.
Look.
He's not a little monkey anymore.
He's wild like a dog.
Ae!
Something's wrong with him too?
Why don't you guys talk?
It's none of your business.
He practices too hard.
If you're worried, why don't you go in?
How can I do that?
Why not?
Can is right in front of you.
The day that you lose him by your side,
it will be the worst pain.
He doesn't like me
the way that Pete likes you.
How do you know...
...that Can doesn't really like you?
We have a match tomorrow.
You should come.
I think he wants you to come.
Why are you helping me?
Why did you help me
when Pete's dad was going to expel me?
Pete asked for my help.
That's right.
Because you're his friend.
Give him some time.
If he doesn't understand,
it doesn't mean he has no feelings.
What's wrong with you?
I'm nervous!
We'll start playing soon.
Why are you nervous?
You're just a substitute.
So what? I'm nervous.
Are you guys ready?
Let's go out there and win this match!
Let's go!
Get up!
(Do your best.)
Ae, get the ball!
Go!
Run!
Techno!
Are you okay?
I can't get up. It hurts.
Can, are you ready to get on the field?
-But Techno...
-Come on.
Fight for the team.
Go!
Can!
For the team!
-Go!
-Okay.
You can do it.
Can.
Tin.
Come here.
Why do we have to lose?
We practiced so hard.
We practiced every day.
We played only two matches.
I want to cry.
You're crying now.
I want to cry more.
You can do that.
I will keep crying.
You can cry so you can forget about it.
You can cry in front of me.
Tin.
I'm sorry.
It's not that I don't like you.
Please don't disappear again.
Don't disappear again, Tin.
I'm right here.
I'm always right beside you.
♪Give me just a few seconds♪
♪so that I...♪
♪will no longer be lonely♪
Tin.
I might be stupid.
I...
I might not understand.
But I don't like it...
...when I see you with someone else.
I also don't like it...
...when you're taking care
of someone else.
When you're not with me...
I really miss you.
Tin.
I like you.
I really like you.
I like you too.
♪Is this what you call love?♪
♪My heart won't listen to me anymore♪
♪I tell myself to stop thinking about you,
but my heart keeps calling out for you♪
♪It's just you and there's only you
that my heart is yearning for♪
♪I don't know since when,
but now I love you with all my heart♪
Tin, can I sleep with you tonight?
Maybe it'll help me
to forget that I lost today.
Someone like Tin if he gets a
fair-skinned and handsome guy by his side.
I'm sure they will be so cute.
Angel and fairy should be together.
Job.
Does a handsome guy
have to be with a handsome guy only?
A handsome guy
should be with a pretty girl.
Why all the girls think that good
looking people should just be together?
Can you ask Tin for me
if he has a girlfriend or not?
Can!
♪Do you hear the
sound outside the window?♪
♪The sound of thunder scares me♪
♪Can I hold your hands to calm my heart?♪
♪Stay with me until the rain stops♪
♪I don't know what to do if you walk away♪
♪Let me please you forever♪
♪I will do everything
to make you stay by my side♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night
without you?♪
♪You know that I like the way you hug
and the way you say I love you♪
♪Just whisper the words in my ears♪
♪I can't barely stand the thought
of you leaving me♪
♪Can you stay with me a little longer?♪
♪Stay with me until the rain stops♪
♪I don't know what to do if you walk away♪
♪Let me please you forever♪
♪I will do everything
to make you stay by my side♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night
without you?♪
♪Can you see the rain?♪
♪I can feel the pain♪
♪Stay with me until the rain stops♪
♪How do I get through the night
without you?♪
♪Can you see the rain?♪
♪Let me please you forever♪
♪I can feel the pain♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night
without you?♪
♪Please stay a little longer♪
♪Please stay for a while♪
♪Hug me tight and never let go♪
♪How do I get through the night
without you?♪