Be my boyfriend, my spoiled prince.
Be my boyfriend, Cantaloupe.
I don't understand how he can be your friend.
Tin likes me.
He just feels sorry for you.
Can and I…
We are…
Spill your secrets to me right now!
You want to know, right?
Watch this.
Do you know now who his boyfriend is?
You…
Can…
And Tin.
You guys are boyfriends?
Wow.
I don’t know if I should call you crazy
or call you brave.
Congratulations.
Wow.
Can.
You’re awesome.
My friend is the best.
Kissing in the middle of the field.
Pond will hear about this.
That's right.
Tin and I are boyfriends.
Is that clear?
Let’s go.
What just happened?
Can.
Tin and Can are boyfriends?
What’s going on?
♪I used to tell you♪
♪That we could never be more than friends♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪This time, you won't be sad♪
♪We will get through it together♪
♪From now on, let me take care of you♪
♪Tomorrow or whenever, our love will be everlasting♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
I don't know how I will ever face them again.
What have I done?
I'm glad that you like me so much that you'd do such a thing.
Hey!
I don’t like you.
I just ran out of patience.
You’re my boyfriend.
Lay can’t ship you with someone else.
Why are you smiling?
If you don’t like me a lot,
then you won’t be this jealous.
I’m not.
Why are you laughing?
You should comfort me.
I told you to comfort me.
There, there. It's okay.
My sugar baby.
I’m still amazed.
Not just you.
I’m still in shock.
Can is so brave.
We should give him a round of applause.
They must really love each other.
That’s why he dared to do that.
I want to laugh when I think about it.
Dude.
Is it that nice to have a boyfriend?
Are you saying that…
No! It’s nothing!
You’re overthinking.
I’ll go then.
What the hell?
I was going to ask if he envies them.
Why is he acting suspiciously?
Why am I thinking about him?
Maybe I’m just lonely.
I don’t think so.
Shit! I just called him!
Hello, Techno.
I dialed the wrong number. I have to go. Bye.
Damn it.
What’s wrong with myself?
Sorry, there is no acknowlegement from your requested number.
Pond.
Do you know what happened at the field that day?
I don’t know.
How come the nosiest person like you doesn’t know about this?
Exactly.
The nosiest person like me doesn’t know about this.
That’s why I’m so angry with myself.
It's about Can and that guy from the English program.
How can I not know about this?
Is my gossiping skill declining?
I know now that's why you're so grumpy today.
How about him?
Ae!
Do you know what just happened?
He knows everything but he never tells me.
I had to ask every member in the football team instead.
I know that Can pulled Tin for a kiss.
Everyone in the university already knows that.
My friends from the English program said all the girls are heartbroken.
Including me.
The students from the English program know about this too?
Everyone in the university knows.
Where have you been?
I missed the chance to be the first one to spread the gossip.
You’re too slow.
Ae.
What are you doing?
You’re choosing a photo again?
Yes.
How long are you going to do this?
I’ll keep doing it.
There’re 365 days in one year.
Will you post 365 photos?
If he’s not here for a year, then I’ll post 365 photos.
If he’s not here for two years, then I’ll post 730 photos.
I’ll keep posting it.
I want him to know that I’ll never stop loving him.
You guys are so serious.
I’ll go to the next class first.
Take care of him.
Make sure that he’s okay.
Noon and Jane are waiting for me.
I’m Bow. My name is Bow and I’m going to find Noon and Jane.
Wait for me, my friends!
Since when did she have new friends?
Hello, Ae.
Can I talk to you?
How do you know me?
Before I answer your question,
let me introduce myself first.
My name is Keen. I’m a student from the Faculty of Music.
Are you Tharn and Type’s friend?
Well, yes.
I know Tharn. We’re in the same faculty,
but we chose a different major.
What do you want from me?
I’ll get straight to the point.
I wonder why you always post a photo every day?
Some photos seem to have no meaning.
Some photos have a short caption.
I know that it’s rude to ask about your private life.
But I’ve been following you for a while now.
I’m very interested in what you post.
I feel like you’re telling it to someone.
It's none of your business.
As I told you that I’m a music student.
I got inspiration from your posts.
I want to tell your story through a song.
I’m not interested. You should find someone else.
Wait.
Listen to me first.
I can do it in my own way. I don’t need help.
Don’t you want to tell that person more than just a few words?
A song can say things more than words.
This song can express your feelings for that person.
Anyway.
I just want you think about it.
I’ve got to go.
Are you okay about this?
You don’t like to deal with a lot of people.
Apart from Keen, you have to talk with his bandmates as well.
You’re right.
Then why are you still…
You know why.
I can do everything for Pete.
Ae...
I want him to know.
Since the day that we broke up,
there's not a day that goes by that I don't miss him.
If there’s anything that I can do
even if I don’t like it, I will do it.
Techno.
What happened to you?
You look like you haven’t slept for ages.
Because of your friend, Can.
He’s been playing with Technic at my house.
He's there for about four days already.
They usually stop playing at around 2 or 3 a.m.
He wouldn’t leave no matter how many times I told him to go.
That’s why I look like this.
Why does he have to stay at your place?
I don’t know.
He wouldn’t tell me anything when I asked.
They will meet up again tonight.
I want to run away from home.
What the hell?
Shit!
Lay!
What are you doing here this late at night?
You scared me.
I should be the one who asks you.
Why are you sneaking around?
How many days already that you come back home at this time?
Well…
Oh right!
I was planning the strategy with Tehcno.
I also went to sleep over at Job’s house.
I’m so sleepy.
I’m going to bed now.
Let’s talk tomorrow.
Ouch! That hurts!
I mean to hurt you.
How long do you think you can avoid me?
Well…
Many days.
So, you and Tin are boyfriends, right?
Tell me.
If you lie to me,
I’ll stab you.
Fine.
I’m sorry
that I disappoint you.
Why do I have to feel disappointed?
You said that you want Tin to be with a handsome and rich guy.
The one who's perfect for him.
But I never said that I’d be against your relationship.
Also, you are my brother.
If Tin already chose you,
then there's nothing I can do.
Are you actually on my side?
Of course.
If dad and mom are not on your side,
I'll be the one who supports you.
Also,
your boyfriend is Tin.
Don’t let him slip through your fingers!
Okay.
I feel at ease now.
I’m going to bed.
Also,
don’t try to avoid me ever again.
Someone like you can’t hide away from me.
Don’t let that knife slip through your fingers.
Shit!
Lay!
It’s you again?
It should be me who said that.
What are you doing down here? I'm going upstairs now.
You can go first. I’m hungry. I’ll find something to eat.
Wait.
Stop.
I’ve got this.
Don’t eat snacks.
Here.
This will improve your skin health.
Your skin will become more resilient.
You'll also get plump skin.
Why do I need to care?
I’m hungry.
I want to feel full.
This will make you full, and it won’t make you fat.
Your boyfriend is Tin.
You should make yourself look better too.
Don't eat snacks.
I know.
This is yummy.
It'll be great if my skin is bouncy
because Tin likes to kiss my cheeks.
I don't want my cheeks to be damaged.
Is it bouncy now?
Tin.
Lay didn’t kill me.
I was really stressed out.
I was avoiding her.
But she wasn’t angry at me at all.
If I know this, I won't waste my time finding a place to sleep.
Whose house did you go to?
Come on.
Don’t be mad.
I was hanging out at Techno’s place
and playing games at Job’s house.
I went back home after Lay went to bed.
Come to my place next time.
I don’t want to.
Your house is too far.
You'll have to drop me off late at night
because there’s no bus around there.
I can't go back home if I go to your house.
But I’m okay now because my sister won’t kill me.
Fine.
I think I'll buy a room.
Why do you have to buy it?
You already have a house and a car.
Why do you need to buy it?
So, we can do something more convenient.
Are you talking about dirty stuff?
That’s right.
It’s not convenient at home.
Why not?
My mom is okay that I sleep over at your place.
If you’re bored, you can come to my house instead.
My mom doesn't mind.
If I go,
do you think that they won’t know
that we…
You’re right.
If my mom hears me making sound…
That's creepy!
She'll barge through the door.
But Tin,
are you going to buy a room just because of that reason?
Prince Tin is extraordinary.
Not just that.
I also want to have freedom.
Then...
Why do you want to buy it after we’re together?
I wanted to exist in that house before.
Don’t worry.
Don’t mind them.
You have me now.
If I meet your brother,
I’ll punch him in the face.
Don't go back on your words.
Trust me.
I’m a man of my word.
(Personal Information)
It’s time for your brother to meet him.
What’s the matter?
About the internship.
I already told your brother that you can’t do it.
Let’s talk about this when the university tells you to do it.
Then why that asshole…
Why my brother can do it but I can’t?
You and your brother are not the same.
What’s the difference?
We’re both a Medthanan family.
Your brother will be responsible for everything after me.
Not you.
Why are you saying like I’m not your son?
I never said that.
What if I ask to live somewhere else.
It’s up to you.
I can see from your face that you didn’t get what you want.
I told you before. You can't do it.
You told dad, right?
Why do you say that?
There's nothing I can do if dad already made the decision.
There’s something that you can’t do?
There’re many things that I can’t do.
Like…
Bringing back my little brother.
That will never happen.
Don’t forget to introduce me to your friend.
Damn it.
That little brother is gone.
That stupid brother
does no longer exist.
Tul.
You have to believe me.
I didn’t use those drugs.
Everyone thought I’m a bad person now.
But I didn’t do it.
I don't care if others don't believe me,
but you have to.
You have to believe me.
Dad and mom hate me now.
But I don’t care.
As long as you believe me.
Of course, I believe you.
Because I’m the one who made you like this.
What do you mean?
This is not funny.
Do you think I’m joking?
I’m the one who put you in that party.
I’m the one who told the news reporters to go there.
I’m the one who put you on the front page.
I’m the one who ruined your life.
I don’t believe it.
You’re kidding me, right?
You’re drunk, right?
I told you not to drink.
It’s not good for you!
How long are you going to be this stupid?
I never loved you.
I want you dead since the day you’re born.
If there’s no you, your mom, and your grandmother,
then I won’t have to live in this shithole.
Now I ruined your life too.
I hate you!
You can hurt anyone
but not the one that is important to me.
You can’t hurt Can.
Hello.
I want to know your master’s weakness.
We made a deal already.
Tell me what you know.
I can’t tell you that.
Don't you remember what I told you?
When you came to see me last year,
I promised you that I would help you every way I can.
I will do everything that you tell me.
But there’s one thing that I ask of you.
I will never do anything that causes harm to Tul.
I will never betray Tul.
Even he chased you away from home?
That's right.
He’s not as bad as you think.
You’re the only family he has.
Do you think I believe that?
He didn't chase me away.
I was the one who walked away from him.
Calm down, Vadee.
What am I going to do?
What should I do?
I have something to tell you.
I’m pregnant.
I’m pregnant, Tul.
You already have a family that you wish for.
Thank you for keeping your promise.
Thank you for not finding me.
I want you to be happy.
That's all I ask.
You’re the world to me.
Tul.
Hello, Can.
Are you awake?
I’m going to pick you up.
I just woke up.
Where are we going today?
Where do you want to go?
I can take you anywhere you want.
I want to go to your house.
I miss your chef’s cooking.
Also, I want to do a movie marathon.
I’m not sure if my brother will be at home or not.
It'll be great if he is. I'll deal with him myself.
Do you think you can do that?
You’re underestimating me.
Come and pick me up now.
I don’t want to fight with you over the phone.
Okay. You should take a shower then.
I’ll finish in three minutes. Bye.
Tin.
The car is ready.
Okay.
Where is he going?
You mean Tul?
He goes to Vadee’s house.
He will stay there tonight.
He told me not to wait for him.
Can!
Go grocery shopping for me when you're coming back.
Mom…
Can I not buy them today?
I can’t remember what to buy.
Also, I don’t know what time I’ll be back.
Why don’t you ask Lay to do it?
She said she had to study for her exams.
I have to study too.
But you’re going to hang out right now.
How do you know that?
Maybe I’m going out to study.
You don’t have any fever.
Mom…
How can my sweet Cantaloupe know how to study?
You always fall asleep when you're studying for exams.
Mom.
You should look at your son in a positive way.
This is called accepting the truth.
You'll never find any mom who is as kind as me.
I can still smile when you fail the exam.
Anyway,
don’t forget to buy me all of this.
Here’s the list.
You can go now.
Tin is here to pick you up.
I wish that I can have a handsome son like you.
Hello.
This is for you.
Thank you, son.
You’re handsome and kind.
And look at my son...
He won't stop complaining just because
I ask him to go grocery shopping.
Let’s go.
I have to come back early to buy these groceries
for my beloved mother.
It's a lot.
Can he come to sleep over at my place tonight?
Huh?
About this.
Don't worry.
I’ll ask someone to buy it for you.
How can you do that?
My mom asked me to buy it. I have to go by myself.
It’s okay.
Calm down.
If Can goes with you, then I'm not worried.
I trust that you will keep him on the right track.
You guys can go now. Don't waste your time here.
Good bye.
Don’t make that grumpy face.
Alright!
I wish that I can have another son like Tin.
Maybe you already have him for a while.
Oh, my Buddha!
You scared me.
Why are you sneaking up on me like that?
Do you know that my mom is always talking about you?
She never gives me what I want.
Isn’t that great?
It can be useful.
I’ll let you ask my mom for me instead.
You said that we won’t come here.
Or do you want to do something with me?
Can!
Stop acting like you don't want to.
I can see it in your eyes.
It’s a good idea.
Because I also miss…
Ouch! That hurts.
If you already know that, then don’t run away.
Someone like me never runs away.
Fine.
Let’s go inside.
Who’s coming?
Tin.
Who’s that?
That’s your asshole brother.
You’re Tin’s friend, right?
My name is Tul.
I’m his brother.
Nice to meet you.
What’s up?
I’m glad that I finally get to meet
my brother’s important person.
You’re such a douchebag.
Tin!
Don’t mess with him.
Tin, I haven’t…
Get inside.
Tin.
Please.
Wait for me inside.
He’s so naïve.
Don’t mess with him.
I'm warning you.
Is he home?
He said he would kill someone at your house.
Excuse me.
Tin!
Should we talk?
Tin told you that I framed him about using drugs, right?
This is...
Where did you get these photos?
I talked to your brother.
Then there's nothing left to talk.
Tin!
Can you stop being silly?
You believe him, right?
You hate me now, right?
♪It was an accident that I met you♪
♪It was an accident that I didn’t care♪
♪It was an accident that I think you’re not important♪
♪It was an accident that our eyes met♪
♪It was an accident that destiny brought us together♪
♪It was an accident that I’ve got no one,♪
♪and you suddenly walked right into my heart♪
♪I accidentally fall in love with you♪
♪What am I supposed to do with my feelings?♪
♪Should I let go of my feelings?♪
♪I should let my heart lead the way♪
♪Whatever happens, happens for the best♪
♪Whether it’s an accident or intention♪
♪It happens for the good♪
♪Whether you speak it out loud♪
♪or express your feeling through your eyes♪
♪It’s still love no matter what♪
♪It might be a coincidence, or it might be luck♪
♪Should I step forward, or should I give up?♪
♪But I already love you so I’ll go for it♪
♪I accidentally fall in love with you♪
♪What am I supposed to do with my feelings?♪
♪Should I let go of my feelings?♪
♪I should let my heart lead the way♪
♪Whatever happens, let it happens♪
♪I already love you with all my heart♪