How was your day today?
How was it?
Well, then, shall we talk?
Tell me a little about yourself.
Who you are, and so on.
Do you know who this is?
No?
It's your family.
Want to have a closer look?
Never mind.
Can you tell me about that day?
About what happened?
I'm sure you remember it quite well.
Don't worry.
From now on,
you can talk to me
about whatever you wish.
Aren't you coming?
Soo-yeon.
Soo-yeon!
It's so pretty.
Give me your hand.
And the other one.
What is it?
Soo-mi!
Welcome home!
It's been so long.
You've changed so much, Soo-yeon.
You've gotten prettier.
But I'm really disappointed in you.
I waited all day for you two,
cooking and cleaning the house.
Why didn't you say hi to me first?
What did you do? Did you play outside?
Were you at the wharf?
You should've changed first
before you went outside.
You guys are so…
Anyway, welcome back home.
Did I startle you?
I see you've gotten better.
I'm so glad you feel better now.
You take after your mom.
You're feeling a lot better too, right?
Right, I bet you're both tired.
Get some rest and come down for dinner.
I'm cooking a special feast for you.
But you have to give me some time, okay?
There's a lot of dishes to prepare.
We just got back.
Things don't look so good right now.
It wouldn't help much if you came.
Yeah, I know.
I have to go. Let's talk later.
You're doing okay, right?
Did I tell you?
Sun-kyu and his wife are coming over.
It'll be all right. I'll take care of it.
Okay, bye.
Listen,
I invited Sun-kyu and his wife
over for dinner this weekend.
Really?
I thought it'd be nice for them
to see the girls after so long.
And to catch up on things.
That was delicious.
Sorry, I have things to tend to.
You must be tired.
You can clean up tomorrow.
Did you set out
your father's undergarments?
Thank you, but that's my responsibility.
And cleaning my room is my job.
So why'd you touch my stuff?
I didn't. It was like that before.
So all those clothes
were hanging there already?
I don't want to have dinner with him.
What?
I said I don't want to have dinner
with that guy.
He's not just some guy, he's your uncle.
Let's not argue today. You just got here.
-And you?
-What?
Aren't you going to follow your sister?
What did that woman say to you?
If she ever gets on your case,
then tell me.
And don't ignore it like before. Okay?
Good night.
What's wrong?
Bad dream?
Was it the closet?
Then what is it?
I keep hearing strange noises.
It's because you've been away so long.
It's okay. Get some sleep.
Somebody came into my room.
He's asleep.
-I know.
-Why were you trying to wake him?
Why would I?
You were trying to wake him just now.
Did you have something to tell him?
It's none of your business.
I just meant that, since he's fast asleep,
don't wake him up. Understood?
I just came down for some water.
Just be quiet. Don't wake him up.
Did you check my room?
Yes.
Who was it?
That woman.
Our stepmom?
Yeah.
You know… it's strange.
What is?
That woman is strange.
And so is this house.
Are you scared?
Everything's gonna be all right. I'm here.
Come here. Let's go to sleep.
I'll always be with you.
Soo-yeon. Go away.
Are you awake?
Yes.
-May I come in?
-No.
Breakfast is ready. Come down.
What are you doing?
Are you on your period?
No, Soo-yeon is.
Soo-yeon?
That's funny.
How could we both get our period
on the same day?
Soo-mi.
It's okay, get up.
That was mom's favorite, huh?
Do this.
Shall we kill them?
Let's set them free.
She'll have a cow
if we mess with her precious little birds.
I'd hate to see that.
Soo-mi.
What are you doing out in the cold?
Are you all right?
Why?
You don't look so good.
Are you feeling sick?
No, I'm okay.
Tell me what's wrong.
I said I'm okay.
Just get rid of Soo-yeon's closet.
Soo-mi, we agreed
not to talk about that closet.
You promised, remember?
Soo-mi…
I know you're mad at me.
And I know I've been a bad father.
You're worse than a bad father.
It's cold, let's go inside.
Not now.
What are you doing?
You scared me.
When did you come in?
-Did you go to the warehouse?
-Yeah.
Soo-yeon, look at this.
Ta-da!
Wow!
-Cool.
-Pretty, huh?
-Yes. Is it Mom's?
-Yup. And, look.
There's more.
It's Mom!
Taritakoom, taritakoom.
What does that mean?
It's a spell to call Mom.
Who told you that?
Mom did.
What?
Mind if I keep this?
Sure.
This.
And this.
Wait!
What's this?
Who did this to you?
Tell me, who did this?
It's okay, tell me.
Was it her?
It was her, wasn't it?
Soo-yeon, what's wrong with you?
I told you to tell me
if something happened!
She did this, right?
Right? Did she do this?
Tell me!
What?
How can you be so cruel?
It's retribution.
If you disobey, you need to be punished.
Does Dad know what you did?
You think your father can help you?
Go get him, then. Want me to do it?
Sit down! Where are your manners?
-What would you mother say?
-Don't talk about my mom.
Listen carefully.
I'm your mother now, got it?
As much as you hate it,
I'm the only one in this world
you can call mother, got it?
Crying over your mom's photos
won't change anything.
Hard to handle, isn't it?
That's too bad. That's how the world is.
The world isn't as sweet
as you picture it.
Sometimes you have to bear the worst
and live on.
Like the way I'm bearing you two!
Tough, isn't it?
I have tolerated you brats
from the moment I came to this house.
I have never met
such ill-mannered menaces like you two.
What?
Why the hell did you even come here?
I can't believe you said that to me again.
I guess you're still sick.
Don't touch me.
-Let me go!
-What's wrong with you?
Are you that blind?
Don't touch me with your filthy hands!
Soo-mi, listen to me.
I don't want to hear it.
You haven't changed.
That's not true, and you know it.
You must try and accept this.
Why is it always me?
Why should I be the only one
to understand things?
Are you really that clueless?
Yes, maybe I don't know.
I don't have all the answers,
so tell me and get it off your chest.
Tell me!
Will it change anything? Will it?
Soo-mi, you…
Don't do this. Please don't.
You'll get sick again.
What?
Fine.
From now on,
whatever happens in this house…
all the filthy things you brought here…
take responsibility for it all.
I'm done talking.
You can answer the phone now.
Do you remember?
My memory's a bit blurry,
but I'm sure it did happen.
When was it?
Hey, remember this?
You jumped into the river
to catch some fish.
Then you started to drown,
and everyone had a fit.
There was another funny story.
What was it?
Oh, yeah, I remember.
Remember that crazy guy?
The funny thing is that
there was never anything wrong with him.
But whenever it rained, he went nuts.
While ploughing the field,
he'd strip off his clothes when it rained,
and run out into the highway.
The funniest time
was when it rained off and on.
So he'd take off his clothes
and put them back on, again and again.
Then he got sick of it
and just went into his house.
Everyone in the neighborhood
laughed so much back then.
But when he was little
he saw him doing that once,
and then he ran together
with that crazy guy.
Our mom saw that
and she almost passed out.
Do you remember that?
You remember, right?
Say something.
Don't you remember?
You remember, right? You must remember.
No, I don't remember.
What?
I said I don't remember.
Why don't you remember?
Are you crazy?
Mi-hee!
What is she saying?
Wait, hold on to her.
-What's wrong?
-Calm down.
Bring some water.
Are you all right, Mi-hee?
Here. Water.
I will hold her.
Calm down.
It's okay.
It's all right, Mi-hee. It's all right.
Please calm down, Mi-hee!
I'm sorry, Mi-hee.
I didn't want to go,
but Moo-hyeon begged me to,
so I had no choice.
Honey.
Yes?
I saw something strange in that house.
What did you see?
There was a girl under the sink.
Just go to bed.
-Can you stay with me?
-Why?
Something's strange.
What's strange?
It's strange.
After the girls came back, weird things
have been happening in this house.
Don't be silly.
Didn't you see it?
You're just having a hard time adjusting.
Get some rest.
No.
There's something in this house.
I'll look around. You lie down.
Open the door!
Open it!
Let me out!
I'll show you.
Get up.
Get out of bed.
Get out now!
I said get out.
Come here, now!
You little brat.
Tell me.
A person can't get any rest in this house.
Who did that to the photos? Tell me.
Who did it?
Tell me the truth.
Was it Soo-mi?
I'll teach you both a lesson.
Was it your sister?
So you like looking at
your dead mother's things, huh?
You like looking at her photos?
Say you're sorry.
I'm not gonna let you out of there
until you apologize.
There's no use in crying.
Say you're sorry and beg for forgiveness!
Sorry.
What?
I didn't hear you.
I'm sorry.
I'll ask you once more.
Do you admit you're wrong?
Stop crying.
I don't want to hear it, so stop it now!
Are you…
Are you mad?
Is that why you're crying?
Fine, let's see how long you hold up.
This will put some sense into you two.
Soo-yeon.
Soo-yeon!
Soo-yeon, I'm sorry.
I didn't hear you.
I'm sorry, Soo-yeon. I'm sorry.
I'll never let it happen again.
Never again.
Don't cry, it'll be okay.
Tell me.
What?
Why the hell are you doing this?
Tell me why you've been acting so strange
since you got here.
You really don't know?
Don't know what? What is it?
I'm talking about
what that woman is doing to us!
So tell me what she has done!
She keeps harassing Soo-yeon.
What?
Didn't you hear me?
I said she keeps harassing Soo-yeon!
She's vicious, evil,
and locks Soo-yeon up in the closet!
Soo-mi, please stop it.
Stop what?
You know Soo-yeon is scared of her.
Soo-yeon, why don't you tell Dad?
Stop crying and tell him now.
Tell him!
Enough!
Soo-yeon is dead.
What?
No.
Soo-yeon is dead.
So pull yourself together.
How long will you keep this up?
It's not true, Soo-yeon.
Soo-yeon…
Soo-yeon, no…
I can't do it alone.
Can you come here tomorrow?
Hmm…
She's getting worse.
Call me when you get there.
I'll pick you up.
Soo-mi, I'll be back soon.
Make sure you lock up.
Soo-yeon!
-Soo-mi!
-Soo-yeon!
Soo-yeon.
Soo-yeon…
I'm sick and tired of your family.
So sick and tired.
How did we come to this?
Don't you get it?
Remember what I told you before?
I said you'd regret it someday. Remember?
You know… what's really scary?
You want to forget something…
You want to erase something
from your memories…
But you never can.
It'll never go away, you see.
And…
And it follows you around, like a ghost.
Help me.
Sure, I'll help you.
Let's end it here.
Soo-mi!
Where's Soo-mi?
Where is she?
Please stop it.
I'm tired of this.
Take this, you'll feel much better.
Soo-mi!
Don't you get it?
You're just having a hard time adjusting.
I guess you're still sick.
We agreed not to talk about that closet.
How could we both get our period
on the same day?
Soo-yeon is dead.
No, I don't remember.
Soo-mi, are you okay?
It's all over now.
You'll feel better here.
Get some rest.
I'll come and visit often.
Take care of yourself. Bye.
Soo-mi, what's wrong? Let go.
Let go, Soo-mi.
Please stop it. Let go of me.
-No, I'll get it.
-Let me take one.
Mom.
Soo-yeon!
Soo-yeon.
Mom!
Mom…
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Did you hear something?
What are you doing up here?
Dad's not here.
What do you mean by that?
Stop acting like you're my mom.
Do me a favor.
Stay out of our lives.
Can you get out of the way?
I have to go.
You might regret this moment.
Keep that in mind.
What can be worse
than standing here with you?
When you're here, I want to be
as far away from you as I can.
Do you get it now?
Soo-mi.
Soo-mi!
Help me. Soo-mi…
Soo-mi…