SEOUL, KOREA
Happy birthday!
-Surprise!
-Happy birthday to you
-Happy birthday, dear Pim
That wasn't funny.
You scared the daylights out of me.
I hope you enjoyed yourself.
Wee, have some cake.
Thank you.
Wee.
He's not fat yet.
No, he's not, but he's diabetic.
I'm sure a bite won't hurt.
Just a bite?
Lucky!
So cute!
-Lucky.
-Is that your name?
Wee calls you Lucky, doesn't he?
You like to solve problems on your own.
You have to learn to confide in others.
So let's turn over the last card,
shall we?
This card tells me
that something you lost
is about to return.
Did you lose something?
The cards say that you may get it back.
No, nothing.
In that case,
it might not be an object.
Have you ever broken a promise to someone?
Maybe that person will come to you
to argue about it.
Yeah.
Don't believe what Jiho says.
She predicted that I'd find my soulmate.
But I'm still single.
Don't be so picky then.
Well, if I were pretty like you,
I'd have a handsome boyfriend like Wee.
It'll sting a little.
Aren't you used to needles by now?
Just a little.
There, all done.
-I'll be right back.
-Okay.
Hello?
Just a second.
Pim, telephone.
Pim!
Is there something urgent?
Pim isn't available right now.
What?
What is it?
Pim,
that was a hospital in Thailand.
Your mother had a stroke.
Should you fly back right away?
If I didn’t move here,
everything would've been fine.
Pim, are you feeling okay?
Here.
I don't want to go back home.
Ever since Ploy died,
it hasn't felt the same.
Do you think it was selfish of me
to drop everything and move here?
Of course not.
But if I didn't insist
on us being separated,
Ploy would still be alive.
Pim,
I already told you.
Her death wasn't your fault.
Nobody expected that to happen.
Your mother is paralyzed
and unable to speak.
The hemorraging
is putting pressure on her brain stem.
We'll have to wait
for her condition to improve
before we can perform surgery.
Mom.
-Mom.
-Excuse me, Pim.
I think we should
let your mother get some rest.
You can wait outside.
Go inside.
Pim.
That was Ploy's favorite song.
Ploy.
Excuse me, ma'am.
If you don't need anything,
I'd like to go home for the day.
Don't you stay here?
No, ma'am.
You're welcome to stay here if you'd like.
So you don't have to commute.
No thank you, ma'am.
It's best I go home.
Wee!
-Wee!
-What is it?
What's wrong?
Wee.
Mom.
What's wrong, Mom?
What's the matter?
-What is it?
-Excuse me, ma'am.
I need to give her some shots.
Noi.
What happened that day?
Why did Mom pass out?
I don't know, ma'am.
Have you noticed anything strange
about her behavior?
Noi.
Well,
I don't know what was wrong with her.
She liked to stay in her room
and cry all day.
Sometimes
I had the feeling
that she was afraid of something.
Afraid of what?
Doctor, how is her condition?
It's rapidly deteriorating.
I think we should operate tonight.
Oh, shit.
Excuse me, ma'am. Ma'am?
Are you okay?
Pim,
are you tired?
Why don’t you go home and get some rest?
I'll stay and wait for the results.
I'm fine, Wee.
She's no longer in critical condition.
But she's still in a coma.
When will she regain consciousness?
I can't say at this time.
It also depends on her spirit.
Lucky!
Lucky.
What is it?
Pim?
Pim! Open the door, Pim!
Pim!
Pim, what happened?
What happened to you?
You're all set.
Pim,
what's going on?
Why did you hurt yourself?
Pim.
Why don’t you tell me what's wrong?
I saw my twin.
What do you mean?
I feel like she's still here with me.
I don't understand.
How could you see her?
Ploy's dead.
Forget it.
It must be the stress.
Pim.
I think you should see a specialist.
Wee.
There's nothing wrong with me.
-How are you doing?
-I'm fine.
I haven't seen you in ages.
You've changed a lot.
Really?
-Have some coffee.
-Thank you.
Pim.
This is Danai. We went to school together.
-Hello.
We were really tight
before I moved to Korea.
We haven't seen each other
in what? Ten years?
Yeah, about ten years.
It's been a long time.
How did you end up meeting again?
Wee called me up
and invited me over.
How is your workload these days?
It's a bit hectic. I still teach.
And I've got too many patients.
Which medical field do you practice?
I'm a psychiatrist.
Excuse me.
Pim.
Do you think that I'm crazy?
Hear me out.
Pim.
Open the door. Pim, listen to me.
Pim!
Lucky!
-Lucky.
-Pim!
From the brain scans,
everything appears normal.
I'm going to ask you
to look at some pictures,
and then I'd like you to tell me
what picture it is that you see.
Shall we start?
Batman.
My answer means that I'm crazy, right?
If I said "butterfly,"
then you'd consider me normal.
Pim,
seeing a psychiatrist
doesn't mean that you're crazy.
Anyone could experience
the same condition you have.
And with time, it can be treated.
Wee is really concerned about you.
He can't stand seeing you like this.
Can you tell me about Ploy?
We promised each other that
we would stay together forever.
Blow them out.
Hey, look at them!
Why did you decide to get separated?
That's enough for today.
I'm going to prescribe some medicine.
It's no use, Doctor.
You can't help me.
From what I can see,
she's suffering from a mild psychosis.
People with this condition
can't distinguish
between fantasy and reality.
Compounded by her feelings of guilt,
and you have a delusional state.
Can it be treated?
Of course. It's not hard to treat at all.
All you have to do
is take her back to Korea.
But it looks like
we'll have to stay here awhile.
We don't know
when her mother will recover.
In that case, why don't you
try a change of scenery?
It might help.
Have some. I've bought plenty.
It's all your favorites.
Try to eat a lot.
I'll help feed you.
There, isn't that tasty?
Everything looks tasty.
Pim, have a bite.
Pim!
Pim.
What's wrong, Pim?
Pim!
Pim.
What should we do?
She followed me.
Pim didn't get better.
I'm going to have to take
her back quickly.
That's probably the best solution.
Hey.
Don't call me a fool.
But do you believe
what they say about twins?
That if one twin dies,
the other one will die soon after.
Pim told me that
Ploy is coming to take her life.
Wee, it's a matter of belief.
It's possible
that twins share a subconscious bond.
But personally speaking,
I attribute it to the attachment
that the living twin has for the dead one.
Wee.
Is something wrong?
No.
I thought you were at the hospital.
I went out to buy you some food.
Come down and eat.
Judging from the patient's condition,
I wouldn't recommend
moving her to Korea.
It would be risky.
I think we should monitor
her condition for a while longer.
-Thank you, Doctor.
-Yes.
You'll have to excuse me.
Yes, Doctor.
VEJ BAMRUNG HOSPITAL
Thank you.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, what's wrong?
Pim.
Wee. I saw her again.
I saw her again.
How can I get rid of her?
Pim.
What you are seeing
is a figment of your imagination.
Take Mickey Mouse for instance.
We can picture him,
but we can't really see him.
If our brain is confused,
what we imagine in our heads
can be transformed
into a perceived reality.
The reason you keep seeing your twin
is because you can't let go of her.
You told me that you see her
in mirrors, right?
Take a look.
Now,
tell me what you see.
Look at Wee.
Pim.
Wrap it, so it won't get infected.
Pim!
Ploy.
Please take this.
So that was why you decided to separate.
Pim,
even Chang and Eng
wanted to separate at one time.
Two people conjoined for life,
it's normal to argue
every now and then.
But our fights got increasingly violent.
And Ploy didn't want us to be separated.
Did you ever feel like Ploy
was a burden to you?
No, I never felt that way.
Pim,
there's nothing wrong
with wanting to live your own life.
But I...
I caused her death.
Once you stop blaming yourself,
you'll stop seeing the image
of your twin.
Pim.
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Which finger is it?
-Forefinger.
-Yes! Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
No, it's not true.
It's not true.
Did you buy it?
Yeah.
Lucky.
Lucky, come here, boy.
-Lucky.
-Pim, that's not Lucky.
I'll talk to them
and see if they can do anything.
Hold on a second.
Noi.
Take the dog away.
Yes.
I'll get back to you later.
Pim.
The hospital in Korea
has approved the transfer.
We can go home now.
Hey!
Pim.
Do you remember the picture
I drew for you?
Did Ploy destroy it?
Ploy...
Ploy! Don't!
Don't, please.
You two got separated
because of me, right?
I hate you!
I want to be separated.
How come you never told me?
What did you want me to say?
That I chose you over Ploy
and allowed her to die?
Ploy! Don't!
Mom!
Oh, no.
Split them out.
Pim was fine.
Wee, do you know...
that Ploy loved you all along?
Pim,
I believe
that you actually saw her.
But without scientific proof,
I can't say if what you saw
was real or not.
Our brain is a complex
and mysterious organ.
What you've been seeing
is merely an illusion.
-An illusion in your mind--
-Stop it, Doctor!
Just shut up! How many times
must I tell you she's here?
She's still here!
Pim.
-10 o'clock then.
- Okay.
-Thank you.
-Hey, where's Pim?
Oh, I thought she was with you.
Pim.
Wee, help me, please!
Help me.
Pim!
Pim.
What's wrong, Pim? It's just me.
Wee.
Pim,
it's okay. We're going back to Korea.
Let's go to the hospital.
Wee.
Pim, don't worry
I'll have your mother transferred tonight.
Wee!
Where's the doctor?
Is something wrong?
I need to transfer this patient tonight.
Please remain calm.
Please page the doctor for me.
I'll page him right now.
What is it, ma'am?
Take a look.
Now,
tell me what you see.
In the mirror,
I see Ploy.
PIM WATTANAKUL
21 JUNE 1975 - 12 SEPTEMBER 1990
Wee, did you know
that Ploy loved you all along?
Wee.
Mom is dead.
Wee, where have you been?
How come you're soaked?
How did she die?
Her condition has improved dramatically.
You can have the hospital in Korea
contact us about the transfer.
I don't know either.
I didn't think her condition
would worsen so quickly.
It's a good thing
she talked to me before she died.
What?
Afraid of what she might have told me?
This belongs to you, right?
Are you surprised?
Ploy.
What are you talking about?
Please stop lying to me.
I went to the temple.
What happened to Pim?
Tell me how she died, Ploy.
Let go!
Ploy is dead, Wee.
Ploy,
why did you do this?
No.
My name is Pim.
My name is Pim. My name is Pim!
What happened to Pim?
Or did you...
Did you do something to her?
We can't keep living like this.
Let's get separated.
No. I want us to be together
until we die.
Why are you doing this?
Do you know?
You're a burden in my life.
No, I'm not a burden!
I'm not.
Ploy, let me go.
Let go of me.
Pim.
Pim!
Mom!
Mom, help!
-Mom...
-Pim.
I didn't mean to.
How could you?
She was your sister.
You've lied to me all along.
Tell me why, Wee.
I'm exactly like Pim.
Why couldn't you love me?
You're pathetic.
Think about the time
we've been living together.
Doesn't it mean anything?
Aren't I the person you said you loved?
This isn't yours.
Wee!
I never thought
it would end this way.
Everyone loved Pim.
When she died,
Mom refused to speak to me.
She treated me
like I was a repugnant person.
I loved you just as much as Pim did.
But you only had eyes for her.
The letters you wrote to her,
I pretended were written to me.
The only way I could make you love me
was to transform myself into Pim.
All the letters you received
were written by me.
So how can you say that you love Pim?
The person you love is me!
I feel bad for Pim
because I'm the one
who received all of your love.
Are you in much pain?
Just hold on.
You hated it so much, didn't you?
Why couldn't it replace your old dog?
Why not?
When they're both exactly alike!
Excuse me, ma'am.
I forgot my cell phone.
Where is it?
I'll get it for you.
I'm not sure.
It might be
in the kitchen.
Wee!
Where are you?
Come out right now.
Or else I'll burn the house down.
Come out!
Shit!
PLOY WATTANAKUL
21 JUNE 1975 - 22 JANUARY 2006
PIM WATTANAKUL
21 JUNE 1975 - 12 SEPTEMBER 1990