♪♪
[Elizabeth] Em? Darlin'?
[inaudible]
♪♪
- [horse snorts]
- Get.
[inaudible]
[grunting]
[straining, coughing]
[panting]
[woman coughs]
Kill me. Kill me.
[breathes shakily]
[woman coughs]
Now, don't you worry, girl.
[shudders]
I will accommodate you.
[woman sobbing]
- [woman coughing and gagging]
- [gun cocks]
[grunting]
[muffled shouting]
[muffled] No!
[shouting]
[grunts]
[horses whinny]
♪♪
[fire crackling]
I often ponder the depths of your loyalty.
- Prove me wrong.
- [sobbing]
Say your name, girl.
Say your name.
[woman crying]
[exhales sharply]
[breathing shakily]
It brings me no joy to do this.
[woman whimpers]
- [grunts]
- [woman groans]
- [belt cracks]
- [woman sobbing]
Silence!
You will speak only
when I instruct you to speak.
[sobbing]
I am responsible for you now,
and I will tame your savage ways.
[whimpering]
- Now, get up.
- No, no!
- Come on.
- [sobs]
Say your name, girl.
- [grunts]
- [groans]
- Comply!
- [sobbing]
[thuds]
You've given me no choice.
Now, please stand up for me.
[sobbing] No, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
[sobbing continues]
Your friends are dead because of you.
You know that, right?
Try to escape again,
I'll drag you to the burn shed myself.
- [flesh sizzling]
- [screaming]
[crying]
Now, let's try this again.
Say your name, girl.
[sobbing] Eden. Eden.
Say your name with pride and conviction!
[sobbing] Eden. My name is Eden.
That's good, Eden. Real good.
Everything will be
all right now, and, uh...
you can stop that cryin'.
[grunts]
Maybe I can get away for supper tomorrow.
You can make us a chicken.
[door opens and closes]
[sobbing]
♪♪
- [rumbling]
- [distant guns firing]
♪♪
[horse whinnies softly]
Y'all seem easily distracted.
[guns firing in distance]
Why don't we break up this monotony
and get y'all focused?
[firing continues]
Go on, sing us somethin'.
Perhaps one of those old Negro tunes.
[soldier laughs]
[workers whistling tune]
[whispering] We need to move.
These fuckers is crazy.
[grunts]
[shushes]
Next time, I won't be so generous.
[bomb exploding in distance]
Back to work. All of you!
Let the sound of Confederate victory
bring joy to your labor.
[distant firing continues]
♪♪
[knocking]
- Milk, chicken.
- [softly] We must try again.
- [man 1] Get down. Get down!
- [man 2] Get off there. Come on.
- Get off the wagon.
- [man 1] Move! Get out of here!
[man 3] What you lookin' at?
Line up. Come on!
- [man 1] Hurry!
- [coughs]
[man 3] Line up! Get over there.
Eden! Get your ass down here, girl!
Separate yourself. Turn.
Mm-hmm.
Look at her hair.
Quite a beauty.
Shall we name her, child?
Mm... Let's name her Julia.
Hmm.
You hear that?
Those are worker hands.
You're dismissed.
[Jasper] Well...
Welcome home, one and all.
- [breathing heavily]
- Now, listen up! All of you.
This here is a reformer plantation
commandeered by the Ninth Infantry
of the Confederate Army of the 13 states.
Wherever you were before,
whatever small freedoms
you might have enjoyed,
I'm here to tell you, that's over.
I don't tolerate any backtalk
whatsoever from inferiors.
In fact, on this plantation,
you will only speak
when given permission to do so.
That means...
absolutely no talking among yourselves
unless one of the white folk
on property...
[men chuckling]
...gives you permission to do so.
If you do...
Oh, we will know about it.
Over here, you will find your cabins.
You will also be given instructions
by one of the overseers
as to your daily duties,
which ought to be followed obediently...
and with a smile.
Here, we whistle while we work.
Ain't that right, Eli?
Raise the flag, Corporal.
The general will be home this evening.
- You're dismissed.
- [man] Get.
Go on. Walk, now.
Get on. Let's go, move.
- [softly] Hey, what is this?
- [whispers] Quiet!
[man] Go, now!
Mm. You started early.
[horse whinnies]
♪♪
- [knocking on door]
- [gasps softly]
[floorboard creaks]
When?
- [knocking on door]
- [breathing heavily]
[floorboard creaking]
[whispering] How many...
Get in here.
[Julia] You're from Virginia, right?
I'm from North Carolina.
Look, I can't do this.
Whatever you're doin',
- I can't do it.
- [thuds]
Listen to me.
Wherever you came from before here,
- you need to forget about it.
- Mm-mm.
That is not possible for me.
- [men shouting in distance]
- [coach strolling]
What are we doin'?
Huh? What is the plan?
You think I haven't tried?
♪♪
We must choose our moment wisely.
But until then,
we keep our heads down
and our mouths shut.
Do you understand me?
I know you.
And I know that you
are my only way out of here.
I'm pregnant.
[horse whinnies in distance]
I need you to listen to me.
You have to keep quiet.
These white people will kill you.
Oh, you think being quiet
is being strong, huh?
What has that ever gotten us?
You ain't no leader.
You're just a talker.
Ain't that right, huh? [chuckles]
You... Hey!
What, you just a coward nigger slave
with a brand and no backbone?
[grunts]
[soldiers chanting] Blood and soil.
Blood and soil. Blood and soil...
[chanting continues]
[marching footsteps]
[all chattering indistinctly]
[chattering stops]
[Him] As you were.
First,
I want to congratulate you
on our defeat of the Yanks at Milliken's.
This is what victory looks like!
[all cheering]
We got those blue-bellied bastards
on their heels, Washington in our sights.
But we must never relent.
We are descendants of the gods
and we will fight with the same
immeasurable courage and vigor.
We will sacrifice our blood
and fertilize this soil of our homeland.
This is the only hope we have
of retaining our heritage,
our way of life.
This land was always ours.
It is our rightful inheritance.
And, rest assured, our nationalist state
will not be stolen from us
by these traitors to America.
I have faith in this
because I have faith in you.
You all are the future.
And it is you who will lead us all
to the ultimate victory.
But for tonight,
let us put away our troubles.
Drink and be merry.
You've earned it. All of you.
And, by the way,
these Sapphires are here
to fulfill your every need,
whatever those needs may be.
- Faith! Family! Folk!
- [soldiers] Faith! Family! Folk!
As you were.
[chattering resumes]
[Purcell] So, which one
of these girls do you like?
- [Daniel] What?
- Which one of these girls do you like?
[whistles] Hey, angel.
Yeah, you.
Come here. I don't bite.
Come on.
My compadre here was just telling me
he thinks you're real pretty.
[whispers] No, man. No.
What, you don't think she's pretty? Hmm?
No, I mean...
Yeah, of course I do.
Well, then. She ain't gonna say no. Hmm?
Talk to her.
You're in charge here.
Um...
Uh... I, um...
Well, I...
[Jasper] Oh, just...
Fuck's sake.
He will meet you at your cabin
immediately following dinner service.
You're dismissed as of this moment.
- Now, go and prepare for your corporal.
- [exhales sharply]
What's that, girl?
[Julia] Yes...
sir.
That's more like it.
Go on, now. Go.
[sighs in relief and chuckles]
Well, you enjoy, all right?
I'm going around back
to the whipping post.
♪♪
[fire crackling]
- [exhales sharply]
- [Julia] If I may?
- I never got your name.
- Daniel. Um...
It's-it's Daniel.
Well, thank you, Daniel.
For earlier.
You said that I was pretty.
[nervously] Of course you are.
Anyone can see that.
It's, um...
It's just been such a long time
since any man has been nice to me.
I appreciate the compliment is all.
How'd you get to be so sweet?
Look, you don't...
You don't have to do this.
I can tell that you're special.
You're not like the others.
Those monsters.
[breathing heavily]
Why'd you speak to me?
You mean, when your friend
called me over before?
No. Why'd you speak to me
when I entered the room just now?
Uh...
I just thought we should have
a proper introduction.
You have a short memory, then.
You heard Commander Jasper.
You speak only
when given permission to do so.
- Is that not right?
- Yes, sir. Uh...
I mean, Daniel.
[shouting] No. It's "sir"!
[grunts]
You don't know shit!
[whimpering] Okay.
I'm as much a Confederate
as any man here.
[muffled] Because I don't wanna sleep
with no filthy fucking mongrel
instead of my own kind,
that don't make me no...
I'm... I'm a patriot!
You understand me?
- [Julia shouting]
- Shut the fuck up!
Shut up!
You're lucky I don't tell Jasper.
You better make him believe
I had my way with you
if you know what's good for you.
You understand me?
- Get off of me.
- [grunts]
- Uh...
- [groaning]
- I'm so...
- [breathing heavily]
[footsteps receding]
[Julia breathing laboriously]
Well, you're forgiven
your tardiness, this time.
Don't make it a habit,
or the stocks will be waitin'.
- [bombs exploding in distance]
- [horse whinnies]
[guns firing in distance]
[distant firing continues]
[whispers] Are you okay?
[crying] Please...
I know. Be patient.
Just keep goin'.
We have to keep goin'.
[groaning]
[whimpers] Oh, no!
[sobbing hysterically]
No! No, no, no!
- [Julia] No!
- [shushing]
- Oh, no! No!
- It's okay.
- It's not okay!
- [shushing]
- [crying]
- [mouthing]
Cracker!
The fuck you just say, boy?
Oh, I'm gonna be right back for you.
[clicks tongue] Hyah.
[Julia groaning]
- What the fuck is the issue?
- She's sick, sir.
[crying hysterically] Oh, no...
Oh... Go on. Go get yourself cleaned up.
May I go with her?
She can handle herself. Get back to work.
- Sir...
- [sobbing continues]
[Jasper] Oh.
Fine. Go clean her up, get back here.
[Julia coughing]
[distant firing continues]
Take hold of him.
[softly] It's okay, boy.
[horse whinnies]
Now...
What was that you were sayin'...
boy?
♪♪
Oh.
You missing your woman?
[guns cocking]
Give me an excuse.
Go on.
No.
Why, that reminds me,
the shed needs cleanin'.
Too many foolish Negroes
with rebellious hearts.
Yeah. Go get that cleaned up, boy.
That should stop you flappin' them gums.
Yes...
sir.
Yes, sir.
Go on, get.
[whispers] Cracker-ass cracker.
[door creaks]
[crying softly]
[moans]
[continues sobbing]
[crying hysterically]
♪♪
- [Him grunting]
- [bed creaking]
[Him grunts]
[panting]
[sighs]
Sweet dreams, Eden.
- [crickets chirping]
- [owl hooting]
[cell phone vibrating and ringing]
[gasps]
[ringing continues]
[vehicles honking distantly]
- Good morning, Steph.
- Good morning, V.
Just making sure
you're ready for your flight.
Skype is at 8:45, and the car
will be there at 9:00.
- Oh, shit. Okay. All right.
- Okay.
- Thanks, Steph. Bye.
- Safe travels.
[groaning]
Another bad dream?
No. I'm... I'm okay.
Babe? [moans] Can you please
do me a favor?
Anything.
Can you get Ken Ken dressed for me today?
Of course. Mm-hmm.
My first meeting is right here
in Georgetown
and it got pushed to 11:00 anyway, so...
Okay. Yeah, I don't know...
how I'm gonna even be
dressed before 9:00.
- I got you. I got you.
- Thank you, babe.
But would it be the worst thing
in the world
if you didn't make it?
[chuckling]
[grunting playfully]
[Veronica] Not today. Not today.
- [gasps] There she is.
- [Kennedi exclaims]
My favorite girl.
- [smooches] Guess what?
- What?
Daddy is gonna get
you dressed for school today.
[gasps] I know exactly
what I want to wear.
- [Veronica] You do?
- [blows raspberry]
- [Kennedi] Hurry up.
- I'm comin', girl.
She said "Hurry," Daddy.
- I'm hurryin', I'm hurryin'.
- Hurry up.
You're gonna pull my arm off.
Okay, okay, okay.
What you wearin' today?
[winces]
♪♪
[Veronica] Well, look at you two.
- [Nick] Look at you.
- [Veronica gasps]
- Mommy loves that dress.
- [Kennedi giggles]
[smooches] Excellent choice, baby.
Yeah, she picked it.
- Hi, babe.
- You stay trendin'.
- [Veronica sighs]
- Paused it for you.
I understand you think you are defending
the plight of the black man.
I guess, in your case,
the black woman.
But we are doing a disservice
to the argument, much less your people,
by conflating race
with basic common sense.
[Veronica on video]
I would say this.
The disenfranchisement
of black people in America
is by design, written
into the actual DNA of this country.
Your argument, however flawed
has been successfully promoted
and propagated through repetition.
We hear it over and over again.
But I'm here to tell you
that this vicious cycle of inequity
will soon be broken.
- [both] Boom!
- Boom!
- [Nick] Boom!
- [Veronica chuckling]
Mommy, why was that man so angry?
Oh, baby, that is a really great question.
[sighs]
Sometimes what looks like anger
is really just fear.
Things are not always what they appear
to be, baby. Does that make sense?
Do you remember when Vanessa
was bullying you at school?
She was pickin' on you?
And Mommy had to come up there
because Vanessa thought
that you were gonna come in class
and take all of her toys away?
And now you two are like best friends.
- So, are you two friends yet?
- [Nick snorts]
[breathes deeply]
- [Nick chuckling]
- Not yet, baby.
Mommy's working on it.
♪♪
Pancake?
Pancake? On a Tuesday?
What is the special occasion?
Well, I was informed
it was pancakes or nothing, so, you know,
- we gotta pick our battles.
- [chuckling]
Um, question, are we vegan this week?
Babe, the struggle is real.
Got it. So, one non-vegan
pancake coming up.
Babe, no. I cannot.
[groans]
[Skype ringtone playing]
Elizabeth?
[Elizabeth on speakers]
Yes. Dr. Henley.
Hi. And please call me Veronica.
[chuckles]
- How are you this morning?
- Oh, I'm fine.
That lipstick just looks
lovely on you.
It suits your skin tone.
I don't think I could pull it off.
[light chuckle]
So, do you have any questions for me?
How-how did you come across my work?
Oh, I saw you on one
of those legacy media networks.
I believe it was a roundtable
discussion about inclusion.
You were so articulate.
It must have been a ratings bonanza.
Those particular segments
do garner a lot of attention.
I don't mean to be curt, but do you have
any questions around the book?
Oh. Your book.
Yes, I believe you mentioned it
on that show that you were on.
As a matter of fact,
I know you mentioned it.
'Cause I thought it was rather odd
that you chose that moment
to be peddlin' your wares.
Well, actually, that particular segment
focused on the lack of inclusion.
And that is exactly
what my book highlights.
Intersectionality of race,
class, and gender.
I wrote
Shedding the Coping Persona
as a roadmap to revolution
for historically marginalized people.
Maybe I didn't catch this earlier,
but who did you say you were with again?
I didn't mention it.
I'm a bit of a talent scout.
Oh. So you're a headhunter.
That makes sense.
I'm a headhunter.
[laughing]
Exactly that.
Oh.
Now, is that Kennedi?
Will you move the camera over?
Oh. She's so cute.
She'll make a perfect little companion
for my daughter.
- I see a playdate in our future.
- [honking]
As my assistant mentioned earlier,
I am short on time this morning.
Oh, no problem. I didn't
mean to trigger you none.
You have fun at your summit,
and I'll see you soon.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
[sighs]
- Who was that?
- Oh, baby. It's nobody.
Don't worry about that woman, okay?
Okay.
- [car horn honking]
- That's my car.
I can't even imagine
what y'all are about to get into.
- Obviously.
- Mommy, wait.
- I'll call you. I love you.
- I almost forgot. This is for you.
Oh, baby.
- This is for Mommy?
- [Nick gasps]
Ken Ken, I'm putting this
with all my important work.
When you look in the sky
and you see that big airplane,
you'll know that's Mommy,
comin' home to you.
- Wow. That's a big head.
- Daddy. Come on.
- [Veronica laughing]
- It's not that big.
And I'm gonna hang it
on my wall in my hotel.
[Nick] Yeah.
[Veronica sighs]
- Daddy.
- Yes?
Twenty minutes of screen time.
- Okay.
- [knocking on door]
- I need you to be strong.
- We got you.
- [door opens]
- [Veronica] Be good.
Mommy loves you. Come here.
Come here. Kiss.
[smooches repeatedly]
Give Mommy all the kisses.
- One minute.
- I'll be back, baby.
I'll be back. Okay, okay.
- I love you, baby.
- Bye. Love you, babe.
- All right.
- All right, be safe.
I love you.
I'll be back, baby.
Love you more, Mommy.
- [door closes]
- [airplane whirring]
♪♪
[instructor] Okay. Release.
And as we begin to gather
our thoughts for the day,
I want you to focus on
bringing positivity and light
to each and every situation
you may face today.
- [exhales]
- Visualize yourself
addressing any obstacles you might face
with the same determination and focus
that you brought to your practice today.
See yourself emerging successful
and victorious on the other side.
Namaste.
- [Veronica] Namaste.
- [knocking on door]
[Dawn] V! V, girl,
I got some tea.
You better open this door
and let me come and spill it.
Positivity and light, right?
- [knocking continues]
- V!
I'm coming!
- No, no. Faster!
- [chuckles]
I'm coming, I'm coming,
I'm coming, I'm coming.
[both screaming]
- Hey. How are you?
- Hey, babes!
- Good mornting.
How is the number one
relationship specialist...
- True.
- ...in the world
doing this mornting, doll?
Well, you know...
Ooh, it's hot. Just flourishing.
You know, being amazing
and fantastic as per usual.
- You're looking sharp. Yes.
- You know how I do. Thank you.
Oh, hello. Why is it
so goddamn hot in here?
I'm trying to create
my own version of Bikram.
You know I need
all the balance I can get.
Well, speaking of balance,
I saw you balance and tag
that ass last night on TV, girl.
- [chuckling]
- You got him all the way together.
- Bye.
- Bye. Thank you.
Okay. Before we get down to it,
how is my favorite
little human in the world,
- Miss Kennedi?
- [door closes]
She's great. She's doing good.
Yesterday was tough, though.
It was tough.
I just... [sighs] Ugh.
It breaks my heart every time
I have to leave her.
Mm. Ken Ken.
I just feel like I'm not doing enough.
It's like when I'm at home,
I'm not working enough.
When I'm working,
I'm not home enough.
I'm not Mom enough.
I'm not wife enough.
Mm-mm, mm-mm-mm.
Okay, you listen to me now. Okay?
Yes, you're a superwoman,
but you're also a human woman.
Okay? And you are doing awesome.
And Miss Kennedi,
or as the world will one day refer to her,
Madam President,
is living her best life
thanks to you, okay?
So be nicer to yourself, please.
- Thank you. I love you.
- Mm-hmm. I love you, too.
- [exhales deeply]
- Now...
[pops tongue]
So, Camille's hostididy ass, right?
- You, girl... Camille was in the...
- Oh, girl. Babe, I can't. I can't.
I... You know I usually would,
but I have to get to this walk-through.
I'm already runnin' behind.
No, I get it. You're too good
for it today.
- [laughs]
- No, I get it.
You tryin' to namaste
in a peaceful space.
And I'm about to ruin that,
so let me just see myself out.
[singing] ♪ I love you,
I love you I love you ♪
You're welcome for this free coffee.
I paid $74.93 for that.
- No, you did not.
- I will Cash App you.
- Stop. All right.
- I will. I will. I will.
All right.
And I wanna remind you
to be good to yourself, okay?
- Be kind to yourself.
- All right.
- Be kind to my friend.
- I will.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
All right, I'll see you downstairs. Bye.
- [sighs]
- [knocking on door]
Girl.
Ms. Henley?
- Yes?
- Delivery.
Oh.
The front desk didn't even call.
Who are these from?
♪♪
- [gasps]
- [Sarah] V! Oh, my God.
Sarah Bee!
I'm so sorry. I did not mean to scare you.
It's okay. I have just been
so jumpy this morning.
I guess it's travel or something.
Okay, I love you,
but I have to run to my panel
"The Exorcism of the Unconscious Past."
[gasps] Ah. "The past is never dead."
"It's not even past."
You know, my nana used to say,
"Our ancestors haunt our dreams
to see themselves forward."
The unresolved past can certainly
wreak havoc on the present.
Listen, have an amazing panel.
You're gonna be incredible.
- I'll see you later, girl.
- I'll see you tonight, babe. Love you.
Hi.
Can I please make a reservation
at Stefano's tonight?
- [phone ringing]
- Concierge.
Of course. Working on it as we speak.
What can I do for you?
May I make a reservation
for three at Stefano's?
Um, let's say around 7:30.
And I'm in the Jefferson Suite.
Sure.
God bless.
♪♪
[Elizabeth] Oh, shoot.
Puddin', I left my key in the room.
Do you mind?
♪♪
[audience cheering]
[Veronica] You know,
I learned very quickly
that black people,
black women in particular...
were expected to be seen, not heard.
Or we risk being perceived
as threatening to the patriarchy.
Or, God forbid,
we continue to get branded
as the "angry black woman."
[audience] Yes.
So, the coping persona
has been this mode of survival
for generations of oppressed people.
What I also learned
through those experiences
is within our authenticity
lies our real power.
[audience] Yes.
And that's even in those environments
which, by design,
demand our complete
and total assimilation.
To the patriarchy, we've
been practically invisible.
But their arrogance is
their greatest vulnerability.
And our greatest opportunity.
[audience] Yes.
And it brings me to a quote
by Assata Shakur.
"The only thing that we have to lose
- are our chains."
- [applause]
Liberation over assimilation.
They're stuck in the past.
- We are the future.
- [audience] Yes.
Our time is now.
It's now.
Right now.
Just a reminder, you can pick up
Shedding the Coping Persona
on your way out.
Twenty percent goes to HBCU schools,
including Louisiana's own Dillard
and Southern Universities.
[all cheering]
[Camille] The way that you
talked to them, the nuance,
and there's a specificity
that I just can't...
[Dawn] Oh, my God.
That was fantastic.
So sorry. That was
really great, you know.
I really enjoyed my session,
but I'm really glad I stayed for that.
- Wasn't that fantastic?
- [Camille] It was.
- [Veronica] Camille, this is...
- I'm sorry, did I interrupt?
- [Camille] No...
- [Dawn] I'm gonna continue to.
I really have to steal her.
Sorry to be abrupt.
- [Veronica] I'll call you.
- [Camille] Okay.
- [Veronica] Thank you again.
- I'm just gonna finish up work
and get back to... Bye.
- [Veronica] Thank you, love.
- [Dawn] Great. Bye.
- Hey.
- You're welcome.
Girl, I could feel her angling in
on our dinner tonight, and no thank you.
She needs
to go sit down some place.
Plus, we could use
a break from academia.
And also, how often do I get my V?
Twice a year?
- Maybe three times a year.
- I know, I know, I know.
Okay, I need you
all to myself tonight. Okay?
- [chuckling]
- No filter. Full Dawn.
Oh, she comes with a filter?
Also, after dinner...
Yeah. You know,
when we leave dinner, it's on.
We gonna be out in
these streets body rolling.
- Oh, dinner. Tonight?
- Yes.
I'm sorry, but I have a date
with my king bed tonight.
I won't be joining.
- [laughing]
- Whack. Wow.
No. I have a 6:00 a.m. flight.
I promised Ken Ken I'd take her
to Katie's birthday party.
Okay. All right. It's fine.
We will keep you abreast
of all of our hoetivities via text anyhow.
Please do. I wanna know everything.
Girl, the hoetivity
is gonna be popping tonight.
Girl, meet me down here at 7:00 p.m.
- We'll Uber over, okay?
- Yes, 7:00 p.m.
And I have to go get dressed.
Oh, speaking of getting dressed,
what are you wearing tonight?
Do not come down here
in mom jeans, okay?
I need all eyes on our table
'cause I'm tryin' to fuck tonight.
You are on board for that, okay?
I won't disappoint. Bye, girl.
[exhales deeply]
Well, hi. Don't you look beautiful?
Are you going to the 49th floor, too?
Shh.
You'll get in trouble for talking.
I'll get... Oh, I'll get in trouble
for talking? Okay.
Shh.
[elevator bell dings]
♪♪
Okay.
[exhales]
[lock beeps]
[door creaking]
[elevator bell dings]
["Calling" by Quin playing]
You rang, darling?
Girl, I said "step it up,"
not murder these hoes.
Mm-mm.
[Dawn laughing]
[Sarah] Okay. Here's a new concept,
what do you think?
Instead of a "fuckboy,"
it's an "inti-mate."
[Dawn] Okay, I love everything about it.
[Sarah] It's someone
who's gonna feed me ice cream
and knows how to soothe
my childhood trauma.
[Dawn laughs] It doesn't sound
like you need to take a Plan B
with that guy at all.
An inti-mate...
I just want somebody
to snuggle me at night.
- That's all I want.
- You deserve.
- Is that so much to ask?
- [Dawn] You can call me.
- You're a great snuggler.
- [Dawn] I am a great snuggler.
[Sarah] Oh, my God. [laughing]
What are you smiling at? Who's that?
[Sarah] Well, you know it's Nick.
Let's see. Dick pics or no?
- [both] Aw.
- Yeah.
See, here I thought marital bliss
was an oxymoron.
Guys, I can 100% confirm that Nick
is not that perfect. Trust, okay?
- But he is kind of perfect for me.
- Yeah.
- Ugh. Girl, she ruined it.
- There it is.
I thought there was tea coming.
- [retches]
- I miss my babies, okay?
- [Sarah] I'd miss him, too.
- [phone chimes]
[all laughing]
[Dawn, as Veronica]
"I miss my baby.
- Oh, he's so perfect for me."
- [Veronica] Please, guys.
[Dawn] "He's so perfect for me.
He's my lobster.
He's the Chandler Bing to my Monica.
He fits perfectly in my little box."
"Like a puzzle piece."
[Dawn and Sarah laughing]
[Dawn in normal voice] Yeah, no,
we're very happy for you, bitch.
- All right. Time to live in the present.
- Okay, babe.
- Yeah.
- Okay, okay.
[horse grunts]
[Dawn] Damn.
- Oh, my God. Okay.
- Shit, are you okay? Holy...
[Veronica] Hi.
Henley for three, please.
We have your table. Follow me.
[people chattering indistinctly]
- [Rebecca] Enjoy your dinner.
- [Dawn] Uh-uh. No, no, no, no.
Sorry, I think what my friend
is trying to say is that...
Actually, babe, I got it.
This table is 100% not acceptable,
and I think that you know
that, don't you...
- [Rebecca] Um...
- [Dawn]...Becky? Mm-hmm.
Listen, I'm actually not gonna go
back and forth with you
about exactly why
this table's unacceptable.
You're gonna seat us over there.
[Rebecca] Oh, um...
[loudly] Thank you so much, Rebecca!
You're doing great!
Yo, get your sis. The Caucasity!
- [Sarah] No, this is good.
- Well, then you're welcome.
- [waiter] Welcome.
- [Veronica] Hi.
- Wine list. Hi.
- Thank you.
My name is Sam. I'll be taking care
of you this evening.
- Will a fourth be joining you?
- No, just us.
Very good. And may I start
you off with a cocktail?
Actually, we will share
a bottle of champagne.
How about a nice bottle of prosecco?
A bottle of Armand de Brignac,
please. Thank you.
[Sarah] Okay, but more to the point,
do you have any apt prospects
for the night?
[Dawn] Mm.
Booked and busy, actually. [laughing]
Actually, okay, so there's this, um...
Ooh, I've been trying to set up
a meeting with this guy, Justin.
Fine. Just like a dark chocolate,
like a 72% cacao, you know?
Just... [smooches]
Chef's kiss.
- [Veronica] Is he fine?
- Yes, he's fine.
- Mm.
- And he's got a friend.
- [Sarah] For me, a friend?
- Yeah, for you.
- Mm. A friend?
- Mm-hmm.
I don't know. That sounds
sort of suspicious.
Like, it can't be good. I feel like you're
leading me into the snake den with this.
[Dawn] Girl, I'm sure he's fine.
- [Sarah] You're sure?
- [Veronica] Oh, my God.
- You're sure he's fine?
- You haven't even met him?
- No, I haven't met him.
- [Sarah] Nope.
This is exactly
what is not happening.
- I am too grown for this.
- It's not...
Okay, you're too grown. No, got it.
I feel blocked. I do.
And that's okay.
'Cause you're grown.
That's cool. It'll just
be you and me tonight
and I will meet up with fine-ass Justin
some other time.
And maybe his friend, too.
[Veronica] Hey. [exclaiming]
Okay. Do not look.
There is a guy at the bar...
[whispers] I said don't look.
...that has been staring at us
the entire night,
and it's creeping me out.
[Sam] Excuse me, ladies.
Before we order entrees,
I wanted to let you know
that the gentleman at the bar
sent this drink specifically for you.
[both] Oh.
Specifically for me.
[whispers] Oh, my God.
He's coming over here.
And he's coming this way.
[chuckles]
[Veronica] Okay, all right.
[man] Pardon me, ladies.
I've had my eye on you.
I just had to come by and tell you
that I think you're quite stunning.
[Dawn chuckles]
Oh, thank you. Oh, gosh,
I'm so flattered, thank you.
- You are extremely handsome yourself.
- Thanks.
However, um,
I'd be remiss if I didn't take the chance
to sort of critique your game
just a little bit.
I'm sure that you can tell,
even from all the way over there,
that we're actually
drinking champagne tonight.
I am a champagne lady,
and we are champagne ladies.
So, sending over a vodka-cran, yeah,
it just shows lack of appreciation
for our situation tonight, so...
Well, what you should have done is,
you should have asked our waiter,
which, again, champagne we're drinking,
and sent over a second bottle
of it for all of us.
And then, you make eye contact
with me from across the room.
- You eye-fuck me.
- Oh, my God.
And I say all that to say...
- Oop, here's my number.
- [man chuckling]
Because this can happen.
Good night.
Oh. [softly] Why did you do him like that?
You know why I did him like that.
He needed to know.
Okay, I'm sorry,
but can we just take a second
to acknowledge that that guy
was supernaturally fine?
Yeah, he was really cute.
So? I'm cute, too.
- [Sarah] That's true. You are cute.
- Yeah.
Hey, to being cute and classy.
- [Veronica] Yes. To being cute.
- [Dawn] To being fine as fuck.
[all laughing]
Well, I definitely look forward
to catching up on this saga.
On a group text, in my bed.
[Sarah] Very safe move.
Wait. Although,
this hotel has been so off.
The front desk.
They didn't clean my room.
So, I'm not even holding my breath
for turndown service.
It's probably a mess.
Really? That's so strange.
My service has been impeccable.
I got the Uber, but I can't
believe we're splitting up.
- I know. I'm so sorry.
- [Dawn] Oh, no, no, no.
Before we split up,
we have to take a selfie.
- [Sarah] Oh, yes.
- [Dawn] Let's get a picture.
Because it did not happen
if it didn't happen...
- You are right about that.
- ...in a selfie.
Where's my lipstick?
- Girl, you look fine.
- Your lips look fine.
No, but I put it in there.
- I could've sworn.
- Come on, come on.
- Okay.
- Get ready and...
- [camera clicks]
- All right, that's it.
- [Veronica] Tag me in that.
- Yes, guys!
- [Dawn] One-take wonders. Everything.
- [Veronica] I love y'all.
- Thank you so much.
- [car horn honks]
One moment.
- Love you.
- I love you.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Get home safely.
- I love you so much.
All right. I hate I have to go.
I have to get home to my baby, though.
[Sarah] Say hi to the family.
All right. Love y'all. Watch her.
- You watch yourself.
- All night.
- Watch her.
- You're gonna be in trouble.
- [Veronica] Bye.
- [Dawn and Sarah] Bye.
Goodbye. Is this our car?
- This is us. Let's go.
- [Dawn vocalizing]
["Warm Leatherette" by The Normal
playing loudly on radio]
The Montgomery Hotel, please.
I think I put it in.
And do you mind turning
that down just a bit?
Thank you.
♪♪
First off, that we are some 5-star ladies.
- [laughing]
- Aren't we, sister?
And I just wanted to comment
that you look like a 5-star gentleman.
- Don't touch him.
- Is that too much?
- I know.
- I wanna have five stars.
- It's too much.
I feel like that was too much.
I shouldn't... I'm sorry, Gus.
I'm so sorry, Gary.
Hey, put your...
Can you turn that up?
- ["Warm Leatherette" continues]
- [phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [woman] Hello, Veronica?
Who is this?
[singing along with the radio]
♪ Blame it on my juice ♪
- ♪ Blame it, blame it on my juice ♪
- Come on, alto.
♪ Ya-ya eee ♪
Wait, hold on, yo, hold on.
♪ Ya-ya-hold, ya-ya-hold ♪
This is Autumn, your Uber driver.
- Oh, there must be...
- I'm outside of Stefano's.
Yeah, there must be a mistake.
I'm in my car right now.
- I'm outside the restaurant.
- No, there's a mistake. I'm here now.
- Okay, whatever.
- Thank you.
Ma'am, do you mind turning down
the music, please?
[loudly] Hello!
Turns out, this color
does look nice on me.
[screaming]
- [man grunts]
- Help! Help!
["Juice" by Lizzo playing
under "Warm Leatherette"]
♪♪
[muffled screaming]
[thuds]
[cell phone ringing]
- [cell phone ringing]
- [gasps]
[door opens and closes]
What do you want? It's 3:00 a.m.
The arrangements
are already being made.
Now, look, the ballot box will go our way.
The court will follow one way or another.
It's under control.
Is there anything else?
Oh, really?
If I see her pathetic husband
on the news one more time
parading around that little girl...
Mouthy darkies are a plague.
I'll take care of it.
I said I will fucking take care of it.
[whimpers softly]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Him] Eden?
Eden?
[strikes match]
They will never take you away from me.
[floorboard creaking]
[stomps]
[creaking]
♪♪
[muffled whimpering]
[muffled screaming]
[screaming echoes]
What'd I say?
[horse neighs]
What the fuck did I say?
I told her yesterday she got one pass.
Now she thinks she can come down to
the fields whenever she goddamn pleases.
Well, she will learn her lesson today.
Girl, go get her.
[Eli] I can head up there, sir.
Who gave you permission to speak, boy?
[softly] I gave myself
permission to speak.
♪♪
[mouthing]
[softly] Tonight.
[softly] We go tonight.
♪♪
[whistling "Lift Every Voice and Sing"]
[continues whistling]
[horse neighing in distance]
♪♪
[wind howling]
[horse snorts]
[exhales deeply]
[breathing heavily]
♪♪
[whispering] I'm here.
[horse neighs]
[softly] No, no, no...
[breathing heavily]
[whistling "Lift Every Voice and Sing"]
- Are you ready?
- Let's go.
[softly] Wait. Wait.
Well, I'll be damned.
[Daniel and Purcell laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
[laughing]
- You're killing me, man.
- Hey, dude, what the hell?
Hey, is this yours?
No, Purcell, you know I know
the rules, man. No cell phones.
- You fucking cuck.
- No cell... What?
Don't say my fucking name
out here, Daniel!
I'm sorry.
I don't fucking want it.
[Daniel] All right.
[both laughing]
[Purcell] You should have seen your face.
[snorts]
[Daniel] Yeah, I'm mad.
I mean, she's talking to me all the time.
[Purcell] Well, no, you gotta
stick up for yourself, all right?
- [Daniel] I know.
- You can't expect every...
- [rustling]
- [Daniel] What was that?
[Purcell] Well, it came
from that direction.
♪♪
Fuck! [laughs]
Man, you scared the shit out of me.
Oh, what is it?
The spooks got you spooked?
It's nothing, man.
There's no one out here this late.
Look at that moon, though. Beautiful.
Yeah. Well, enjoy it, snowflake.
[Daniel] Fine, you traitor.
[Purcell] Yeah, yeah, write
about it in your diary, Romeo.
[owl hooting]
[chuckles]
[exhales]
I need to piss, man.
I'm gonna take a piss.
Let me get these fucking things off.
[Eli, softly] Daniel.
You're not supposed to say my fucking...
[Daniel choking]
- [Eli] Get the damn phone.
- [Veronica] Got it.
Oh, shit.
Listen, if I don't make it,
the world has to find out
about this place.
It has to end tonight.
I know there's service at the cabin.
Let's go.
[both breathing heavily]
- [beeping]
- [Eli] Come on.
[line ringing]
[operator, breaking up]
911, what's your emergency?
What's your emergency?
My name is Veronica Henley.
I have been kidnapped.
There are so many of us here.
- We're on some sort of plantation.
- I'm sorry, ma'am, you're breaking up.
- I need you to send help right now.
- Did you say "plantation"?
- Hello? Hello?
- [beeping]
♪♪
[sighing]
We need his face to unlock this phone.
That's the only way
we can send our location.
I got you.
♪♪
[Veronica screams]
[Eli yells]
- [Him grunts]
- [Eli groans]
- [Veronica screams]
- [Him yells]
[Him grunts]
[Eli groans]
[Eli grunting]
[Eli grunts]
- [thuds]
- [screaming]
[both grunting]
[groans]
No fuckin' loyalty!
Eden!
[groans]
My name is Veronica!
- [flesh squelches]
- [Him groaning]
[breathing shakily]
Open your eyes, motherfucker.
I said, open your motherfuckin' eyes!
- [Him groaning]
- [panting]
[phone unlocks]
[keypad clacking]
[line ringing]
[Nick] Hello?
- Nick?
- V? V!
[voice breaking] I'm okay. I'm alive.
V, no. No, no, no.
Tell me exactly where you are.
I don't know, but I'm getting out.
Oh, my God.
Everyone has been searching for you.
I can't talk right now.
I need you to call the police, now.
I'm gonna send you a pin.
- Mommy!
- Oh.
- Okay, okay, V. No. No, stay with me.
- [softly] Baby. I love...
- [phone beeping]
- Hello?
[breathing shakily]
Come on. No. No, no, no.
- [phone chimes]
- [breathing heavily]
[sniffling]
♪♪
Professor.
I'm sorry.
[breathes deeply]
[horse chuffs]
♪♪
[Veronica grunting]
[Him breathing heavily]
♪♪
[panting]
[grunting]
[Him breathing heavily]
[Him] This doesn't end here.
We're nowhere...
and everywhere.
[scoffs]
What the fuck are you doin'
out of your cabin?
It's the general, sir. He's hurt.
- Please come quick.
- Wait.
- Come quick. He's hurt.
- [Jasper] God!
[Veronica] Oh, God. Oh.
Jesus Christ. Senator?
Senator Denton! Sir?
Eden! Hey! Eden?
Eden, open this door!
Shh.
[Jasper] Please, open the fuckin' door.
Open the door.
Jesus fuckin'...
- Eden, open this fuckin' door right now!
- [guard] Open the door!
[Jasper] No, Veronica!
Veronica, Veronica, listen to me.
Please. Veronica!
- [guard] What the fuck is she doing?
- [Jasper] Open that fuckin' door!
[Jasper and guard screaming]
[Jasper] No! Get off!
♪♪
[soldiers shouting indistinctly]
- [soldier 1] The hell is that?
- [gun fires]
[soldier 2] Go on, mount up! Let's go!
[birds cawing]
[gun firing]
Get, girl! Get!
Get, girl!
♪♪
[horse neighing]
[groans]
[Elizabeth] Eden!
♪♪
Get, girl!
- Eden!
- [gun fires]
Eden!
You're not gonna get out of here alive.
Now, why can't you just accept that?
Accept what you are.
You are nothin'.
You ain't nothin' but a cotton picker.
You think you're better than us...
but you ain't better than me,
you fuckin' cunt!
- [gun fires]
- [horse neighs and grunts]
- [gun cocks]
- My father kept insistin'.
He said you were spreadin' such filth!
[twig snaps]
I told him you weren't worth the risk...
but he couldn't resist,
the movement be damned!
He just had to have you.
Every single one of you I picked,
except for you.
His favorite girl.
Now, of course, like always...
it's up to a woman
to clean up the mess of a man.
[rustling]
Eden?
- Get your black ass out here!
- [rustling]
[horse neighs]
[snorts]
[gasps]
[Veronica] Get the fuck up.
- [Elizabeth choking]
- Get the fuck up.
Get the fuck up!
[choking]
♪♪
[yells]
[both groaning]
[Veronica screams]
[both grunting]
[screaming]
What kind of woman are you?
[Elizabeth groaning]
[screams]
[panting]
- [men shouting in distance]
- [guns firing]
♪♪
[panting]
[gasping]
Get, girl, Get.
♪♪
[choking]
Go, Daphne. Get, girl.
[breathing heavily]
[guns firing in distance]
[guns firing]
[horse neighing]
["Home Soon" by Vagabon playing]
[breathing heavily]
[gunfire echoes]
[soldiers shouting indistinctly]
[horses neighing]
[screams]
[explosions echo]
♪♪
[sirens wailing]
[inaudible]
["13th Century Metal"
by Brittany Howard playing]