Continuing with the STIC,
or the Standardized Test
for International Colleges,
a general knowledge exam
for students who wish to apply
to US universities.
This year, the body overseeing the exam
discovered that
a cheating incident occurred,
leading to the leaking of exam questions
in many countries throughout Asia.
Further investigation is pending.
It's not mine.
My name is Rinrada Nilthep.
I'm in my final year
at Krungthep Thaweepanya School.
You can call and check my academic record.
The STIC isn't beyond my abilities.
STUDENT RECORD: MISS RINRADA NILTHEP
GPA: 4.00, SEVENTH GRADE,
ACADEMIC YEAR 2011
NINTH GRADE
Straight As since first grade.
Honor student from seventh grade
to ninth grade.
First place in the school district's
mathematics competition.
National Crossword Champion.
And in sports, this one is for swimming.
You don't have to say anything else.
It's enough already.
You don't have to ask anymore
whether or not we want to accept Lynn.
Instead, you need to ask Lynn
whether or not she wants to study here.
What do you say, honey?
I don't have to give my decision
right now, do I?
It's not that I don't want to study here.
I just think my old school
suits me better.
Because if I move here,
Dad will have to pay
almost 150,000 a year.
How did you get 150,000?
One semester is only 60,000.
so that makes it 120,000 a year, right?
Correct.
However, I commute with my dad,
as he teaches at my old school.
If I study here, I would have
to take the Skytrain,
including the motorbike taxi
from the station. That is 80 baht a day.
SKYTRAIN- 50 BAHT
MOTORBIKE- 30 BAHT
Return trips over 8 months,
which is 170 days,
excluding public holidays,
that makes it 13,600 baht per year.
Then there's the cost of lunches.
I get rice with 2 side dishes
for 20 baht at my old school.
Here, it's 35 baht.
Then there's also the cost
of my school supplies
and my new school uniform.
All in all, I think...
it might not be worth it.
NEW UNIFORMS- 1,184 BAHT
NEW BOOKS- APPROX. 875 BAHT
Gold medal in math.
Honey.
I can afford it.
-No, you can't.
-Yes, I can.
What if we waive the tuition fees?
Vit.
And let's include
the free lunch program as well.
I want to show that we appreciate
Lynn's academic abilities.
Is it worth it now?
It's worth it.
Now, it's worth bringing this.
It's worth it, right?
LETTER OF AUTHORIZATION
LYNN
TENTH GRADE
Done.
Wait!
We have to use this ID
for the next three years.
You have to look good.
You're new here, aren't you?
I'm Grace.
I'm Lynn.
-What are you doing?
-Let me have a look.
Take off your glasses.
Trust me.
Wow!
Pretty!
Come on, smile.
Ready? One, two...
Go now.
Quickly. Off you go.
GRACE
Our ID numbers follow each other,
so we have sat together for three years.
Actually, we're really close.
Everyone says Lynn is smart.
As for me, well...
I'm good at extracurricular activities.
Some people might even think I'm dumb.
This term, the headmistress came up
with a new rule.
To be in the school play,
you need a GPA of at least 3.25.
Why? I'm too dumb to appear
in a school play?
I think acting is harder than studying.
Really?
Really.
Look.
I have had tutoring
with Mr. Sophon for weeks,
but I still don't know shit.
And math really pulls my grades down.
The answer is C.
What?
You knew the answer
after only a quick glance?
And upside down, too!
It's super easy.
Union A and B intersect with C.
Do the ones in brackets first.
Then the intersection of C
is just what's left in C.
-That's the answer.
-Yes.
I got it!
Scholarship kids are really excellent.
One more question--
Will you be my tutor, Lynn?
Why not?
If you teach me,
I'll buy you a milkshake every day.
No.
You'll get to review the lessons
every evening.
Not enough.
What if...
If you agree,
I'll get to be your first student,
Teacher Lynn.
Teacher Lynn!
I like the sound of that.
I'll teach you all of this today.
Grace told you that I helped her
with her studies?
That's true.
But there's nothing wrong
with tutoring a friend, right?
It's the time everyone
has been waiting for.
MIDTERMS
Thirteen...
Stop it. Take a deep breath
and clear your mind.
It's crystal clear.
Students, you may begin the exam.
MIDTERM EXAM, MATHEMATICS
MATHEMATICS
60 QUESTIONS FOR 30 POINTS
WHAT IS THE ANSWER
FOR UNION A AND B, INTERSECT WITH C?
WHAT DOES THE SHADED AREA SHOW?
WHAT IS THE SUBSET
OF INTERSECTION A AND B?
WHICH ANSWER IS CORRECT?
Mathematics.
I have warned you before
that it's not easy.
People who knew
that they didn't understand,
but still didn't come to me
for tutoring...
Well, it's too late for them now.
They're out of time.
Grace!
The questions are just like those
on the teacher's cheat sheet.
-Yes?
-You can do it, right?
No.
What do you mean? I taught you already.
I can't remember.
Why are you two talking?
No talking, no cheating.
I won't tolerate any nonsense
in my exam room.
IF X^2 - 13X + 42 = 0,
WHAT IS THE VALUE OF X - 13/2?
51. D
MISS RINRADA NILTHEP
Grace.
The answer.
Should I write my name on the scrap paper?
Of course, you should.
Haven't you taken an exam before?
I'm sorry, sir.
B D C D A A C A C A...
STUDENT REPORT CARD
MISS RUJIRA SAETONG
A 3.87! I got a 3.87!
I got a 3.87!
What did you get? What did you get?
An easy 4.
Are you free tomorrow? Let's celebrate.
Sure. Where shall we go?
How about Pat's place? It's convenient.
You have a swimsuit, right?
Pat, would it kill you
to just get in normally?
I guess not,
but it wouldn't be cool.
Damn! I got water in my ear.
Mr. Pat, dinner is served.
Just leave it there.
Babe, I'm getting cold.
PAT
Are you diving to look for coral, Grace?
I have been asking Grace
to invite you over many times.
We're in the same class,
but we hardly ever talk to each other.
Grace, though...
-She's always, "Lynn this, Lynn that."
-Shut up.
Are you jealous?
Grace always tells us
that you're so smart.
Without your help, Grace's grades
wouldn't have improved.
I have even told her that
I want to have a best friend like you.
I have noticed
that you have a lot of close friends.
I do.
But none of them are that close
that they would lend me
their erasers during an exam.
What is it?
You also want to appear
in the school play?
Smart people like you just don't get it.
But thickheads like me,
we're all dying to get good grades.
Right, babe!
Dad said he'll buy me a new car if I pass.
Sounds good?
I know we aren't that close.
But if you agree...
I'll pay you 3,000 per subject.
Per person.
Per person?
What do you mean?
I have five more friends, you see.
Oh? What if the teachers find out?
Don't worry about that.
All of my friends can be trusted.
And they're all willing to pay 3,000 each.
Think about it. That's for one subject.
How many subjects are there
in each term, Grace?
If you don't count PE...
Thirteen, right?
So, for just one exam,
you'll get 13 times that amount.
That's 234,000 baht.
A nice number, 234,000 baht.
In exchange for your brains.
You can think of it as getting
your school's tea money back.
What "tea money"?
Seriously? You really didn't know?
Everyone has to pay.
The dumber you are,
the more you have to pay.
I had to pay 400,000.
As for him, he donated 20 iMacs
to the school library.
But I got a scholarship.
The scholarship is for studying.
Don't forget your maintenance costs.
RECEIPT FOR STUDENT FEES: 200,000 BAHT
DIVORCE AGREEMENT
MR. PRAVIT NILTHEP
AND MRS. SUJIKARN PHAIBULRUNGROJ
What's gotten into you?
I was going to sell it to buy a new car.
It seems like
you haven't played it in ages.
I just remembered
that yesterday was Mom's birthday.
Why did you want me to move
to this school so badly?
Many students who graduate
from this school
get scholarships to study overseas.
I wanted to give you better opportunities.
Dad, I'm not like Mom.
Have you ever wondered
if I would have been happier
at my old school?
Three points.
Don't make too much noise, okay?
Consider our neighbors.
Come and have dinner.
I'm off to bed.
I admit that I paid Lynn.
But paying your friend for music lessons
can't be against the law anywhere, right?
Or can it?
Are you going to send me
to an international court?
Have any of you ever heard
that classical music
can help with the brain's development?
We'll use four songs
to represent A, B, C, and D.
Memorize the movements of my fingers.
This is A.
When you memorize it,
remember it starts with the pinky
and ends with the thumb.
This is B.
B is 4, 3, 2, 1, 3, repeated twice.
This is C.
And this is D.
I'll give you three answers and skip one.
Then, I'll repeat the pattern.
So, it won't be suspicious.
This will keep the marks low enough
to stay under the teacher's radar.
Answer the other questions yourselves.
I'll start giving you
the answers at 9:15 a.m.
Meanwhile, start answering
the other questions.
FINALS 2013
8:30-10:30 A.M.
A
-D.
D
C
Goodness.
This shirt is expensive.
Getting rich from teaching piano?
It's okay to wear new clothes, you know.
At school, they say
you're a stingy teacher.
Well, I guess a new pair of pants
wouldn't hurt, too.
CLASSICAL PIANO LESSONS BY TEACHER LYNN
More people want to join
your piano lessons.
CONGRATULATIONS TO SCHOLARSHIP STUDENTS
MISS RINRADA NILTHEP, ELEVENTH GRADE
ACADEMIC YEAR 2013
MR. THANAPHON VIRIYAKUL, ELEVENTH GRADE
ELEVENTH GRADE
BANK
Stay tuned. We'll be back in a moment
with another episode of Teen Genius.
The next team is almost ready.
It's true that Lynn and I study
at the same school.
But we're not friends.
Actually, we're rivals.
What's the matter, Bank? Are you nervous?
You had noodles for lunch?
How did you know?
You have some on your shirt.
Your shirt's creased as well.
Here's a baby wipe.
Give it a wipe.
THAI LIFE INSURANCE
5,000 BAHT
Hey! If we win, there's a 5,000 reward!
Actually, we'll get less than that.
It's taxed at 3%, so we lose 150.
So, it's only 4,850, or 2,425 each.
That's still a lot, though.
It's enough for a salmon buffet.
If we really win,
will you go out for dinner
with me tonight?
No.
I don't like eating out.
It's a waste of money.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
It's just that you sound like my dad.
Is that good or bad?
If it's like Dad, I guess it's good.
Messy hair, wrinkled shirt,
you're exactly like him.
What is it? I'm just fixing up your hair.
We'll be on air soon.
We have to look good.
You need to look smart.
Are you ready?
The final question.
Tell me the value of pi with
as many decimal places as possible.
It's 3.1415926535897932--
That should do it!
The winner of Team Genius this week is...
Krungthep Thaweepanya School!
I'm amazed.
How did you work out
the value of pi so quickly?
I didn't work it out.
I just memorized it.
Memorized the value of pi?
As a kid, I enjoyed playing
memory games with my dad.
The value of pi, names of people and dams.
Very smart indeed.
It's fitting that you're one
of our scholarship students.
Come and have a seat.
I didn't ask you to come here
just so I could praise you.
I also have some good news to tell you.
The Singapore Embassy
is offering scholarships.
They're full scholarships,
from bachelor's degrees to doctorates.
In terms of grades, behavior,
and determination,
you're the only two who are worthy
of being sent to take
the scholarship exam.
There's a little problem, though.
This scholarship is only given
to one student per school.
But that won't be a problem, right?
I mean, you were teammates yesterday.
But now, you are rivals. Fun, isn't it?
LITTLE BANK LAUNDRY SERVICE
The machine's not working again.
I can't finish the laundry in time.
MATHEMATICS
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
Your hands are all calloused.
It's understandable
that you think I cheated.
But thinking that Bank cheated as well...
Apart from my father,
I have known no one
more hardworking and honest
than Bank.
Bank!
What's wrong, Tong?
Did you finish studying for the exam?
I'm just like you. I got sick
and didn't get through it all.
I'm like you in every way,
like I told you.
Then finish studying.
Help me, man.
GRADE 11 ROOM 2
Let me copy.
I really can't fail this time.
I tried. But this piano code is too hard.
What piano code?
Nothing. It's nothing.
It's just that I won't copy for free.
I'll pay you for it.
Three thousand. Is that enough?
Let me copy. Your grades won't go down.
Wait! Listen to me. Bank.
Wait for me, Bank.
Bank!
Damn it, Bank!
Can't you help a brother out?
Man, you're cruel!
Come on! Hurry!
Today, you're all taking
the exam together.
Don't sit next to your classmates.
Okay. You can all begin.
CLASS 1
CLASS 4
CLASS 3
CLASS 6
11. B
39. D
40. THIS EXAM PAPER IS SET 1.
Sir!
How should we answer question 40?
There are two sets of questions.
Which set did you receive?
Just answer according to the set you have.
Two sets?
A. SET 1
B. SET 2
40. A
WATCH OUT, TONG IS COPYING YOU
Lynn. Which set do you have?
What is the set number?
Set One.
Leave Set One here.
What is it?
Row three.
Banjong.
Crew cut, wears glasses.
He's copying Rinrada
who's sitting next to him.
I'll go and see for myself. No problem.
You can go.
What is it? Tell me.
You have 30 minutes left.
A. SET 1
B
D
40. A
Tong!
What?
Switch the exam papers.
Quickly!
BANJONG WONGPOOM
Twenty minutes left.
1. B
Lynn!
What is it?
Should I erase your name
and write mine instead?
No need. Just sit still.
6. A
Ten minutes to go.
35. A
Last five minutes.
40. B
B. SET 2
Time's up!
You can stop writing now.
Hey!
You can put your pencils down now!
That's enough!
Don't you have enough As?
That's it!
GOSH! THE TEACHER'S PLAYING HARDBALL!
WE NARROWLY MADE IT. THANKS, LYNN.
Is it worth it? That was a close call.
Well, it's 3,000 each for 25 people.
What do you think?
Rinrada!
You didn't write your name
on the scrap paper.
Miss Rinrada, Class 11/3,
and Mr. Banjong, Class 11/1,
please come to the headmistress's office
immediately.
I can assure you.
If you don't believe me,
have Tong retake the exam.
Then, you'll know the truth.
I have asked the two of you to come here
because Thanaphon says
there has been cheating.
There are two sets of papers.
It's not worth cheating.
I'll give you the chance
to tell me the truth.
Banjong, did you cheat or not?
We'll soon find out.
Thanaphon, Rinrada, you are both excused.
Banjong, you stay here.
Lynn, don't leave just yet.
What are these numbers doing
on your worksheet?
They're not the ones from your exam set.
Please don't get caught.
Everything will be fine.
It's probably about the scholarship.
It's like this. We have evidence that
Lynn did the exam paper for her friends.
Lynn.
Tell us why you did this.
If you don't tell me, I'll expel you.
For the money.
It's, well...
Tong tried to hire me
to take the exam for him.
For 3,000 baht.
I'm extremely disappointed in you.
Vit.
I accepted your daughter
because she was a good student.
But being a good student isn't enough.
She also needs to exhibit good behavior.
You're a teacher, too.
You must understand.
Doing the exam for your friend
is considered cheating.
It's a serious violation of school rules.
Actually, I could expel you immediately.
But since this is the first time,
I'm just cutting off
your free scholarship.
Yes, ma'am.
Can't Tong and Lynn just retake the exam?
Remember, Lynn.
School is a place for studying,
not a place for making money.
What's so funny?
-You have no manners.
-No.
That's not it.
Mr. Pravit.
You're a teacher.
Didn't you teach her manners?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't have been the only one
using the school as a place to make money.
What do you mean by that?
I'm talking about the tea money
that my dad paid.
It's not called tea money.
It's called school maintenance fee.
The school maintenance fee.
Isn't it the tuition fee?
Enough, Lynn. Enough.
Please let my daughter continue here.
I will take care
of the remaining tuition fee.
Let's go.
Fine.
But there's one condition.
You're banned
from the Singapore scholarship.
Let's go.
What's the scholarship got to do with it?
It's true that I helped my friends
copy my answers,
but I never copied anyone else's.
All of the results that I have achieved
have been the product of my own ability.
Other students have such ability as well.
People like Thanaphon
deserve the scholarship more.
If you can't accept this condition,
it's better that you leave.
All right, Vit?
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go.
Good luck with the scholarship.
If evidence has been found...
then I guess Lynn may have cheated.
CONGRATULATIONS TO SCHOLARSHIP STUDENTS
ACADEMIC YEAR 2013
But I'm not involved.
MISS RINRADA NILTHEP, ELEVENTH GRADE
Both of us being honor students
doesn't mean...
MR. THANAPHON VIRIYAKUL
we have the same personality.
MISS RINRADA NILTHEP
Just what I thought.
You definitely wouldn't have done that
for merely 3,000 baht.
Piano lessons.
Didn't you ever think
that it might have been better
to actually teach your friends?
But the headmistress
cheated us first, Dad.
How can you call it cheating
when I paid willingly?
So did my friends.
You still don't see
that you did something wrong?
I'll take the blame.
It's my fault
I can't blame anyone else.
If I can't even raise you
to be a good person,
how dare I ask other people
to pay for your tuition?
I'll sell my car to pay what's left
of the tuition fee.
As for this shirt...
I don't want it anymore.
And let's forget about going abroad.
You're not going anywhere anymore.
Stay here with your dad.
Return all of the money to your friends.
No matter how much you all think
that Lynn is a bad person...
she's a really good friend of mine.
I'm sorry for being a crybaby...
but I'm not just putting on an act.
TWELFTH GRADE
So, do I look great or not?
Not bad.
Casting is tomorrow.
This isn't all you asked me
to come for, right?
How have you all been?
Can you all take care of yourselves
for the two terms we have left?
Pat and I have other things
to worry about.
Has Pat told you?
We just got back from France.
The trip was a lot of fun.
Yes, because you left me behind.
-Well, it was a shopping spree.
-Mom.
I got you something, too--
-Pat.
-Yes?
Grab me some red wine from the cellar.
Why don't you get the maid to get it?
Yes, sir.
Grace, would you like some more dessert?
I'm fine, thanks.
We invited you here today
because we wanted to thank you.
Thank me for what?
For helping Pat with his studies.
You have no idea
how much we have been stressing out
over his grades.
But as soon as you two started dating,
Pat has become a whole new person.
What I'm saying is that
you're smarter than all of those
famous tutors.
Actually, we have been planning
for some time
to send Pat to the same college
I went to in Boston.
Judging by his earlier grades,
I know that he definitely won't make it.
So, this is what I'm thinking.
You should go with him,
so you can help him
with his studies there.
Sounds good?
There's no need to worry about expenses.
Accommodation, food...
We'll take care of it.
As for the tuition fees...
If you are short...
you can always feel free to ask me.
I already have all
of the information ready.
Please have a look at it.
If money isn't an issue, say yes, okay?
You know about the STIC exam, right?
It's like the GAT/PAT
for entry to US universities.
It's held at the same time
around the world.
I need to take the STIC
and I need to take it within this year.
If I don't,
I won't be able to apply
to the universities in time.
HOW TO BLITZ THE STIC
I have already risked
a lot for you, Grace.
It's really hard for me
to ask you for help.
But Pat and I really don't know
what else to do.
Pat says he's going to hire you
for 600,000 baht.
HOW TO BLITZ THE STIC
Excuse me. Could you return this to Pat?
Okay.
Could I borrow a pen and some paper?
I REALLY CAN'T HELP YOU THIS TIME, SORRY!
Miss.
Would you like to reserve a room?
As for time zones,
the STIC is held at the same time
and date worldwide.
This means that these countries over here
will take the exam earlier
than other places.
To put it simply,
if both of you take the exam in Thailand,
while I take it somewhere
where it's held earlier,
such as in Sydney, Australia,
that means four hours earlier
than Thailand,
we get to see the exam questions sooner
and answer them sooner as well.
I can send the answers back to you
and to other people in Thailand, too.
As many as we want.
Using this method,
not only will I be helping you
get a passing score
to get into a university,
I'll be getting revenue
from other customers as well.
After deducting expenses,
we can split the profits.
Isn't it too risky?
Risky? Not at all.
Who is this?
It's Teacher Lynn, babe.
This is the only way
for me to have enough money
to go and study with you
without having to ask anyone for help.
Oh, I forgot to mention.
I'm going to Boston
with both of you as well.
It will be so much fun to go together!
You two will be responsible
for finding customers for me.
As for the exam itself,
I'll take care of it.
Wait a minute.
Before we get to the part about customers,
I get the time zone thing,
but I'm still confused.
How are you going to get the answers
out of the exam room?
Secretly write them down?
Memorize them.
Memorizing them is the best way.
It's the safest.
And it leaves no trace.
I'm sorry.
Are you one of the X-Men?
The STIC has more than 100 questions.
Can you remember all of them?
Yes, I can.
If I have enough time.
However, after I'm done
with the questions,
there's not much time left.
The best I can do is remember half
of the questions.
Only half?
There's one person who could help.
But he won't.
What's up, Mom?
Yes, I'm done.
Mr. Rut's house?
Can't it wait until another day? Tomorrow?
I have my scholarship exam at 8:00 a.m.
Okay.
Hey, you!
Your basket grazed my mirror!
If you had said sorry--
That hurts...
It's 250,000 for a passing score.
It's not that much money for you, is it?
The tutoring fee for the STIC
is way more expensive.
Let's think about it.
We need to try and find 30 customers.
More than this and it will be risky.
Any less and it won't be worth it either.
I have almost 30 people
in my STIC group chat already.
If you can ask your friends there to join,
I'll knock 5,000 off the original fee
that you're supposed to pay me.
But wait.
You must make sure
no one knows about this.
Especially that loser, Bank.
Hey, no need to worry about that dumbass.
He won't tell anyone.
Why not?
Didn't you hear?
The dumbass got beaten up.
He's in the hospital.
The best part is
he didn't make it to the scholarship exam.
SEMINAR: EXCELLING IN EDUCATION
I believe that everyone here
wants to pass the STIC
to turn their dreams into reality.
That's Steve Pat.
I have a way for everyone
to obtain satisfactory scores.
All you can take into the exam room
is a 2B pencil, an eraser.
Your exam ID...
And your passport.
Communication devices
are strictly prohibited.
So, I'll hide the phone with the answers
to be sent back to Thailand
in a cistern in the exam room toilets.
I'll send the answers back
during the breaks.
The exam is divided into three sessions,
with two breaks.
Wait. Just a second.
How do the customers get
the answers into the exam room?
Not everyone can memorize
all the answers like you.
Barcode.
Everyone will receive a 2B pencil
with a barcode on it.
The different widths of the lines
in each barcode
will represent a different answer.
From left to right.
Starting with the thickest line,
which stands for A,
then B, C, and D.
Sounds cool, right?
But the fun doesn't stop there.
There are four pencils.
One pencil for one section.
And these numbers next to the barcode
are for the grid-in questions.
GRID-IN ANSWERS
For the essay, they use
already-published material.
I'll send keywords,
so you can Google them.
-That's mine.
-I'm not giving it to you.
-It fell.
-Hey!
I'm telling you how to do this,
but you'll have to write
the answers yourselves.
To summarize, on the exam day,
everyone has to leave
the meeting point by 7:30 a.m.
in order to reach the exam rooms in time.
We'll provide a motorbike to take
each person to their exam venue.
Finally, everyone has to pay in cash
within the next two weeks.
Otherwise, the deal is off.
One other thing
I need to emphasize is that...
what we are about to do together
must be kept secret.
Does anyone have any issues?
If not,
we'll end the seminar now.
We will unite
in our educational quest
to obtain scores that will allow us
entry to any college.
We need to be able to choose our school,
not let it decide whether or not
we can study there.
Hey, that's rough, Bank.
What's up?
I was sorry to hear about it.
That you weren't able to take
the scholarship exam.
Same here.
What happened that day...
I didn't mean it. Really.
I wouldn't know
whether you meant it or not.
What I do know is that you're responsible
for what happened to me as well.
I have a proposition for you.
What is it?
It involves taking an exam.
Taking an exam or cheating in an exam?
For me, using the word "cheating"
means someone loses something.
But here, we'll make money
and others pass exams.
Everyone wins.
Bank.
We are both losers, actually.
We weren't born winners
like Pat and Grace.
We have to try harder than other people
to get what we deserve.
Look at what happened.
We're not the same.
You cheated.
But I was just unlucky.
True.
But don't you see
that even if you don't cheat,
life cheats you anyway.
This is Grace's home address.
See you tomorrow if you're interested.
HONEST TRADE PRINTERS
WORK EFFECTIVELY
Sit down here.
Hey.
You're not going to sit?
This is what's going to happen.
First, you and I fly to Sydney, Australia
and take the STIC together.
Hey, Lynn.
You're missing one document.
Dad, that Teen Genius show that I was in,
they want me to appear
in it again, in Sydney.
BY THAI LIFE INSURANCE
They need your bank statement for my visa.
Who are you going with?
I'm going with Bank.
It's not just us.
Our teacher is going too.
Secondly,
you and I will each have to memorize
half of the exam questions.
Don't forget.
Bank memorizes the first half,
and Lynn the second half.
Section 1 has 52 questions.
Start.
52 QUESTIONS
44 QUESTIONS
16 GRID-IN QUESTIONS
For the final section,
you need to leave the exam room
before the end
to send the essay question in time.
Time's up for Section Four.
Start the essay question.
It shouldn't be hard for you
to remember the title.
The hard part is that
they won't let you leave early.
To avoid any suspicion,
you will have to act sick.
Sure.
I can throw up.
So, do I have to puke now?
-No.
-No! You don't.
Go now.
So, how much is my cut?
One million.
How much is yours?
Two million.
What do you say, Bank?
Everything is in your hands.
TOILET
Got it!
In time.
You should have just said yes
from the start.
Hey, guys!
See you tomorrow at 1:00 p.m.
Have you lost it?
Doesn't the plane leave at 11:00 p.m.?
What's the rush?
There's one more thing
we need to rehearse.
That's enough.
You can't keep on grilling someone
who's innocent!
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
Watching an innocent man's tears
stream down like this.
That's way too much, Pat. Way too much.
I have used up all my cards.
You guys are acting
like we have really been caught.
I get it already.
If you get caught,
we'll let you be the fall guy.
Last question
before heading to the airport.
The last question.
Ready?
What if Bank gets caught?
What will you say?
That has even less to do with me.
I have never even been his friend.
I have seen him at school
for the last four or five years.
I haven't noticed him
having even one friend.
He looks like a douchebag too.
And he's a weirdo.
He even got beaten up outside the school
and ended up on a scrap heap.
So, are we done?
Stop!
Calm down, Bank!
Bank, stop!
I told you to stop!
Dumbass!
-Stop it!
-You motherfucker!
What the hell are you doing?
You were the one who told me to say this.
So, why are you mad at me?
Pat! Stop!
Bank. Bank, stop!
What is it? What?
-I...
-You... What, then?
I never told anyone
that I once woke up on a scrap heap!
Now, do you know what I'm angry about?
All of you set this up, didn't you?
Set it up so I couldn't take
the scholarship exam!
All of you were in on it, right?
You guys knew, right?
Right?
You knew, right?
Why aren't you dumbasses answering me?
Bank! Cool it, man!
I don't want to hear
any more from you again!
Bank, give it a break.
Let's talk about this.
Let's talk about it, Bank!
You're okay now, right?
I'm sorry, Bank.
Bank.
I'm really sorry, Bank. I'm really sorry.
I didn't know
they were going to go that far.
Bank, just listen to me first.
You're still going to take
the STIC, aren't you? Bank.
-I'm begging you.
-That damn STIC!
Bank, listen to me first, Bank.
I'm listening to you!
It's just me and my mom at my place.
She's like a hunchback, doing the laundry.
I'm not rich like you!
It was my dream to get a scholarship,
to help my mother have a comfortable life.
Damn you!
Bank.
If you don't take the STIC,
my dad will kill me.
Please, Bank.
We both win, don't you see?
Bank, I'm begging you.
In that case...
send those thugs to beat up your dad!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Wasn't it you who told me
that you needed him?
So, if I don't play dirty,
do you think he'll agree to help you?
Lynn!
Let's talk first.
You were in on this too, weren't you?
I didn't have a clue.
Please try to understand Pat.
He did it because he wanted
to help you with your plan.
Without any consideration
about who might get hurt?
THE FUTURE OF LAUNDRY
Grace, return everyone's money.
I'm pulling out.
Wait, Lynn.
Calm down.
If that's how it is,
I respect your decision.
You don't have to do it.
No more clients, okay?
Just the three of us. The original plan.
Don't you understand?
When I said no, I meant no.
Okay.
It's up to you, then.
I only have one request.
Don't be mad at me.
If I had half of your brain,
I wouldn't do anything this stupid.
Please?
The plane is leaving in three hours.
Let's go, Lynn.
Bank.
I'll go through with it.
At least there's money in it.
I won't get beaten up for nothing.
What if I told you that...
I didn't want to do it anymore?
I'm not begging you.
I'm here, thanks to you.
I slept on a scrap heap,
thanks to you as well.
All of this shit is happening
because of you.
Don't you think you're responsible
for this, too?
SYDNEY
Here. Your phone.
Lynn.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
Well...
your nose.
You know...
I have never been abroad before.
Starting tomorrow,
the world is our oyster.
Let's take a selfie together.
FINAL TEST
HONEST TRADE PRINTERS
45 MINUTES
10-MINUTE BREAK
The first break is from 5:15 a.m.
until 5:25 a.m.
WE'RE READY
All right.
BANK?
I WANT ANOTHER MILLION
One more million? You ass!
-Ass!
-Hey, Pat!
WHAT'S WRONG?
Damn!
TRANSFER THE MONEY WITHIN FIVE MINUTES
OR FORGET ABOUT THE ANSWERS
Damn it! Asshole! Five minutes?
Ask him. What the hell is wrong with him?
-Pat! Pat, calm down.
-How can I calm down at this time? Fuck!
-Hey!
-Bank! You bastard!
THIS IS GRACE.
I THOUGHT WE ALREADY AGREED
ABOUT THE MONEY.
THE FIRST MILLION IS FOR THE JOB.
THE SECOND IS FOR THE SCRAP HEAP.
MONEY TRANSFER: OCTOBER 8, 2016
THIS IS ALL I HAVE IN MY ACCOUNT.
I'LL SEND MORE WHEN I GET THE ANSWERS.
-Come on.
-There it is. Let's go!
Okay.
Back in the game.
NEXT, GRID-IN ANSWERS
HONEST TRADE PRINTERS
FOR SALE
Don't we have to leave here
before 7:30 a.m.?
Yes.
-It's almost 7:00 now.
-How long do we have to wait?
I'm supposed to get more than this.
I have already paid you.
Hey, it's past 7:00 a.m. already.
Why aren't they sending the other answers?
I don't know!
-Good morning.
Is Lynn here? I can't contact her.
I haven't seen her.
Lynn told me that she was
going to Sydney for a competition.
No wonder I haven't seen her.
I'm sure she'll bring back a medal.
But I found this permission letter
that I had signed at the house.
When I called the show, no one answered.
So, I came to this address.
Can someone tell me why Lynn is in Sydney?
If the two of you don't answer,
I'll go and tell the headmistress.
Tell me now what you're up to!
NEXT
Lynn and Bank are dating!
They went on a secret trip together.
Lynn thought you wouldn't let her go,
so she lied.
I didn't know how to stop her.
I think it would be best
if you go back and talk
with your daughter in person.
Come on!
Sir.
Love is a beautiful thing.
Shit!
What's up?
It's 7:00 a.m. already.
The motorbikes are leaving.
They're saying it's past the time
they agreed on.
Explain to me first what's wrong.
I don't know anything!
I'll speak to them myself.
What's wrong with your leg?
It's 7:30 a.m. already.
-What's up?
-Where are the barcodes?
-I already paid you.
-You said it will be okay.
-You'll get it soon.
-We'll be late!
Hey, you'll make it. I promise.
Pat! We ran out of stickers!
Here you go, 500 baht each.
Just a minute. Chill. Thanks.
Shit!
Hey! Please open the door!
Can you open the door, please?
Come on!
Grace, it's almost 7:30 a.m.
Do we have all the answers?
Not yet. There are still six to go.
Why does it say "Edge"?
It says "Edge."
What's Edge?
There's no signal.
What happens if we don't make it?
And the money that we paid?
If we don't make it,
we want our money back!
-Come on!
-Have we got them yet?
These three bikes,
go to the Bang Kapi venue.
These two rows, head to Sutthisan.
Are you on your bikes?
Put on your helmets! Quickly!
Take one set each.
One set each.
Okay, we're all set! Helmets! Quickly!
Helmets, quickly! Put them on and go!
Let's go!
I'm from the embassy.
A Thai student has confessed
using his phone's dictionary.
We're dealing with it.
What will happen to him?
They'll probably cancel his result.
Worst case, they'll ban him
permanently from the STIC.
As for the others,
they'll let them go
if they don't find anything.
Wait here first. I'll take care of things.
They have been investigating
for two or three days.
Just a moment.
What's the matter?
I need to use the bathroom, sorry.
Of course.
Lynn!
It's Lynn FC!
TEACHER LYNN FC
Thank you, Lynn!
We're throwing a party for you
at our place tonight.
What are we celebrating?
Bank got caught.
And I had my result canceled, Pat.
Well, we'll find another
exam venue for you, won't we?
If you don't retake the exam,
you won't be able to apply
to a university in time.
Hey, Lynn!
Lynn, you have to apply
to retake the exam.
Please, Lynn. Pretty please?
I have changed my mind already.
Both of you already have
the results you needed.
But we can't go and study without you.
Don't you both know...
that university exams
aren't multiple-choice?
Even if I went and studied with you,
you wouldn't be able to copy my answers.
I'll find my own ride.
ARRIVALS
Where's your boyfriend?
Where is he?
I wanted to invite him for dinner.
Why didn't you tell me
about your boyfriend?
-Dad...
-What?
I have something to confess to you.
What is it, honey?
Tell me.
ARRIVALS
Why did you choose to study Education?
I would like to be a teacher
like my father,
so others can benefit the most
from my knowledge.
So, do you have any previous experience
in tutoring others?
Have you ever taught anyone before?
Yes, I have.
I SCORED 1,460 IN THE STIC
Being a teacher isn't just
about being smart in academics.
Do you think that
you can set a good example
in other ways too?
GRACE: LYNN, WHEN ARE YOU COMING?
PAT: BANK HAS TAKEN HIS SHARE.
COME AND GET YOURS.
I'm not going to lie.
GRACE: HURRY UP. I MISS YOU.
I have done a lot of bad things
in the past.
But I will learn from them
for my own benefit
and for others.
LYNN LEFT THE CHAT
But it's such a waste.
To be honest, with this much
knowledge and ability,
you could have gotten a scholarship
and gone abroad to study.
Haven't you considered this?
I think that...
there are others who deserve
a scholarship more than me.
STUDENT EXPULSION LETTER:
THANAPHON VIRIYAKUL
CONGRATULATIONS TO SCHOLARSHIP STUDENTS
MR. THANAPHON VIRIYAKUL, ELEVENTH GRADE
MISS RINRADA NILTHEP, ELEVENTH GRADE
BANK: COME OVER TO MY PLACE TONIGHT
Come in.
The store looks nice and fresh,
Little Bank.
I'm sorry. It's Mr. Bank now.
Are you laundering money?
You were expelled from school
because the embassy reported you, right?
So, what's next?
That's the reason I asked you over.
Did you apply for the GAT/PAT exams?
I have a proposition for you.
GAT/PAT INTENSIVE TUTORING BY BANK
EVERY SATURDAY AND SUNDAY
I have a foolproof plan.
Much safer.
We can get the answers out to more people.
More importantly, there are more customers
for the GAT/PAT than for the STIC.
But this plan requires...
Teacher Lynn's assistance.
How much more money do you need?
If your cut isn't sufficient...
you can get mine from Pat.
Go and get it.
No. Wait a minute.
It's not about whether it's enough or not.
It's about how much more we can make...
in the future.
Lynn.
I have done the calculations.
This time,
there's at least ten million in it.
For that much money, don't you think
that it's worth the risk again?
You see it, right?
That even if we get caught,
that wouldn't mean jail.
Actually, Lynn,
are you going to study for four more years
for a five-figure salary
when we could have millions by then?
Why settle for a stupid desk job?
Because for me right now,
no amount of money is worth it.
Lynn.
If you won't do this...
I'll tell everyone
that you were the mastermind
behind the STIC scandal.
I guarantee that you'll end up
being banned
from studying abroad, just like me.
Fine.
We're even, then.
It won't just be you.
It will also be Grace, Pat.
And all the customers who took the STIC
that time will be caught up as well.
Think about it, Lynn.
If they find out about it,
they'll cancel all of the scores
in the country.
On top of that...
your father will be devastated, too.
Don't be afraid, honey.
We'll get through this somehow.
Smile, honey. Smile.
Smile like your dad.
Miss Rinrada?
You once told me, didn't you...
that if we win, we would win together.
If we go down,
we would go right down together.
I won't be the only one
taking all the blame again.
If you don't do it,
I'll make sure you go down with me.
What do you say, Lynn?
What's it going to be?
Everything is up to you now.
You're right.
Everything is up to me.
Subtitle translation by Karina Suvapataya