Mom! Mom!
Don't fall asleep!
Wake up! Wake up!
Mom! Mom!
Mom, wake up!
Sak!
It's a curve!
No curve is too curvy
because I am that gutsy.
Sak!
Truck!
RAILWAY
A train's coming!
So what?
-Let's gamble with our lives.
-Gamble?
Not my life. No more of this shit!
The word "no" is not in my dictionary.
Is this the right time to act cool?
It's not an act. It's in my DNA.
Damn you!
Sak, stop!
I said stop!
ONE MONTH EARLIER
ALARM RINGING
MR. SAKRIN PAEWONG
Though your butt is saggy,
I still love you dearly.
Hi! My name is Sakrin.
I was born and raised in Ayutthaya.
Other people's kids give their mom a kiss.
My damn son slapped my butt.
This is Suree, my mother,
a former pub singer in Suphan Buri.
Now she provides laundry services
in Ayutthaya.
See you, Mom. See you, Grandma.
This is my beloved grandmother.
She's very ill, but that doesn't stop her
from being a pain.
Hey, Sak.
BILLS
The bills came early this month.
Take care of them for me.
No problem.
Hello, everyone!
This guy is Uncle Preecha.
My Father's friend, an ex-cop.
-Hello, Aunty!
-Who the hell are you?
Suree, your mother-in-law has Alzheimer's?
Sak, I forgot to tell you.
Uncle Preecha and his son are moving back
to the neighborhood.
You're still around?
Of course, I'm still around.
I'm super strong.
When I was border police,
I was the strongest in the unit.
I had to swim every day
to use up my extra energy.
-Really?
-Yes.
I thought you were dead.
You have a foul mouth just like your dad.
You still have buck teeth
just like before.
Why don't you just smack my head?
-Okay.
-I'm joking.
You haven't heard this.
My son will be an assistant manager
in a bank soon.
He's working in a bank?
Yes.
Watch out for scammers.
Have you heard the news
about someone getting scammed
and losing money?
If you knew, why didn't you warn them?
It's me who got scammed!
Working as a banker is lame.
Look at my son. See? No shame at all.
Your son?
Whenever he visits,
I always worry he might steal something.
Calm down, Norasingh! She's my friend.
So, what does he do?
Is he an entrepreneur?
He's unemployed.
-Dad!
-Asshole! I am your father.
Ungrateful boy!
No respect even for your own father.
Where's Sak?
He left for work. Why waste time?
I see.
Norasingh, greet the grandmother.
-Who the hell are you?
-You talking to me?
Singh! Motherfucker!
You're going to punch such an old woman?
-I don't discriminate.
-Damn you.
Look at her age!
No need to punch. Just blow and she dies.
And this is how I commute
to Bangkok everyday.
PAY BILLS
MEN'S RESTROOM
BIKEMEN - OLD MARKET
Right, I told my family I was a banker.
But I'm just a bikeman.
To the Skytrain.
Please hurry. I'm already late.
It's never too late
if your death isn't due.
Honda Wave.
Thirty-four grand.
Scoopy I 2016, also 34 grand.
Scoopy I,
but 2018.
Thirty-nine grand.
Wow!
Honda Wave...
but not an ordinary model.
Dual exhaust.
With sidecar selling fruit and coffee.
Dang!
The whole thing, I'd say almost 50 grand.
Amazing!
Unbelievable! You can't even see.
You are out of this world!
You are so good,
we need to give you a trophy.
No.
The trophy will say,
"Sakrin...
works at this bike station."
Your mom would be proud.
Shit. I just hurt his feelings.
I'm sorry.
We have a client.
This is Jai.
Gold medal runner at my school,
who I had a crush on.
The thing is,
I don't want her to recognize me
because I'm a lowly bikeman.
Number five.
Sak! What's wrong with you?
Your turn. If you don't go, I will.
Mister.
-Where do you want to go?
-To NCB Bank.
-I see.
-Please get on the bike.
Here.
Please sit.
Aren't you Sakrin?
Wow! It's really you.
Remember me?
Jai.
It's me, Jarunee.
The orange team's drum major, also
a gold medal runner during Grade seven.
It's been ages, but I still remember you.
-Good memory, right?
-Right.
It's nice to see an old friend.
Yeah.
Well, I have to pay you.
Twenty, right?
Twenty-five.
Did you just raise the price?
It's been a while now.
Give me a discount, please.
How stingy.
Please.
Please...
Aren't you prettier than before?
Is that a compliment?
It's a compliment...
said with great confidence.
Twenty, okay?
Okay, I'll take it.
Yes!
So...
You're working here?
Why have I never seen you around?
I used to be a trainee at headquarters.
Then they sent me here.
You are late.
Because you didn't pick me up.
The skytrain also--
If I had picked you up,
we both would have been late.
I'm the respectable...
-assistant manager.
-Assistant manager... You can't be late.
This is Ae, my boyfriend.
This is Sak, my old friend.
We accidentally met.
Well...
Let's meet again, so we can catch up.
In case you want to call me.
See you.
The reason
that Sak pretends to be a banker...
You know why?
Why?
He's afraid.
Afraid of what?
Afraid that if his grandmother
knows the truth,
she might be shocked to death.
He's still googling for a job in a bank
till this day.
JOB POSITIONS IN A BANK
NOT AVAILABLE AT THE MOMENT
When he comes to Bangkok,
do you know who he's afraid
to run into the most?
Who?
Mr. Preecha, his dad's friend.
Why's it so crowded? No empty seats.
Hi!
Why are you running away? It's me.
Sak!
Why did you run?
You are acting really weird.
Don't cry!
Just keep shitting.
In this scenario,
you think I can't find you?
Oh, I'm wrong.
This is different from a movie.
Window.
I farted, sir.
No need to report. You can fart.
You are really something.
For such a small boy,
you store so much shit. I'm leaving.
Shit.
Hi, Sak.
Hi, Uncle.
You said you worked in a bank in Bangkok.
How come you have a motorcycle key?
It's my friend's.
I see.
What are you doing in Bangkok?
I'm going to open a doll shop.
I came to buy dolls in Bangkok.
Your mom is coming, too.
She's catching up later.
My son, Norasingh, is sick,
so I paid your mom
to help me bring back the dolls.
Let me ask you.
Why did you run from me?
Who said I ran?
I saw you run just now.
Attention, next station is Bang Sue.
It's my station. See you later.
Thank you for this.
Damn the announcement!
I was getting the answer.
Sak is acting really weird.
Next person, please.
I have eight checks, two water bills,
four electricity bills. Deposit 200,000.
Withdraw 60,000. Transfer 35,000.
Come again, please.
You are a newbie, right?
Yes.
Well, I...
can't remember all of that.
Okay, let's deposit this check first.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Ae, this is our new trainee.
I want you to be her mentor.
-Hi, Mr. Ae.
-Hi.
-What's your name?
-I'm Noi-Nae.
Noi-Nae?
Cute name.
If you get to know me better,
I'm more than just cute.
Good to know.
We have a client.
This girl again.
Whoever gets this one,
prepare to change the tires.
I'm not going.
You can't do that.
Don't forget.
We never refuse service to a customer.
Our motto is to give the best service.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Are you okay?
Yes.
The path is never too narrow.
Slow down.
Goodness!
See? We got through.
No.
No? We clearly got through.
My knees are ruined.
You suck as a biker.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Preecha.
Where is that alley again?
I forgot.
Hello.
Hello, Preecha.
Hello!
Bad reception.
Boy!
You.
The lady is calling you.
-Really?
-Really!
Do you know the alley
behind The Grand Postal building?
You are a bikeman.
How come you don't know it?
Now what, Suree?
She didn't answer the phone.
Will she be able to get here?
Who are you talking to?
No one. I'm just muttering.
You mutter very loudly.
So what?
Go straight.
Turn left at the next traffic light.
But...
You sound very familiar.
Have we met?
Are you from Ayutthaya?
You look familiar, too.
Why don't you answer her question?
What?
I only said he was acting weird.
Why did he take off?
-Why did you run a red light?
-So we'll get there quickly.
I'm not in a hurry.
Are you fake monks?
What?
Are you working together?
-No, we--
-Where's your alms bowl?
Where's your temple boy?
-We--
-Someone will pick you up, right?
Don't lie to me. I'm an ex-cop.
Shit!
-Accident ahead!
-I know.
Stop the bike!
Your eyes give it away.
Keep it cool, man.
Watch out!
Bikers always ride on the sidewalk.
How dangerous!
Luckily,
I helped you just in time.
I wish I could've used my hands,
but my hands are not available. So I--
-Kicked me.
-Yes.
You don't mind, right?
I don't.
Father, watch out!
Thank you very much.
I owe him my life.
I'm glad that you saved him
from a fatal accident.
You don't mind, right?
-I don't.
-He doesn't mind.
What are you doing?
Honey, have I told you
that Sak got promoted?
He follows in your footsteps.
Same position.
Are you happy? I am really happy.
Hey, Sak!
You're back already?
Suree,
I took your fridge to the repair shop.
-Really?
-It's really broken.
Nothing works.
I want to ask you something.
The story you told me.
Who was he?
If I knew,
would I ask you in the first place?
He sounded and looked familiar.
But I've never known any bikemen.
Well, hear me out.
Next time I go selling dolls in Bangkok,
take me to the spot where you met him.
I will find out who he is.
Trust me,
he won't get away from an ex-cop like me.
Why are you sweating like pig?
-I sweat easily.
-Really?
Let me see.
What are you doing?
Checking your pulse.
Your pulse is dancing like a go-go girl.
-Suree.
-Yeah?
-Do you think he's weird?
-Who?
Your son.
I don't think so.
You are the weirdest one in this house.
I'm not.
Your mom is the weirdest.
Have you changed her battery?
She's still like a statue.
You are really rude. Just go away.
When you have time,
play a fun song so she can dance.
I FIXED YOUR BUTTON
Long!
-Long!
-What's up?
What can I do for you?
Can someone deposit this check for me?
The bank will be closed in ten minutes.
Yeah, I know.
No problem.
I'll ask Sak to run this errand.
-Sak.
-Yes?
Go to the bank
and deposit this check for our client.
Don't you see
I have to deliver these pork rinds?
I know, but it's the same way.
You can drop by the bank
and deposit the check.
Go! Go! Go!
This moron.
I must tell him everything.
This guy is fast.
You're dead meat!
Naa, ain't you pretty?
Thank you very much.
You are glowing.
Have you been working out or something?
I jog.
You jog.
You have to watch out for accidents.
I have a new interesting insurance plan.
-Yes, I'm looking for one.
-I'll choose the best plan for you.
If you die soon,
your kids won't get much money,
but the funeral will be grand.
But if you live for a long time,
your kids will be very rich.
Are you interested?
Hold on!
The bank is closed.
You can't close now.
We still have three minutes.
Is your watch running slow?
No way! See this?
I still have three minutes.
The time on my watch matches Big Ben.
What is Big Ben?
It's a place we use to set the time.
Next time, explain it that way.
Don't use big words. I don't understand.
I'm tired and confused. You understand?
I bought a new phone.
I'm not boasting.
This one can do FaceTime.
What is FaceTime?
You are such a hillbilly.
If you use FaceTime,
you can see their face, too.
Big face on the screen.
-Wait!
-What, bro?
Why all the hurry?
What's the big deal?
I just want to deposit a check.
It's a big deal.
My life is like this.
So unfortunate
that I have to meet a dude like you.
Can you give my position some respect?
Give me some respect as a guard!
Thailand is always like this.
If it's ten people, then it's ten checks.
Rules are not respected.
If I could choose,
I'd have fled to Italy.
-I'm annoyed. I'm fed up.
-Just a sec.
What?
What's going on, Mom?
It's FaceTime.
I know what FaceTime is.
I want to see how you're doing at work.
My dear boy.
-See? I'm working.
-Wait. Wait.
Your bank is closed now.
Did you finish your job?
It will be closed soon.
Why do you want to know?
Close the door, Wichien.
-I have to go.
-Who is Wichien?
-We don't have time, Wichien.
-Stop! Stop!
What's going on?
I have a check to deposit.
You want to deposit a check?
Let me see.
The bank is now closed.
Can you come back tomorrow?
I told you.
Please leave.
Hello, teacher. The bank is closed.
Can you tell the client that I'm sorry.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
We are going to battle.
Mind your own business.
-Wait.
-What?
What does "battle" mean?
Scum like you--
That motherfucker!
Scumbag, I'm exhausted from chasing you.
I'm fucked.
Let me see your stupid face.
You wanna fight me?
Damn it!
My old wound. Fuck!
Shit!
I'm leaving. My dad is here.
I have to get the hell out.
Stop.
I told you to stop.
It's you guys, right?
I didn't do anything.
I have petty crimes on a daily basis,
instead of working on big cases.
I have to find the guy
who punched the security guard.
I didn't punch him.
The other guy punched him.
The fine for an assault case is ten grand.
What?
Can I pay 500?
The fine is between 500 and 10,000.
So you won't do it again.
If you don't pay, you can go to prison.
What's wrong?
I lost my wallet.
They always have an excuse.
Then call your family to bail you out.
MY FAVORITE CONTACTS
MOM
-Why can't you call your mother?
-Sir,
my mom thinks I'm a badass.
I don't want her to know I'm a jackass.
So what?
Hello.
Cherry, is that you?
The line is busy.
Now what?
Hello.
I need a receipt.
Thank you.
I called all my friends,
but nobody answered.
Don't worry.
I will pay you back the ten grand.
No hurry.
Is the day after tomorrow okay?
Day or night?
Is the daytime too late?
Before lunch, right?
I'm joking. You can pay me back any time.
-Why are you laughing?
-Nothing.
You loaned me the money.
Can you be my honey?
Of course not. You have a boyfriend.
-Where's Mom?
-She's delivering some laundry.
-Somsak, same time tomorrow okay?
-Sure.
What are you looking at?
You look like
someone punched you in the face.
No one punched me.
I just tripped and fell.
I see.
You look like you got punched.
Holy shit!
What?
It can't be fixed?
How much is a new one?
Really?
Okay. Hold on. Let me ask my son.
Josh, the repairman,
said it's too old to fix.
Not worth it. It's bound to break again.
We should buy a new one.
A used one is 8,000.
With the repair service fee,
we have to pay 12,000.
What?
If you don't have money,
I'll ask Josh to fix the old one.
Who am I? I'm soon to be...
an assistant manager at the bank.
By the way,
the cut looks pretty deep.
Does it hurt?
Yes, it hurts.
You have to be more careful.
I can't sit.
My family needs the money.
-Can I pay you back 1,000 baht a week?
-Sure, but with interest.
But I don't mean money.
You have to give me free rides.
Twice a week.
Thank you. You are very kind.
Yes, I am beautiful and kind.
If you ever break up with your boyfriend,
I'm right here waiting.
How sweet!
I am so sweet that you can eat me up.
Now you are pervy.
Well, I'm not a funny guy.
I am a pervy guy.
Gosh!
You're free on Sunday, right?
Yes, what's up?
I'm cooking some curry.
Ask your friends from the bank to join us.
And this time,
don't bail on me.
It happened too many times.
What a waste of food!
Do you understand?
Yes.
This is Pakorn
from the credit department.
This is Ong-Art
from the foreign currency...
department.
Hi, ma'am.
Very nice to meet you.
Because at the bank,
Sakrin always tells us about you.
So, we...
really wanted to visit you.
But...
in our department,
we've been busy all the time.
Taking care of...
foreign currency,
we really don't have free time.
Foreign currency,
American dollars or English pounds?
Our bank doesn't mess
with those currencies,
because...
they fluctuate constantly.
Rise and fall all the time.
So we focus
on the Myanmar kyats
and Vietnamese dongs.
For this quarter,
our bank came up with a policy
to sell all the kyats and dongs.
Then we will focus on the Indian rupee.
It is clear now.
Sak,
come with me.
Yes, Mom.
You guys giggle a lot.
-Right, sir.
-Did you smoke some weed?
The weather is very nice today.
-Indian Rupee?
-Yes, sir.
Are you sure?
About what?
That they work at the same place as you.
Why did you say that?
He asked, so I answered.
You really fucked up.
What did you expect?
Want some drugs?
-I quit a long time ago.
-Not for you.
I mean, we give him a drug.
What drug?
Here, speed.
Why?
Ong-Art and Pakorn
don't look like bankers to you?
Not even a little,
especially that Ong-Art guy.
Sak told me this old man loves
to find faults in other people.
So what?
If he takes this drug,
he'll be busy with something else.
He'll stop scrutinizing us.
Suree, you don't buy this either?
You don't have to answer.
You just question your boy.
I will interrogate those two.
Why am I here?
Just in time.
Wow!
-What a beautiful watch you have!
-It's Rado's.
Gold case, same model as George Clooney's.
The weather like this, I think...
we should have a drink.
It would be...
an honor for us.
Wait!
Did you put a drug in here?
I'm an ex-cop, you know?
The smell can't trick my nose.
Mr. Ex-Cop,
if you are skeptical,
I will...
drink first.
Your turn.
-You once told me.
-What?
Don't judge a book by its cover.
Though Ong-Art looks like that,
he's one of the best we have.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
I believe you.
What's happening to me?
Why do I want to work this much?
The house looks very messy.
It's dusty everywhere. God damn it!
I can't stand it.
This is no place to live.
I have to do something.
-The pill is too strong.
-Hold on.
I can't.
You have to throw up.
This is like a country house.
All the dust from the road.
Drivers just don't care.
Young man, are you cold?
It's windy here.
You probably ate too much. I forgot.
When you iron,
you have to drench the clothes
like when you fry grasshopper.
So the clothes will be fragrant
and good for wearing.
Young man, you want me to iron your suit?
Take it off and I will take care of it.
I'll get you some water.
Sewing machines
are not only for women,
men can use them, too.
Whether patching, mending,
or stitching, it's as easy as pie.
I grew up
in the Thai Toray Tetoron factory.
Rinse your mouth.
My hand!
God damn it!
It's okay. I shed very little blood.
What a big mess! I have to mop the floor.
Rinse some more.
When you mop the floor,
no need to change the water.
One bucket is enough. Don't waste water.
More. More.
Feeling better?
I told you not to drink it.
This is not helping.
Maybe I have to go swimming.
I have too much energy.
What is going on?
Nothing. The heat got to him.
Sakrin.
Sakrin!
Hi!
What are you doing here?
Why did you call me?
I saw a guy.
He looked just like you,
but he was wearing an office uniform.
Yeah?
I took my eyes off him for one second,
and he's gone.
What are you doing here?
I dropped off my regular customer.
Then I picked up some stuff.
Why do you look exhausted?
The stuff is heavy.
-You're sweating a lot, too.
-It's hot today.
Hello, baby!
I don't understand.
I told you to deliver all these papers.
How many times
will you make the same mistake?
I didn't mean it, baby.
How many times have I told you
not to call me baby at work?
Four times.
Wow!
You asked me to note it down.
The first time,
I wanted it sent to Salaya branch.
Where did it go?
Pattaya.
The second time,
I wanted it sent to Horkanka.
Where did it go?
Saochingcha.
Well noted. Just how I taught you.
They sound similar.
Don't.
But I--
No, no.
Especially when--
Hush...
If you can't do simple tasks,
you'll be a teller forever, won't you?
Use your brain.
Are you okay?
Not okay.
Eat up.
It's strange
when your boss is your boyfriend.
When he scolds me,
I don't know how to feel,
scared for being scolded by a boss,
or hurt for being scolded by a boyfriend.
Have you been together long?
Quite long, since college years.
He was my senior.
He led the college's cheer squad.
He was a runner, also.
A runner?
Yeah.
-You don't believe it, right?
-Wow!
Let me see.
Sorry.
That's okay.
Everyone has the same reaction.
He's very different now, right?
-Just a little.
-Liar!
Why do you always say things
like words on bumper stickers?
When I say them out loud...
they give me courage.
And more importantly...
I can text them as pickup lines.
What did you send?
YOU HAVE RECEIVED A PAYMENT
Nice!
I thought you sent me a cheesy line.
What if I really had
sent you a cheesy line?
Hello?
Now?
Okay.
I have to go to work now.
What job?
-Delivering some stuff at a carnival.
-Take me with you.
Check, please.
No, let me treat you.
Eight hundred and twenty baht.
It's okay.
We can split it.
The gesture makes me happy enough.
How about you pay 420,
and I pay 400? You treat me 20 baht, okay?
Okay.
How nice!
What's nice?
Usually, I order pork barbeque.
I've never delivered it before. It's fun.
Next time can you deliver it to my house?
Give me one free set.
I will ask the owner for you.
HAUNTED HOUSE
Sakrin.
You know what? I love your job.
Why?
You can go anywhere you want.
Not like me.
I have to sit in the bank all day.
But I'm the kind of person
who's scared of everything.
I only stay in my safe zone.
I thought of quitting the job often.
Several times a day.
I never have the guts to do it.
But when it's time,
I will quit.
What will you do?
What's that?
CAPTAIN JAI
Am I crazy?
I'm so fed up with uneducated people.
You don't even know how to use a toy gun,
how can you make a living?
It's really easy.
Here!
Keep it down.
I said keep the gun down, not your head.
I guess you want me to
-beat you up.
-Norasingh!
She's our customer.
Can't you spare a child?
Go get some wet dolls.
These dolls are already dry.
Go!
Little miss, you shouldn't play with guns.
You better go
to the lucky draw booth over there.
Shooting game!
Wow!
-Let's go.
-I don't think it's a good idea.
Why not? Let's go.
No.
Let's go.
My dearest fair goers!
Please visit my shooting booth.
The prize is a big doll.
Three sets for 100.
Why are you wearing a helmet?
I will tell you later.
I want to know now.
Do you want to play?
-Yes.
-Then, let's go.
Mister.
Mr. Baldy!
Miss,
don't call me baldy.
You are lucky my son is not here.
Otherwise, he would kill you.
I'm partly bald.
How much is a round?
Three sets for 100.
I'll give you 200.
With that many bullets,
you can shoot until dawn.
One tray is enough, I think.
How much is one tray?
Thirty-five baht.
Here it is.
Young man!
Are you crazy?
Wearing a helmet to a fair.
Don't tell me that you are a baldy, too.
You don't need to hide it.
Just show your head.
Nothing's wrong with a bald head.
Enjoy the game!
How can I get a big doll?
If you can shoot five small ones,
you can get a big one.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy the game.
Can you shoot the dolls for me?
Okay.
I want that one
next to the red one with the yellow heart.
No, not that one.
PREECHA
Yes?
Hello, Suree.
I'm working my booth at the temple.
There are many things to see here.
Would you like to come? Shit!
Why did you shoot him?
Young man, aim at the dolls.
I'm sorry, sir.
Suree.
The temple at the intersection.
The name of the temple-- Fuck!
That's the name of the temple?
Are you fucking crazy?
Which side are you shooting at?
If you shoot at this side,
I'll move to the other side.
You said you wouldn't do that.
It was an accident.
Focus.
Suree, are you still there?
It's clear now. Go away!
You aimed at me.
Why don't you shoot my eye? Motherfucker!
Asshole!
Where did he go? How fast! What the fuck?
Is he gone?
Probably.
Why did you shoot him?
It was an accident.
What about the helmet?
Why are you wearing it?
I forgot to take it off.
-You forgot?
-Yeah.
Why are you smiling?
It's nice to be like this.
What are you talking about?
Let's play something else.
Let's go.
Don't you want to know
about the helmet anymore?
No!
JAI
Hello! Are you still awake?
Yes.
Are you free tomorrow night?
I'm not sure.
Never mind, then.
I'm free.
Can you come with me tomorrow?
-How do you know he's cheating on you?
-I just know.
Are you sure he's in his room?
Absolutely.
Why did you bring us?
Noi-Nae.
Yes?
Why are you wearing my shirt?
I wanted to try it.
No, no. Don't touch my things.
You know I don't like it.
Give my shirt back.
Okay.
Which room is it?
One...
Three...
Your man boobs are very cute.
When I'm excited,
I can't control my boobs.
Two...
Five.
Jesus!
Wow!
This is why you don't read my messages,
right?
Noi-Nae! You bitch!
You sit down! What?
-Calm down, baby!
-Why should I calm down?
Babe, calm down. It's nothing.
Nothing? She's naked.
-I'm sure this isn't some game. Don't beg!
-Just don't move.
It's really nothing.
Nothing? Then what is this?
-Baby, just stay there.
-I'm the baby, she's the bitch.
You are the baby. I am sorry.
Please help me.
Do you like fake boobs?
They are real.
How can they be real?
I can tell they are 350 cc.
Who do you think you are?
You think you are that good?
A lady-killer?
Look at yourself in a mirror, fatty!
-Can I leave?
-You want to leave?
-Come here.
-Wait!
-Baby!
-My shirt!
Open the door! Give me some clothes!
Shut up!
Nervous? Why didn't you think
before you acted? Nervous now?
-Open the door!
-Wait.
You...
please help me.
Please.
-I think we need to help.
-No, don't.
Let's just watch the situation.
Mr. Ae!
-Open the door!
-Just a second.
What is going on here?
-Please help me.
-Don't.
People are fighting. Don't get involved.
It's dangerous.
Give me some clothes!
Shit!
You meatball!
I told you to bring me the clothes.
I'm so fed up.
All these times,
no matter how much you sucked,
or got fat, or changed,
I've never minded.
You've never cared, never listened to me.
Whenever I needed help,
you were never there.
Always said you were busy.
You didn't have time.
Open the door!
We split the bill at restaurants.
You never treated me.
It's okay that you don't treat me.
But sometimes I have to treat you.
Baby, calm down.
I know you are angry, but...
The girl is naked out there.
And this apartment,
everyone knows it's my room.
It won't look good for me.
Please help me.
Don't worry. Calm down. Chill out!
Are you all right?
I guess it's a good thing.
At least, I am out
of one of my safe zones.
Thank you for coming with me.
You can go now.
Sak.
Do you remember Mr. Wittaya,
your dad's friend who works in a bank?
I think so.
He texted me the other day,
said he had good news.
What news?
He's going to start working at your bank.
He's throwing a party at the bank,
so he asked me to sing there.
I will introduce you to him.
Shit!
Sakrin.
-What?
-Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Thank you. You can request any song.
Please tell me the songs you like.
It was a disaster at your house.
This place is even worse, too many people.
You are worried over nothing.
Are you sure about this?
Hi!
What did you greet him for?
We have to blend in.
I thought you would bail on this one,
Chatchai.
Who is Chatchai? I'm Pakorn.
Pakorn. Really?
Why did you change your name?
Too bad.
Pakorn is better.
Never mind.
Let's drink together tonight.
I will get us some drinks.
Wait here, Sumet.
I'll be back. Let's go.
Baby, I need to talk to you.
I have nothing to talk to you about.
I saw your friend around here.
Who?
Your bikeman friend.
But I saw him in a bank uniform.
-Do you see anything?
-He's here. Oh, no.
Uncle!
You are here, too?
How could I miss such a big event?
Where are you going?
-I'm hungry. I'm gonna grab something.
-No need.
There's plenty of food here.
Here. Have some bruschetta.
Open your mouth.
No, I already bit this one.
Okay, I'll go grab something.
Don't go!
Here, sticky rice and mango. Want some?
Don't take it. There's only one cup left.
Let me have it.
I'll get something else for you.
It's okay. I'm full.
I'm going to the toilet.
What the heck?
He said he wanted to eat something.
Now he's going to the toilet.
His behavior is really suspicious.
You left us there.
I didn't leave you guys.
What are these?
I grabbed the whole tray.
Only foreign brands.
Let's leave. The longer we stay,
the more problems we'll have.
Mr. Ae...
I have an urgent matter
that needs your attention.
Why leave so soon?
There's still plenty of food.
Preecha.
Have you seen Sak?
I saw him just now. He went to the toilet.
Speaking of toilets,
I've been singing for hours,
I want to pee, too.
I can't hold it anymore. I have to go.
Is she crazy?
What's the point of telling me that.
Let's leave, Sak.
Are you Sakrin?
I'm Uncle Wittaya,
your dad's friend.
Hello, sir.
-Hi.
Your mom sent me some photos.
You are even more handsome in person.
Let's go talk outside.
Wait! Sorry, sir.
-Mr. Wittaya?
-Yes.
Since we have the honor of meeting
one of the bank executives,
how about...
you have a drink with us,
the lowly employees?
Really?
In the restroom?
No problem, sir.
This way, if we get drunk,
we can vomit here.
Good idea.
-Cheers!
Sir, have you seen Sak?
No.
What's going on?
Look at the time.
Even though the customer's rushing us now,
we still have to work tomorrow.
They can't hold their liquor.
Let's go see you mother.
My nephew's name is Suchart.
He also works here.
Do you know him?
-The guy in the glasses?
-He doesn't wear glasses.
That's him, my nephew.
Ae, come here.
That's Suree.
Wonderful! Now we all can meet.
Sak.
-Hello, Director.
-Hi.
Where is Mrs. Pranee's paper?
Is it in the car?
Remember? Mrs. Pranee.
Which Pranee?
That Pranee.
Pranee, Pranee.
Pranee!
Please excuse us.
Uncle, you know that guy?
He's my friend's son.
Wittaya,
where did Sak go?
He said he had some work to do.
Sakrin. What the hell is going on?
You have to explain everything.
I graduated almost a year ago.
I applied for a job at several places.
They all rejected me.
That's why I work as a bikeman.
I'm the only son in the house.
I can't make any of them proud.
Why do you want to work in a bank?
It's not a cool job.
People these days don't think that way.
I don't care about others.
It's not important
how other people think these days.
My dad used to be a banker.
He used to work in a bank.
He was everything for us.
He provided for us.
Mom and Grandma used to live well.
When my mom looked at him,
it was obvious how she felt.
Now that he's gone,
everything's changed.
I want my mom to be proud of me
the way she was proud of my dad.
How long are you going to keep lying?
I don't know.
But...
I don't know what to do either.
Don't lie, then. Tell them the truth.
I'd rather die.
You are overreacting.
The truth will never die.
It's okay to tell the truth.
You are not my family,
you don't understand.
So what now?
Are you going to be a biker
who pretends to be a banker forever?
-That's a stupid idea.
-Yes, it's stupid.
You don't know what I've been through.
I sent my resume to dozens of places.
Three times to TMB, four times to SCB,
twice to Kasikorn Bank,
five times to Bangkok Bank,
six times to GSB, once to Krungsri Bank.
They all rejected me.
I partnered up with a friend.
He took the money and left.
It's not like I want to be
a poor bikeman for the rest of my life.
Whatever.
You wouldn't understand.
Right, I don't understand.
I don't understand
why I care for a loser like you.
Now I know your secret.
I will tell everyone.
I'm really drunk.
Let's go home before anybody catches us.
Where did that bastard go?
You bumped into him.
Is he dead?
I don't know if he's dead,
but he peed his pants.
Shit. He should have pissed
in the toilet first.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm at fault.
SAKRIN
If you don't forgive me,
I will keep apologizing.
Doctor, will he survive?
He is safe now.
Then why is his tongue like that?
It's a side effect.
You agreed to see me.
You're not angry anymore?
Wrong.
But I have something important
to say to you.
Listen.
If you are afraid to tell the truth,
why don't you make it a reality?
Try again.
NORTH CHINA BANK
AVAILABLE POSITIONS
I've tried 21 times.
How do you know
you won't succeed the next time?
Listen.
A lie is like a bandage.
It can cover up the wound,
but it will never heal it.
Do you want to keep that wound
for the rest of your life?
You can say cheesy things, too?
Don't change the subject.
I will tutor you. Okay?
Fight!
We're starting now?
You can use this conversation
with Chinese customers.
Our bank has Chinese customers.
Have you left the house?
Soon. Almost ready.
Let's meet at the station.
Don't forget your book.
I won't forget it.
TYPE YOUR NUMBER TO CHECK THE RESULT
DOWNLOADING
The Internet is slow.
Want to try again?
YOU DID NOT GET THIS POSITION
The page might not be working properly.
I will check at the bank again tomorrow.
It's okay.
You don't need to check it.
I didn't get the job.
Hello! What's up?
Ae is going to your house.
What?
Mom.
You are blocking the TV, you know?
I know.
She just doesn't care.
Ma'am,
do you know your son...
is a liar,
a fraud.
Who? Who is a fraud?
Your son.
The reason I'm here today
is that I want you to know the truth.
Your son is a liar.
He did many bad things.
What did you say? Come again.
From the beginning?
Yes.
Ma'am.
I'm here to tell you...
your son lies about everything.
He lies to his salami.
What salami?
I'm not talking about salami.
I meant his family.
He lies about everything to everyone.
He just keeps lying
and making a big mess, ma'am.
All right.
Write it down.
Thank you.
-Ma'am.
-I said write it down.
Right.
Serves you right!
A liar like you!
The truth is you are just a lowly bikeman.
Asshole.
Stop pretending.
Mom!
Grandma!
Grandma is dead.
Going through the market
takes seven minutes.
What are you talking about?
I am calculating the best route.
Crossing the railway will take...
-five minutes.
-What?
Sak! It's a curve!
Sak!
Truck!
A train's coming!
Sak!
Let's go. What are you waiting for?
HOSPITAL
ACCIDENT AND EMERGENCY
I'm sorry.
I don't want you to feel embarrassed...
that your son is just a bikeman.
I'm not embarrassed.
But I'm angry that you lied to me
for a long time.
Why didn't you tell me
before that jerk did?
Though it was bad, your grandmother and I
would've still felt better than this
if you had told us yourself.
We all...
have lied to others at some point.
I also lied to you.
The day after the party at the bank,
I bought a train ticket and followed you.
FOR MOM
You might be embarrassed
that you are a bikeman,
but I'm not.
The way you are not picky about jobs...
you're doing your best
to support the family.
I think it's too cool and admirable
to be embarrassed about it.
Honey,
I am proud of you. You know that?
Believe me. If your dad were here...
he'd have said the same.
As for your grandmother,
you can apologize to her later.
These are the medical expenses
up to today.
BALANCE: 7,423 BAHT
I heard your grandma's in the hospital
and you don't have any money.
So I want to help out.
-How would you help me?
-What a question!
I'll help you pay the bill.
That's okay.
You don't need to.
But I want to help.
I'm already here.
Hi!
How did you get here?
The same way you commute.
I'll hang up now.
It's wasting phone credit.
How did you know
my grandmother was in the hospital?
Everybody knows.
Thank you, but you don't need to help.
The bill is...
too expensive.
Told you it's expensive.
There must be a way.
Look over there.
There!
Hey, bro!
I heard you don't have enough money.
So, we...
brought you some.
Give you.
I and my friends.
Open.
Where did you get the money from?
How dare you ask that?
Do I look poor to you?
You look penniless.
Listen to him.
I shouldn't have asked.
So where did you get the money from?
Fast cash
and a new bike to ride here.
FAST CASH
APPROVED
Take it.
You can pay us back when you can.
But...
No "but" between true friends.
Though we are lowly bikemen,
you can trust
we are as good a friend as any.
-How's that?
-You are very cool.
Hello.
Hello. I'm calling from SCB.
May I speak to Mr. Sakrin?
Speaking.
Our bank has a position available.
We would like to invite you
to work with us.
What did you say?
You are the first on our waiting list,
so we chose you.
-Really?
-Yes.
Can you start working next week?
Next week?
Yes, definitely.
Okay. See you. Bye.
Bye.
What are you grinning about, Sak?
The bank has a position available.
You mean...?
Mom!
Sak got a job at the bank!
-Yeah!
Great job, my son!
What are you doing?
I'm going to bed.
What time do you go to work on Monday?
Why do you ask?
I have something to tell you.
About what?
I will tell you when we meet. Good night!
What?
Initially,
I want you to work at the front.
-Yes, ma'am.
-If the customers have any problems,
or need some advice,
you can ask your senior colleagues.
Okay.
He was fired
because he messed around with a trainee.
It's against our rules.
Don't make the same mistake.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's continue.
As for this spot,
it's only opened
when we have too many customers.
MISS JARUNEE KITMANGMEE
Here's your desk.
She was our employee.
She just resigned.
But some of her stuff is still here.
-She quit?
-Yes.
Well, that's it.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes, ma'am.
Uye, can you check
if Mr. Ong-Art is coming?
Where are you?
What did you do?
What did I do?
You quit the job,
so there's an open position for me.
If you wanted to help me,
you didn't have to do it this way.
Who said I helped you?
So why did you quit?
I want to get out of my safe zone.
You mean...
you are a pilot now?
No.
What?
Then why are you wearing this uniform?
You also wore a bank uniform
when you were not an employee.
I want to try it, too.
But soon,
I will make it a reality...
like you did.
Are you done trying on the uniform?
I'm done.
Do you want to have dinner? My treat.
Sure.
Did you answer too quickly?
You don't have to treat me. We can share.
I'll treat you. Don't worry.
What a sugar daddy!
It's nice to eat out with a lady.
Can you please be my baby?
-I want to have pork barbeque.
-What?
No answer for me?
Let's eat first.
Okay?
Subtitle translation by
Tongta Suthummarangsi