BIKEMAN 2
Wanna go have lunch? My treat.
So generous of you.
Of course.
Can I be your treat?
-I want pork barbeque.
-What?
You're not gonna answer that?
Well, let's eat first. Okay?
Okay.
-We need to get away from that truck!
-Why?
Come on! Go!
Why are we rushing? Who is that?
I'll tell you later! Go!
Father.
Where and when are you taking me
on your pilgrimage?
We'll travel next month
because it's an auspicious time.
We'll walk northeast.
A new monk like you
should walk to meditate,
and nothing will alarm you.
Monks!
What the hell?
Father, I've seen monks
jumping across walls,
but never onto a truck.
How did you do that?
I don't know how I got up here.
Help me get down.
Such rash driving.
They'll get hit by a truck.
That sounds like a truck.
-Put me down.
-Father.
Now do you know how we got up here?
Yes, sir.
I think we should start
our journey tomorrow.
What about the auspicious time?
We can't wait around
for another truck to hit us.
We'll die first.
So who was that?
-That's my dad.
-What?
Sakkarin, quick!
I'm trying!
Didn't you see my car?
Where the hell are you going?
Damn, you're as bald as me,
but you got a barcode-like
hairstyle going on.
Let me give you some advice.
Never wear a hat.
You'll get a rash. It's humiliating.
What do you want?
Don't talk to me like that.
I was a cop, you know?
Cobra-class, you know?
-No.
-Fine. Whatever.
Come any closer, and I'll knock you down!
I'll beat you up. Don't you dare!
There you are. The cop is here.
Sir, you don't have to stop me.
Stop you? I'm only here to see what's up.
Well, this guy ran into my car
that's parked here.
He didn't even apologize.
He was just going to leave.
-Where did you park?
-Right here.
You can't park here.
Shit. Did not expect that.
So what? Move the car
if you two want to fight.
If you won't move it, then go pay
the fine at the station.
-Move!
-Where are you going?
To the station!
Shit, that's twice you crossed the line.
Barcode, watch the back for me, will you?
So?
Do you know how some people
aren't close to their fathers?
I'm one of them.
My parents split up
when I was a little kid.
I lived with my mom in Ayutthaya.
When she died,
I had to move in with my dad.
I didn't stay home much during college
because I didn't want to see him.
That's why I don't really tell anyone
about him.
But then he came to Bangkok
and happened to see me.
He probably wanted to talk.
What a small world!
All of that
just because he wanted to talk?
What if we owed him money?
He would kill us.
Maybe.
Ae keeps sending me songs.
Stop texting me and sending me songs!
That's it!
Jai!
Hey, Sak.
-What's up?
-Where is Long?
-What's going on?
-A lot.
Damn. I'm out.
Hold up. Listen to me.
-What?
-Sit down.
Some drama?
Can't you just tell me later?
I'll get some food.
Sit down.
But I'm hungry!
Let me order you some food via Grab.
What?
-Chicken and rice, then? With soup?
-Sure.
Hey, you!
-Did you order the food?
-Yeah.
I knew it. This address was so familiar!
You deliver food now?
Of course! When there isn't much business
at the motorbike taxi stand,
I work as a Grab food driver.
So easy to apply, and you make good money.
Everyone is doing it.
How much?
It's 140 baht.
Your treat, then.
Son of a bitch.
I have to deliver and buy you food?
You're crazy!
Why are you here, anyway?
Shouldn't she delete his number
if she's over him?
She still reads his texts.
Even though she complains, she looks sad.
Ae just texted me. He's so persistent.
"Hungry? Eaten anything yet?
If not, let's get something to eat."
Lame!
He doesn't even know
this is a break-up song.
Stupid men! So shallow! Men suck! Idiots!
Even though he's an asshole,
I still can't get over him in a day.
So you're not over him?
I see. That's why you're sad.
Not just sad. I'm annoyed, too.
Well, like I said, love,
it hurts people differently.
Hold on.
You're telling him to stop hoping?
No. Don't stop.
-Keep hoping.
-What?
Because...
you are more special than all of us.
Keep your chin up, Sak.
One day,
Joom
will see it.
Her name is Jai.
Well, she looks like a "Joom."
Jai. Why did you run away
from me yesterday?
Damn. If only I could stop being afraid
and learn how to drive again,
I would be able to drive
and deliver clothes farther.
But the course costs almost 5,000 baht.
So expensive, right, Mom?
See? Not even listening.
-Are you leaving for work?
-Yes, Mom.
Hello, everyone,
I'd like to introduce you
to the new generation of entrepreneurs.
Nora-singh!
-Hello.
-So smooth.
I have something really nice
to show you today.
It will make your life better.
Dad. Tell them.
Golden jewelry.
Real ones cost 20,000 baht.
This one costs 200 baht.
-Son.
-Yes.
-Convince them.
-Right away.
What's up with you two again?
You're so old-fashioned.
This is the latest way to make sales.
It's called a rap.
Isn't his dancing cute?
Shit, the tie doesn't go with it.
I was a street fighter
Fiercer than all, not a loser
Tell me your troubles
And I'll fix all your errors with my fists
But now I'm a new person
Throwing away all of my bad deeds
Now I'm selling jewelry, come look
Come see
You can touch them
Earrings, necklaces, bracelets
To make you look stunning
Turn heads, crowd amazed
They'll ask where you got them
They'll get jealous
Call you a rich thug
Miss, do you want some?
Why are you spitting so much?
Are you crazy?
Auntie didn't say anything.
Her spits did sync
with every beat, though.
When did you start chewing that?
-None of your business.
-What?
Stop it.
So you ran away from me
because you quit your job?
When did you quit the bank?
About two weeks ago.
Why?
-I want to study to become a pilot.
-A pilot?
Do you think it's that easy
to become a pilot?
I let you come to Bangkok.
That doesn't mean
you can decide things on your own.
Got a boyfriend?
Why?
My friends have kids.
It'd be nice if you met them.
They have good jobs.
I'm an adult now.
I can choose my own boyfriend.
Doesn't mean you'll choose a good one.
-But--
-No "but."
-But I have a boyfriend.
-What?
Who is he?
You don't know him.
-I want to see him.
-What?
Bring his whole family,
so I can meet them all at once.
-But--
-That's it.
Is it the guy with the motorbike?
Sorry.
Something wrong, Jai?
So... she doesn't want to be
controlled by her dad,
so she lied about dating me,
and so he wants to meet our family.
What? The whole family?
Yes. Can we go?
What's her father like?
He's very strict.
At work, he's in charge of workers
blowing up rocks at the mine.
And he likes to shoot for fun.
Sounds like this guy needs to meet me.
I'm sorry, but I can't do it.
Sak, you're about to lie again,
and you're asking
everyone to lie with you.
You can do what you want. I'm out.
Suree.
-Suree.
-What?
What now?
What's the problem?
Your dad doesn't know who's in his family.
Hello.
-Hello.
Everyone, this is
Uncle Term and Uncle Mee.
-My dad's assistants.
-Yes.
All here? Let's go.
-You forgot something?
-No, Dad.
It's good that you're here.
Can you talk to your dad?
Tell him not to get involved
in risky business.
What business?
I don't want to say it.
You should go ask him yourself.
If both of you can't even say it,
how do you think I'll bring it up?
You're his daughter. We're just employees.
He'll listen to you.
Let's go. The car is over here.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Sak didn't really want to go.
-Yeah.
But Jai said,
if things go wrong there, he can leave.
It's much better than letting her dad
come and meet him here.
We have to help him, then.
Hello?
I get that you want to help,
but don't you have to work?
Fine.
I'll send you the address.
Okay?
-Don't tell me those guys--
-Yeah.
Where is Dad now?
There.
He's shooting the birds
that like to shit around here.
Is that right?
Hello.
This is my boyfriend.
I don't believe it.
What a coincidence.
Well, today's coincidence
is not like that day's incident.
Nora-singh, say hello.
You don't have to give him
any respect. Just say hi.
Why are you grinding your teeth?
The vibes are turning bad around here.
Are you all here?
Yes. Expecting anyone else?
Well, two more will be joining us
in the afternoon.
Let's get some drinks, then.
Thank you for coming.
I'd like to get to know all of you,
especially...
Welcome.
Is there something going on here?
I'll tell you later.
Today is gonna be super fun.
He'll want to question both of us.
You need to know how to impress him.
Don't mess it up. Otherwise...
we are screwed!
Sit down.
-Why do you like each other?
-Who are you asking?
Both of you.
You go first.
I think he'll ask
why we like each other.
And I'll tell him it's because you are...
...a nice person, a family guy,
and he also has a stable job.
You?
Why do you like my daughter?
What should I say?
Just say anything.
But you should be prepared.
And...
don't let him know
you're my fake boyfriend. Got it?
So what?
What makes you like her?
Because she's cute?
Or pretty and petite?
Or because she's sexy,
playful, and friendly?
I like her butt.
All I could remember
from our childhood is...
Jai's butt.
We were in the same class.
And she always ran very fast in PE.
I could never catch up.
And all I saw was her butt.
But after I got to know her,
it wasn't just that.
She is very kind.
Even though she's a klutz,
and it's funny how
she always walks into stuff,
she makes people happy
when they spend time with her.
She likes to help people.
If she hadn't tutored me,
I wouldn't have been able
to work in a bank like I do today.
Whatever I have achieved today is because
she helped me.
And...
I'd like to make her happy
in the same way that she makes me happy.
That sounds incredible.
But it's too much.
Unrealistic.
Mom, do you remember
when you first met me?
You told Sak's dad you didn't like me.
You thought I wasn't a hardworking person
because I was a singer,
and he'd end up
taking care of me when we got old.
Look at how things turned out.
Your son decided to die first.
And I've been taking care of
both you and Sak ever since.
It proves that you cannot judge someone
so quickly. Am I right?
Sure.
So now that you understand,
you don't hate me anymore, right?
I still hate you.
Damn.
Hello, everyone.
Sorry we're late.
You look dapper.
Is everyone here?
Let me introduce everyone, then.
My dad, Sakda.
And these two...
These two?
-They are--
-Wait.
Let them introduce themselves.
We're Sakkarin's uncles.
I'm Aong-aj, and this is Aj-aong, sir.
So you work for an airline?
Well, yes, we're captains.
Usually, I'm not in Thailand so much.
Always flying.
Usually Eastern Europe.
Going farther and farther.
I spend most of my time in cold cities.
Enough!
Stop blabbing about your job.
I'm glad to be able
to come here and visit Jam's father.
It's Jai.
-Now, this is what you should know.
-Wait.
I thought you said you have
a mom and a grandma.
So who are they?
Damn it, Sak!
You didn't tell him I was coming?
Well...
his mom...
She fell ill. Very ill.
What's wrong?
Stroke.
Oh, no. She's actually okay.
You don't have to lie.
It's the truth.
His mom got so sick
she needed to be on bed rest.
She needed to use her hands
to lift her legs just to switch sides.
Luckily, I found some herbal medicine.
I gave her some.
Now she doesn't use her hands anymore.
So she's better?
No, she can't even lift her arms now.
Still on bed rest.
Probably the side effects.
What's wrong? Want some to chew?
Will that help?
It'll help to pass the time.
It's quite hot.
Dude! Stay on track.
I didn't get enough sleep.
I'm so thirsty.
Here.
Excuse me.
I'll go check if my employees
have your rooms ready.
What a shame.
I was just starting to have fun.
Want to leave right now?
I don't think he believes us.
Right?
Relax. I'm doing very well here.
-"Very well"?
-Yeah.
You keep adding stuff
and rambling on about nonsense.
Nonsense?
This is what a conversation sounds like.
I'm a professional.
One more thing!
My dad really likes jungle food.
He also likes to cook.
-Remember?
-I remember.
Almost dinner time.
What would you like?
I like jungle food.
And...
I'd like to try to cook too.
Good. I like jungle food, too.
You'll help me in the kitchen today.
Okay.
Yes, Mr. Reang. We got the stuff.
Thank you so much
for getting someone to find it.
-Yes.
-What do you think is in there?
Maybe some boar meat.
Boar meat, my ass! What moves like that?
Thank you.
Oh, fuck!
-What?
-No, no, no.
Cooking the snake might be too much, Dad!
Why?
But your boyfriend said
he'd like some jungle food.
Hi, Mee. What?
Chai wants to know
if we can reduce the price?
But our prices are the most reasonable
in the area.
-Why does he keep pressuring us?
-What's wrong with you?
No, he's already getting a discount.
Girl, tell your dad to look over here.
-Dad!
-I won't!
Even though he's a regular,
this is the price!
This is fucking intentional!
Hey, Mee. I have another call. Hold on.
Hello.
-Who's this?
-It's me!
Who?
Look over here!
Are you crazy?
The snake is so close
it could bite our ass!
What's wrong?
What you're holding is what's wrong.
Well, let me know
if there's anything I can do to help.
The snake is already tired.
It won't bite anymore.
Look.
-Jai.
-Yes?
Get the pan ready.
And, you, come make the chili paste.
I'll get the whiskey.
It'll help with the aroma.
Maybe...
How about this?
You make the chili paste,
and I'll get the whiskey.
Or what you said.
Come on, go. Go.
Quick.
I'm going.
What?
The snake's gone.
The snake's gone!
Man!
This is insulting!
As a mine owner,
he should treat us better.
Son of a bitch.
We only get some stir-fried cobra.
-Yeah, so cheap.
-Shut up!
-Where did it go?
-How would I know?
Is it near your legs?
Where did it go?
-Or did it get out?
-What?
Your suit looks very nice.
What airline is that?
-Vulture Airline.
-Is that a real airline?
We fly like a vulture looking for corpses.
Amazing.
Where are you going? Wait for me!
Everyone, the snake got out!
I don't know if it's over there.
Shit!
How did you let it get out?
-Yeah.
-I don't know. It just got away.
-There!
-Where?
No. That's not it!
-Find it. Move the table.
-I'm looking!
-Come down and help.
-Shit!
I'm looking!
This one.
Yes, Reang.
I'm about to cook it.
-Find it.
-Son of a bitch!
Where is it?
Find it before I kill it.
-Hey!
-Leave me alone!
You have to help too.
-It's not my job.
-What?
It's Buddhist Day today.
I don't want to hurt animals.
It's not my job either, you know?
Let's find it, quick!
Not here.
-Nora-singh.
-Yes, Dad.
-Look at that corner. Find it?
-Not here, Dad.
What about there?
-Where?
-Not here either.
-Look closely.
-Not here.
Look below.
-Still not here.
-Lower.
This is the lowest. Not here.
Lower than that!
Not here.
Why is my mouth so dry?
Move it. Move the table.
Where did it go?
What?
That's the wrong snake?
Why is that?
What's so different about this one?
This one is aggressive?
Don't tell me it's under there.
Not here.
Is that...
Of course, it's me.
It's up my leg now.
On my calf now.
Almost at my crotch.
Don't you dare! Those are my balls!
Quick!
Quick! It's almost at my balls!
What should we do?
Get something to beat the snake with!
Help your dad.
That won't do anything!
-My balls!
-Bigger one!
-What are you waiting for? Hit it!
-Hit it!
-Stupid snake.
-You've come here to die!
-Hit it!
And I thought I would spare you.
Hit it! Hit it! Hit it!
What am I? A drum set?
Beating me like that.
What do we do now?
It's probably dead now. Get it out.
-Just pull it out.
-You do it.
Why me?
-Come on.
-Pull it out.
Go on.
Pull it out.
Throw it away!
Please forgive me, snake.
Is that blood?
Snake's blood.
What's that mark?
Probably a pimple burst.
Did you get bitten?
Take that back! I'll slap you!
No snake can bite into my thick skin!
Everything is back to normal.
Don't touch me!
Dad.
I said don't touch me. I can walk!
-So obvious.
-Yeah.
Look, he's sweating,
and his lips are turning blue.
Shit, your dad got bit.
I think it's fine.
I opened the bag, and it's quite mellow.
No need to change. Yeah. Bye.
-Let's go to the doctor.
-What?
-Tell your dad.
-Dad, let's go to the doctor.
Why the hell are you talking
without any sound?
Shit, his hearing is gone.
Why is it so quiet?
This is bad.
What?
Can't hear you!
Louder!
You got bit!
Who's a bitch?
What's going on?
You're really lucky
that we have the antidote on hand.
I've administered the dose.
You should get better within two days.
Why the cast, Doctor?
Well, this has nothing to do
with the snake bite.
His leg was broken, so I put a cast on.
By the way, did someone beat you?
My asshole son finally got me.
It wouldn't have come to this
if you had taken better care of the snake.
Hi, Thep.
Your son is back from Australia?
Okay.
I'll take my daughter to meet him.
I just need to take care
of something first.
Sure. See you next week.
Bye.
Dad.
Sakkarin didn't mean to cause all that.
Don't defend him.
I'm not stupid.
How is it possible
that the family sells gold
and one of them is also a pilot?
Tell your boyfriend and his friends
they don't have to fool me any longer.
I want to meet who they truly are.
And then I'll decide
if they're good enough or not.
They can leave if they don't like it.
Clear your schedule too. Next week.
You can stay here, but I'm leaving.
Look at the cast on my leg.
And the owner of this house hates me.
I won't help Sak if I stay.
I'm leaving!
You're not going to say anything?
You don't even care. Not even listening.
Who am I even talking to?
I think you should go.
He doesn't care at all.
Of course, I should go.
What kind of person
doesn't do anything all day!
He just plays with his gun.
Shooting birds.
I wonder if he has hit any.
Son of a bitch!
Of course, right when I'm leaving.
-Nora-singh.
-Yes, Dad.
Is that blood?
No, it's all shit.
Then why is it so sweet? Let's go.
-Let's go to the hospital.
-Let's go wash this shit off.
Let's calm down and talk.
I know your business isn't doing so well.
Not many buyers for minerals or rocks.
Wouldn't it be better
if you sold me this place
so I can turn it into a 5G antenna field?
The money you're offering me
is chump change...
compared to what you'll make
from a 30-year contract
with the cell phone company.
It's ten times more
than what you're offering.
Wouldn't it be better if I did it myself?
Go home.
Well, it's up to you, then.
Good day, Sakda.
I don't understand.
Why does Dad have to be so strict?
Because he works a dangerous job.
It's normal.
I've never gotten to choose anything
on my own, you know?
Since Mom's been gone,
Dad's been choosing everything for me.
And now he wants
to choose my boyfriend too.
Maybe he just wants the best for you.
Sure...
but he never asks
if that will make me happy.
Maybe he doesn't know how to do that.
Just like how I wanted
to make my family proud by lying.
To be honest, I used to wish
I had someone else's dad.
Having a strict dad is better
than having no dad.
But I don't have a mom.
Well...
if we were really dating,
we'd have a mom and a dad.
I see what you're doing.
Don't blame me for trying.
He was about to get bitten
by a snake, so I jumped in!
Suree...
At that moment,
I didn't think about my life at all.
Of course, I didn't want to die,
but Sak is just like my son.
Maybe the snake thing
was his plan, after all.
This is the detonator.
We dig a tunnel
into the mountain and set up a bomb.
We keep the detonator here
for safety reasons.
The bomb's timer is set
so they'll go off one after another.
Make yourself at home.
How can you make yourself at home here?
I don't think he wants
to show us his mine.
He just wants you to see
what will happen to you if you upset him.
That's reassuring.
I came back to tell you
that Sakda hates your son!
Then, you take me there.
-Fine, but promise me...
-What?
Are you taking her?
Are you crazy?
Let's go.
Let's have a drink.
Thank you.
This is my mom.
Oh, really?
Not your grandmother?
Mom!
Did you get better?
I was told you were in a coma.
She's all better now.
Is that what you told him?
Was it Aong-aj?
It's good that your mouth
is not twisted anymore.
You do look pale, though. Is that normal?
Long was just rambling.
That’s why I’ve been sneezing a lot.
So what changed your mind?
Why do you think he wants
to meet our family so much?
He probably wants to get to know us
and see if he can accept us.
-That's why I'm here.
-Yeah?
I have the right to see this family, too.
I also want to know if I can accept
my daughter-in-law's family.
Daughter-in-law? We're not even dating.
So sad.
How did it go yesterday?
He doesn't like us that much.
Not surprising. Look at your friends.
But I don't like that guy either.
This will be fun.
Here, sir.
No name on the letter.
We don't know who sent it.
Quiet! Did you hear something?
How did you get in here? Get out!
Get out!
What's going on?
What the hell is this?
Shit. Right in the middle.
What is it, Suree?
I don't know how he got in here!
Don't tell me you were going to rape her!
Give me the towel!
This is awkward.
All of you! Get out!
Not yet! Nobody moves!
-What?
-What's going on?
All of us!
I heard something weird.
Like a sound?
Nora-singh! What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm practicing my rap.
You're an idiot! In the middle
of the night? Are you crazy?
Let me hear it.
I got real gold, rare gold
If you get cold, let me get a hold
I got my bike--
Shut up! No more rapping!
Now get the hell out!
Get out!
Let's go. Out!
Suree, go on. I'll keep guard.
What are you thinking?
Nothing! I regard her as my sister.
Such a nice guy.
I see you take up a lot of space, Suree.
Go!
I'm so done.
Let's be honest.
I don't think it will work.
Then let's do this.
What?
My dad knows a lot of things,
and he likes to teach people.
And he's very happy doing it.
So what's he going to teach me?
I have an idea!
Sak! Where are you taking me?
You said you always
wanted to learn how to drive,
but it was too expensive, right?
So what?
Ready?
You said you'd take care of it. Did you?
I'm an impatient man.
I want to see things get done.
I already cut the brake lines on his car.
But are you sure we want to go that far?
Driving is not that hard.
I knew how to drive,
but then I got into an accident.
So I got scared and stopped.
I've forgotten how to drive since then.
Why are you telling me this?
I'm saying I'm not stupid!
Let's go, then.
Show me how you change gears.
But first, you need to step
on that clutch pedal.
Then change gears.
Step on it and change the gear like this.
What?
I can do it myself. No need to touch me.
Let's go, then.
Release the clutch and step on the gas.
Yeah. That's it.
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I thought
you were the grandmother.
I'm sorry I burst in
when you were in the shower.
I'm sorry I haven't been
exactly nice to you.
But this is who I am.
Drive properly. Step on the gas!
Step on it!
Cargo bike! Turn!
Watch out!
Oh, my God!
-Chickens!
Stop! Stop!
What the hell?
I told you to brake.
I did! The car wouldn't stop!
Of course, it would! We almost died!
Well, you're a terrible teacher!
Well, you're a terrible driver!
I didn't want to learn in the first place!
I didn't want to teach
in the first place either!
How can he call me stupid?
How dare he!
He is the stupid one!
What a terrible day!
Take her to a driving school.
She's too far gone.
-Take it!
-Okay.
Must have gone badly.
No doubt.
This is bad.
Only someone on the inside
can mess with my car.
Can you look into it?
Yes, sir.
So he's starting to get suspicious?
Then you guys must hurry.
If cutting the brake lines didn't work,
what else could we do?
She quit?
Yes, she left a long time ago.
Didn't you know?
But I saw Oui,
and she said she just saw Jai.
She said she was going back to Ayutthaya.
Ayutthaya!
Or could it be...
I just bit my own tongue.
Off I go.
There you are.
Tell your boyfriend
to join me for drinks tonight.
-Okay.
-Why are you smiling?
My dad always relaxes when he's drunk,
so you can score some points.
But I'm not a heavy drinker.
Just ask Long and Preecha to help you.
-You think it'll help?
-Yes.
-Sak! You bastard!
-What?
Not you.
I mean you!
It's a shame that you're rich,
but you don't know how to dress like it.
You need some jewelry. Look!
Let me give you some advice.
You need a little gold on you.
You really wanna make a sale now?
He's drunk.
It is the perfect time to sell.
I heard that!
I don't mind. I'm also drunk!
I don't like gold.
You don't like gold?
Why didn't you tell me?
Then you'll like this.
This is a talisman, right here,
a good one.
It's very easy to use.
Just chant this mantra.
Buddham Saranam Gacchami.
Dhammam Saranam Gacchami.
Sangham Saranam Gacchami.
It'll protect you 24 hours a day.
Take your stuff back.
I see you're a fierce one.
You must try this.
This is what they call "Heavy Metal."
How is it? Look.
Metallica fans
will want it as soon as they see it.
They'll take it right off your wrist.
I'm going to be honest.
I don't like fakes.
Son of a bitch! You can't say that
when you haven't even bought my stuff.
Let me give you some!
Calm down!
I'm sorry.
Let me take care of it.
How much is it? Couple thousand baht?
This is 360K.
How much?
360,000 baht.
I should go to bed.
When did you get so sleepy?
When you said 360,000 baht.
Is that the liquor's price or a plane's?
So damn expensive!
Let's go to bed, or we'll miss
the monks in the morning.
No turning back, quick.
Can I pay you back in installments?
Let me announce
the buffalo racing event in Chon Buri.
It takes place every year
on October 18th at Ban Bueng.
My honored guests,
before we start another race...
Hi, Grandmother.
Hello.
Do you remember me?
I'm Ae, Jai's boyfriend.
You fell down once, and I helped.
Are you alone?
Let me get to the point.
I'm Jai's boyfriend,
but we got into a fight.
I've been calling her,
but she hasn't picked up.
I really want to see her. I love her.
Has she been here at all?
Want some of this?
Some of that?
No, Ma'am. I don't like it.
I'd like to see Jai. Is she not here?
She went to her dad's house.
Her dad's house? Where is it?
Want some of this?
No, ma'am. I don't like it.
I don't chew that at all.
Her dad's house?
Never mind. Now I know she's
at her dad's house. I'll find it.
I've got a map.
Really? You've got a map?
Why didn't you say so?
If you don't mind, Grandmother,
can I have it?
I'm sorry, but it doesn't look good.
-I figured.
-What?
I'm just thankful for the help
you and your family have given me.
I know no one
can change my dad's mind that easily.
-Nora-singh.
-Yes, Dad.
Sakda is biased against all of us.
Yeah. It doesn't matter how nice we are.
Look. He left us here
in this shitty market.
There isn't even a Starbucks!
It's noon now.
Where do I get pizza around here?
-How much for this chewing gum?
-Five baht.
-Damn! Can it be two baht?
-No, sir.
I don't have enough money!
Why don't you try to meet
your dad's friend's son?
Why should I? I don't like them,
and I don't want to know them.
Maybe you'll like them.
Maybe the son's very handsome,
and they're super rich.
I don't like someone that easily.
And you don't get over someone
that easily either, right?
Let me tell you something.
Jai!
Ae!
For someone who drunk liquor
worth 360,000 baht yesterday...
Today, he's drinking a 30-baht one.
What a joke!
Sakda, can we sit with you?
I assume that is a yes.
Do you have a problem with me?
I do.
Do you ever want to slap my face?
Every single time.
I feel the same.
Let's do this.
We'll both drink and slap each other.
And after that, we become friends!
You said it.
A man like me always...
Keeps his word.
-When in Rome...
-Do as the Romans do.
-I tell you it's bad...
-Then it's good.
-I tell you it's good...
-Then it's bad.
That's not right!
Who goes first?
You shouldn't have asked.
Since you're the host, you can go first.
Fine.
Ae!
Your love
Your voice saying that you care
Your hands
Touching my forehead when I get sick
Everything
Every chapter is still here
Doesn't matter
How much time has passed
Everything
Every chapter keeps telling me
Who I am since I've lost you
Ae!
I'm the foolish one
True love is here
But I can't take care of it
And I've only realized
When it's too late
It hurts and I want to go back
But there is no way
Bravo! Bravo! Bravo!
You're going to regret this.
Do you really need to stand up?
That's too much!
Nora-singh! Stay out of this.
Can you check?
Your hair is still there.
Just the bald spot, then.
Check your dad out. My best move.
I'll give you that.
Have you seen Sakda?
Why are you here?
I'm here to make up with you.
How did you find me?
It doesn't matter.
My heart told me to come here.
Please come back to me.
Ae, let go of me!
Boss,
-something's up!
-What?
Quick, boss!
Shit! Why did it have to be now?
Sakda!
-Stop!
-Let go!
Ae, let go of me!
Who the hell are you?
And who the hell are you?
-I'm her dad!
-Hi, Dad.
I'm not your dad.
Well, no, but you're her dad.
What the hell are you talking about?
Here's the thing.
My name is Ae. I'm Jai's boyfriend.
Impossible. Jai's boyfriend
is right there.
Him?
No, bullshit! I'm her boyfriend.
Jai. What is up with this clown?
What's going on?
Ae, you'd better leave.
Dad, calm down.
You can't tell me to calm down.
Wait. Can you hear me out, Dad?
I'm not your dad!
Get the hell out of my house.
Sak, let's go.
Mom, wait.
He's kicking all of us out,
and you still want to be here?
Let's go.
Get out of my way!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mom.
It's all my fault.
I just thought...
coming here to please him
would please her, too.
I'm such an idiot.
Everything is ruined.
Forget it.
But...
do you really think someone would love you
just because you please them?
Listen to me, Sak.
That's not the only reason
someone would love you.
Look at your dad when he was alive.
He didn't try to please me at all.
Nothing romantic.
But every time
that I had problems or I was upset,
he was always there beside me to help.
He wasn't able to help all the time,
but he was there.
Now, that is love.
Thanks, Mom.
What's going on?
Where are you going, Sak?
I'm going to help them, Mom!
Let's go help them get along.
Are you crazy?
We just left, and now we're going back?
Wait here a moment, Mom.
Take this for me.
What?
-Jai!
-I thought you left.
What about your dad?
He went out. What's up?
I've been thinking about it. I want--
Hello, Uncle Term.
Are you with the boss? I can't reach him.
He's not with me.
I think he went to the mine.
Your dad wanted me
to find out who's been trying to kill him.
Kill him?
I know who. I'm sending it to you.
If cutting the brake lines didn't work,
what else could we do?
Hurry up and think.
So you can get the money.
Why do we have to come this far?
This is well past the spot.
Well, Mee said maybe
we can find some minerals here.
So he asked me to bring you.
That's not possible.
I already checked from the satellite.
There's nothing left here.
It's just a waste of time.
But... Mee said there might be some.
Hello.
I'm going to call the police.
You try to get a hold of the boss.
Tell him not to go to the mine
because they'll try
to kill him with a bomb.
Okay.
What's going on?
I'll get Mee to come talk to you, then.
You wait here, okay?
It's right here, Sakkarin!
Where are you going?
Long story, Mom!
Suree, stop pacing.
Your blood pressure will go up.
So...
No one is going to help Sak at all?
Just going to sit here and do nothing?
Who here knows how to drive?
You're looking at the one.
I know how to drive.
But my leg is broken.
No chance. No one else can drive.
He's not picking up.
There's not much of a signal.
Hello.
Did you get him into the cave?
All done.
Good. Let's do it.
Are you really serious?
Why do you ask? We've come this far.
Mr. Kongphop wants to see it happen.
Get it done.
Look!
They're following us!
This is a nice place to walk
on our pilgrimage journey.
It is also safe here, don't you think?
Yes, Father.
Watch out!
Father!
What the hell? Learn how to drive!
Did you even see the monks here?
Yeah, we are monks. Not some goats.
Father, watch out!
Where are you going, Father?
-I'm done.
-Father?
I'm done being a monk. Done.
Should we stop?
They will ram us to the ground.
Let's not give up! Hope is just like air.
Just because we can't see it
doesn't mean it's not real.
Sak! Here I come!
Suree,
can you drive faster?
I just learned how to drive again.
This is good enough!
Good enough? Here's good enough!
Here!
I'm going to give you a big one.
-Nora-singh!
-Yes, Dad.
Give them the big ones.
You go, Sak! The path is clear!
It'll be a while before someone passes by.
Stay there, suckers!
Have you seen my dad?
Yeah. He went into the cave with Bo.
But Bo already left,
and I saw him go into the office.
-And Dad is still in there?
-I think so.
You go get Dad in the cave.
I'll stop Uncle Bo.
Okay.
What now, Sak?
You go help Jai.
I'll help Jai's dad in the cave.
-You're going alone?
-Yes.
He's right to go alone.
He needs to rescue someone.
You're not thinking straight!
What if the person he rescues gets hurt?
Someone needs to be there and help.
He's right to go alone!
There must be two people!
It will take up too much space.
How much space can it take?
Pick someone thin.
-Who?
-You find him!
What the hell are you looking at?
I shouldn't have said
that you needed someone thin.
Come on. I'm glad you're with me.
But I'm not really glad.
-Uncle Bo, don't!
-Jai!
Let go of that. Give it to me!
-Let go!
-You let go!
Jai, let go!
-Jai!
-Uncle!
Where are you?
I'm outside, Sak!
You go ahead!
Jai! Quick! Stop the bomb!
I can't stop it! He already set it off.
Shit!
Sakkarin, are you in the cave?
Sakkarin!
He must be.
Why does that sound so close?
Oh, my God.
Is there no other way to stop the bomb?
Yes, there is.
Usually, they set a bombing route.
Two to three bombs per zone,
and they'll set a timer.
When you press the button,
the bombs will detonate
from the inside to the outside.
But the outside already blew up!
Really? Then something is wrong.
What do we do now?
There are two more ways.
First, we need to find the second remote.
Where is the second remote?
Where is it?
-Think! Where is the second remote?
-Where?
You need to ask Mee.
What? Would he give it to us?
Yeah. What's the other way?
Is there another way?
You just said so.
Is there anyone else working here?
Another way.
There!
Turn that off.
-What's up, Jai?
-Dad!
They're going to kill you!
Sakkarin is going there now!
-You need to get out! There's a bomb!
-What?
Here's the breaker.
If we can turn that off,
it will cut all the electricity
inside the cave.
Then the bomb won't detonate.
-Do you have a ladder?
-I did before.
-What about now?
-It's right there.
But don't worry.
We have a hydraulic system here.
Just press this, and it'll come down.
Why is it not coming down?
Must be broken.
What a waste of time. Get on my back!
Dad, run!
Where are we going?
We'll go find Mee.
We need another remote to stop the bomb.
-Wait.
-What?
How are we getting there?
Here.
What the hell are you doing? Get on!
Let's go!
Higher!
I can't reach it, Dad.
I can't push any higher!
I can't reach it! Almost there!
Step on my head!
Are you sure?
You already stepped on it, you asshole.
Stay still, Dad! You keep moving!
Higher!
I'm already standing on tiptoes!
There are four! Which one?
The right one.
Not that. It's the left one.
Son of a bitch! Just say, "The left one!"
It's not coming down.
Try the other one!
Which way is it?
I hope this is the right way.
Bo, did you press the button?
I did.
But they tried to stop me.
Right now they're trying--
Bo?
Hi, police, where are you now?
Jai?
Did you see Sakkarin?
Found him!
Which way?
Take a right. That's zone B, a shortcut.
Okay.
They're going to zone B.
What? Don't go to zone B.
Don't go to zone B!
Don't go to zone B! Tell them!
It's a dead end!
Sakkarin, do you hear me? It's a dead end!
Go!
DANGER
LANDSLIDE
The bomb!
Dad, it's broken!
Sakkarin!
What's wrong? Sakkarin!
Sak!
Sak! Are you still there?
Say something. You stupid son!
DAD
I'm still here, Mom.
Jai, wait for me.
I'm driving your dad back to you.
-There they are!
-Yeah.
I see them!
Shit!
Why did you stop?
Stop, my ass! We're out of gas!
So what now?
It's okay. We can go on.
Go, quick. Hold on tight!
Holding on tight!
They won't get away.
Where are you going?
Sakkarin! What's wrong?
Sakkarin!
Come here.
We both can't get out.
You get out and leave me here.
Go on.
Don't waste your time.
No!
Go!
I want you to tell Jai
that I'm so proud of her.
I'm so glad
to have a daughter like her.
I wanted her to be a good student,
and she was.
I wanted her to have a good job,
and she got a position at a bank.
I always tell everyone
how lucky I am
to have her as a daughter.
But I've never told her that in person.
I guess I've lost my chance now.
No.
Both of us can still get out.
We can do it.
That's impossible!
Listen to me.
It's impossible!
Dad! Dad, don't do this. Dad!
You must get out, Dad. I don't want this.
No.
You have to trust me on this.
Stop!
Stop now!
Where are you going?
I told you to stop!
Stop!
A little bit more, Dad.
Where are you going?
-Let me go!
-Dude, stop the bomb now!
We did it!
What's that?
Probably the coil.
Sak!
She doesn't want
to be controlled by her dad,
so she lied about dating me,
and so he wants to meet our family.
I'd like to make her happy
in the same way that she makes me happy.
It's too much.
Where are you going, Sak?
I'm going to help them!
Wait for me.
I'm driving your dad back to you.
There!
Sak!
The police arrested a suspect today,
an entrepreneur,
charging him with the attempted murder
of the owner of the mine.
They think the motive
is connected to the land's royalties.
Do you want to talk?
I'm not the one who wants to talk.
Dad, you're always so strict.
That's why I'm always afraid of you.
I never had the courage
to be direct with you.
Your mustache alone scares me.
Ever since I was little,
I always did what you told me to.
I studied accounting
because you wanted me to.
I worked in a bank
You have no idea
what I had to go through each day.
I had to sit on this one chair,
right under the AC.
I had to tolerate all kinds of customers,
get scolded for every little thing.
I got yelled at for small mistakes.
And then the boss came
and yelled at me some more.
You said you choose everything
for my happiness,
but it is your happiness.
I'm not happy
with the things you choose for me.
I didn't want a dad like this.
So strict. So controlling.
I wanted to run away from you.
But not anymore.
When I saw that bomb go off...
I only thought about one thing...
I wanted you to come back and be with me.
You can scold me whenever you want.
I know now
that you love me
because...
I love you very much, too.
Is that all?
Dad!
I love you, Jai.
I know.
I'm going now.
Going where?
Anywhere! I'm an adult.
So...
Yeah.
I know now
that what you said about her
was not exaggerated at all.
Take good care of her.
But she doesn't like me.
Of course, she does.
I'm her dad.
I can tell.
If you don't believe me,
go ask her yourself.
What's wrong?
Well...
I have a question.
Okay.
So...
What is this between us?
Attention, passengers boarding the train
from Kanchanaburi to Bangkok...
Let me say goodbye to my dad.
...train number 486,
please wait on platform 7.
Sak, you're not coming?
We're leaving. Come on.
Okay.
-Quick, we're leaving.
-Okay.
Here.
-Hey.
-Yes?
You raised him well.
It's very good
that you raised him this way.
Thank you for that.
Sure.
Hello, Thep.
I'm sorry.
I can't take my daughter to meet your son.
Look...
My daughter already has a boyfriend.
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
Talk later.
-What are you smiling about?
-Nothing.
The train is here.
Let's go.
Attention, passengers
boarding the train from Kanchanaburi...
-Good luck, kiddo.
-Bye, Dad.
Please have your tickets ready...
Go.
Please board and find your seat.
The train is currently leaving the station
from Kanchanaburi to Bangkok.
Passengers, please remain seated
while the train is moving.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going? We're leaving now.
I must do this.
When did you get so brave?
Attention, the train
will be delayed for five minutes.
Don't tell me.
Delayed quite often, huh?
One slap each, now we're friends.
Delayed by five minutes.
Come visit me sometimes.
Sure.
Don't jump. It's dangerous.
Honey.
Ae.
How did you get here?
It doesn't matter.
I know now that I can't live without you.
I remember how we used to be.
I can't live without you.
Give me another chance.
Let's get back together.
No!
Ae, listen.
We're over.
No, not over! Listen to me.
I have a new boyfriend.
Bullshit!
Lies!
Who is it?
He's right here.
It's Sakkarin.
I don't believe you.
I don't buy your fake boyfriend story.
He's not a fake boyfriend. Watch this.
I want to kick his stupid tongue.
You really think
I'll believe you because of that?
We did more than that!
Let me show you.
Don't!
Is he dead?
-Let's go.
-Yes, ma'am.
Jai!
What?
What was that?
What was what?
What you did.
That is it.
That is what?
Go figure it out.
I don't want to figure it out.
I want to hear it.
Are we...
together now?
Yes. I think so.