Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
NETFLIX PRESENTS
Priming the detonator now.
Don't trigger until we are safe.
Hot chocolate?
I'm Naomi.
I work for the police.
What's your name?
You don't need to be afraid.
You're safe here.
Anything else you want?
Cookies, maybe?
Can you tell me what happened on board?
Were you traveling with your parents?
Worldwide, the markets are showing
an 8% surge,
driven mainly by airline stocks.
Analysts predict
a strong course correction
which means the markets might face
some instability for some time.
In spite of the market's current high,
it's still a risky moment
in terms of investment opportunities.
This volatility is also confirmed
by the fact
that gold is at a new seven-year high.
The situation resembles earlier periods
of an overheated market…
Hello.
Where's your mom?
She'll be here soon.
She told me to check our bags.
Wait, I'll help you.
Thank you.
What have you got in there? Rocks?
-Hello, little man.
-I've checked the luggage.
No problems.
You're awesome.
-Elias?
-Yes?
I love you.
See you in a bit, Mom.
There you are! Sweetheart.
There you are. You did great.
Is this yours?
Yes.
I have a prescription.
Mommy will be right back. You stay here.
-Okay, I promise.
-Good.
Excuse me?
It's daytime in America now.
Look, we are here.
It's night here.
And New York is over there, to the west.
It's day there now. We're flying this way.
But the earth turns this way.
So night will be five hours longer for us.
We'll land at night,
even though it'll be day here.
Wow.
That was a real scientific presentation.
-Isn't your mother back yet?
-She's taking her medicine.
But there's a doctor in America,
Dr. Brown, who can help her.
He'll kill off her bad blood
and plant new bone marrow.
So she'll start making new, healthy blood.
I'm a scientist, too. A physicist.
I'm going to a convention in America.
-I'm Elias.
-I'm Farid.
-Do you have siblings?
-No, no siblings.
-Do you have a favorite team?
-Dragons.
Cool.
Hey, Mom. This is Farid.
He helped me with the luggage.
-Would you like to sit down?
-No, thanks.
It's a bright boy you got there.
He sure is.
Come on, honey.
Here, Mom.
Rainer, there's no need to be rude.
Those are our compartments.
Just sit, dear.
-Are you comfortable?
-Yes, I'm fine.
So, would you like some coffee, gentlemen?
-Oh yeah. I'll take--
-Black, two sugars?
-You're the best, Julia.
-And one with lots of milk?
Bastian?
Yes, right.
Robert, the guy in 1A is all yours.
The new guy fits all the clichés.
-Are you jealous?
-Excuse me?
Well, now you're not the only one
after the copilot.
The safety instructions
have been placed in the seat pocket
in front of you.
We are third in line for takeoff
and are expected to be in the air
in a few minutes.
Please fasten your seatbelts
and secure all baggage
under your seat
or in the compartments above.
Ensure that your seats and tray tables
are in the upright position.
So?
No idea.
What are we going to do?
You wait in the car. I'll get help.
Someone's freaking out.
Everything is fine, honey.
Go back to sleep.
Hey, Michael. Do you need help?
No worries. I've got it.
Answer! Where is he?
It's gonna be all right, sweetheart.
We're turning around.
No.
Everything is fine, sweetie.
They are just avoiding a storm.
Don't worry.
Look ahead.
Elias, cut it out.
Put it back.
-We can hide down here.
-Stop it right now. Put it back!
Peace be upon you.
Elias, I said stop it!
Move!
That was just my son.
-No!
-Get up.
It's all right.
"Rejoice
community of…
Muslims."
"Rejoice, community of Muslims."
"In our blessed martyrdom,
Allah the Almighty has allowed us
to carry out an attack on godless Europe."
I have been forced to read this message.
We have nothing to do with the hijacking.
Please help us. Allah akbar.
Read it how it's written.
Already?
You can't do that.
Go back to your seat!
-I thought you were dead.
-It's fine, honey.
We have to turn the plane around.
It'll be fine.
Go!
Don't look.
Fuck.
-What are you doing?
-I study aerospace engineering.
Sit down! They'll kill all of us.
Brother, why New York?
-I'm going to a convention.
-Me too.
Nonsense, they're not terrorists.
Why? Because they don't have beards
and pray towards Mecca?
They want to crash the stock market.
Like the bombing a few years ago,
the soccer club.
I've spent a few hours
in a flight simulator, but I…
It will be all right. I promise.
Did you drink blood?
You have to take your medicine.
Hey, everything okay in there?
That wasn't me.
They've got the autopilot on.
Don't.
Let them jump first.
-Turn the plane around.
-What?
I said turn the plane around!
But we're way closer to Europe!
Shit!
Turn around!
Now!
Fuck!
Open the door. Elias!
Can you hear me?
Listen.
You're right. Don't open the door.
No matter what, you're safe in there.
We'll make it. I promise.
Here. It's all right. Okay?
Your baby has been crying
for two hours. Everything all right?
I'm here.
I was hoping you'd come back.
You killed my son. Do you know that?
He bit me.
He had no control over it.
But you do.
No one does.
The evil is too strong.
We are all cursed.
We bring nothing but suffering
to this world.
No! No, stay here!
Come back in. They'll be back!
-Go back.
-I won't leave you alone.
Come! Hurry up!
Help me!
Wait!
Hide. Get in there.
There's no deity but God.
Muhammad is the messenger of God.
Leave her alone!
I have to kill your mama. She's evil.
You're the evil one!
Don't move!
Can you do that?
Can you shoot someone?
Come on!
We are cursed.
We cannot allow this evil
to keep spreading.
This evil cannot keep spreading!
We have to stop it.
You have the evil within.
And you cannot
control it.
Everything okay?
-I want to see my mom!
-No.
Elias, stay here.
Out of the way!
-Mom!
-Elias, stay here!
Let's get out!
We need help!
Help!
Did he bite you?
Ingelore?
Ingelore, where are you?
I'm looking for my wife.
Give it to me.
Out of the way!
Let me through!
-I need to find my wife.
-Where is she?
The monster got her!
She's not a monster!
Hey, not through here.
Hey, kid! What's wrong with your mother?
-She doesn't have leukemia.
-I never said that.
-Don't hurt her, please.
-I won't, I promise. What's her name?
-Nadja.
-Okay. You stay here. Watch him!
Sure.
Mama, watch out! They want to kill you!
Mama! Can you hear me?
They want to kill you!
Nadja? Can you hear me?
Elias sent me. We don't want to hurt you!
Ingelore!
Ingelore. What happened to you?
Oh no, this can't be.
No!
Give it to me! Come on!
-Wait! Hold on.
-You killed my wife!
Hey! Stay here! Stop him!
Don't do it!
No!
Don't shoot!
We can't let them come up.
You have to help her!
He bit me.
I can't feel my fingers!
Shit.
Stay here.
Oh my God. Elias! Get some help, quick!
Quick!
Help me!
We need heavy people
to weigh down the hatch!
No!
Don't bite him!
Stop, go away! Don't drink his blood!
Elias, get back. He's dangerous.
He wants to be healed, just like you!
-No! Don't!
-Calm down!
I'm right here.
My hand got caught in the cargo hold door.
Your mom helped me.
Come.
Elias. Come.
Turn the plane around.
-Do it!
-I have to check our route. We're too low.
-Mom.
-What's going on?
She wants us to fly to New York.
But we're too low and short on fuel.
We have to divert to the nearest airport,
or we'll crash into the sea.
-Turn that plane!
-We can't make it to New York.
Do you understand?
It's dark down there.
Come on, let's go!
They wanted to blow down the door.
Watch out, it's on!
Not anymore.
It's gonna be fine. We'll wait until dark
and catch the next plane to New York.
Mom, look how far we've come.
Mom! Please, we'll can do it.
Dr. Brown will make sure
we get the Cytarabine.
We'll have enough time
to plan the next flight.
Shit.
Fuck!
-What's wrong?
-I don't know. Something's wrong.
-Bastian!
-What's going on?
Get down.
Wait, I'll help you.
Hey, what are you doing?
We can help them!
We can hide them down there!
If we open the door,
we'll never get it shut again.
We can't land.
What do you mean?
You want to crash the plane, or what?
They'll hide in the cargo bay
until dark and then get out, all of them.
We have to inform officials.
And tell them what?
We have vampires on board?
No, we have to…
We have to land and then jump.
Here. If we attach this to the fuel tank,
it'll blow up the whole plane.
How do we get there?
-That's the fuel tank.
-Fuck. Shit.
What?
The detonator has no timer.
Is there a remote?
-Yeah.
-Where is it?
Curtiz had it.
-Where is that arsehole?
-In the rear cargo hold.
Okay.
-Does this lead to the back?
-Yes.
Man!
Shit! It's way too narrow.
Can we detonate manually?
Yes. But then we'll blow up too.
You land the plane.
And as soon as you're out,
I'll blow it up.
No, Mama!
-Yes, Elias.
-We can get you out of here.
-You can hide in here.
-Elias, we have no other choice.
-I can fit. I can get the remote.
-Elias, it's over!
Do you hear me?
Forgive me, please.
I can get past with this.
Elias--
Stay here, Elias! Shit!
Fuck.
No! That's suicide!
He'll make it. Look.
That's the remote control.
Elias, can you hear me?
The cell phone is the remote control.
Be careful. Don't press the big button.
Elias, come back.
Elias, you hear me? Come back.
Elias, run!
No!
Shit!
How hard is it to land the plane?
What? Why? We'll make it.
I entered the coordinates.
We fly to the destination automatically.
And the landing?
You have to stay in the air corridor
and brake. No problem at all.
-Can you handle it?
-What?
With contact to ground control,
anyone can, even with one hand.
You'll have to look after my son.
What do you mean?
Please, just promise me.
I promise.
Hey, what are you doing? No!
Mama! Help me!
Go away! No!
No!
Come on!
Come and get me!
No. Elias.
Mama!
Talk to me, please.
Shit!
Autopilot.
No! Go away!
Stay with me.
Where's Farid?
You mean Farid al Adwa?
He's still on the plane.
The police have him under control.
You have to get him out.
No matter what Farid told you,
he's one of the bad guys.
No! You have to get Farid out
to save him from the vampires.
-The plane is full of them.
-Calm down. What happened?
You have to get Farid out of there
before sunset.
We need your help.
Can you tell me
how many kidnappers there are?
They're all dead!
-Dead? How?
-They are all monsters!
You have to get Farid out of there
before the sun goes down!
-No! Stop it!
-Calm down.
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Let…
You have to
save
Farid.
No. Please! Don't!
You have to get Farid out!
Where's my teddy?
My bear!
Elias! I'm here!
-I'm here! Elias!
-Farid!
No!