I never get to know how you are
The news died down after we had parted
You have someone else in my place.
Is she good to you?
Do I appear in your dreams?
Or have you forgotten everything?
Do you still miss me
When you are alone?
Since you left
Your life seems to have changed
I still feel lonely and sad
Only loneliness was left in me
I still miss the old times
When there was only us
But there's only emptiness
And loneliness now
Do you know that I miss you?
I miss you every time
I'm alone
Since you left
Your life seems to have changed
I still feel lonely and sad
Only loneliness was left in me
I still miss the old times
When there were only us
But there's only emptiness
And loneliness now
Do you know that I miss you?
I miss you every time
I'm alone
Excuse me. Can I have a cigarette--
Taweesuk Alley, please.
Ninety-five baht.
Here you go.
Should we cook for real?
Hey, are we allowed to play with fire?
I don't know.
I'll ask Mom.
What about others?
It's all right. I'll join later.
Honey.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm all right.
Do you have a session today?
Of course.
Will you finish late?
Yes, I have to stay late to grade papers.
Again?
Come on, I'll try to find some time
next week.
I'm not asking for my own sake.
You're working too hard
that we barely have the room to keep
all the money now.
-I'm leaving.
-Okay.
Miss,
your daughter is already too old
to have an imaginary friend.
I think she should receive a full therapy
at the hospital.
I'll show you something.
Can you tell me about Toto?
I can't
because
Toto doesn't want me to.
Why? Is it because Toto doesn't like
your mom?
She's not here right now.
You must not tell anybody, okay?
Toto has buried
Pug in the ground,
because he doesn't want me
to get thrown out of the house.
When Pug grows up,
it would be as if
Mom has two children,
and she will love Pug more than me.
Please, miss.
Please do something
before it's more than just a pet.
Hello, honey.
I still can't find my wallet.
You really haven't seen it anywhere,
right?
No.
Oh, you went back to the office yesterday,
didn't you?
You might have left it at the hospital.
Oh, right.
I'll go back to look for it again.
-You're forgetful these days.
-Doctor.
I'm hanging up.
I have to go back to work now.
Professor, what are you looking for?
It's my wallet.
I have no idea where I left it.
Well...
When was the last time you saw it?
Never mind.
So, are the students ready?
Yes, they are.
Dr. Jib.
Please dress properly. Your shirt is out.
Oh, I'm sorry.
The part right here,
please freeze it in another room.
Oh, very good.
Have you located the bicep tendon?
Is it around here?
Yes, look for it, so you can answer
Professor Suthee when he comes.
Are you doing it right?
Of course, I strictly followed
all the procedures.
Look, here's the flexor
that Professor Suthee talked about.
-It's right here.
-Where?
-You idiot!
-You guys are shrieking like scaredy-cats.
Hey, Dr. Jib.
I have taught you to become
a medical professor.
I didn't teach you to become friends
with those students.
What's his name?
His name is Siwapong, sir.
Siwapong.
Tell him
I have to deduct 30 points from him
for acting inappropriately
as a medical student.
For you,
if you still can't control your students,
I can't approve your status
as a medical professor.
How's Usa doing?
What?
I'm talking about Usa.
We haven't seen each other in ages.
Well, she's fine.
By the way, what do we do
about Professor Dararai?
Sir.
I'm talking about Professor Dararai.
Well...
The students want her signature
before they withdraw from her class.
Just leave it like that.
I'll take care of it.
You can go now.
Excuse me, then.
Let me know when you have to be
on duty at night.
-Aey.
-What?
Let me know when you have to be
on duty at night.
Why?
It's so that I can find some company.
Are you scared?
It's pretty spooky around here,
but you'll get used to it soon.
Chon.
Did you see something?
Hey.
Don't do this.
Really, someone got murdered
near the main road last week.
I don't believe you.
-How is that funny?
-You're such a chicken.
So what?
You're a sissy.
-I'll put it right here.
-Okay.
Hey.
I wanted to ask you since you came in.
-What is it?
-Whose car is that?
It's the owner's car.
He let you use the car?
Yes.
I hardly use it.
He's very kind.
I want to meet him in person.
When is he coming again?
He rarely comes.
He's been busy lately.
Have you found a place to stay?
I have been here for just two days.
I also haven't unpacked my boxes yet,
and you already want me to leave?
No, I'm just afraid that if he shows up,
I wouldn't know what to tell him.
Do you have money?
Yes, I do.
Are you sure?
Sure, I'm fine.
-Chon.
-Yes?
Are you thinking straight these days?
What do you mean?
No sane person would put a rice cooker
in a fridge. Take it out.
Oh, I'm sorry. I forgot.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm just absent-minded.
Do you need help with anything else?
Remove the shell of the prawns
and clean them.
Why don't you do it yourself?
I don't want to commit a sin.
Hey, aren't you afraid I'd commit a sin?
You're already a big sinner.
Just do it and stop complaining.
Okay.
Let me ask you a serious question.
What now?
Do bears really eat bees?
I have no idea.
Don't they teach you that
in medical school?
Do they really eat bees?
-Come on, I really want to know.
-Hey.
Hey, Chon.
If you don't stop talking,
I'll eat you instead.
-So, you don't want the prawns anymore?
-No!
Are you done yet?
Hey, Chon!
What did you do, Chon?
-That hurts!
-Be quiet. You're crying like a baby.
What are you looking for?
I'm looking for a needle and a thread.
A needle?
Why do you need it?
Are you going to stitch it up yourself?
Yes.
No! Look at the wound!
Go and get a real doctor to treat me!
I told you not to shout.
I'm a doctor. Can't you trust me?
Also, stop talking.
Stay here. I'll find a needle
and a thread.
Hey, if somebody finds out,
don't tell them you're with me.
Got it?
Why are you making that face?
"I understand."
Very well.
What are you doing here by yourself?
Oh, what happened to your hand?
Come, let me look at it.
Wow, it's a really deep cut.
Why are you treating it yourself here?
Well...
I...
Do you cook your own meal?
Oh, yes.
I was slicing a prawn.
Maybe it wasn't completely dead,
so it took revenge.
Okay.
I...
Tell me honestly.
So,
which drugs are you on?
Doctor.
I'm not on drugs.
If you don't believe me,
you can test my urine.
My urine, my blood, my hair, anything.
I'm clean. I'm not on drugs.
Excuse me.
Please look at the light.
How many fingers do you see?
One.
Three, maybe.
Please do what I tell you.
Touch the tip of your nose,
and then touch my index finger.
Do it back and forth.
-Like this?
-Yes.
Yes, and touch my finger.
Yes.
-And?
-Touch your nose, back and forth.
Touch here.
Faster, please.
Do you have any other symptoms,
such as insomnia
or hearing things?
I don't remember.
Can you remember how many fingers
I just showed you?
Listen, Doc. I was cut by a knife.
I don't think that has anything to do
with counting your fingers
and touching my nose.
Then, please look at your name and tell me
if it's spelled correctly.
CHONLASIT
It's already correct.
Chonlasit.
Please try to talk to this person.
She might be able to help you.
Who's this?
She's a psychiatrist.
I got cut by a knife, Doc.
-Dr. Jib.
-Wait up.
-They need you immediately at ER1.
-Excuse me.
Wait up.
Excuse me.
Please give me a second.
-Please let us through.
-Excuse us.
Please let us through.
It's an emergency case.
This way please, Doctor.
Hang in there.
Hey, why did you have to be
so secretive back there?
Aren't you a medical student?
I don't think they would mind you
borrowing their equipment.
Hey.
I could be expelled
for stealing a government's property.
Would you be able to look after me
if I get kicked out?
You're exaggerating.
Hey.
Are you that rich?
I helped you, and you're complaining.
"Usa."
Which Usa is it?
A psychiatrist.
-A doctor who treats psychopaths.
-What?
That psychopathic doctor referred me
to a psychiatrist for a knife cut.
I bet he'd send his wife to a dentist
if she were giving birth.
Chon.
Have you been sleeping well?
I...
have been having nightmares.
What are those nightmares about?
Chon.
I think you really need treatment.
Are you also saying I'm crazy?
I just want you to take care of yourself.
If something happens to you,
I'll have no one left.
We only have each other, Chon.
Chon!
Let go!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Aey.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
See the doctor tomorrow.
Please, I beg you!
I'll soon be strangled to death
if you don't!
DR. CHOOKIET WEERASAKKUL
INTERNAL MEDICINE DEPARTMENT
USA 091-8999065
I'm borrowing this for now.
I'll give it back.
DR. USA
I really want to know
who Chonlasit is.
Let's just say it's related
to Professor Suthee's job.
For the details--
Hey, Jib. I'm hanging up. He's here.
Hello.
Are you Dr. Usa?
Yes.
Please take a seat.
Have some water first.
Thank you.
Put it down first.
Well, Mr. Chonlasit.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Well, Dr. Usa.
I've been having nightmares
quite often lately.
What did you see?
I saw a murder.
I don't know who was killing whom,
but I saw the scene over and over.
-The victim was a woman.
-Over and over.
Her body was hacked to pieces.
-It seems real.
-I have no idea
how those images got into my head.
-The victim was a woman.
-But,
as days go by,
they keep coming back
over and over
until they seem real
-like they weren't dreams at all.
-You...
Are you going to say I'm crazy?
What does it feel like
when you're spaced out?
Everything was blank,
as if I...
I were sleepwalking,
but I was still conscious.
It's as if the dead woman
that I saw in my dream
wanted me to do something.
Why do you think that way?
I'm not sure.
You wouldn't want your wife
to see these photos, right?
I'm Dararai.
Find me.
She told me to find her.
Find who?
Why are you taking my picture?
Are you done?
Yes, I'm done.
What about the test result?
I have to analyze it first,
then I'll call to make an appointment.
I'm leaving, then.
Bye.
-Bye.
DARARAI
I don't think I'm going back again.
Why not?
It's useless.
Did she prescribe any medication?
No, there's no medication nor treatment.
Nothing.
You have to take some rest.
I don't think you understand.
He told me he's an engineering student
at Ratanaraj University.
Did he give you the same information
when you met him?
I didn't get into that much details
about his personal history.
There's another interesting point.
During the session, he mentioned a name.
What name?
Dararai.
Dararai, does it ring a bell?
No, it doesn't.
Why are you asking me?
Well, he mentioned this name
and your university,
so I thought you might know something.
Hello, Dr. Jib.
Just a second.
Usa, I have to go.
I need to hang up.
The nurse came to get me.
DARARAI RATANARAJ UNIVERSITY
RATANARAJ UNIVERSITY
GUEST LECTURER
DR. DARARAI SUWAMONGKOL
Hey.
I'm going to bed now.
By the way, don't stay up too late.
Okay, Mom.
Who are you calling mom?
DR. DARARAI SUWAMONGKOL
Chon!
What are you doing?
What are you looking for?
Dararai.
Faculty of Medicine.
-Excuse me.
-Yes.
I would like to see
Professor Dararai Suwamongkol.
A moment, please.
Nok, another one is here
to see Professor Dararai.
Are you the teaching assistant
of Professor Dararai?
Yes.
May I have a word with you?
May I ask who you are?
I'm Usa Pattanaphong.
Pattanaphong...
What are you looking for?
How are you going to find it
if it's this dark?
Do you feel
that this cabinet is at the wrong place?
It's just like
it's supposed to be somewhere else.
It struck me since the first day.
So?
Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to move it.
There might be something behind it.
Chon.
This isn't our house.
Hey.
Tell me honestly.
What if the story about
this Dararai person is
something you just made up
in your own head?
Where are you going?
I'm going to prove
that she's not just my imagination.
Which class did she teach?
She was our lecturer
on Therapeutic Hypnosis.
By the way, please keep this to yourself.
The students called her The Witch.
There are so many stories about her.
For example, this room.
On that day, I was her TA.
When I think about it,
it gives me the creeps.
This kind of memory is called
unconscious memory.
It is a remnant of a traumatic incident
that leaves a strong impact on the mind.
Even though we want to forget it,
or have already forgotten,
we can wake it up anytime.
Don't you get it?
I already told you.
Excuse me, please hang up first.
The class is still ongoing.
I'm hanging up.
I still have class.
I'm really in class.
Okay, I'll call you back.
The benefit of exploring this memory is
to locate the course of various illnesses,
either mental
or physical illness.
Physical illnesses that
were caused by mental illnesses...
Don't answer it yet.
Can you tell me
what you understand
about unconscious memory?
Well,
it's the kind of memory that...
I'm sorry, professor.
I didn't catch it just now.
Could you please explain it again?
Sure.
Let me answer the call first.
No, let it continue ringing.
How are we supposed to study then?
The whole class is waiting.
It's disturbing others.
Can you tell me
what the most embarrassing moment
of your life was?
What are you saying?
It doesn't make any sense.
Didn't your parents ever teach you
any social manners?
My parents have nothing to do with this.
FOUR MISSED CALLS
When was it?
I was eight.
The belt...
Who was it?
My dad.
Dad, please don't hit me.
Dad!
-Please, let me go!
-Professor, that's enough!
Please, don't hit me.
Do all of you understand
the meaning
of unconscious memory now?
This is it.
One by one, the students dropped out
of her class.
The professor herself also disappeared.
People always come to ask me for her,
but I really don't have a clue
of her whereabouts.
Why don't you go through her profile?
Well, she was a guest lecturer,
so we only have her name,
but not her details.
Why don't you ask the person
who recommended her to teach here?
Well...
It's a little complicated.
Well.
Don't get mad at me if I tell you this.
Why?
It's because I'm telling you
that Professor Suthee was the one
who got her the job.
Excuse me.
-Yes.
-Is Professor Dararai here?
Nok, he's looking for...
I'm afraid she's not here.
So, there's a professor
called Dararai here, right?
Yes.
May.
Finish your vegetables
and brush your teeth.
May!
Stop playing and brush your teeth!
Please listen when I tell you what to do.
May, let's go and brush your teeth.
Today, I went to
the Department of Psychology.
Sweetie, go on.
I'll catch up with you later.
I was looking for some information
for a case I'm working on.
Really?
There were people asking for you.
Who?
There were many.
There were professors
and a faculty member.
A faculty member?
The one named Nok. Do you remember her?
Hey, this is the concert we went to
the other day.
Yes.
You left us halfway through.
May and I had to come back alone.
Why did you have to go inside?
I should be going home now.
Where did he go?
I'm always in trouble.
You have really picked
a nice room to enter.
Where are you?
Ngor, have you seen Dr. Suthee?
I haven't seen him since I got here.
Good morning, Doctor.
-Hello. Is anyone here yet?
-Not yet.
Here's the note I wrapped up for you.
At three o'clock in the morning,
the police were informed of a murder
at Ratanaraj University Hospital.
At the scene, the police found the body
of Ms. Napat Duangkaew
on the floor of the hospital's museum.
There were deep cuts on her face and body.
The police believes
that the dead woman fell
on the barbed wire in the museum.
Initially, the police assumed
that it was an accident.
But they haven't confirmed anything yet.
They are still investigating the case
and collecting evidence
to verify the death.
She was a faculty member
of the Department of Psychology.
She's a teaching assistant
of the department.
Excuse me for a second.
-Hello, Usa.
-Jib, what's going on there?
It's like what you have heard.
It was an accident, right?
We still don't know.
They're doing the autopsy right now.
Why?
Do you know the dead person?
I went to talk to her yesterday.
Are you here to do the autopsy?
Yes.
This way, please.
The body is right there.
I didn't make it in time, right?
Do you think this is really going to help?
Anyway,
if what you're doing makes
you feel better,
then do it.
There are plenty of trees here.
Why don't you water them?
This one is dying.
There's no point trying to save it.
Chon.
Where did you put the umbrella?
What if that faculty member's death wasn't
an accident like the police said it was?
What if she was murdered?
She was killed because
I dragged her into this.
Chon.
Don't think too much.
It was not your fault.
Of course, it is.
I don't know how I can comply
with what the woman named Dararai wants.
Chon, don't!
-Fuck.
-Chon, stop!
Please, can you stop torturing yourself
with these thoughts?
I can't shake them off my head!
Chon!
Have you been waiting long?
Jib.
Why didn't you ever tell me about this?
How do you want me to say it?
I feel
that it's a family affair,
and I didn't want to meddle in.
How important was she to Suthee?
Actually, the professor felt very guilty.
That's all I know about Dararai.
SUWAMONGKOL
Prestige Clinic, may I help you?
Hello. Is Dr. Usa there?
I tried to call her,
but I wasn't able to get through.
Dr. Usa has gone to see someone
at Ratanaraj Hospital.
Thank you.
After a while,
the professor did try to
distance himself from her.
Whenever Dararai called, I was always
the one who answered the phone for him.
So, everyone knows about this, right?
No, that's not it.
I'm the only one who knows.
Usa.
Don't tell anyone that you heard
all of this from me.
Dr. Jib.
Where's Dr. Usa?
Did she come to see you?
Oh, yes.
She just left.
Well, Dr. Jib.
Do you know the woman
named Dararai?
Why?
It's Dararai. Do you know her?
Why are you asking me this?
What more do you want from me?
Well...
If...
if you know Dararai or anything about her,
please don't tell anyone about it.
It's very important. Don't tell anyone.
Otherwise, you might become
the next victim.
Just like that faculty member.
CHONLASIT'S CASE
Hello, Mom.
What's wrong, honey?
Usa, what's wrong?
About Dararai Suwamongkol,
the woman you had an affair with...
I know it's over,
but I just want to tell you.
Why did you do this to me?
You cheated on me.
Usa.
It's over.
She'll never come back
into our lives again.
SUBJECT: OUR PICTURE
Fuck!
My name is Dararai.
Find me.
I beg you. Please, leave me alone.
I'm scared. Please, leave me alone.
Please, don't do anything
to those who are involved.
Please, don't kill anybody.
Aey!
Let's go to the hospital now.
It will happen.
It will happen to you.
Find me.
Yes.
I'm on my way.
You're Ms. Usa, right?
The victim was struck with a blunt object
and was thrown into a vat
that was filled with
strong acidic solutions.
There's one thing
I'd like to ask you.
USA
I found this name card
at the crime scene.
More importantly,
your name and phone number
are written on it.
Do you have any idea
whom the victim gave this name card to?
You wouldn't want your wife
to see these photos, right?
Fuck!
SUTHEE PATTANAPHONG
DR. SUTHEE PATTANAPHONG
I want to meet him in person.
When is he coming again?
He rarely comes.
He's been busy lately.
Please contact us immediately
if you have more evidence.
Thank you.
Could you please find the address
of this patient for me?
May.
May, get Ngor on the phone, please.
Is this Dr. Usa?
It's Chonlasit speaking.
Do you remember me?
Are you home now?
No, where are you?
I'm outside your house.
You must come back here quickly.
I have something important to tell you.
Don't go inside my house.
I'm coming now.
Don't go inside!
If you go in, I'll call the police.
Hey.
Don't be afraid.
Stay with me first.
Dr. Usa.
I'm Chonlasit. Do you remember me?
Where's May?
May!
-May!
-Dr. Usa, please listen to me first.
-May! Where's my daughter?
-Dr. Usa, please calm down.
I have something to tell you.
It's important,
and you must know the truth.
Your husband killed
the woman called Dararai
because she planned to blackmail him.
That's not it.
Your husband also murdered your friend.
Your husband murdered Dr. Jib.
He also murdered the faculty member.
He murdered everyone who knew about it.
I have to tell you this
because
Dararai wants me to tell you.
Now, your husband has kidnapped
my sister.
You have to tell me where he is.
Where is he, Doctor?
You have to tell me.
He's going to kill my sister, Doctor.
You must tell me!
Tell me where your husband is!
Stop! I can't take it anymore!
I can't treat you anymore.
Let me tell you something.
You sister is dead.
The sister you're talking about
is dead.
How do you know?
You killed her.
You killed everyone.
You killed Jib.
You killed Nok,
and you killed Dararai Suwamongkol.
That's not true.
What are you talking about?
Don't talk nonsense.
I didn't do it.
The police already know about it.
Just accept the truth.
Let me help you.
I didn't do it!
It was your husband!
I don't know anything about this.
He took my sister. He's going to kill her!
You aren't Chonlasit.
Chonlasit is at drawer number 19.
Chonlasit
is dead.
CHONLASIT SUWAMONGKOL
CAUSE OF DEATH: SEVERE BLOOD LOSS
AGE: 21
Please give us the way.
There was an accident.
Go faster!
Chon!
Chon, you'll be all right.
Suthee, please don't let him die!
-You can't go in.
-Suthee!
Suthee, save my brother.
Chon!
It's enough. You did your best.
Suthee.
Can you keep him like this for a while?
There were only two of us.
Please don't leave me.
I have no one left anymore.
What if all of these are
just something you made up in your mind?
Why are you treating it yourself here?
Tell me honestly.
So, which drugs are you on?
Then, please look at your name and tell me
if it's spelled correctly.
Are you Dr. Usa?
They seem real,
-like they weren't dreams at all.
-You wouldn't want your wife
to see these photos, right?
She'll never come back
into our lives again.
There were people asking for you.
It was the faculty member called Nok.
Do you remember her?
-You might become the next victim.
-What more do you want from me?
You killed everyone. You killed Jib.
You killed Nok,
and you killed Dararai Suwamongkol.
Chonlasit is dead.
I didn't kill them. It was your husband.
CHONLASIT'S CASE
COURTROOM NO. 1
This is
Dr. Suthee's brain waves
when he thought he was Chonlasit.
Also,
we have tested his blood pressure
and his heart rate, and they show
significant discrepancies.
From now on, I would like
the psychiatrist to continue
with a detailed explanation.
The defendant is ill.
The medical term for his condition is
multiple personality disorder.
It is a form of hallucination.
Those who suffer from this
normally build another personality,
or thinks that he's another person.
Sometimes, he may have interactions
with imaginary people.
This is the case of Dr. Suthee,
who believes he is Chonlasit
and is still living with his sister.
Do you know the details of the murders
of Dararai Suwamongkol
and the other victims?
Yes, I do.
Do you know
who the killer is?
Yes, I do.
Can you tell us
who killed
those people?
Dr. Suthee did.
The court has decided
that in order to ensure
the defendant a fair trial,
the case will be temporarily suspended.
The defendant will be sent for
psychiatric rehabilitation.
When he is fully recovered,
the trial will be resumed.
The court has suspended the case.
Dr. Suthee.
We are taking you back to the hospital.
Mr. Chon.
Mr. Chonlasit.
Does he stand a chance of
going back to normal?
It's like he's trapped
in his subconsciousness
and refuses to wake up.
You mean he's stuck in a dream,
like a sleepwalker?
It's more like he's been hypnotized.
Are you serious?
Do you really believe that?
-How can a lawyer believe that so easily?
-Since you left
Your life seems to have changed
That's almost right.
I never get to know how you are
The news died down after we had parted
Suthee.
Look into my eyes.
Every time you hear this song,
you'll feel the happy memories
that the two of us have shared.
Do you still miss me
When you are alone?
If you ever think of leaving me,
this song
will remind you
of the bad things you've done to me.
It will possess you.
Even when I'm already gone,
you'll never be able to forget me.
Since you left
Your life seems to have changed
I still feel lonely and sad
Only loneliness was left in me
I still miss the old times
When there was only us
My name is Dararai.
Find me.
Since you left
Your life seems to have changed
I still feel lonely and sad
Only loneliness was left in me
I still miss the old times
When there was only us
But there's only emptiness
And loneliness now
Do you know that I miss you?
I miss you every time
I'm alone
I have forgiven you.
I'm going to set you free now.
Subtitle translation by Kong Rithdee