Mommy.
What is it, Xiao Le?
Poke! Got you.
Silly boy.
You little rascal. Where are you?
I'm coming to get you.
Xiao Le.
Xiao Le, come here.
Did you do this?
Answer me. Did you do this?
-Yes.
-Don't you have paper to draw on?
Why must you draw on the walls?
It was an accident.
An accident?
How was this an accident?
Why don't you just admit it?
It's all right, ma'am. I can clean it.
Go get the cane.
Go.
You know we just repainted the house,
and I've told you so many times
to be careful with your crayons.
Why don't you ever listen?
Put your hand out.
Sir, do you want to eat now?
What about ma'am?
She didn't eat.
Later.
Okay, sir.
What's wrong?
I recognize this piece.
You know me well.
I know something's wrong
when you play this one.
What happened?
Just feeling guilty.
I caned Xiao Le earlier.
Why?
He drew on the staircase walls.
We just had them painted--
I know.
Where is he now?
In his room. He's probably still awake.
I'll go tuck him in.
No, let me.
You better eat. It's late.
Not sleepy yet?
Patches is hungry. He wants a bone.
He wants a bone, huh?
Here. A bone.
Better now?
I want to hear a story.
Now?
Yes. Read me a story?
Which one?
Hansel and Gretel.
Again?
Aren't you bored of it? I certainly am.
Wait.
Read from this page.
From here?
Okay.
"And so, Hansel and Gretel discovered,
their stepmother wanted to abandon them
in the forest.
Hansel quietly sneaked out of the house,
and gathered as many white pebbles
as he could.
The next day, as Hansel walked
with his family deep into the woods,
he laid a trail of white pebbles
along the way,
so that they could find
their way back home."
Mommy, if you didn't want me anymore,
would you abandon me in a forest, too?
Maybe.
Of course not, silly.
Mommy will never leave you.
Shall we go to bed now?
Come on, lie down.
Hold still.
Your grandmother used to say
that a birthday is an occasion
for new clothes and new shoes.
Keep them closed.
They are.
No peeking.
Okay.
Guess what Mommy and Daddy got you
for your birthday.
A dog?
There you go. Happy birthday, baby.
-What shall we call him?
-Patches.
Patches? You've already got a Patches.
That's right. Pick another name.
How about Mozart?
Mozart? Like Mommy's favorite composer?
Okay, Mozart it is.
Hold on, boy. Mozart.
Mozart! Wait for me!
The party's at 3:00. Don't be late.
I just have this one meeting,
and then I'll be home.
I won't be late.
Mozart.
Xiao Le, don't run.
Your shoes.
-Nora.
-Yes, ma'am.
I have a headache.
I'm going upstairs to take a nap.
-Okay. Yes, ma'am.
-Okay.
Where's the birthday boy?
Ma'am? Are you looking for Xiao Le?
Yes.
-He's over there.
-Okay. Thank you.
Xiao Le.
Look how big you've gotten.
Do you remember me?
You've forgotten me already?
I took care of you when you were a baby.
Mozart, come back here.
-Nora.
-Yes, sir?
Is ma'am there?
She's upstairs, sir.
Please can you tell her I'll be late?
Yes, sir.
Where's Xiao Le?
Hold on, sir.
I think he's outside, sir.
Can I talk to him?
Yes, sir. I'm looking for him.
Mozart.
Xiao Le?
Mozart!
Papa wants to talk to you.
Papa, where are you?
I'm still in a meeting. I'm almost done--
Sing me Happy Birthday.
What?
Sing Happy Birthday for me.
Xiao Le, I can't right now.
Please?
Happy birthday to you...
Louder.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Xiao Le
Again.
Xiao Le, I'll sing to you
once I'm home, okay?
One more time. Please.
Happy birthday to you
Mozart!
Happy birthday, dear Xiao Le
Mozart.
Happy birthday to you
Mozart!
Hello?
Xiao Le?
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, ma'am.
Patches will keep you company now.
Okay?
Coming.
I want to see Jia En.
Jia En.
Jia En?
Why are you doing this to yourself?
Come on. Get up.
Get up.
Come on.
I remember
when I found out I was pregnant,
I took the home pregnancy test
over and over.
Went through five of those test kits.
You know, just to make sure.
I miss him so much.
I still feel his presence
in every room,
every corner of the house.
I don't know how to let him go.
I was Xiao Le's nanny once.
I loved him very much, too.
I know his spirit lives on through you.
When I was just a baby,
my mother gave me away
to a family in Ipoh.
There was an old man there
who could see things.
He was a medium.
A spiritual advisor.
I was very close
to the neighbor's daughter.
One day, while she was playing outside,
she got run over by a car.
For weeks after the funeral,
I would wake up with a start
in the middle of the night.
I felt something shaking me,
tugging at my blanket.
Only the old man knew.
He told me
the spirit of the neighbor's daughter
had returned.
But her parents had moved out,
left the past behind.
They were gone for good.
So she didn't know where to go anymore.
What happened then?
The old man performed a ritual
to remind her that she was dead.
So her soul could journey on peacefully.
From that night on, I slept fine.
Nothing disturbed me anymore.
The soup's cold.
-Auntie.
-Yes?
Is the old man still there?
He passed away years ago.
But since then,
his oldest son has taken over.
He's here in Singapore now.
What if I don't want to send my son away?
What if I wanted to bring him back,
have him here by my side?
Could this man help me?
Are you sure this is what you want?
She loved her son very much.
And he was her only child.
Can't you have another child?
Her womb is very weak.
She's had two miscarriages before.
After she had Xiao Le,
the doctor told her she wouldn't be able
to have any more children.
The date and time of his birth.
And of his death, too.
If you want Master
to bring his spirit back,
you must do exactly as he tells you.
Don't question his methods. Just obey.
How will Master Chen find him?
I won't.
He will find me.
Wherever he is,
I will bring him back.
Sir, the car is here.
-Thank you.
-That's alright.
I'll be back by Thursday.
My itinerary's on the bedside table.
Yeah, I saw it.
Will you be okay?
-It's just five days. I'll be back--
-Don't worry. I'll be fine.
You better go. The taxi's waiting.
Jia En.
Jia En?
Is everything ready?
Yes. Come in.
Master Chen says he'll be here by 10:00.
The maid should be asleep by then.
-Is everything ready?
-Yes.
Ah Ling, we can get started.
Master, the boy's tombstone
has not been erected yet.
His grave is in front of the big tree.
It's the fourth one from the left.
Here's the map.
I'll go with you.
It's better if you stay here with me.
What are you going to do?
We have to perform certain rituals
at the grave.
In order to lead his spirit home,
we have to bring back a part of him.
A part of him?
-What do you mean?
-Tong.
Don't worry. Just wait here for us.
Keep some incense burning at the altar
until we come back.
Don't forget.
Hello?
Yes. Okay, got it.
They're back.
Please come in.
They need to do this
in order to bring him back.
Remember, the finger
must always stay in the box.
Burn some incense every day.
At midnight,
give Xiao Le some of his favorite food.
The more you encourage him,
the stronger his spirit will be.
Remember, you have to do this
until you know his spirit is back.
How will I know when he's back?
You'll know.
Chicken wings. Your favorite.
I got it from the restaurant you like.
Mommy. Mommy.
Poke.
-Where were you last night?
-What do you mean?
I woke up during the night.
You weren't in bed.
Where were you?
In the study room.
Doing what?
Nothing.
Nora says you've been spending
a lot of time in there.
That's where the piano is.
You haven't played the piano since...
You lock yourself up in that room.
And you lock it up when you leave.
It's the only room I can go to
in this entire house...
where I can grieve.
Jia En,
I miss him too.
-I do, but we have to move on.
-Move on?
We can't spend
the rest of our lives like this!
If you wanna talk to someone--
You mean, a psychiatrist?
-Dr. Lim has helped you before.
-De Wei, I'm not crazy.
-I just need you to understand.
-Understand?
Isn't that all I've been doing
these past few months?
I'll see you later.
Hello? Auntie?
The number you have dialed
is not available. Please try again--
-Let's go. Mommy has to go home and cook.
-But I wanna play on the swing.
You want to play?
Ah Jian.
Hello? Auntie?
Jia En, is everything all right?
Where were you?
I've been trying to reach you.
I didn't have my phone with me.
I need to see you.
I'm busy at the moment.
When will you be free?
Is something wrong?
Xiao Le?
This is where we left off.
Do you want me to read to you?
If you do,
give me a sign.
"The children waited for the moon to rise,
then they followed the trail of pebbles.
The trail led them back home,
safe and sound.
However,
they would not be safe for long..."
Come on, Xiao Le.
I know you can do it.
It's exactly as we left it.
I'm sorry, sir. I'm sorry, ma'am.
But he's very, very sick. And so young.
It's okay, Nora.
We'll arrange for a flight
for you to go back and...
You should go back and see him.
Thank you, sir. Thank you, ma'am.
Will you be all right, ma'am?
Don't worry. I'm going to be fine.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry, Xiao Le.
I overslept.
Mommy will be early tomorrow night.
Okay?
-Your name is Anna?
-Yes, ma'am.
It says here you're Cambodian.
Where did you learn to speak Mandarin?
My previous employer
couldn't speak English.
So I picked up some Mandarin.
Can you cook?
Yes, ma'am.
-How about gardening?
-I can do that too, ma'am.
I love gardening and cooking.
I thought you said she liked to cook.
That's what she told me.
Maybe it tastes better than it looks.
Even he has reservations about her.
I think we should give her a chance.
There's something
I wanted to talk to you about.
What is it?
Perhaps it's time to move out.
No.
I found this nice, quiet place.
I can show you--
But I don't want to move.
-Why don't you want to move?
-Why do you want to move?
Because Xiao Le's gone.
-He's gone.
-No, he's not.
-No, he's not!
-What are you talking about?
De Wei,
I just don't want to move, okay?
Can't we just stay here?
Just like I used to play it.
Jia En,
I want to tell you something.
I will always love you.
No matter where I am,
or where you are,
my love will always be with you.
-Play it again.
-But I'm tired.
Play it again.
Okay.
Mom, where are you going?
Mom?
Xiao Le, don't do that.
Or I'll stop playing.
Xiao Le.
Xiao Le!
Xiao Le, stop it!
Xiao Le.
I know you're frustrated.
I know something's bothering you,
but this is not the way to behave.
Do you understand?
Xiao Le, are you listening to me?
This is not funny--
Ma'am, do you want me to clean this room?
No. I don't want you to enter this room.
Not ever.
Is that understood?
Yes, ma'am.
Why don't you go clean the other rooms?
I've already cleaned
all the other rooms, ma'am.
Then go clean your own room.
Yes, ma'am.
I want you to think about
what you did last night.
Think about it very carefully.
De Wei?
Where were you?
I should ask you that.
I just got back.
-Really?
-What do you mean?
I heard the car pull in half an hour ago,
and you say you just got back?
I was hungry.
I went to get something to eat.
Really?
Why would I lie to you?
Morning, ma'am.
Morning.
I'm gonna be late again tonight.
Hmm.
Anna.
-No dinner for me tonight.
-Yes, sir.
Are you mad at me?
No.
If you are, then let's talk about it.
You don't have to be like this.
What are you talking about?
You know what I'm talking about.
No, De Wei.
I'm tired.
Jia En. What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
What the hell are you doing?
Jia En!
Anna?
Anna.
Why haven't you cleared the table?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Tell me, what's wrong?
Nothing, ma'am.
Anna.
Last night, when I was asleep,
someone touched me.
Touched you?
What do you mean?
Someone pushed my face into the pillow.
I couldn't see who it was.
What did he do?
What did he do to you?
He pulled down my pajamas,
and then,
he pulled down my underwear.
Sorry. Excuse me a moment.
-What are you doing here?
-You didn't answer my calls.
-I was in a meeting.
-What's going on, De Wei?
Is something going on
between you and Anna?
We'll talk about it when I get home.
I want to know now. I need to know now.
Listen, Jia En.
I'm going to call Dr. Lim.
I saw you leaving Anna's room
the other night.
I told you.
I went to the kitchen
to look for something to eat,
but I didn't know where anything was.
So I went to Anna's room
to see if she could make me something.
But she was asleep.
So I left.
Jia En.
This has gone far enough.
I've been trying my best to understand,
but you come in here, to my office,
embarrass me in front of my staff.
This has to stop.
Sorry. Please continue.
Why don't you shut up and eat?
Come on, eat.
Stupid dog.
Eat or I won't feed you anymore.
Just eat your food, stupid dog.
We have to take her down to the station
to record her statement.
Miss.
I'll pick you up later.
Were you able to reach Master Chen?
He's not in Singapore.
He's at a mountainside retreat.
He'll only be back later this month.
I can't wait that long.
What happened?
That spirit in my house...
it's not my son.
I don't know what it is,
but I know it's not my son.
It's not Xiao Le.
Master Chen once taught me a ritual.
What kind of ritual?
A ritual that can identify the spirit
in your house.
What do I need to do?
I can come to your house and show you.
But your husband...
He's away on business.
All right.
We'll perform the ritual tomorrow night.
This will be the gateway.
The spirit will pass through here,
but as long as we stay within the circle,
we'll be okay.
Light these.
Sit down.
When the spirit passes
through the gateway,
you'll see its reflection in the mirror.
If it's Xiao Le,
it will be his face you see.
Let's try again.
Master Chen said he could only get here
the day after tomorrow.
He'll come here straight from the airport.
I'm gonna ask Anna to pack her things.
I'm sending her back to the agency.
Jia En,
it's better if you don't stay here
right now.
Go to a friend's house.
And what if that thing follows me there?
I'll be putting someone else in danger.
You do what you need to do.
Where are you going?
If that isn't my son in the grave,
I wanna know who it is.
Hello?
Hello, Anna. Is everything okay?
Yes, ma'am. I've already packed my things.
I'll be back in about an hour.
-Okay, ma'am.
-Bye.
One.
Two.
Three.
His grave is in front of the big tree.
It's the fourth one from the left.
Four.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Could you tell me whose grave this is?
Which one?
That one.
Uncle, I really need to know
who's buried there.
My son is buried in the next grave.
Please.
That grave is unmarked.
Who's buried there?
I don't know.
How could you not know?
You're the caretaker.
The people who brought him didn't tell me.
You must at least have a name.
No. I don't know his name.
How is that possible?
There must be some record of him.
The cemetery wouldn't let just anyone
bury their dead here.
Unless they approached you directly.
They paid you off, didn't they?
I barely make any money on this job.
I have six mouths to feed.
They'll starve to death.
Coming.
OUTGOING CALLS
AUNTIE
Hello?
Hello? Jia En?
Ma'am?
Anna.
-Anna.
-Ma'am?
Anna.
He was my son.
Several years older than Xiao Le.
Right from the day he was born,
we knew there was something
wrong with him.
When he was a child,
we thought he was just a little odd.
But the older he grew,
the more violent he became.
When he was a teenager,
he started attacking people.
One day,
my sister brought her daughter over
to our house.
My niece had a fever,
so we let her rest in the bedroom.
We were only away for ten minutes...
Mei Mei, we're back.
Sis...
I wasn't home when Ah Tam died.
That day,
my husband sent me out on an errand.
He gave Ah Tam some pills
so he would sleep.
It was the last time I saw my husband.
By the time I came back,
he had packed his things and left.
You killed your own son.
Master Chen tried to bring him back
several times,
but each time he failed.
Your son is lost.
He cannot find his way back.
However, there is a way.
He can follow another spirit home.
A soul that has just died.
With this soul to guide him,
your son can return.
You used Xiao Le to bring your son back.
My son's death...
Did you have anything to do with it?
No.
I loved Xiao Le. You know I loved him.
But the thing is,
when he died, I thought...
maybe there's a way for both of us
to find our sons.
You understand, don't you?
I wanted my son back, just like you do.
Jia En.
Jia En!
Anna?
Help me!
Come out.
Come on out.
No. He's upstairs.
Don't hide in there.
Stop it!
Tam, you listen to me.
You don't belong here. Please go away.
Leave us alone.
You don't belong here. Stop troubling us.
Enough. Enough!
Xiao Le?
Xiao Le.
Stop!
Ah Tam.
It's time to go home.
Jia En.
Please forgive me.
Xiao Le.
You're still here?
I never left.
No matter where I am,
or where you are,
my love will always be with you.
Mommy.
Jia En!
BELOVED SON
HANSEL AND GRETEL
So you can always find your way home.
Xiao Le,
Mommy and Daddy will always love you.