BUCKING BRONCO
Damn!
MIGHTY ELEPHANT
It's a Thai folk song.
-Okay?
-Yeah.
Excuse me.
Pick one.
Hurry.
BUFFALO BILL
Bottoms up!
-Bottoms up!
More, more.
-Good? Okay?
-Okay?
FORCE OF THE TIGER
WOMANIZER
Bottoms up!
INFALLIBLE WOOD
Come in. Make yourself at home. Wait.
Just a sec.
Seriously, you live with your mom?
Yes.
Your mom or wife?
My mom.
That was my mom when she was young.
Where's she?
She's studying abroad.
Okay, I'll believe you.
The speaker's broken.
Here.
Too bad, right?
There'll be no intro.
We can get straight to the hook.
Holy shit!
We have to call our client
early in the morning.
I thought you'll be coming back on Sunday.
It's now Saturday past midnight,
so it's Sunday.
I see.
That is your mom?
That's my sister.
-Take it off.
-She's just borrowing it.
It's all right.
-Take it off.
-It's mine.
How can you let her wear it?
Who is she? Do you even know her name?
Seriously.
Do you?
What?
What's my name?
It's Aoy.
-What?
What's my name?
Kate.
Right?
Chompoo.
Ann?
No.
I've been gone for four years.
-Do you do this every day?
-Do what?
I told you not to bring girls back home.
Why not?
-It's my house too.
-Can't you start using your brain?
Can you?
-Instead of using only your balls.
-Hey, be nice.
Don't mess with the family jewels.
Fine.
-Jane, open it.
-No.
If you want to fool around, do it outside.
Do you understand?
What's with you?
What now? She already left.
If you don't care about me,
at least care about my friend.
If you do it again,
I'm gonna tell Muay for real.
Okay, fine.
Sorry, Mom. I won't do it again.
Please. I really won't do it again.
That's all.
Sleep outside tonight.
Coochie.
Jane.
It's not funny.
I'm your older brother!
It's been ages
since anyone's called me that name.
But once Jane's back,
that name returns too.
I really hate that name.
Actually, my name's Chut.
When I was a kid,
I dreamt of having a younger brother.
Uncle, why are you late?
Hurry, Chut. Your mom is in labor.
Hold on tight.
Hey, John. Little John. My brother.
John doesn't fit the baby anymore.
She's a girl.
It felt like the whole world
was falling down.
Chut.
You're a big brother now.
Love your sister a lot, okay?
I was forgotten.
Everyone doted on Jane.
Uncle, take me to see Seng, please.
Chut, stop bothering me.
And when she got older,
her flawlessness and perfection
made me a total loser in everyone's eyes.
What’s with your grades, Chut?
Social Studies, math, computer, all Fs.
You even got an F in English.
You're a mixed race!
Are you collecting Fs?
Look here, straight As.
Of course, she's good at everything.
Your reputation has spread
-around...
-Great, keep it up.
...my brother.
Who would want to be your big brother?
Chut, get out of the way.
We only need a photo with Jane.
Oh, I'm here as her guardian.
Being a big loser of a brother,
what's the big deal?
Could you please move
to the left a little?
No, not that way.
I meant to your left.
A bit more.
More, more.
Perfect. Okay, say cheese.
Damn her.
Just wait, she's gonna get it.
The lowest point of my life was
when I let her play baseball with me.
Fireball!
Hey, Chut.
He's bleeding.
Does anyone have a handkerchief?
It'll be dirty.
This is better.
Laurier really is absorbent.
Is that a chin or a pussy?
It's got a pad stuck to it.
Pussy.
Hey, don't call him that.
Calling him Coochie is better.
That works.
Coochie. Coochie.
I woke up to a new name, Coochie,
which Jane gave me.
Coochie.
Since when do the younger ones
name their older siblings?
I'm five years older than you!
Coochie, why don’t you
put the food in the bowl?
I'm too lazy to wash it.
You're so lame even
in the smallest things.
I'm not surprised that your life
has always been lame.
So, all those who eat from a Baggie
are lame too.
Why don't you put
the seat down afterwards?
She's so fussy with me about everything.
I don't wanna touch your piss, understand?
-You won't. Just touch this.
-How's that not possible?
-I didn't piss on that.
-It must spray--
Do you think I peed like this?
Luckily, I was released from this torture,
when she got a scholarship
to study in Japan.
Coochie, I'm leaving now.
Sayonara.
Sayo-tempura.
The day she left to study abroad
was the day I had been dreaming of.
It was heaven!
Four years of total bachelorhood.
Four years.
Damn!
Why did it go so fast?
Goddamn it!
It's over.
So lame, loser, useless.
Every little girl's fantasy
is to have a big brother,
like the song, "The Best Big Brother."
That song...
So that I could play boyish games.
Just shoot it.
"Arsenal's in the lead."
-Be crazy about football like him.
-You're one point ahead, right?
If you score half a ball, then you win.
-Got it?
-Read the same comic books.
This, then this, and this.
Why do they read
from the back to the front?
Because it's the Japanese way.
-Only this side.
-Get to copy his cool moves.
Or even play baseball with him.
Fireball!
But having a big brother like Coochie...
Darn it, Jane!
That's mine, don't color on it.
-Can't I?
-No!
Give it back.
Darn it!
That singer is such a liar!
Think about it,
he's five years older than me.
Instead of helping me with homework,
-look.
-Chut.
This year, you have to study with Jane.
And please try to pass this time.
I'm tired of regrading you.
I'm so embarrassed
-to have a big brother like him.
-Loser.
I've been using Excel
ever since I was in fourth grade.
What, fatty? I'll poke you blind.
Miss? May I go to the toilet, please?
If I have to study
in the same class as him,
I'd rather skip class.
When I had to move to Bangkok to study,
Mom put a down payment
on this house for us.
Did you find it?
It's just the two of us.
Instead of the older one
taking care of his younger sibling...
-Here you go.
-...it's me who has to take care of him.
See.
The light works.
Why are you lying there?
What a burden.
The only time Coochie wants
to be the big brother...
is when a guy likes me.
-I'm Bon.
-What Bon?
James Bond?
Bon Jovi?
Just Bon.
Why don't you look trustworthy?
Are you hitting on my sister?
Sometimes, I wish I were an only child.
It's an owl, not a tiger.
You didn't have to scream that loud.
Is the owl your pet?
You should return it.
What now?
The owl.
My client moved abroad.
So, I have to take care of it for now.
So, are you an account executive
or a slave?
I've been trying to send it to them.
What's taking you so long?
I just said that I'm trying.
Why the fuss?
What do I eat it with?
Toast.
Go make your own toast.
Coochie...
No! Gross!
Gross, who's gonna eat after you?
-Gross?
-Yeah.
Gross.
So disgusting.
What?
Why are you all dressed up?
Meditation retreat?
I have a job interview.
Graduating abroad
isn't enough to get a job.
You gotta have style.
I'm off.
Yeah, yeah.
You're damn cool.
Hi.
I'm here for a job interview.
Please go inside and turn right.
Thanks.
Mr. Kaiwa.
She looks so young.
Will she be able to handle the job?
But I like this look.
She looks a bit Caucasian.
I think she understands us, Moji.
Shiruku, smell fresh for seven days.
What are your thoughts on this, Ms. Jane?
From the information on the internet,
more men are doing household chores.
I believe they also do their own laundry.
But no one has done
any marketing activities
targeted to this group.
But you probably have a missus
who does your laundry, right?
Missus?
I mean wife.
I'm still singer.
You meant single, right?
Single. Super single.
And how about you? Who does your laundry?
Catch!
I do it myself.
It's odd that a beautiful woman
like you is still single.
Or do you have any problems?
Ms. Jane.
Is there something wrong?
Nothing.
It burns.
-Burns?
-Burns.
Burns?
It means that reality hurts.
Well, then I apologize.
It's all right.
It's funny.
I think she's your dream partner.
One more question.
Ms. Jane, do you play baseball?
-What?
-It's our new employee initiation.
What's this feeling?
She's one woman who looks so charming
while holding a baseball bat.
Today, I'll show her how cool I am,
and make her my girl!
Are you sure you don't wanna change?
I won't hold back.
Throw it already. It's getting late.
You've got two strikes now.
There's a certain rhythm when swinging.
Think before swinging the bat.
Shit!
Did you play often in Japan?
You're good.
When I was a kid,
I used to play with my brother.
I didn't know Thai kids play baseball.
Not really.
But my brother was crazy
about this comic book and played.
So, I was crazy about it too.
The comic book was Sayonara Home Run!
Ryo.
Baseball Thunderclap.
Fireball!
Hey, are you two
still trying to make home runs?
Go home.
You know the death moves too.
When I was a kid, I was obsessed.
How come you speak Thai so well?
Well, although I grew up in Japan,
my dad is Thai.
But he died when I was young,
so he didn't have a chance to teach me.
I had to persevere
and practice on the karaoke.
Persevere.
That's a hard word.
What Thai song uses that word?
Number seven
Study hard, persevere
-Don't be lazy
-Oh, yeah!
All good kids
Must have ten responsibilities
Snow isn't as fair as this.
I can't believe that you know that song.
Why are you so dressed up?
I'm going to work.
I've been working for a month.
Haven't you noticed?
What's for breakfast?
There.
You have a meeting with a client today.
Aren't you in a rush?
If it's pouring like this,
my client won't be awake.
What's that?
Your presentation?
-May I see?
-Leave it alone.
Stop it.
Nosy.
I hope it sells.
For sure.
Look who you're talking to.
Are you really gonna pitch it like this?
Yeah, they're already different.
Baldy Kaiwa will buy it no matter what.
MUAY
Don't listen to Jane.
You know she hates me.
No.
So, what do you want, then?
Well, it's up to you, then.
No...
My phone's dying. I'll call you later.
Oops, bye.
Excuse me.
Could you take a look at this?
I'm not sure what I did wrong.
It says, "Error."
Actually, it's for your Shiruku work.
-What should I do?
-You'll break it. Relax.
That's not right.
Chill.
The paper's stuck here.
Go wait over there, okay?
Am I in the way?
Get up.
I'm getting up.
Move back.
More.
Stand on this. Don't move.
Stand on it.
Yeah.
Don't move.
When it says, "Paper Jam,"
snatch it out of this slot.
-And then pull the paper out.
-I see.
-I said stand on the paper.
-I am.
Get up.
-You're an intern, right?
-Yeah.
-What's your name?
-Dear.
You're still a student.
Why are you dressed like that?
Why is it so short?
Do you have a hidden agenda?
You can't.
Dress properly. Are you going clubbing?
Let me be myself.
-But you're an intern.
-Don't look, then.
I'm not.
-Don't dress like this. Dress properly.
-You're looking at it.
Okay.
And when it says, "Paper Jam,"
take it out like...
Pull it out like that. Simple.
Close it too.
See, you can't fix it either.
Wait.
Can I get off now?
Morning, Mr. Moji.
Good morning.
-Hello.
Come in. Have a seat.
-Mr. Moji.
-Yes?
Shiruku's new idea really hits home.
-Thank you.
-Targeting male customers.
This audience analysis
-has a lot of vision to it.
-Thank you.
Mr. Moji, you're my dream client.
Thank you very much.
-Awesome.
-Thank you.
Ms. Jane, welcome.
This is Ms. Jane, our new brand manager.
She's the one behind this idea.
-This idea?
-That's right.
Hello, everyone.
Mr. Saito assigned me
to be Mr. Moji's assistant.
I'll be taking over
the detergent account from Mr. Kaiwa,
who's taken over
the window cleaner account.
It's great to be a part of the team.
Mr. Chutchawin, you're Zono's
account executive, right?
It's Sono.
From the brief
that I received from Sirugu--
Hold on, I'm sorry.
It's Shiruku.
Could you also pronounce
our brand correctly?
Okay.
According to Shi-ru-ku's brief,
targeting its male customers,
we have three print ads
for you to choose from.
The first one, a new summer look.
"Convenient for mister, easy for missus."
The second one.
"Convenient for men, easy for women."
And the last one.
"Convenient for guys, easy for gals."
How is it?
I love all three of them.
They're all equally good.
It's so hard to choose.
Ms. Jane.
You might think that they're the same,
but they're really different.
Okay.
If using synonyms makes them different,
then it's different.
Next time, you don't have to bother
with choices, then.
Just making a really good one
would be better, Coochie.
Who's that?
It's Mr. Chutchawin here.
Back home, we call him Coochie.
Coochie.
Oh, you're both from the same town?
We live in the same house.
Sometimes, we even share the same bed.
We're siblings.
-I see.
Let's go inside.
Muay.
Jane.
Good morning, Moji.
Good morning.
We finally meet.
Jane always talks about you.
-Yeah.
-Close up for me too.
Sure.
This one will be picked up this evening.
-No problem.
-Thanks a lot.
-Thanks.
-No worries.
-Jane.
-Yes?
Well,
I...
want to formally introduce
myself to your brother.
What do you think?
But he already knows you.
But not as his sister's boyfriend.
You don't need to tell Coochie about us.
Why?
Or are you not confident in me?
It's not like that.
I don't want him to be involved.
Just let him be.
He'll find out when it's time.
But we're not doing anything wrong.
Love shouldn't be kept a secret.
If you wanna love, don't hide it.
Love shouldn't be kept a secret
If you wanna love, don't hide it
-Make it happen
-We have to make it happen, you know.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Oh, my, Moji.
You've been listening
to too many Thai songs.
THIS PERSON IS NOT ALLOWED TO GO INSIDE
Are you upset about anything?
In Japan, clovers have
a very good meaning.
But it also means having secrets...
that can't be said, untold.
-As for lavender...
-Another one.
You used to live in Japan.
Do you know its meaning?
It means I have doubts about you.
A whole bouquet.
As for this...
In Japan, there's no other meaning.
It's just our one-month anniversary.
Who's the slut now?
What about you? Skanky?
What?
I'm just saying
that you've been dressing sluttily.
Why?
What have you been up to?
Nothing.
Why the sharp voice?
Coochie.
Have you talked to Muay yet?
-Have you?
-No.
Why?
Haven't you seen it yet?
She ranted all over Facebook.
What rant?
"Someone like you isn't a limited edition.
Generic. A knock-off, fake,
rip-off, a sissy.
You dick!"
-Did she mention any names?
-No.
Just "#loserchut!"
#LOSERCHUT!!
-Damn Muay, she's--
-Hold it, Coochie.
Don't talk about her that way.
Good for her.
Reading it gives me satisfaction.
Muay deserves a better man.
You’re a bad business partner.
As a boyfriend, you're the worst.
And how is kissing in public
better than me?
Wait.
I pecked.
And I pecked my boyfriend.
-Your boyfriend?
-Boyfriend.
-You have a boyfriend.
So? I have a boyfriend, and?
-Hello?
-Hello, Mom.
Yeah, what?
I have something to tell you.
-What is it?
-Your favorite child, Jane.
She may look all naïve.
But she's really slutty, you know.
She's got a boyfriend now.
-He's Japanese, too.
-What?
Why didn’t she tell me?
You won't approve, right?
Wow, she's gone international like me.
You're the one.
Stop bringing home random girls.
-Your sister has moved back.
-Come on, Mom.
She's worse than me.
There is a leaked clip of her.
What?
What clip?
Send it to me.
-Now!
-Okay.
Hello?
PORN CLIPS
Chut?
Have you sent it, yet?
I've sent it.
-Oh, Mom.
-Yeah?
-Don't tell her that I told you.
-Okay.
I have to go. I'll watch the clip.
What did you send Mom?
-What are you talking about?
-Here.
Let's watch it together.
I can't believe you tried
sending porn to Mom.
You sent priming instead of porn.
You're so retarded.
Make sure there aren't any real ones.
Ouch!
As for the clothes,
we've changed it to red
as commented.
But I still have one problem.
The location we used
has too much green in it.
It reminds us of our competitor,
the one we want to beat.
But it’s a yard.
Isn't it supposed to be green?
This is redoing the entire storyboard--
-What?
-Mr. Saito said
that the power of the brand's color
is essential.
-So, it's worth changing.
-What?
-Do you want a house without a yard?
-Okay.
We'll redo the storyboard
as soon as possible.
Charging tigers!
-Yes!
Next, we'll have the production house
send the queues.
The next step, Mr. Gun,
you can have the production house
send the queues.
And if there are any other details,
I'll e-mail you directly, okay?
Okay.
It won't take more than a week.
How long will it take?
I said one week.
One week.
Jane.
What's with you?
-I'm standing right here.
-Just chill, Chut.
-About one week.
-I see.
Okay, Mr. Gun.
Do you have a parking ticket?
I'll stamp it for you.
Thanks.
-Excuse me, I have to go.
-I see.
Okay.
Geez, look at her.
We've already changed
the storyboard thrice.
They're the boss.
And their comments
are so damn stupid. Are they crazy?
The yard's supposed to be green.
How can everything be Shiruku red?
They should do laundry
in a Chinese shrine.
Calm down, Chut.
If they keep being stupid,
I'll sell this idea to their competitor.
Mr. Chut, you should resign from the team.
Mr. Moji, why are so serious?
I was just kidding.
Thais always joke around like this.
Japanese don't joke around, right?
Even so, this is really a sensitive issue.
If Mr. Saito finds out,
he won't be pleased.
But Mr. Saito doesn't know.
It's just between the two of us.
Are you going to tell Mr. Saito?
I don't have a choice.
It's our company's policy.
If you don't resign,
we'll have to dismiss your company.
Why so serious?
Is this what you want?
Be careful. The ending won't be pretty.
The end is the end. It has nothing to do
with being pretty or not.
Right?
Whatever.
You better watch out.
I'm gonna get you good.
What do you want me to watch out for?
I'm glad we're now on good terms.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
You make my blood boil!
Blood boil...
-Are you hot?
-What?
Do you want some water?
Is this what you want?
I don't think Jane will agree.
Mr. Chut, you know?
You were the guy
in front of the flower shop, right?
My apologies.
Actually, I've never liked you.
Don't make me hate you.
Because... I can get Jane
to break up with you.
So, what will it be, Moji?
Fine, then.
I'll keep this a secret.
That's it.
There's no need to be so stiff.
Okay. I'm going now.
You're gonna get it, tiger!
Moji.
You're worse than him.
You didn't punish that guy
because he's your girlfriend's brother?
I think...
you've been in Thailand for too long.
You've become passive.
You're not using all your potential.
In two months, there will be
a shuffling of positions.
You will have to go back to Japan...
to the head office.
Start over again.
Relearn our organization's
culture and ethics.
You must go back.
Moji, why did you defend him?
Don't tell me he told you
he'd make me break up with you.
How did you know?
That's so damn Coochie.
Does he even know what he's done?
What a demon!
But...
I'm relieved...
that Chut finally knows about us.
What are we going to do now?
What about the others?
Aren't they coming?
I didn't invite anyone else.
Why are you playing only with me?
When you move back,
you'll get to play with better people.
Think of it as a last farewell, then.
Okay.
In that case, if I win,
you'll have to take me out.
And if I win...
will you marry me?
Moji.
Don't do this, please.
If you win, I won't bother you.
I'll do anything you want.
It doesn't matter
whether it's been two months or two years.
If it's love, it's love.
Jane, what are you afraid of?
Couples who get married early
have an 80% failure rate.
But if we break up right now,
that'll be 100%.
Aren't you going to listen to me?
Fine, then.
If you want to play, then let's do it.
I once thought...
this is how I'd propose to you.
Thanks.
It's a very sweet proposal.
But...
I'm sorry, Moji.
Jane.
It burns.
RE: CHANGE OF POSITIONS WITHIN THE COMPANY
ATTENTION: SONO ADVERTISING CO., LTD.
Shiruku Thailand would like to notify
the shuffling of positions.
First, Mr. Mojikawa
is to be moved to the Marketing Department
at the head office in Japan.
Second, we request
Sono Advertising Company
to remove Mr. Chut
from being Shiruku's account executive.
To be effective immediately.
SINCERELY YOURS
MS. JENKWAN RIANSUWAN, BRAND MANAGER
MR. CHUTCHAWIN RIANSUWAN IS DISMISSED
ARE YOU GOING TO DO THIS TO ME, FOR REAL?
Hello?
Which Aey is this?
Oh, Aey Anyaporn.
About the quotation, right?
Sure. I'll send it to you.
Okay.
CHUT, THE TELEPHONE WIZARD.
HE CAN TALK TO A GHOST CALLER.
WHICH AEY IS HE TALKING TO NOW?
LAY OFF. HE'S GOT TIME.
MS. JANE'S REALLY CRUEL.
FIRING HER OWN BROTHER.
CHUTCHAWIN: I'M STILL IN THE GROUP!
Shit!
Busy?
No.
It's watching a series or photocopying.
Do you wanna go clubbing?
My treat.
Okay.
Let's go.
This is fun.
I didn't think you're into these places.
Let's come again.
Sure.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Hey, you're drunk as a skunk.
If I slap you, it wouldn't hurt, right?
I'm not drunk.
If you don't believe me, try--
-How was it?
-It hurts.
My bad.
Are you sober, Coochie?
Don't call me that name.
I hate it.
Your sister is so pretty, you know.
But she's got such a sharp tongue.
When I see you two,
it's like you hate each other.
Actually, I've never hated Jane.
But...
I hate myself when I'm with her.
Then, you should tell her that.
Tell her what?
Well, tell her,
"Jane, my dear, I don't hate you, sis.
I just hate myself when I'm with you.
I love you, sis."
-Like that.
-That makes me wanna puke.
No?
No way.
Do you have any siblings?
You're so damn lucky.
Hello.
This way.
Sorry for all the trouble.
You could've just left him at the bar.
The bar begged me to take him home.
He puked up all his guts.
He'll sleep well tonight.
Are you really gonna leave him like that?
Don't worry.
He'll wash it off when he wakes up.
Cutthroat.
You're not mad at Chut, are you?
Why?
Did he say something?
No.
He's upset with work, so he's complaining.
But I don't really get it.
When siblings fight,
does it have to be so dramatic?
You're an only child, right?
I'm lucky, right?
Can I ask you a question?
Why do you call him Coochie?
COOCHIE, DON'T FORGET
TO PICK ME UP FROM THE LASIK CLINIC!!
It's me, Moji.
Moji.
Yes?
Thanks for picking me up.
I told Coochie, but he probably forgot.
So, I have to bother you. Sorry.
Do you know you're really cute right now?
You look like Kamen Rider V8.
Do you know Skyrider?
They've got big bug eyes.
Moji, I'm not supposed to laugh.
-Let's go. I'll take you home.
-Wait a sec.
I...
I don't want you to misunderstand me.
I do love you.
But...
I'm worried about my family.
I'm worried about my mom, auntie,
the house, and Coochie.
Please say something.
Are you pouty?
I can't see anything.
I'm not mad at all.
-Really?
-Because I know
how it feels to be far away from family.
So, I've already decided
to leave Shiruku and find a new job here.
You don't have to do that for me.
Jane, I can live anywhere.
All I need is you.
We don't have to get married right now.
Okay?
Don't touch it, you'll infect your eyes.
The doctor will scold you.
-Moji.
-Yeah?
How many kids do you want?
Four.
Maybe two?
The ring?
Well, I have it with me all the time.
I love you, Jane.
Your family's already here.
Chut said that he'll be representing
your mom.
You are Jane, right?
Ma'am.
You speak Thai very well.
My husband was Thai, that's why.
You and Chut can speak Thai with Mum.
She understands but doesn't speak it well.
I can speak, but you probably
won't understand.
Chut and I are the same.
We're mixed race,
but we can't speak French.
Our dad went back when we were young.
You can just tell them that he left us.
Excuse me?
Mom was asking
-how many kids we're planning to have.
-I see.
These two are workaholics.
If they're gonna have kids,
-they'll have to pump a lot.
-Pump?
Pump.
Pump?
Pump! Pump! Pump!
Hey! Why did you step on my foot?
You'll have to give the kids hybrid names.
Like it could be either Thai or Japanese.
For example.
If the Japanese name is Tsubasa,
then we'll call him Surasak in Thai.
Sorry.
-Excuse me.
-That's enough, Coochie!
We can't eat it anymore.
It's now plum soup.
I'm so sorry.
All right, let's get to the point.
To marry Jane...
the dowry is ten million.
Coochie!
Baht, not Yen.
Is it normally this much?
-I can find it.
-Moji.
Don't listen to him.
Then you can't get married.
It's not a problem.
I'll do anything.
All right, then.
So it's settled.
Jane.
Jane and I have planned
to get married next month.
We're in a rush.
But it should be possible.
We'll be leaving for Japan
one week after the wedding.
Your honeymoon?
No.
Jane decided to move
to Japan with me after the wedding.
Why don't I know about this?
-I've already told Mom.
-But she didn't tell me this.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know she'll be moving to Japan.
So, no more marriage.
-Chut.
-Sorry.
Chut.
-Let's go home.
-Chut.
-Let's go.
-Coochie.
Let's go.
-Can't we talk first?
-No.
No wedding. Let's go home.
Go.
You have no right
to stop me from getting married.
Why not? Mom said I was representing Dad.
I'm not allowing it.
You have no right.
I know why you're doing this!
You're upset with me and Moji
about work, right?
It's got nothing to do with that.
Moji's a loser.
What the hell.
He has to move. Why force you to move too?
Is he crazy?
If he wants to marry you, he has to quit.
Hey, Jane!
Think more about it.
It's only been a few months
and now wedding plans?
Are you out of your mind?
Moving to Japan.
How's it gonna last?
You're speechless.
You're not that confident in Moji either.
And you have to think about this.
How are you gonna live over there?
Who's gonna take care of the house?
What about the payments?
What now?
Did you not like what I said?
You've never done anything
with this house.
Me!
It's me that does it all!
The dishes, cleaning, laundry.
It's all me!
Coochie.
You're so damn selfish!
The reason I've said all this
is because I'm worried about you.
Really?
I don't think so.
I think you're afraid.
You're afraid of not having
your own slave,
paying the mortgage.
I'm done talking.
Do you know that, at first,
I turned down Moji?
Because I was worried...
about how you're going to live
when I'm gone.
Do you know what a burden you are?
This house.
You haven't even paid for half of it.
Whatever you paid, I'll pay you back.
And I'm gonna sell this house.
And you'll have to live somewhere else.
Don't run me off like some animal.
I'm your big brother.
And have you ever acted like one?
You can leave whenever,
but we can't live together anymore.
Please forgive me for my rudeness.
It's all right.
Let bygones be bygones.
I wasn't thinking
when I asked for the dowry.
When people love one another,
money shouldn't get in the way
of their feelings.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
I'm really glad that we're
going to be the same family.
You don't have to worry about Chut.
He's got nothing to do with this anymore.
My mom gave me her blessing to marry Moji.
My first grandchild
will be as sweet as you.
Are you listening?
JANE
BLOCK THIS CONTACT
Forget it.
It's my wedding gown.
For my beautiful daughter-in-law.
We're now a family.
"Because my husband was Thai."
"Coochie, you have no right!"
One, nine, four, zero.
Welcome.
They even play Cuban news
in the comfort room.
It’s awesome.
Try...
Wait!
What are you doing?
Sorry, I didn't mean to.
I don't think of you that way.
And all the dates we had together?
What do you think I had in mind?
So, you were fishing?
Were you thinking of getting a catch?
Is that it?
Now what?
Damn you.
The place wasn't packed, right?
No, it wasn't.
That's good, so we can go back again.
-Yummy.
-There wasn't a long wait.
Yeah.
It's past 2:00 p.m., I can't sell it.
It's only two minutes after.
I was here before 2:00,
but that guy was slow.
I really can't sell it.
Sir.
I can't close the lid.
All right, I'll...
Chut.
This is Mr. Watanyoo
from Thai Life Insurance.
This is Chut, our top account executive.
Chut will take care of your account.
Hello, I'm Chut.
Hi, I'm Watanyoo. Just call me Yoo.
Okay.
Be careful of your cup,
you might spill it.
It's okay.
Did you get wet?
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
Get me some tissues.
My apologies.
Here.
Tissues.
I looked the other way
with Shiruku's case.
When they pulled you off the team,
I thought that was enough punishment.
But what is this?
You haven't even started your new project,
and now I've caught you
drinking in the office.
I'm really sorry.
Take a week off.
We'll talk when you get back.
What do you mean, "we will talk"?
I'll be straight with you.
I don't know which account
I should give you.
When you return
and you still want to work here,
I might have to reduce your salary
or demote you.
Are you trying to get me to leave?
Bingo.
DAD CLEANS, MOM CARES.
NEW LOOK. SUMMER FRAGRANCE.
SHIRUKU
Can't you help me?
No one's called me back.
What about your boss?
Stupid.
Who curses clients that often?
I didn't kill anyone.
Hold on. How did my getting fired
spread to your office?
You better tell them that I quit,
I wasn't fired.
Yeah. That's all.
Dear.
Yes?
If you're free, please attend.
You can go with Mr. Gun.
For me?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
How's Coochie doing?
I haven't talked to him lately.
He moved out to an apartment.
I heard that will be his last week
in the office.
Dear.
Could you do me a favor?
You got an invitation too?
Are you going?
It's far, Maha Sarakham Province.
There isn't an airport either.
You sound like you're not going.
I'll go.
Of course.
It's my sister's wedding.
I'm sending you my friend's contact.
He's looking for an account executive.
Take a look.
Think of it as a farewell gift.
Thank you.
You're invited.
What's your name?
Dear-Raporn?
Am I right?
Kwan-Ruedear?
Oh, Duang-Dear.
This one for sure. Dear-Ratee.
Right?
I think you should attend.
MAHA SARAKHAM
THONGCHAI AUTO PARTS
Wow, beautiful.
You're as beautiful as I was
when I was young.
Are you done?
-Okay?
-So beautiful.
Here, once more. Tighter.
Thank you.
Why hasn't Coochie come back?
He's not answering my calls.
Please tell him that I miss him.
I wanna drink beer with him.
Watch your step.
Jane, look at your mom.
She's Moji's biggest fan.
Look at the camera. That's great.
Turn left. Then right.
Like that.
Quickly. Yes, like that.
Closer to the groom.
Yes, that's it.
In and out, in and out
I can't follow the game
What's with this song? Bobbing in and out.
The Ninja song.
Is this the Japanese song
you wanna sing for them?
I couldn't guess it on my own
Will your brother come?
Eat up.
Your aunt can start her own comedy club.
What are you doing?
Here, let me help.
-It's hot.
-Thanks.
-No worries.
-Be careful.
-Let me help.
JENKWAN RIANSUWAN
This is my old PE uniform.
Do you see it?
"Jenkwan."
Is that a "C"?
CHATCHAWIN
Is that Chut's full name?
You wore his hand-me-downs?
Yes.
Not only his uniforms,
but also all his old clothes.
I see.
"Convenient for guys, easy for gals."
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
COOCHIE, YOU BETTER COME TO MY WEDDING.
Joe.
This work's from last year.
These are the awards I won.
Our team is very lucky to get
one of Sono's top account executives.
Yes, sir.
As agreed, you can start immediately.
Already?
Of course. Why wait?
Can you start tomorrow?
Can I start next week?
I have some business
to take care of at home.
Too bad.
What's brought you here, Riansuwan?
Good evening, sir.
-Can I go in?
-Sure.
COOCHIE: I'M HERE HANGING OUT AT SCHOOL.
COOCHIE: I'LL BE HOME LATER.
JANE: WHERE ARE YOU?
COOCHIE: ON YOUR RIGHT.
There's Thai silk and a handbag in here.
I want you to give it to Moji's mom.
Here.
I can give it to her tomorrow.
What's the rush?
Are you drinking again?
It's not alcohol.
It's just soda.
Coochie.
I'll be leaving for Kitakyushu next week.
I don't want to leave
while we're still fighting like this.
I'm sorry...
for throwing you out of the house.
You don't need to apologize.
How are you?
Have you been to any interviews, yet?
I might look shabby, but I got an offer.
I got a new job.
You know,
actually, I'm very afraid
of marriage and moving to Japan.
Especially when you disapproved of it.
It's not that... I don't love Moji
or afraid he might do something bad to me.
But Japan...
traveling and living there
are very different.
Living there...
is quite stressful.
Are you saying...
that I've been right all along?
So much, I'm quite mad.
Don't think too much.
How about...
you have my blessing to get married
and move there.
Even though you don't need my blessing.
Says who?
No matter what, I need it.
You represent Dad.
Do you think Moji and I will last?
Of course.
Right?
If you follow the Four Truths of Buddhism,
you'll last.
What?
The Four Noble Truths.
"Mercy, kindness, honesty,
and detachment."
Wait a minute.
Those are the States of the Mind.
-Really?
-Yeah.
MERCY, KINDNESS, HONESTY, DETACHMENT
Are you trying to teach me
the Buddhist scriptures?
You got them mixed up.
It works, right?
I'm gonna go now.
Thanks anyway.
For what?
For coming to my wedding.
Stop with the flowers.
Stop arranging them for a sec?
Help me carry this to the car.
You're such an obstacle to my transition.
You know there's no testosterone
left in me.
I'll wait for you outside.
Here.
Is it necessary?
Just take it.
I wanna give you one.
It’s probably leftovers.
CHUTCHAWIN RIANSUWAN AND FAMILY
What family?
Are you mocking me?
If the young one marries first,
the older one will be a spinster.
It's a trick.
Okay.
I'm going to the hotel now.
You can meet up at 4:00 or 5:00 p.m.
Come on, Jane. Let's go.
Let's go.
Oh, my god!
JOE: I'VE ALREADY INTERVIEWED
YOUR BROTHER.
JOE: DON'T WORRY, I'LL TAKE CARE OF HIM.
JOE: DON'T FORGET
TO TREAT ME A MEAL. HEHE.
JANE AND MOJI'S WEDDING CEREMONY
Hello.
Thank you.
-Your gift.
-Thank you.
One, two...
Be cheerful!
Hey, Coochie.
-Oh, Seng.
-It's been so long. What's up?
Good, good.
Let's go get tanked inside.
All or nothing.
They're not serving alcohol, yet.
Let's warm up somewhere else.
Hey, why are you parking here?
What the hell?
Have you caught anything?
I got two.
Fish?
Yeah.
Can I buy it?
The rod?
Yeah.
It's expensive.
How much?
Two.
Thousand?
Yeah.
-What?
-I'll throw in the bait too.
-Cheers!
-Bottoms up!
Thanks to the chairman of the ceremony.
But the ceremony isn't over yet.
According to Japanese tradition,
the bride will read her letter
to her family.
Put your hands together for Jane!
Before I read my letter,
I'd like to tell everyone here
even though we've been together
for a couple of months,
I'm not pregnant.
My letter to my family.
I know that my family isn't perfect.
When I was born, there was only my mom,
who's a bit stingy.
And my aunt
who remains single
and won't leave my mom's side.
She got you too.
Mom and Auntie are both strong women,
raising two naughty kids
to be the adults we are today.
I've never built a family before.
I don't know how hard it'll be,
but I think it must be very hard.
By the time we catch any fish,
I'll be eaten alive by the mosquitoes.
Can I really ask you?
Don't you want to go--
MOM
Thank you, Mom.
Every time I was in trouble,
-Is Coochie really not coming?
-...Mom always helped me out.
No matter which path I've chosen,
Mom has always supported me.
I should go.
My wife must be looking for me.
Will you take my wedding gift?
I don't know what happened
with the two of you.
But...
people only get married once, dude.
I might have to build my family
in a far-off place,
but I want everyone here to know
that you are my family.
I will be my mom's daughter,
my auntie's niece,
and...
Coochie.
He's been an influence
ever since I was a kid.
JENKWAN TAKAHASHI
I like reading Japanese comics
because of him.
When I grew up,
I always liked Japanese stuff.
I studied in Japan,
and I even have a husband
that's half-Japanese.
And now that I'm married,
I'm going to move to Japan.
All of this
is because of Coochie.
And look.
It's his own sister's wedding,
yet, I don't know where he is.
Can I stop being his sister?
But even if he might be
the lamest big brother...
there's no way we can stop being siblings.
I'll try to find Chut. I'll be back.
Did you find him?
I couldn't find him.
Holy shit!
Eighty missed calls!
I'm dead!
Coochie, dude. Hurry!
TWO MISSED CALLS
Where have you been?
Why didn't you go
to your sister's wedding?
Here.
Did you know
she left the house in Bangkok to you?
And look what you did.
Does this make you feel good?
Giving me the house.
Finding me a job!
Will you ever stop looking down on me?
"Coochie can't find a job on his own."
Right?
It's embarrassing.
Having my sister asking others for a job.
You're better than me.
Better at everything.
Everyone knows.
You don't have to try so hard.
Yeah.
I suck.
I'm a loser, I know.
So what?
When you're gone,
it'll be my problem
if I sleep on the streets.
Chut.
Jane's just trying to help.
-She's worried about--
-I'm talking to my sister, not you.
Coochie.
That gift for his mom.
Why?
Are you afraid I'll give her
something crappy?
We all have to attend your wedding,
or else you'd lose face?
I'm not really wanted there, right?
I know you've never been proud of me.
I know.
Having a brother like me.
Is it very embarrassing?
If so...
we don't have to be siblings anymore.
That's all.
Should I go after him?
It's okay.
Hello.
Once I got settled here,
Japan really isn't that stressful.
Honey, I'm home.
Welcome back.
Bon appétit.
-Please eat up.
-Thank you.
I'm off.
It wasn't that easy at first.
Some Thai dessert?
Thai dessert?
-Sticky rice.
-Rice.
It gradually got better.
I'm home.
-Let me help.
-It's all right.
How are you, little one?
-Hello!
I got you a mobile.
It makes noise too.
My family gradually got bigger.
If you think about it,
it's almost perfect.
Cheers.
-Okay?
-Yes.
We have to use this, don't we?
-Here, do this first.
-And it won't...
-Like this is good.
-Good.
-That's enough.
-It's faded...
-Hello.
-Hello, Ms. Dear.
Please come wait inside.
Yes, Ms. Dear?
How are you, Ms. Dear?
Chut, how long has it been
since we last met?
Jane's wedding, right?
-Yes.
-What do you mean yes?
You didn't even make it.
Hey, perfect timing.
I'll be going to Japan for work.
Which city is she in?
I might meet up with her.
Some city. I've never been there.
Some city?
Nothing.
Seriously, have you ever visited Jane?
Don't you want to visit your nephew?
How long has it been?
When was the last time you saw her?
Wow, Chut.
I must say you really are a lame brother.
What?
I think Jane would like to see
her big brother.
When the bat hit him,
can you believe
that I didn't even know myself?
-It was funny at first.
-Chut.
-Chut!
-But after he didn't wake up,
-I was frightened. A part of me thought,
-Chut!
"How would it be if he really died?"
Everyone shut up!
Call an ambulance.
Thinking back, he only busted his chin.
But that day,
I cried all the way from school
to the hospital.
Chut, wake up.
It was the most tragic moment in my life.
Wake up, Chut.
He's like a burrito.
I'm jealous of people with siblings.
SO AWESOME
COOCHIE
YOU CAN DO IT, COOCHIE, FIGHT ON!
SUPER COOCHIE FIREBALL!!
CHATCHAWIN RIANSUWAN AND FAMILY
JENKWAN RIANSUWAN
MOJIKAWA TAKAHASHI
"DON'T GET TOO DRUNK.
YOU HAVE TO SEND ME OFF TONIGHT."
Mom.
-Auntie.
-Moji.
How are you, son?
-I miss you.
-I miss you, too.
My turn.
-How are you, Auntie?
-I'm great.
Say hello to Grandma.
Let me see. Who is this?
-She's got pretty eyes.
-Jane.
Look who's here.
Oh, my beautiful grandson.
Who's this? Who's this?
Come to Grandma.
Come on, baby.
Jane.
I'll take care of it.
You stay here.
Let's see. Go see your uncle.
Hey, Coochie, try holding your niece.
-I don’t know how, Mom.
-Come on. Give it a try.
Give it a try.
Say hello to your uncle.
Look at her face.
She's not gonna hurt, right?
Don't cry.
She's still looking at her uncle.
She must really love him.
She must love him, doesn't she?
Mommy, I'm home!
Hello, Grandma.
-Welcome back.
Ryo-chan.
That is Uncle Coochie.
Say hello to him.
Hello, Uncle.
-That's great.
JENKWAN RIANSUWAN
Come here.
Ryo-chan, right?
Right?
You're a big brother now.
You have to love your sister a lot.
Okay?
Mommy.
What did Uncle say?
Fireball!
Come on.
Yay, I caught it.
Scene 58.
Take...
-Cut.
-Cut five. Take three.
Action.
Cut.
Chut didn't see me, right?
He didn't know it's you.
Jane.
I got phlegm.
Ouch!
-I'm sorry. Oh, my god!
-She got my eye.
Sorry.
Coochie, next week...
I forgot the city's name.
Kitakyushu.
Action.
Next week...
I'll be moving to Katakoshi.
She's just making up names.
Dear-Raporn?
Kwan-Ruedear? Dear-Ratee?
Dear-Thikamporn?
Dairy queen?
Oh, Dear who lives in Rangsit?
Action.
For example,
a name like...
Tsubasa or something.
There are bones.
Oh no! There're bones?
Is this the Japanese song
you're going to sing for them?
Yeah!
Whatever.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I do.
I forgot my lines.
Damn it. What's next?
I was wondering why
you were scratching so long.
-I couldn't think.
-Scene 42, cut 4, take 2.