[birds chirping]
[vehicle approaching]
[speaking French]
The usurper.
[woman speaking English]
Caro? He's here.
-Professor Perlman.
-Welcome, welcome.
-Thank you so much
for having me.
-Oh, my goodness.
You're bigger
than your picture.
Well, I couldn't get
all of me in the photo.
That's the problem.
[laughing]
[speaking other language]
He seems very confident.
-Mrs. Perlman.
-Annella.
[speaking English]
Oliver. Very nice
to meet you.
-Thank you for having
me in your home.
-Welcome.
[speaking other langugae]
Where's Elio?
I'll go down.
[Perlman] Elio?
-[speaking English]
You must be exhausted.
-[Oliver] What gave me away?
[indistinct chatter]
Hey. [in French]
Darling, come help
Oliver take his things
up to his room.
-He's already here?
-Yes!
[Perlman speaking English]
Every single one
of these will.
Elio, Oliver.
Oliver, Elio.
-How you doing?
-Nice to meet you. Elio.
[Perlman] You must
be exhausted.
-A little bit.
-Come, come, come.
May I bring your things
up to your room?
-Uh, sure. Yeah.
-My room?
[Perlman laughs]
Follow him.
-You're very
welcome here.
-Si.
Our home is your home.
[both blowing]
[speaking other language]
You're leaving?
-Hello.
-Hi.
Nice to meet you.
[door bangs shut]
Oh.
[speaking English]
My room is now your room.
I'll be next door.
We have to share
the bathroom.
It's my only way out.
[snoring]
[piano music playing faintly]
[bell ringing]
[bell ringing in distance]
We're being
called for dinner.
[knocking on door]
[snoring]
[gasping]
Sorry.
Yeah.
We're being
called for dinner.
Oh, yeah, I'm probably
gonna pass.
Will you make
an excuse for me
to your mom, though?
Thanks, man.
So, this is your
old room, huh?
Thanks.
Later.
[door closing]
[speaking other language]
I'll take care of the tart.
-[speaking English] Ah.
-Wow. Look at this.
Good morning, Professor.
-Good morning.
-Back from the dead.
-Was I out that long?
-It seemed like it, huh?
-How are you?
-I... Well, rested now.
-Thank you.
-I'm glad.
Would you like
some espresso?
[Oliver] I would love some.
Thank you very much.
This looks amazing.
I didn't take your
seat, did I?
Oh, no, no, no.
It's okay. Please.
Did you...
Did you recover
from your trip?
I did. Yeah, big time.
-Thank you.
-Good.
I could show you around.
That'd be great.
Thank you.
Is there a...
Is there a bank in town?
I'd love to start
an account while I'm here.
[in Italian] Let me do it.
[in English]
Sorry.
-It happens to the best of us.
-Yeah, well... [laughs]
None of our residents
has ever had a local
bank account.
-Really?
-Mmm.
Should I take him
to Montodine?
I think they're closed
for summer vacation.
You try Crema.
Crema?
[speaking other language]
Thank you.
[speaking English]
Is this your orchard?
-[Perlman]
These are Annella's trees.
-[Oliver] Oh, wow.
[Perlman]
Peaches, cherries, apricots...
Pomegranate.
"Melograno."
Mmm.
Have another egg.
Oh, stupid.
No, no, no.
I know myself too well.
If I have a second,
I'm just gonna have a third,
and then a fourth,
and then you're just
gonna have to roll
me out of here.
-Delicious.
-[Annella] Darling?
[Oliver] Thank you.
Shall I give him
Anchise's bike?
[livestock bleating]
[dog barking]
[Oliver] So, what does
one do around here?
Wait for the summer to end.
Yeah?
What do you do
in the winter?
-Wait for summer to come?
-Well, we only come
here for Christmas
and some other vacations.
-Christmas?
I thought you...
-And Easter as well.
-Thought you were Jewish.
-Well, we are Jewish,
but also American,
Italian, French.
Somewhat atypical
combination.
Besides my family,
you're probably
the only other Jew
to set foot in this town.
I'm from a small town
in New England.
I know what it's like
to be the odd Jew out.
[Elio chuckles]
So, what do you
do around here?
-Just read books.
-[bells chiming]
Transcribe music.
Swim at the river.
-Yeah?
-Go out at night.
-I don't know.
-That sounds fun.
All right, buddy,
thanks for the help.
[Elio] Sorry.
Sorry about that.
It's all right.
All right, later.
[Perlman]
What do you have there?
That should all be...
[laughing]
Oh, what is this?
These are the
continuation of these
archaeology department...
[Perlman]
These are archaeology?
[Oliver] Yeah, those are
archaeology. The rest of these
should be history.
[Perlman] Ah, okay.
-More apricot juice?
-[Oliver] Yeah.
-Here, tesoro.
-Thank you.
[in French]
Help yourself, darling.
Thanks.
[piano music playing]
[speaking English]
Help yourself
to some more.
The word "apricot"
comes from the Arabic.
It's like the words
"algebra," "alchemy,"
"alcohol."
It derives from
an Arabic noun
combined with the
Arabic article "al"
before it.
The origin of our
Italian albicocca
is al-barquq.
It's amazing that
today in Israel and
many Arab countries,
the fruit's referred to
by a totally different
name, Mismish.
I may have to disagree
with you there, Professor.
Ah?
I'm gonna talk etymology,
so just bear with me
a second. Um...
You're right in the case
that most Latin words
do find their origins
in Greek words.
However, in the case
of "apricot,"
it's a little bit more
of a complicated journey.
Ah. How so?
Well, here, the Greek
actually takes over
from the Latin.
Latin word being,
praecoquum or precoquere.
So it's, "Precook" or,
"Pre-ripen,"as you know.
To be precocious or premature.
And the Byzantines,
to go on,
then borrowed praecox,
which became
prekokkia, which then
became berikokki,
which is how
the Arabs got al-barquq.
That's courtesy
of Philology 101.
Flying colors.
He does this every year.
It's about drink time.
Let's go here.
-[in Italian] Ciao, Romano.
-Ciao, Oliver.
-How are you?
-All good.
[in Italian]
Ciao, boys!
All good?
All good!
[speaking English] Let's see.
What have we got?
-Can you start please?
-Of course!
[indistinct chatter]
[Elio] Good morning, gentlemen.
[all greeting]
How do you know
about this place?
Okay.
[in French] Go, Chiara!
[speaking English]
No, no, no, no, no!
[whooping and clapping]
[in Italian]
He's better than the guy
who came last year.
Remember?
Get in there!
Much better!
See how cute he is.
[indistinct chatter]
Elio, water!
[speaking English]
Perfect timing.
-[Oliver] What's the matter?
Are you all right?
-Huh?
-What, pinch a nerve?
-I'm okay.
Here. Hold this.
Trust me.
I'm about to be a doctor.
Hey, hey, come here.
See? That's the problem.
You're too stressed.
-You just gotta
relax a little bit.
-I am relaxing.
Marzia,
come here for a minute.
Back me up here.
-Feel that. Right there?
-[man] Oliver.
-It's too tight, right?
-Yeah.
-He needs to relax.
-[man] Oliver!
Later.
You should relax more.
Okay, guys, ready?
[whooping]
[Oliver] Okay, our ball,
our ball, our ball.
Twelve serving 11.
Mine, mine, mine, mine.
Go, go, go. Yeah, good.
It's yours, it's yours.
[in Italian]
Sweetheart, Auntie Marcella
and the others are coming
over for dinner.
Is Oliver staying with us
or going out?
Don't know.
What a movie star!
Yes, those Americans...
Sparkling wine!
He's late.
Don't you think...
Don't you think
he's impolite when
he says, "Later"?
Arrogant.
[in English]
I don't think
he's arrogant.
Just watch.
This is how he'll say
good-bye to us when
the time comes.
With his... "Later."
[all laughing]
Meanwhile, we'll have
to put up with him
for six long weeks.
Won't we, darling?
I think he's shy.
You'll grow to like him.
What if I grow to hate him?
[Annella speaking Italian]
Oh, no, sweetheart.
-Take his plates away.
-Very well, madam.
[Annella] Darling?
[indistinct conversation
in Italian]
[speaking English]
Elio, play something.
[in Italian] I don't want to
Why not?
Because I don't want to.
Why don't you go
to Moscazzano with others?
Because I don't want to.
[Annella speaking English]
You're spoiling
everyone's fun.
[low cheering]
Play well, darling.
[sighing]
[playing lively
classical music]
[birds chirping]
[bell tolling]
[blowing]
[knocking on door]
-Hey.
What are you doing?
Reading.
How come you're not
with everyone else
down by the river?
-I have an allergy. It's...
-Yeah, me too.
Maybe we have the same one.
Hmm?
Why don't you and I
go swimming?
-Right now?
-Yeah.
Come on. Let's go.
Do we have
to go right now?
-I'll go get changed.
-Okay.
-Meet you downstairs.
-Mmm-hmm.
See you downstairs.
[door opens and shuts]
Elio, what are you doing?
Reading my music.
No, you're not.
-Thinking, then.
-Yeah?
About what?
It's private.
You're not gonna tell me?
I'm not gonna tell you.
He's not gonna tell me
what he's thinking about.
[Annella] Elio.
I guess I'll go hang out
with your mom.
[Oliver] More apricot
juice, please.
[Annella] That's a good boy.
Thank God you're helping me.
[laughter in distance]
[indistinct chatter]
[playing slow tune]
-[Oliver] Sounds nice.
-[stops playing]
[Elio] Thought you
didn't like it.
Play it again, will you?
Follow me.
[indistinct chatter
and laughter]
[plays same tune faster]
That sounds different.
Did you change it?
-Well, I changed it
a little bit.
-Why?
I just played it the way
Liszt would have played it
if he'd altered
Bach's version.
Play that again.
-Play what again?
-The thing
you played outside.
Oh, you want me to play
the thing I played outside?
-Please.
-Ah. [mutters] Of course.
[plays with slight variation]
I can't believe
you changed it again.
-Oh, I changed it a little bit.
-Yeah. Why?
I just played it the way
Busoni would've played it
if he'd altered
Liszt's version.
And what is wrong
with Bach the way
Bach would've played...
Bach never wrote it
for the guitar.
In fact, we're not
even sure Bach
wrote it at all.
Forget I asked.
[plays first tune]
It's young Bach.
He dedicated it
to his brother.
[piano music playing]
[music plays gently
on headphones]
Hey, Professor.
Hello.
Here, please.
I need help.
[Oliver] Just be honest.
How bad is it?
[Perlman] I think
your insights here
are persuasive, but...
-Ciao.
[in Italian]
Have you been to the river?
[bubbling sounds]
[old man] Mafalda!
Isn't she beautiful?
-[Oliver] Elio.
-Mmm.
[Oliver speaking English]
You sleeping?
I was.
Listen to this drivel.
Tell me what you think.
-Wait.
-What?
Can't hear you.
[groans]
[Oliver] "For the early Greeks,
Heidegger contends,
this underlying hiddenness
is constitutive of
the way beings are,
not only in relation
to themselves
but also in relation
to other entities generally.
In other words, they do not
construe hiddenness
merely or primarily
in terms of entities'
relations to human beings."
Does that make
any sense to you?
Doesn't make
any sense to me.
I don't think
it makes any sense
to your dad, either.
Maybe it did
when you wrote it.
That might be
the kindest thing anybody
has said to me in months.
"Kind?"
Yep. Kind.
♪ Time like silent stares ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ With no apology ♪
♪ Move towards the stars ♪
♪ And be my only one ♪
-Hey, Elio.
-Hey.
Hey!
[song continues playing]
[in Italian]
Come here.
What's going on?
Is he trying to
get it on with her?
Elio, he already succeeded?
What do I know?
I'd love to be
in his shoes.
Who wouldn't love
to be in her shoes?
She wants him,
no matter what!
♪ Lady, lady, lady, lady ♪
♪ Don't walk
this lonely avenue ♪
♪ Oh, lady, lady, lady, lady ♪
♪ Let me touch
that part of you ♪
♪ You want me to ♪
["Love my way" playing]
Coming?
I'll come later.
[excited screeching]
♪ A kiss is not enough ♪
♪ Love my way ♪
♪ It's a new road ♪
♪ I follow ♪
♪ Where my mind goes ♪
♪ They'd put us
on a railroad ♪
♪ They'd dearly make us pay ♪
♪ For laughing in their faces ♪
♪ And making it our way ♪
♪ Love my way
It's a new road ♪
♪ I follow
Where my mind goes ♪
♪ Love my way ♪
♪ It's a new road ♪
♪ I follow ♪
♪ Where my mind goes ♪
[in French]
Are you mad with me because
you are mad with Chiara?
Why would I be
mad at Chiara?
Because of him.
Because of who?
Of Oliver.
Turn around.
Meet me here tomorrow night?
[screaming, splashing]
Wait for me!
Come on.
[speaking English]
We almost had sex
last night...
Marzia and me.
Hmm? Well, why didn't you?
I don't know.
Well, you know,
it's better to have
tried and failed, right?
All I had to do
was find the courage
to reach out and touch.
She would have said yes.
Well, try again later.
Try what later?
I just heard from
the people in Sirmione.
They say they've
come up with something.
Oh! Fantastic.
Going there today.
-Would you like to come along?
-I would love to.
Thank you.
-[Annella] Smell this.
-Can I come, too?
Ah, on the condition
you remain silent.
Silent as in,
"He has too many opinions,"
or silent as in,
"Just not telling anybody
what an amazing
thing you've dug up"?
Well, nothing
has been dug up.
It's what has
been brought out,
out of the water.
[cycle bell rings]
Ciao, Chiara!
[in French]
What are you doing?
Going to Lake Garda
with my dad.
He wants to show Oliver
where he's dredging.
Can you tell him
I came by?
He's inside with my dad,
helping him.
You were amazing last night,
on the dance floor.
-He's a good dancer.
-A good dancer.
He's good-looking, too.
-Want to get us together?
-No.
[chuckles]
Come in.
[indistinct conversation]
[speaking English]
Dad always sits up front
with Anchise to navigate.
[cycle bell dings]
She seems to
like you a lot.
She's more beautiful
than she was last year.
I saw her naked
on a night swim once.
Great body.
Trying to get me
to like her?
What would be
the harm in that?
No, no harm.
Just typically like to go
at those things on my own,
if you don't mind.
[speaking other language]
I'll drive today!
Just don't play
at being the good host.
[Perlman] Anchise,
take the afternoon off.
[speaking English]
What's going on, boys?
Oliver, come.
Sit up front.
Be my navigator.
What? What?
[engine revs]
[distant chatter]
-[laughing] Dr. Roseburg.
-Samuel!
[Rosenberg] Benvenuto.
[Perlman] Look who's here.
He's grown a bit, eh?
And this is Oliver.
[Teresa] Ciao.
Ciao, Teresa.
[Perlman] Oh!
Ah.
[in Italian]
[Rosenberg]
Sammy! Come on!
Truce?
[Perlman speaking English]
Hey, boys.
[Perlman] The ship went down
in 1827 on the way to Isola
del Garda.
Gossip has it this statue
was a gift from Count Lechi
to his lover, contralto
Adelaide Malanotte.
There are four known sets,
after the Praxiteles
originals.
This fellow's at number three.
The Emperor Hadrian
had a pair, dug up at Tivoli,
but one of the more
philistine of the Farnese
Popes melted them down
and had them recast
as a particularly
voluptuous Venus.
Who'd like to go for a swim
before we head back?
We're all such pros.
If I got my own statue,
it would probably be on there.
[whooping]
[Oliver] Elio!
[Elio] Oliver!
-[Elio] I have to go.
I have to go.
-Hey! Hey!
Goodness.
-Are you going, too?
-No, no.
I should stay and do
some work on my book.
Come on. How about a drink
to celebrate the day?
-Okay, maybe just one.
-All right!
[crickets chirping]
Marzia?
[birds chirping]
[playing piano softly]
The Cosmic Fragments
by Heraclitus.
[Oliver] The meaning
of the river flowing is not
that all things are changing
so that we cannot
encounter them twice,
but that some things stay
the same only by changing.
[footsteps approaching]
[knock on door]
-[knock on door]
-Mmm.
[speaking other language]
Sorry, Elio. I brought
some clean clothes.
Mmm.
Leave the door open.
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.
[fly buzzing]
[voices in distance]
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
[Annella speaking English]
Darling, have you
seen my Heptaméron?
Mafalda.
It's in German.
Okay.
I can't remember where
we left off, but I think
you'll like this one.
Come here, darling.
So, I'll translate, huh?
[reading German]
[in English]
"A handsome young knight
is madly in love
with a princess.
And she, too,
is in love with him,
though she seems not to be
entirely aware of it.
Despite the friendship..."
[reads softly]
"...that blossoms
between them,
or perhaps because of
that very friendship,
the young knight
finds himself so..."
[reads softly]
"...so humbled
and speechless
that he's totally unable
to bring up the subject
of his love.
Till one day,
he asks the princess
point-blank..."
[reads softly in German]
"Is it better
to speak or to die?"
I'd never have the courage
to ask a question like that.
I doubt that.
Hey, Elly-Belly.
You do know that
you can always talk to us.
[birds chirping]
[Elio] My mom's been
reading this 16th-century
French romance.
She read some of it
to my dad and I the day
the lights went out.
[Oliver] Yeah, about
the knight that doesn't know
whether to speak or die?
[Elio] Right.
[Oliver] So,
does he or doesn't he?
"Better to speak,"
she said.
But she's on her guard.
She senses a trap somewhere.
So, does he speak?
No.
-He fudges.
-Hmm.
It figures.
He's French.
I gotta go to town
in a little bit to pick
some things up.
Oh, I can go. I'm not
doing anything today.
Then why don't
we go together?
Right now?
Yeah. Right now.
That is, of course,
unless you have more
important business going on.
[mock imitation]
Mind if I put
this in your bag?
Yes, please.
[in Italian]
I straightened the wheels
and inflated the tires.
Perfect. Thanks.
[speaking English] I fell.
I was coming home
the other day, and I scraped
myself pretty badly.
Anchise insisted
on applying some sort
of witches' brew.
I think it helped.
[gasps]
[cows mooing]
Hold this for a second,
will you?
-Want one?
-Sure.
Not bad, huh?
Not bad at all.
I thought
you didn't smoke.
I don't.
-So, World War II, huh?
-No. This is World War I.
You'd have to be
at least 80 years old
to have known any of them.
I never even heard
of the Battle of Piave.
Battle of Piave was one
of the most lethal battles
of World War I.
170,000 people died.
Is there anything
you don't know?
I know nothing, Oliver.
Well, you seem to know
more than anybody else
around here.
Well, if you only knew
how little I know about
the things that matter.
What things that matter?
You know what things.
Why are you
telling me this?
'Cause I thought
you should know.
Because you thought
I should know?
'Cause I wanted
you to know?
Because I wanted you to know.
'Cause I wanted
you to know.
Because there's no one else
I can say this to but you.
Are you saying
what I think
you're saying?
Don't go anywhere.
Stay right here.
You know I'm not
going anywhere.
They mixed up
all of my pages.
I'm gonna have to
retype this whole thing.
I'm not gonna have
anything to work on
this afternoon.
-This is gonna set me
back a whole day.
-[bell chiming]
Damn it.
I shouldn't have
said anything.
Just pretend
you never did.
What does that mean?
We're on speaking
terms, but not really?
It means, we can't
talk about those
kinds of things
Okay?
We just can't.
Hey!
[in Italian]
Let's go, American!
[panting]
-[speaking English] Ready?
-Let's go.
Pretty much.
-You thirsty?
-Yeah.
[in Italian]
Good morning, ma'am.
Excuse me.
Could I ask
for a glass of water?
[Oliver chuckles]
Il Duce.
"People of Italy"
That's Italy.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
[speaking English] Come on.
This is my spot.
It's all mine.
I come here to read.
I can't tell you
the number of books
I've read here.
Oh, my God.
It's freezing.
The spring
is in the mountains.
The Alpi Orobie.
The water comes
straight down from there.
[Oliver] I like
the way you say things.
I don't know why
you're always putting
yourself down, though.
[Elio] So you won't,
I guess?
You really that afraid
of what I think?
[both chuckle]
[Oliver] You're making things
very difficult for me.
[sighs]
I love this, Oliver.
What?
Everything.
[chuckles]
Us, you mean?
Eh, it's not bad.
It's not bad.
[sighing]
Better now?
Mmm-mmm.
No, no, no.
-We should go.
-Why?
I know myself. Okay?
And we've been good.
We haven't done anything
to be ashamed of,
and that's a good thing.
I wanna be good.
Okay?
Am I offending you?
Just don't.
I think it's starting
to get infected.
We can stop by
the pharmacist's
on the way back.
Excellent idea.
[in Italian]
So we got the government
of Bettino Craxi...
Because we don't do anything
but talk, talk, talk.
Let me speak.
We have five parties
that do nothing but fight.
Smoke and shut up!
Let them speak, him, her.
I'd like to know
what they think too.
Annella, what do you think?
A five party government!
Darling, I think
it's the historic
compromise...
Don't say that.
Compromises are tragic.
You've changed since
you inherited this place.
What's that got
to do with it?
What are you saying?
You're mad, darling.
You asshole!
-She's right.
-And you don't say
anything to her.
Say something.
You're resigned.
Why don't we talk
about the death of Bunuel?
Bunuel was a genius
-Know him?
-Cinema isn't the answer.
Cinema is a mirror
of reality and it's a filter.
They broadcast
The Phantom of Liberty
with constant interr...
Everyone loves Bunuel
Let's hear his opinion
He doesn't know
anything about Italy!
Say something.
Give us your impression.
Do you have an impression?
Darling, he's American.
That doesn't mean stupid!
[laughing]
Just stop.
I don't give an easy ride
to some politicians.
She didn't say that.
I'm going to go mad.
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
It happens all the time.
-Mafalda, ice?
-It's in the fridge.
You get used to
absolutely everything.
Don't you realize
you're mixing everything up?
What are you
talking about?
-There's no more
politics, nothing.
-He's left too.
[softly] Elio.
Elio?
[speaking English]
You all right?
Sit for a second.
If you insist...
That wasn't my fault, right?
No.
I'm a mess.
Well, the kitchen
table sure is.
[winces]
Ow! Where'd you
learn to do that?
My bubby used to
do this for us
when we were sick.
Trust me, it helps.
I used to have
one of these.
-You used to?
-Yeah.
How come you
never wear it?
My mother says
we are Jews of discretion.
Well...
I guess that works
for your mother.
Funny witch.
[both laughing]
[groaning]
Fuck, you'll kill me
if you do that.
I hope not.
[laughing] Ciao.
Hey, are you leaving?
-Where's Elio?
-He's inside.
He had a bit of
a nosebleed during lunch,
and he's just resting.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Okay. I'll be
back in a minute.
-Bye.
Don't go anywhere.
[in French]
You okay?
Are we going out?
I don't know if I can go out.
If my mom sees, she'll worry.
-She will?
-Yeah, she's a pain.
Where's Oliver?
[chuckles] Don't ask me.
[laughing, chatting]
Where's Oliver?
-Didn't he go out?
-Would you like
a smoothie?
No, thank you.
We're having dinner soon.
All right.
I'm going out tonight.
-Don't make me worry.
-What are you
talking about?
This is no good, madam.
-Let him do
his own thing.
-Fine.
Why's she hassling me?
I'm 17.
She's worried
about you.
You like him,
don't you? Oliver?
Everyone likes Oliver.
I think he likes you, too.
More than you do.
Is that your impression?
-No, he told me.
-When did he say that?
A while ago.
[in Italian]
Mafalda, do you know
where Oliver is?
I have no idea.
♪ It's been a long, long time ♪
♪ Since I've memorized
your face ♪
♪ It's been four hours now ♪
♪ Since I've wandered
through your place ♪
♪ And when I sleep
on your couch ♪
♪ I feel very safe ♪
♪ And when you bring
the blankets ♪
♪ I cover up my face ♪
♪ I do ♪
♪ Love you ♪
♪ And when you play guitar ♪
♪ I listen
to the strings buzz ♪
♪ The metal vibrates
underneath your fingers ♪
[door opens]
♪ And when you crochet ♪
♪ I feel mesmerized and proud ♪
♪ And I would say I love you ♪
♪ But saying it out loud
is hard ♪
♪ So I won't say it at all ♪
♪ And I won't stay very long ♪
♪ But you are the life ♪
[Oliver urinating]
♪ I needed all along ♪
♪ I think of you ♪
♪ As my brother ♪
♪ Although that sounds dumb ♪
♪ And words
are futile devices ♪
[flushing]
[speaking English] Traitor.
[exhales]
Traitor.
[woman on TV] This is Craxi.
I draw the center of Craxi...
[laughing]
[in French]
-Hey.
-[Marzia] Hi!
It's me. Is that Marzia?
[Marzia] Sure it is!
Can't you tell?
Sorry.
Is that for me?
Thanks.
[Marzia] Do you really
read a lot?
I love reading too,
but I don't tell anyone.
Why not?
-I don't know.
-[bell chiming]
I think...
people who read are...
kind of secretive.
They hide who they really are.
Do you hide
who you really are?
No, not with you.
Not with me?
Why?
Because...
I think...
you're going to hurt me,
and I don't want to be hurt.
You're so hard.
Wait.
Kiss me.
[Elio] Is that good?
[Marzia] Yes. [moaning]
[Elio] Are you lying?
[both grunting]
[Elio] Oh, fuck, I'm sorry.
[Marzia] It's all right.
[laughing]
[Elio] Are you mad at me?
Are you angry?
What's so funny?
Why are you laughing?
Leave me alone.
Fuck, that felt good.
[Elio speaking English]
Please don't avoid me.
It kills me.
Can't stand thinking
you hate me.
Your silence is killing me.
I'd sooner die
than know you hate me.
I am such a pussy.
Way over the top.
Can't stand the silence.
Need to speak to you.
[Oliver] Did someone have
a good night last night?
-[speaks French] Not really.
-Mm.
[speaking English]
Well, you must be tired, then.
Or were you playing
poker, too?
I don't play poker.
Several hundred color slides
of our boxer
and the others like him
arrived yesterday from Berlin.
We should start
cataloging them.
That'll keep us busy
till lunch, I imagine.
Sure.
Beautiful, aren't they?
They're all
so incredibly sensual.
Because these
are more Hellenistic
than 5th century Athenian.
[Perlman] Most likely sculpted
under the influence
of Praxiteles.
Right.
Greatest sculptor
in antiquity.
[Oliver] Grow up.
I'll see you at midnight.
[Elio] Grow up.
[Perlman] Muscles are firm.
Look at his stomach,
for example.
Not a straight body
in these statues.
They're all curved.
Sometimes impossibly curved.
And so nonchalant.
Hence their ageless ambiguity.
As if they're daring you
to desire them.
[door opens]
[indistinct chatter
in distance]
Don't forget, Isaac and Mounir
are coming for dinner.
-Also known
as Sonny and Cher.
-Okay.
I'd like you to wear
that shirt they gave you
for your birthday.
No.
Darling, they got it
for you in Miami.
I'm sorry.
It's too big.
-Come on.
It will make them so happy.
-It looks ridiculous on me.
I'll try it on
for Oliver.
If Oliver thinks
I look like
a scarecrow in it,
I'm not wearing it.
Oliver?
Hey, what time you got?
It's 2:00.
-Well... Later.
-Later.
Mafalda.
[gasps, laughs]
[in Italian]
I won't be here for dinner.
Okay, Mr. Oliver.
-[ringing bell] Ciao.
-Ciao.
[cows mooing]
[squealing]
[in Italian]
Hello, Mafalda.
Marzia.
[in French]
Where are we going?
You'll see.
[laughing]
Stop it!
[hissing, laughing]
[tuning radio]
♪ Don't come easy ♪
♪ To me ♪
♪ How can I find a way ♪
♪ To make you see I love you? ♪
♪ Words don't come easy ♪
♪ Words ♪
♪ Don't come easy to me ♪
♪ This is the only way ♪
♪ For me to say I love you ♪
♪ Words don't come easy ♪
♪ Well, I'm just a music man ♪
♪ Melody's so far
my best friend ♪
♪ But my words
are coming out wrong ♪
♪ Girl, I reveal
my heart to you ♪
♪ And hope that you believe
it's true ♪
♪ 'Cause words ♪
♪ Don't come easy to me ♪
♪ How can I find a way ♪
♪ To make you see I love you? ♪
♪ Words don't come easy ♪
♪ This is just a simple song ♪
♪ That I've made... ♪
[honking]
[birds chirping]
[honking continues]
[in French]
-How are you, buddy?
-Hey!
-It's been ages.
-It has, yes.
-How are you?
-You've grown.
-How are you.
-I'm good.
Good to see you.
[speaking French]
Remember Marzia
from last year.
Hello.
-Marzia, remember Issac?
-The girl from Paris?
Good to meet you.
Want to eat
with us tonight?
[in English]
No, no. I have to go.
-[in French] You're sure?
-Yes.
-[in English] Okay.
-Have a nice evening.
[in French] Goodbye.
[in English]
This right here is
the brand-new china that
you guys so kindly sent to us.
It looks wonderful.
Come here, Mounir, Mounir.
-Come, come, come.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can't put it on now.
They've already met me.
-Yes, you can.
-It'll look like
a put-up job.
-Papa, it'll...
-Yes.
-Papa, it'll look like
a put-up job.
-No misbehaving tonight.
No... No laughing.
When I tell you to play,
you'll play.
You're too old not to accept
people for who they are.
What's wrong with them?
You call them Sonny and Cher
behind their backs.
-That's what Mom calls them...
-Then you accept gifts
from them.
The only person
that reflects badly on
is you.
Is it because they're gay
or because they're ridiculous?
If you know as much
about economics
at Mounir's age,
you'll be a very wise man,
indeed.
And a credit to me.
Now, just get into this, you.
[excited chatter]
These are unbelievable.
I just...
Hey, look who's here.
[playing slow tune on piano]
[tempo increases]
[slows tempo]
[applause]
Sorry. I have to go to bed.
I'm sorry. I'm so tired.
[Perlman] Thank you.
Elio. Elio.
-Thank you.
-Good night.
Good night.
[Elio] Do I know you?
[door opens]
[loud laughter in distance]
[Mounir] Thank you again
for everything.
[indistinct conversation]
-They're never
gonna make it.
-No, no. They're fine.
[blowing horn]
I'm glad you came.
Yeah, I'm nervous.
[whispering]
I like what you've done
with the place.
It's nice.
[chuckles]
You okay?
Me okay.
[laughing]
-Can I kiss you?
-Yes, please.
[door bangs shut]
[giggles]
[Oliver] What are you doing?
[Elio] Nothing.
Does this make you happy?
You're not gonna get
a nosebleed on me, are you?
I'm not gonna get...
Off, off, off, off, off.
Yeah. Just pull it.
Or I'll pull it.
[breathing heavily]
[both panting]
[Elio] Oliver.
Call me by your name,
and I'll call you by mine.
Elio.
Oliver.
-Oliver.
-Elio.
Did we make noise?
Nothing to worry about.
I don't know.
Mafalda always looks
for signs.
Well, she's not
gonna find any.
[Elio] You wore that shirt
the first day you were here.
Will you give it to me
when you go?
[birds chirping]
Let's go swimming.
Are you gonna hold
what happened last night
against me?
No.
Elio. Come here.
Take your trunks off.
[Oliver]
Well, that's promising.
You're hard again.
Good.
[chuckles]
Professor, I got your note.
Thank you for reminding me.
I'm gonna go into town
and pick up
those typed pages today,
so maybe this afternoon
would be a good time to...
Later.
[all laughing]
We'll look them over later,
before you leave.
Okay. So, later.
Later.
Oliver.
[Oliver] You're not
sick of me yet?
No, I just...
I just wanted
to be with you.
I'll... I'm gonna...
I'll go.
Do you know how happy I am
that we slept together?
I don't know.
Of course, you don't know.
I don't want you
to regret anything.
And I hate the thought
that maybe I may have
messed you up or...
I don't want either of us
to pay for this,
-one way or another.
-No, I...
It's not like
I'm gonna tell anyone.
You're not gonna be, like,
getting in trouble.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
Are you happy I came here?
I would kiss you if I could.
[Mafalda speaking Italian]
Times change.
[Pasquina] Thank God
we had the partisans.
[Mafalda] I know, but times
have changed. It's different.
[Pasquina] What do you
think of Bettino?
[Mafalda] I don't like him.
[Pasquina] I like him.
[Mafalda] I'm happy, actually.
I don't know. We'll see.
[Pasquina] Anyway,
they make the rules.
Pasquina!
Hello.
Hello, ma'am.
-Tortelli cremaschi.
-Yes.
[music playing on radio]
[tuning]
[mid-tempo song plays]
[in English]
Oh, fuck.
[exhales]
[suppressed moans]
Fuck.
What did you do?
-Nothing.
-No?
[chuckling]
Oh, I see.
You've moved on
to the plant kingdom already.
What's next? Minerals?
I suppose you've already
given up animals.
You know that's me.
I'm sick, aren't I?
I wish everybody
was as sick as you.
Please don't do that.
-You want to see
something sick?
-Please don't do that.
You want to see
something sick?
Please don't do this.
Hey. Please don't do it.
Why are you doing this to me?
-What are you doing?
-Stop.
-You're fucking hurting me.
-Then don't fight.
[crying]
Sorry.
It's okay.
I don't want you to go.
[Elio] God,
we wasted so many days.
Why didn't
you give me a sign?
-I did. I did.
-You didn't give me
a sign.
When?
You remember
when we were
playing volleyball
and I touched you?
Just to show you
that I liked you?
And the way you reacted
made me feel
like I'd molested you.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-No, it's fine.
I just decided
I should keep my distance.
I don't know.
I come out here for hours
almost every night.
I didn't know that.
That's funny, I...
I thought that...
Yeah, I know
what you thought.
Stop. Stop.
"For Oliver.
From Elio."
[Marzia] Elio?
[in French]
You disappeared
for three days.
[in English]
I had to work.
[in French]
You completely disappeared.
[in English]
Yeah, I don't know. I just...
[in French]
I had a lot to do.
[in English]
Am I your girl?
Oliver has to go to Bergamo
for a few days.
Oh?
Research at the university.
Then he'll fly home
from Linate.
But what about Elio?
Maybe it could be nice
for the two of them
to get away
for a couple of days, no?
What do you think?
You know you've been
our favorite student?
-You must come back.
-You sure you're not
just saying that?
-Oliver.
-Thank you very much,
Professor.
Oh, man.
Please, please
come back soon.
Come back? I'm just
going home to pack.
I'm moving here.
You're welcome.
Oh, well...
-Thank you guys so much.
-Of course.
Oliver, Oliver.
-Come back.
-It's been...
Come here, come here.
It's been amazing.
Thank you guys.
Well, later, Perlmans.
[laughing] Later.
Later, later, later.
-Ciao. Ciao.
-Ciao.
-Arrivederci.
-Arrive-ciao! Ciao.
-Ciao, ciao.
-Ciao!
Ciao, ciao. Ciao, ciao, ciao.
Tell Elio to call
when you get there.
[bell ringing]
-Oh, no.
-[sighs]
[in French]
Come for dinner tonight.
Bring Marzia.
Bye, darling.
[in English]
-What?
-Nothing.
♪ Oh, to see without my eyes ♪
♪ The first time
that you kissed me ♪
♪ Boundless by the time
I cried ♪
♪ I built your walls
around me ♪
[Elio screaming] Yes!
♪ White noise
What an awful sound ♪
[Oliver screaming] Oliver!
[Elio screaming] Elio!
Elio!
♪ Hand of God, deliver me ♪
♪ Oh, woe is me ♪
♪ The first time
that you touched me ♪
-Oliver!
-Elio!
♪ Oh, will wonders
never cease? ♪
♪ Blessed be
the mystery of love ♪
♪ Lord, I no longer believe ♪
Yes!
♪ Drowned in living waters ♪
♪ Cursed by the love
that I received ♪
♪ From my brother's daughter ♪
♪ Like Hephaestion who died ♪
♪ Alexander's lover ♪
♪ Now I'm prone to misery ♪
♪ The birthmark on your... ♪
[laughing]
Oh, God.
[Oliver singing]
♪ And I'm feeling low ♪
♪ Understand I'm feeling low ♪
[imitating song music]
[music playing in distance]
You hear that?
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, it's this way.
Come on. Come on.
You're missing it.
Come on.
[whooping]
Ja! Ragazzi!
Don't stop.
♪ A kiss is not enough... ♪
This. This.
This. You.
You are...
♪ Love my way ♪
♪ It's a new road ♪
[bell dinging]
♪ I follow... ♪
[in Italian]
If you'll excuse me...
Just one second.
One second!
♪ They'd dearly make us pay ♪
♪ For laughing in their faces ♪
♪ And making it our way ♪
♪ There's emptiness
behind their eyes ♪
♪ There's dust
in all their hearts ♪
[Oliver in Italian]
I saw them last year.
Richard Butler... Fantastic!
[girl speaking Italian] Really?
We saw them in concert too.
We hitchhiked to London.
[in English]
What'd she say?
♪ It's a new road ♪
♪ I follow ♪
♪ Where my mind goes ♪
Excuse me, excuse me,
excuse me.
[train approaching]
[Elio] Did you get
your passport?
You get your passport?
[announcement over speaker]
[blowing whistle]
[train blowing horn]
[speaking French]
Mafalda?
Mom?
Yeah, it's me.
Yeah, everything is fine.
I'm at the station...
in Clusone.
Listen, Mom, can you...
[stammering]
Can you come get me, Mom?
[indistinct chatter]
[music playing on car stereo]
Ciao.
[speaking English] How are you?
Good.
[in French]
I read the book
you bought me.
The poems...
They're really beautiful.
I love that...
Antonia Pozzi.
I'm sorry, excuse me...
that you're sad.
I'm saying that because
I wanted to tell you
I'm not mad at you.
Not at all.
I love you, Elio.
Stay friends?
For life?
For life.
[in English]
Missed you at dinner.
So...
Welcome home.
Thanks.
-Oliver enjoyed the trip?
-Yeah.
I think he did.
You two had
a nice friendship.
Yeah.
You're too smart
not to know how rare,
how special
what you two had was.
Oliver was Oliver.
[chuckling]
[in French]
Because it was him.
Because it was me.
[in English] Oliver may be
very intelligent but...
He was more
than intelligent.
What you two had
had everything and nothing
to do with intelligence.
It was good.
You're both lucky
to have found each other
because you too
are good...
I think he was
better than...
I think he was better
than me.
[exhales]
I'm sure he'd say
the same thing about you.
Yeah. He'd say
the same thing.
It flatters you both.
And when
you least expect it,
nature has cunning ways
of finding our weakest spot.
Just remember,
I am here.
Right now, you may not
wanna feel anything,
maybe you never
wanted to feel anything.
And maybe it's not to me
you'd want to speak
about these things
but feel something
you obviously did.
Look, you had
a beautiful friendship.
Maybe more than
a friendship.
And I envy you.
In my place,
most parents would hope
the whole thing goes away.
Pray their sons
land on their feet,
but I am not such a parent.
We rip out
so much of ourselves
to be cured of things faster,
that we go bankrupt
by the age of 30.
And have less to offer,
each time we start
with someone new.
But to make yourself
feel nothing
so as not to feel anything.
What a waste.
Have I spoken out of turn?
And I'll say one more thing,
it'll clear the air.
I may have come close
but I never had
what you two have.
Something always held me back
or stood in the way.
How you live your life
is your business.
Just remember,
our hearts and our bodies
are given to us only once,
and before you know it,
your heart's worn out.
And as for your body,
there comes a point
when no one looks at it
much less wants
to come near it.
Right now,
there's sorrow, pain.
Don't kill it,
and with it,
the joy you felt.
Does Mom know?
I don't think she does.
[door opens]
[in Italian]
-Have you been
to the Gaverine?
-Yes.
Latkes.
-May I?
-Happy Hanukkah!
To you too.
[indistinct chatter]
[in English]
She looks a bit weak.
She comes highly
recommended by my...
Her special
area of study is...
[phone ringing]
I'll get it.
[speaking other language]
Hello?
[Oliver speaking English]
Elio, you there?
-Hi.
-[Oliver] Hey.
-How are you.
-[Oliver] I'm good.
I'm good. How are you?
-How are your parents?
-I'm good. They're fine.
Good.
I miss you.
[Oliver] I miss you, too.
Very much.
-I have some news.
-News?
What, you're getting married?
I suppose.
I might be getting married
next spring, yeah.
You never said anything.
Been off and on
for three years.
That's wonderful news.
Do you mind?
[Annella] Oliver.
[Perlman] Oliver.
-Oliver.
-[Oliver] Hey, hey, hey.
[Annella] Darling,
when are you coming back?
[Oliver] I wish I was.
[Perlman] You caught us
in the process of choosing
the new you for next summer.
-And guess what?
He's a she.
-[Oliver] Oh, no.
[Oliver] I was thinking
of calling to tell you guys
I got engaged.
Wonderful!
-Congratulations.
-Mazel tov!
-Congratulations, Oliver.
- Thank you, thank you,
thank you.
Listen we'll leave you...
We'll let you speak to Elio.
-Happy Hanukkah!
- Happy Hanukkah!
Bye, sweetheart.
[sighs]
They know about us.
[Oliver] I figured.
How?
[Oliver] Well, from the way
your dad spoke to me.
He made me feel
like I was a part
of the family.
Almost like a son-in-law.
You're so lucky.
My father would have
carted me off
to a correctional facility.
Elio.
[whispering]
Elio. Elio. Elio. Elio.
[Oliver whispers] Oliver.
[Oliver sighing over phone]
I remember everything.
[fire crackling]
♪ I have loved you
for the last time ♪
♪ Is it a video? ♪
♪ I have touched you
for the last time ♪
♪ Is it a video? ♪
♪ For the love, for laughter,
I flew up to your arms ♪
♪ Is it a video? ♪
♪ For the love, for laughter,
I flew up to your arms ♪
♪ Is it a video? ♪
♪ I have loved you
for the last time ♪
♪ Visions of Gideon ♪
♪ And I have kissed you
for the last time ♪
♪ Visions of Gideon ♪
♪ For the love, for laughter,
I flew up to your arms ♪
♪ Is it a video? ♪
♪ For the love, for laughter,
I flew up to your arms ♪
♪ Is it a video? ♪
♪ For the love, for laughter,
I flew up to your arms ♪
♪ Visions of Gideon ♪
[Annella] Elio.
Elio.
♪ Is it a video? ♪