( crickets chirping )
( dog barking )
( stairs creaking )
( door opening )
I can see you.
JAVIER: ...pull into
this gas station,
the guy was like,
"Yo, man,
you got problems."
Like, "What the hell
do you think
I pulled in here for?"
So your car broke down
on the way to your blood check.
Yeah, smoke,
everything.
I'm willing to give you the
benefit of the doubt, Javier,
but a judge won't.
I missed a couple
of meetings?
What's the problem?
I mean, I don't even know
what I'm doing here.
You're here because your son
has gotten into fights
every day at school,
and the last one sent
one of his classmates
to the hospital.
Juanita came here
for help voluntarily
before the court stepped in
and made it mandatory,
that's what
you're doing here.
He's on a
dangerous road.
Your history, all the violence,
all the anger,
that's his future
unless you break the cycle.
I heard you, Mrs. Lynch.
( over phone ): You're
trying to steal my boy!
No one is trying
to steal your child.
Then what are you trying...
They found bruises
and cigarette burns...
I told you,
he was playing
with some sparklers.
Mrs. Lynch, I read
the medical report.
I don't wanna talk about it
I want a lawyer.
If you feel that you need
legal representation
that's perfectly
within your rights...
I don't need your help,
in no case. You've already
interfered enough.
You... Hello?
( dial tone beeps )
How many active
cases you got?
Thirty-eight.
Okay.
Wayne, come on!
Look, I'm buried here.
I'm sorry, Em,
we all are.
(people chattering )
( sighing )
ANSWERING MACHINE: You have
three new voice messages.
Hi.
( beeping )
Hey, it's Suze, missed you
at yoga the other day,
give me a call.
Hey, Em, it's Jackie.
Just checking in,
hope you're good.
DOUG: Exhausted,
her career path
questionable,
her faith in
mankind shaken,
she resisted her tendency
toward introspection
and decides to go
have a drink with her
charming friend Doug.
(people chattering )
I am so in your head.
Be honest.
The whole psychology
thing, it's just about
scoring chicks, isn't it?
Regrettably, yes.
Mmm-hmm.
Two.
Well, what are we
gonna drink to tonight?
The never-ending
fun of a career
in public service?
Yeah.
You know,
I sit there talking
to these families,
the authority
on everything.
And I have these moments
where I think I might
be totally full of it.
Everybody's
full of it.
In the end you're
a number to call
for people who don't
have anyone else.
There's no way
that's bad.
Anyway, I've done
some soul searching
and I just want to say
that if a full-on
relationship feels like
too much right now,
I'd be willing to
consider a purely
physical one.
What?
Nothing.
What, you might actually
enjoy yourself.
Yeah, yeah,
I probably would.
( laughs )
It's just...
I know, I know,
the job,
you get home, no time
for anybody else. Whatever.
Listen, I'm giving you a month.
Okay? One month.
And then?
I don't know.
Probably give you
another month, but that is it.
Except for two more,
then, it's over.
If it were
anyone...
What are they
doing to you?
( dog barking )
( children laughing )
What?
Emily Jenkins.
Child Services?
We spoke
on the phone?
You said the 17th.
It's the 17th.
Is not.
I'm sorry,
but it is.
Monday the 17th.
The day of our
appointment.
Hi.
Come down,
I'd like to meet you.
My name's Emily.
What's yours?
Lily.
That's a pretty name.
Is there somewhere
we can talk?
So, when are you
expecting your
husband back?
Because we've found
that it's better
when the whole family
participates.
Well, he's not
here, so...
Do you have some way
of contacting him?
Not if I don't
know where he is.
( electric whirring )
EMILY: Is that...
Would you mind
asking him to
join us, please?
He doesn't have
anything to say.
Will you ask
him, please?
MARGARET: Edward.
That lady is here
from the state.
She wants to talk to you.
EDWARD: I don't have
anything to say,
tell her that!
I told her already,
she wants to anyway.
( clanging )
( whispers ):
It'll be okay.
( door opening )
( inaudible )
Hi, I'm Emily.
Okay.
I'm here because
we received a call
that Lilith
is showing serious
signs of neglect.
Now at this point
we can only assume
it's the result
of family problems.
( inaudible )
Eddie says
we don't have
family problems.
Well, many families
won't realize that
they're having problems
until it's too late.
And that's where
we come in.
We help families
communicate
and learn healthier ways
of resolving conflict.
Eddie says we don't
need your help.
Mr. Sullivan,
is there a reason
why you won't speak
to me directly?
Is there a reason why
your husband won't
speak to me directly?
( stamping foot )
Eddie doesn't like
speaking out of anger.
There's no laws
against being
weird, Em.
I didn't say weird,
I said scary.
That man sat there
staring at me
the whole time,
and the mother is
his emotional slave.
Wait, you didn't just fly
to New York and meet
with my parents, did you?
Wayne?
( sighs ): All right.
All right. Are there
any cuts, any bruises,
any signs she's
being abused?
No, not physically.
But this girl's in
trouble, I can feel it.
You wanna know
what I can feel?
The lawsuit we're
gonna get hit with
if we violate
her parents' rights
without any evidence
they've done
something wrong.
All right, Wayne.
You put these
files on my desk
and you ask me
to tell you
what's going on.
I've told you,
I've done my job,
what you do
with it is yours.
( stutters )
We're not
perfect parents,
we know that,
but we figure
if they know how
much you love them
a lot of the other stuff
takes care of itself.
She knows how
we feel about her.
So, tell me,
Mr. Sullivan,
since you've suddenly
acquired the
ability to speak,
doesn't it concern
you a little
that Lily's grades have
dropped from A's to D's
in three months?
Of course it does,
she's our daughter.
So you have no idea why
your daughter falls asleep
in class every day?
Why she can't sleep
at home? No idea?
Bad dreams maybe?
Don't tell me you're buying
this whole "daddy's
little girl" routine?
Look, they're not
my favorite people
either, okay?
But we can't
guarantee every kid
a happy childhood.
I wish we could.
Let me talk to her.
She wants to talk.
Alone.
Em, we do not
have a case.
Just five minutes, okay?
Talk to them about
how much they love kids.
( children laughing )
Hey, girls,
slow down!
I used to wish
I had a sister when
I was growing up.
To play with
and to talk to
about all those
things that you
just can't tell
anybody else,
you know?
Did you ever wish that?
That you had a sister?
( gasps )
( giggling )
( grunts )
Well, that was
a silly thing to do,
wasn't it?
What's happening
with you?
You know I can help.
Let me help you.
What is it,
sweetheart?
They hate me.
I'm sure they
don't hate you.
They do.
I hear them.
They go into the
cellar and talk.
What do they
talk about?
Sending me
to hell.
You heard
them say that?
( recorder clicks )
You can tell him.
He's on your side.
It's okay.
Lily, did you hear
your parents say they
were gonna hurt you?
( elevator dings )
I was just thinking
about you, got a nice letter
from Sandy Hutchinson.
Well, well, well.
It's sitting right in
front of me, which means
our good friend Wayne
has decided it fails
to meet the criteria
for child endangerment
and has told you in
no uncertain terms
to leave it alone.
Surprise, surprise.
I'm sorry, Emily. I can't.
Please, Mike,
I'm really
desperate here.
( typing )
Emily.
Now, you know how
dear to my heart
the work you do is,
but the department doesn't
pay me to stake out
potential child abusers.
Last time almost
cost me my job.
This little girl heard
her parents say
they're going to
send her to hell.
Sickening as that is,
you're a part of the
system that deals with
those situations, I'm not.
Mmm-hmm. But sometimes
the system doesn't work.
Well, maybe you
should just let it.
Wow. Feel like
I'm talking
to Wayne here.
All right. You don't
want to get involved,
that's fine,
but don't bullshit me,
Mike, I'm running out
of people I respect.
Okay. No bullshit.
Bring me evidence
of a crime,
I'm all over it.
Till then...
( Edward panting )
( school bell ringing )
( children chattering )
BOY: Let's go,
hurry up!
Lily! Lily!
( Emily exclaims )
Hi. I came to
tell you I hadn't
forgotten about you.
I'm doing
everything I can.
If I disappear
will you come
look for me?
You're not
going to disappear.
If I do?
( school bus honking )
I have to go.
They get mad at me
when I miss the bus.
Lily, wait. Wait.
Here. It's my
home number.
If you get scared,
I want you to
call me, okay?
I'm gonna get you out
of there, I promise.
Okay.
( phone ringing )
Hey, this is Doug,
here it comes.
( beeping )
Hey, it's me,
thought you might
be awake.
Just calling 'cause...
Well, I don't really
know why I'm calling.
Call me if you
get this, okay?
...proposal in
Morton Township
has some residents...
MAN: Here we go
golfers and shoppers...
Let's look at
the crepe batter.
In order to make
the crepe batter...
( hip-hop music playing )
( phone ringing )
Too late, I met
someone else.
LILITH: Emily.
Lily? Are you okay?
I'm scared.
Why, honey?
Why are you scared?
( crying ): They're
waiting to get me,
I can hear them.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
( sighing ):
I'm falling asleep.
Okay, listen.
Go over and open
the window.
Can you do that?
I'm sorry.
Lily? Lily?
( tires screeching )
( phone beeping )
( door creaking )
( phone ringing )
( over phone ): Yeah, Barron.
Mike, it's Emily.
That girl that I told you
about, I think she's
in a lot of trouble.
Emily, you're going...
No, I know what you said.
Mike, you're not
listening! Help me!
( screaming )
( muffled screams )
What are we
doing here, Emily?
Saving her life!
They're asleep
like we should be.
They're not asleep.
( muffled screaming ):
Did you hear that?
I didn't hear
anything.
Leave her alone!
No!
LILITH ( screaming ):
Let me out!
( grunting )
( screaming )
Did you hear that?
Police, open up!
Stop!
Break, break it down.
Break it down!
Help me. Help me.
BARRON: Police!
Lily!
( muffled screams )
God!
Oh, my God!
LILITH: No! Help me!
Please, help me.
I got you,
I got you, I got...
( grunting )
( Emily shushing )
( Barron sighing )
( Lilith sobbing )
Okay. I got you.
What the hell's
the matter
with you people?
( Lilith sobbing )
EMILY: I got you.
( shushing ):
It's okay, honey.
I got you.
It's okay.
( brething heavily )
JUDGE: The egregiousness
of the crime makes
the competency question
all the more relevant.
I hereby order the
defendants to undergo
psychiatric evaluation
to determine their
fitness for trial.
Steal a pizza,
San Quentin.
Try to kill your kid,
Freudian dream analysis.
You're gonna hate me
for saying this but
my money's on crazy.
What kind of people
put their kid
in an oven?
Bad people.
Remember that when
people were just bad?
Before everything
had a diagnosis
and a justification?
It's human nature.
What's the most
important thing
that we talked
about that you have
to remember?
It's not my fault
what happened.
That's right.
You know what?
It's not.
( whispers ): Good.
I'll see you soon.
Hey.
Hi.
That is some seriously
proactive social work
happening there.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
How's she doing?
Typical reaction.
But she blames herself.
We'll get there.
I'm gonna put her in
a group setting, see if
I can get her to open up.
Group therapy for kids,
when am I going to
get used to that?
See you later. Okay.
See you.
Hi.
Good news. They say
you can get out
of here tomorrow.
Doug said I might
have to go
to a state home.
Yeah, but it's only
temporary, till we
find you a nice family.
Why can't I
live with you?
Sweetheart, that would
never be allowed.
Why?
Well, it's complicated,
I mean, there's this
whole process,
and I'm not even
a foster parent.
So...
It'll be fine.
Hi, Barb.
Hi, Em. Right this
way, little lady.
I'll check in,
in a couple
of days, okay?
I don't want to
stay here, I want to
live with you.
Please.
I'll be good.
Lily, it's impossible,
I told you.
Will you try?
Honey, listen,
even if they said yes,
it would never work.
I work all day
and I'm hardly
ever home and...
I'm sorry,
I'm just not
mom material.
How do you know if
you've never tried?
EMILY: So, it's just
until we can find the
right family for her,
just until we can
place her in a
really good home.
You know you'd
have to give up
the case,
conflict of
interests and all.
Yeah.
Can I ask you a question?
Why are you doing this?
What Lily needs right
now is a safe,
supportive environment
with someone
she trusts.
The system can't
provide that for her,
I think that I can.
Better than anyone,
given my training.
We spend so much of
our time negotiating
red tape,
I think if we look
at this situation,
this one situation,
this one child,
it's clear what's
best for her.
How long till
Foster Services can place
her in a permanent home?
Three weeks, three months,
it's hard to predict.
( children chattering )
No more visits.
What?
They said yes.
It's your
new beginning.
Okay. It's what I
like to think of as a
glass-half-full situation.
Bathroom.
Kitchen. Fish.
And this is your room.
Be okay?
You live alone?
Just me.
Just us.
What's this?
It's chamomile.
Helps me sleep.
You know none
of this should
ever have happened.
If I could make it
go away, I would.
You did.
Here. Climb in.
Night night.
( door closing )
( gasps )
( sighs )
Okay. All right.
Here we go.
Just got to grab
some of her things.
Okay.
So, here's the key.
You're not coming?
I got 15 other
places I got to be.
So make sure you
lock it on the way
out. Okay? Bye.
( door creaks )
( door creaking )
( alarm ringing )
( sighs )
The kids at school
are saying all this
stuff like saying
my mother is a puta
and I mean, I know
we can't go back home
but I miss it.
Sometimes when
our parents aren't
getting along,
it's better if they
spend some time apart.
That's what
a restraining
order does.
She's starting
to come out
of her shell.
It's good,
but you got to
expect some hiccups.
And you can't undo
10 years of trauma
in six weeks.
School? Too soon?
No, I don't have
a problem with
her going back,
just as long as she's
comfortable with it.
I went by the house.
I think her mom
and dad were
barricading themselves
in their room at night.
How sick is that?
Well, fear and hatred
are part of the same
pathology.
LILITH: See you. Bye, Diego.
GIRL: You too, Lily.
Oh! But I forgot.
DIEGO: Bye.
LILITH: Bye.
You don't think
they're crazy.
Well, I'm coming around.
I love you.
Love you, too.
( school bell ringing )
Wayne's looking for you.
Okay.
Wayne wants to see you.
Yeah, I got it.
What's up with Diego?
Oh, hey.
Look, why don't we
go talk in my office.
No, tell me
what's going on.
Well, we don't...
We don't know why yet
but he killed both
his parents last night.
( chattering on police radio )
Excuse me... Go ahead.
BARRON: Officer,
let her through.
What happened?
Gets a tire iron
from the garage,
comes back inside,
locks all the doors
and windows,
and kills them
in their sleep.
"Slaughters" would
be a better word.
( sighs )
Oh, my God!
( gasps )
A 10-year-old did this?
There's no way.
I was there
when they
brought him in.
Took three guys
to subdue him.
And the kid was
climbing the walls.
( barking )
Man's best friend, huh?
( cell door buzzing )
( crying )
What happened?
Tell me what
happened.
I killed
my mom and dad.
Every family
you sit down with,
every day of every week,
it's a family in crisis.
Those are your odds.
Well, that's your job,
trying to beat them.
( sighing )
( sobbing )
You're one
person, Em.
You can't
save the world.
I know somebody
you did save.
Yeah.
You okay?
It's just work.
Don't worry.
I think you have
a hard job.
So do I.
People have kids
and then they decide
they don't want
to be parents.
And then the kids
grow up thinking
it's their fault.
Is that what
your parents did?
You said
you were alone.
Yeah.
I never met my dad.
And my mom...
My mom had problems.
She must have
scared you.
Why do you say that?
You don't like
to talk about it.
You're a clever
little girl.
Sweetheart.
Breakfast.
What you got?
Let me see.
You went through
my things?
I'm sorry. I wanted
to know about you.
Is that your mother?
Mmm-hmm.
What happened to her?
She died when I was
about your age.
How?
An accident.
It was raining
and she was
driving too fast.
We had an accident.
Are you mad at me?
No, I'm not
mad at you.
But I need you
not to do that
again, okay?
Go through my private
things without asking.
Okay? All right.
Omelet's getting cold.
Better hurry.
( people chattering )
You watch, six months,
their lawyer
will hire an expert
to say they're rehabbed
and they'll sue for
custody when they get out.
She's not going
back there.
I'll take her out
of the state before I
let them near her again.
Didn't hear
you say that.
You guys okay?
Mmm-hmm.
We're great.
She's sweet,
very intuitive
about everything.
You wanted to talk
about something?
We pulled the Ramirezes'
phone records.
There was a call
that night
before the murder.
From who?
The call came from
your house, Emily.
What?
I'm not accusing
you of anything,
I just want to
know what was said.
But that's impossible.
I mean, I might have called
them the week before
or something, but I...
I'm talking to you
as a friend, you
know that, right?
Mike, did you
not hear me?
As a friend, I'm telling
you that I didn't
call that family.
He's in my group.
Why, did
something happen?
We're trying to
figure out why.
Diego got a call
from here, last
Thursday night.
I'm just wondering
if he might
have said something.
That wasn't me.
You didn't call him?
Lily, it's difficult
sometimes to tell
the truth,
but I know you will
because you're
a good kid.
I am telling the truth.
My backup files
are in the cabinet.
Diego's is in there.
Maybe you got curious
and went through some,
dialed a number?
It wasn't me,
I swear.
The call came at 2:00 a.m.
You ever up that late?
I didn't call him.
Mike, she said no.
Maybe somebody
made a mistake.
Yeah, maybe so.
Why would Diego do this?
He loved his mom and dad.
You never want to
think anyone you know
is capable of
that kind of thing.
In your mind, it's always
some nameless,
faceless creature.
Sometimes, the city
seems full of them.
But they're just people,
like you and me.
She's lying.
( gasps )
Do you believe me?
I believe you.
I need to ask you
something about the
night it happened.
Did you get a call?
Really late?
You didn't.
Diego, I know
that you did.
The call came
from my house.
( gasping )
What's the matter?
( choking )
What's scaring you?
Diego.
It's okay,
it's all right.
Deep breaths,
deep breaths,
you'll be all right.
Can we get some
help in here, please?
( beeping, door closing )
Who called you?
Was it Lily?
Did she say
something to you?
Something
that scared you?
El dijo.
"El dijo"?
What do you mean,
"He said"?
Era un hombre.
It was a man?
( chair squeaking )
Do you
like working here?
Well, photocopying
isn't much fun.
What?
Knock, knock.
Sorry I'm late, guys.
You ready to go, kiddo?
So, how's school?
Fine.
Any of your classmates
giving you a hard time?
No, they've been nice.
You sleeping okay?
That's not really what
you want to talk about,
is it, Doug?
You got me.
Question 16, am I
afraid of the dark?
You answered no.
Question 23, am I
afraid of being alone?
You answered no.
26, am I afraid
of my parents? No.
You answered no
to everything
in that section.
I think that some of those
should have been yeses.
Everybody is
scared of something.
Working through our fears,
conquering them,
is how we get better.
So, I want you
to tell me,
what scares you?
I'll tell you what
scares me if you tell
me what scares you.
( laughs ):
Fair enough.
When I was a kid,
I was climbing a tree,
and I accidentally put
my hand through a giant
hornets' nest.
And they didn't
like it. I was stung
over a hundred times.
They had to rush
me to the hospital.
Been afraid of
hornets ever since.
I don't climb
many trees either.
Everybody has fears.
Now, what scares you?
Me.
You scare yourself?
Sometimes.
Why? What about
yourself scares you?
I have bad thoughts.
About what?
People.
People in general
or certain people?
Certain people.
Like who?
You.
You have bad
thoughts about me?
Why?
( scoffing ): I just do.
Did I do something
or say something
that upset you?
It's just the
way you are.
How am I?
Facile.
Facile?
( laughs )
Do you even know
what that means?
Easily comprehended.
Often lacking
sincerity or depth.
You're smug, too.
Want me to tell
you what that means?
If I seemed smug
or facile I want to...
( laughs ):
Don't apologize.
Why not?
You're a grown-up.
It's embarrassing.
Number 12, I worry
about what's going
to happen.
Yes or no?
You want me
to answer that?
Yes or no?
No.
That should be a yes.
Should we talk
about school now?
My grades are
getting a lot better.
I talked to a lot of kids,
I don't think I've ever
felt like that before.
Like what?
( sighs ): Threatened.
( elevator dings )
I know a specialist,
I'm gonna call
him in the morning.
( chair squeaking )
Are you mad at me?
No. No,
I'm just tired.
Want me to
brush your hair?
No, thanks.
Are you sure?
Some other time.
It will make you
feel better.
I'll get the brush.
I said no,
thank you.
Doug said something,
didn't he?
Doug? No. Doug says
you're doing great.
What did he tell you?
Nothing.
( phone ringing )
Hello.
( static over phone )
Try again, sorry.
( phone ringing )
( hornet buzzing )
( exclaims in pain )
( buzzing )
( flushing )
( water running )
( sighs )
( buzzing )
( shouts )
( grunting )
( panting )
( buzzing )
(screaming )
( hornets buzzing )
( screaming )
( grunting )
( panting )
( flushing )
( hornets buzzing )
( panting )
( high-pitched buzzing )
( screaming )
( bone snapping )
PRIEST: For as much
as it hath pleased
Almighty God,
of his great mercy,
to take unto
himself the soul
of our dear brother,
here departed,
we, therefore,
commit his body
to the ground.
Earth to earth,
ashes to ashes
and dust to dust,
in sure and certain
hope of the resurrection
to eternal life,
through our Lord,
Jesus Christ, amen.
( Emily crying )
You think it's my
fault, don't you?
It's no one's fault.
It was an accident.
BARRON: There was
no sign of forced entry,
he was alone
and the doors
were locked.
I know he didn't
kill himself.
He was scared.
He came out of that
room with her, Mike,
and he was scared.
He said she
threatened him.
Emily, you're in shock,
let's not get carried away.
Diego, he said it was
a man on the phone.
There was no one
else in the house.
Do you think I don't know
how crazy this sounds?
Kid in that state of mind
is not the most
reliable witness.
But why was he in
that state of mind?
Why was Doug?
Pull my phone records.
See if she called him.
I already did, Emily.
There was no call.
So, you're saying that
you've seen this before,
someone just
dying like that?
Truly?
I'm shocked
every day by the violence
people do to themselves.
Her mom and dad had
deadbolts on their
bedroom door, big ones.
Something came
through that door,
and whatever it was,
they didn't want it
ever coming through
there again.
Hey guys, come on,
are you ready?
Yeah.
WOMAN: Let's get to it?
MAN: Yeah.
( elevator bell dings )
MALE INTERVIEWER: Take me
through the conversation,
Margaret, about the oven.
Eddie said,
"We're gonna burn her,"
and I said, "Okay."
So it was
Edward's idea?
Just the oven part,
we both wanted her dead.
Why did you say that it
was God's will that you
should kill your daughter?
( chuckles )
Why is that funny,
Margaret?
'Cause she's
not my daughter.
You think your
daughter is the devil?
Evil incarnate?
I don't care
what you call it.
But you have stated
that she kills people?
Not by her own hand,
they just die.
I had two brothers,
Eddie had
three sisters.
( crying): Soon as
she was born, they
just started dying.
Me and Eddie, I guess,
she couldn't get rid
of us until she found
somebody else.
MAN: The nurse on duty
heard screaming,
found Mrs. Sullivan
on the floor clawing
at her own skin,
absolutely convinced
she was on fire.
( Margaret gasping )
( crying )
In no condition
for visitors
as you can see.
If you'd like,
I can let you
see Mr. Sullivan.
Okay.
( gasps )
I know I'm probably
the last person you
want to see right now,
but you're the only
one that I can talk to.
Who died?
A friend.
You're scared.
You ought to be.
Is she...
What is she?
I can tell you
what she's not.
She's not a daughter of mine.
She's not a 10-year-old
having trouble in school.
And she's not some
innocent victim whose
door you busted down
and life you saved.
She's not going
anywhere soon, lady.
Not till she's good
and done with you.
Done with me how?
However she wants.
You think it's an accident
her ending up with you?
She saw you
coming a mile away.
Why me? I don't
have anything.
You have that
you're good.
Kindness. Decency.
That's what
she feeds on.
Bleeds you dry,
moves on to the next.
We were a big family,
she went through us
like a wrecking ball.
It's like she
sees everything.
And what she
doesn't see,
she senses.
Like when you call
a friend and they pick
it up before it rings?
( chuckles ):
They say
when you're born
you're given
your eternal soul.
The part of you that
lives on, lives again.
Whatever evil she is,
didn't come from us.
It was already there.
From the moment she
came into being, she brought
something with her.
Something older,
destructive.
Soul of a demon.
What does she want?
To know what your
idea of hell is
and make you
live there.
( lock clicking )
( school bus stopping )
( door opening )
Hi.
You weren't there
so I took the bus.
Sorry, work,
I lost track of time.
It's okay,
I know how busy you are.
Doesn't matter anyway,
the bus stops right at
the end of the street.
So I can always get home,
whether you're there or not.
Lucky.
Where's the phone?
It wasn't working, so...
Wow. That one, too.
We had gym today.
I'm gonna have a shower.
Are they being
nice to her?
Who?
My mother.
How would I know that?
I thought you said
you were going to see her.
I never said that.
Hmm.
I must have dreamt it.
EMILY: Nancy.
Emily.
I'm so sorry about Doug.
I know you two were close.
Do you have a minute?
I was just wondering
if you've had any luck
finding a place for Lilith?
Still looking.
You know, more kids
than homes right now.
So, how long
you think we're
talking here? Like...
Honestly,
she's not my
first priority.
She's in a safe environment
with someone who
understands her needs.
Nancy,
if there's anything that
you could do to expedite
the process...
Are you serious?
Emily, you petitioned
for custody, you got it.
She's your
responsibility.
Make it work.
How?
How do I make it work
if it's not working?
With the same coping
skills you teach these
moms and dads every week!
Walk the talk, Emily!
Walk the talk!
( therapist speaking
indistinctly )
See you next time.
Good work.
( children chattering )
( inaudible )
GIRL: Why is she hurting...
Hey, wait a minute.
Who do you think you are,
barging in there like that?
It's okay, Diane,
Emily's been under
a lot of stress lately,
but she's really nice
to me and I hope I can
stay with her a long time.
Don't ever do that again.
LILITH: See you
next week, Diane.
Don't worry,
it was all a
misunderstanding.
You're not
going back there.
Why, Emily?
Why, Emily? Why, Emily?
( shouting ): Why, Emily?
( elevator stopping )
Why, Emily?
Can I go back to
group next week?
You're never
going back there!
Are you sure?
( elevator cables creaking )
No. No.
( screams )
( alarm beeping )
( screaming )
( elevator bell dinging )
WOMAN 1: I know.
WOMAN 2: You were
terrific back there.
MAN: Really enjoyed
the service, Father.
PRIEST: Thanks.
Mike.
Emily.
They are not crazy,
Mike. Her parents.
They're right about her.
You want to wind up
where they are?
Keep talking like this.
Emily, you're
grieving for Doug
and you're still
confused about
what Diego did.
Aren't you?
Diego grew up
in a bad home,
he saw violence,
he repeated it,
that's the cycle.
You know that
better than anyone.
Why did she lie
about calling him?
Because she's a liar,
but that doesn't mean
she made him do it.
Let me tell you
what Lily is.
She's a damaged child,
she's a deceitful child,
she's a manipulative child.
But a damaged,
deceitful, manipulative
child is not a demon.
You think I'm crazy.
You believe in there.
But out here it's
all just bullshit?
Mike, you know
I'm not crazy.
Don't run away from this
just because it scares you.
I'll tell you what is
scaring me is not
recognizing my friend.
Get some help. Seriously.
Mike...
I don't want to
report you.
( clock ticking )
Good night.
( dialing )
( phone ringing )
Mrs. Lynch,
I told you that...
( over phone ): Do you think
I'm an idiot? Do you think
I'm just making this up?
That's not what you said.
I'm not stupid.
Yeah, no.
You never said anything
about unsupervised visits.
No, that is not
what I said.
You said if my husband
got help, then my son
could come home.
I did not. No.
Nothing between
the lines there.
You never said that...
Who do you think you are
telling me
how to raise my son?
Mrs. Lynch...
You know nothing about me.
You know nothing about my son.
Will you please
let me respond?
How I raise my child is
none of your business.
Would you let...
Would you...
How my son and
his father relate...
( shouting ): Shut the
fuck up, you miserable,
miserable woman
before I come and
beat your ass like
you beat your son!
I have your address!
Think about that
before you call
and swear at me!
Okay, so, you're certainly
in no state of mind to
be here right now.
Come on, it's late,
you look like shit,
go home.
I don't want to go home.
( cell phone ringing )
Hello?
( static over phone )
It's for you.
Emily Jenkins.
LILITH: You shouldn't
leave me home alone,
Emily.
Wayne?
( chair squeaking )
( breathing heavily )
( exhaling )
There you are.
I made supper.
Don't ignore me.
My mother used to
ignore me.
( bolting door )
( thunder rumbling )
( knocking on door )
Emily? Can I come in?
I'm scared.
( knocking continues )
( thuder clapping )
Emily? Please?
I know you're in there.
( banging door )
Please, Emily?
( foosteps retreating )
( banging, gasping )
LILITH ( shrieking ):
Let me in, let me in.
Let me in, let me in,
let me in, let me in,
let me in,
let me in, let me in.
( screaming ):
Leave me alone.
( rattling )
( screeching )
( Emily screaming )
( yelps )
Please, help me.
( banging on door )
Please! No, please
open the door?
( screaming ):
Open the door,
she's coming!
Drive.
There's nobody out there.
Drive!
There is nobody
out there. Look.
There's
nobody out there.
( engine starting )
( door opening )
( panting )
( softly ): It's okay.
( screams ):
Leaving the child unattended
is a jailable offense.
You have to do
what I say.
If I say I want
to go to group,
you have to do it.
If I say I want
a new dress,
you have to do it.
If I say I want
ice cream every day,
after school,
( crying ):
you have to do it,
okay?
Don't be sad.
This is your
new beginning.
Emily.
I tried to call you.
Good news, we found
a home for Lily.
Family in Cloverfield.
Really good people.
They're picking
her up Friday,
after school.
What's the matter?
They're perfect.
EMILY: If they take her...
The whole thing
starts all over again.
You can't let her go,
you can't let her stay.
Leaves you one option.
I can't.
You have to.
You don't understand.
Don't tell me I
don't understand.
You've had her,
what, two months?
I had her 10 years.
We had her 10 years.
Think of it as
a test of faith.
I don't wanna
have any faith.
How about anger?
You got some of that?
How? How do I...
Kill her?
In her sleep.
That's the only time
you got the upper hand,
is when she's sleeping,
but she almost never does.
We checked on her room,
every night
for three months.
First night she slept
was the night that you
busted in our front door.
And I'll tell you
what I'd do different,
count yourself
dead at the outset.
Accept that going in,
use it to your advantage.
If you're not afraid,
she can't hurt you.
( sighs )
EDWARD ON TV: No money,
no way to contact her.
Must have went 80
on the way back,
straight through,
didn't stop for nothing.
When we got home,
she was waiting for
us on the doorstep.
Where is she now?
Some family, somewhere?
MARGARET ON TV: Eddie said,
"We're gonna burn her,"
and I said, "Okay."
They did what I
said for a while,
but then they stopped
and started
with the secrets.
But they weren't
really secrets,
I guess,
because I always knew
what they were thinking.
Don't leave me.
It's okay, Maggie.
I'll check on you later.
( door clicking )
( Lilith screaming )
( gasping )
( crying )
( screaming )
( men chattering )
( in Lilith's voice ):
I'm glad you're getting
the help you need, Daddy.
( screams )
( screaming )
( grunting )
MAN: Get somebody
down here now.
Somebody call it in.
Base, this is Sanchez.
We're gonna need
medical personnel right
away to the cafeteria...
Edward Sullivan...
I know.
Something
I want you to hear.
This came in this morning,
right about 2:00 a.m.
You might wanna sit.
( beeps )
LILITH: ( in deep voice ):
...decide what to do with
you and your family, Michael.
( static buzzing )
Every time I think
about it, a voice in my
head says, "Kill them."
DOUG: Who is this?
LILITH: ( in deep voice )
Just a little girl.
Up past her bedtime.
Lilith?
( Lilith giggling )
You were right.
She did call Doug.
She used your cell phone.
Took me a couple of
extra days to check
your cell phone records,
but that's what
she's been using.
She's tearing
me apart.
You're not crazy,
Emily. This is real.
Edward said
I have to kill her.
I'll help you.
Keep her at the house.
DOCTOR:
Physically you're fine.
How's the stress?
I'm not sleeping.
I was hoping
you could give
me something.
Take one of these,
you'll sleep.
Lily?
( dog growling )
What?
Oh, my God.
( growling continues )
( growling )
( loud buzzing )
( gun cocking )
( growling )
( gunshot )
( loud buzzing )
( cell phone buzzing )
( static over phone )
Who is this?
Emily, it's Wayne,
I just got a call,
Mike's dead.
No, he's...
Listen, Em.
They think
he shot himself.
Emily? Em?
( crying ): No...
Emily?
Emily, are you okay?
( hip-hop song playing on TV )
( crashing )
Get out of my house!
( in deep voice ):
Don't yell at me!
( panting )
LILITH: Emily,
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Can I come in
so we can talk
and work it out?
Emily?
Stay away from me!
Don't be mad. I said
I was sorry. I'll brush
your hair for you.
Stay away from me!
( banging )
( screaming ):
No! No. No.
( gasps )
( screams )
LILITH: ( in deep voice ):
Emily. Emily.
We need to learn
healthier ways of
resolving conflict, Emily.
Most families
don't even know
they have a problem
until it's too late.
( grunts in male voice )
( chuckling )
What are you doing,
you silly pumpkinhead?
( chuckling nervously )
You don't want me
to come under there
and get you, do you?
( crying ): No.
I'm going to count to three.
One, two...
No.
Two and a half,
two and three quarters,
three. Here I come.
No! What do you want?
What you wanted
from your mother.
I want you to love me.
Okay. I will.
Come tuck me in.
( crying ): Oh, my God.
( kettle whistling )
LILITH: Emily.
Chamomile.
Maybe you should have it,
you look stressed.
I'll have one later.
I'm really sorry
that I let things
get like this.
We'll do better
from now on.
We have to.
Someone could get hurt.
What should
we do tomorrow?
Surprise me.
I'm not so good
at surprises.
You're getting better.
( glass shattering )
( sirens wailing )
( distorted ):
Everybody get out okay?
( Lilith chuckling )
Ma'am, anyone
else inside?
Yes or no?
That was mean.
You follow us downtown,
we'll find someplace
for you to stay.
Miss?
You okay?
I'm fine.
Maybe we can
find a hotel with
a swimming pool.
( tires screeching )
Where are we going?
You said
I should surprise you.
She hated herself.
And she hated you.
They said it was
an accident, but
you knew it wasn't.
Your mother.
That's why
you never had any
kids of your own.
That's what you're
afraid of, isn't it?
The part of you
that's her.
What are you?
Slow down!
What the hell are you?
You're upset,
you shouldn't
be driving.
( horns honking )
YOUNG EMILY: Mom.
( gasping )
Mom, slow down.
You're scaring me.
Mom!
Slow down, please!
Look out!
It's not real.
Yes, it is!
It's not real!
( laughing )
( panting )
Are you scared?
I'm not.
( gasps )
( grunts )
( distorted ):
I'm not afraid.
( screaming )
( Lilith screaming )
Just die!
( screaming ): No! No!
No!
( gasping )
( panting )
( sirens wailing )
( "Army of Angels" playing )