- Previously on "Chucky"...
- I'm sick.
[knock at door]
- Rachel Fairchild,
you're under arrest.
- It all comes back
to Andy Barclay.
- Well, you think he'll know
how to find Chucky?
I wanna be Jennifer Tilly.
I wanna be a star.
Hello, Nica.
I stabbed you in the thigh
ten minutes ago.
You didn't feel a thing.
[screams]
Andy Barclay?
- You know about Chucky
and you're still alive--
makes you one of the lucky few.
How do we find him?
He'll find you.
- [screams]
- I'll let you go
on one condition.
What?
Kill Jake.
- Charles Lee Ray,
he was one of us.
Growing up right over
on Sherwood Lane.
Welcome home.
[screams]
- Mom?
- [screams]
- [evil laughter]
[suspenseful music]
[evil laughter]
♪
Mom!
[eerie music]
♪
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Logan, I'm so sorry.
Bree's passing is
a tremendous loss
we will all feel
for a very long time.
- If there's anything
you need...
Yeah.
[somber music]
Hi, good to see you.
♪
- I can't imagine
what they're going through.
- Yeah, well, imagine it
on your own time, Nathan.
I've got a hard out at 3:00.
- Mom!
- Michelle.
What?
I've expressed my condolences.
What more can I do?
I have a meeting downtown.
I'm sorry.
♪
Thanks.
Hey.
I'm so sorry, Devon.
- So you're staying
with your aunt?
Uh, yeah.
- Maybe me and Lexy
can come over later
and figure out what to do next.
♪
What?
I'm on lockdown.
My parents think it was
another accident,
but I was here,
so they also think I'm Satan.
I think everyone does.
- I found out why my mom showed
up that night.
Someone called her.
Said I was in trouble.
Told her I was here.
It was Chucky.
He wanted me to see her die.
- He did the same thing
to Junior.
To me too.
Why is Chucky killing
our parents?
And why is he rubbing it
in our faces?
'Cause he's a dick.
What should we do?
Nothing.
- He's not gonna stop coming
for us just 'cause we gave up.
So we try to survive.
I mean, if we split up,
at least he has more ground
to cover.
Devon, we can still do this.
- We just--
- No, Jake.
We're not good together.
Maybe he's right.
Maybe we should just go home
for now.
I need to be there
for my family in case Chucky--
Jake, you happy now?
[ominous music]
Junior.
You happy?
You ruined everything.
Everyone around you dies.
My mom, Devon's mom,
even your own parents!
You're a fucking curse.
Junior, stop!
- This is none
of your business.
- Look, I'm sorry about
your mom.
This is not Jake's fault.
Oh!
Junior!
♪
You can all go to hell.
Get inside.
You okay?
[engine roaring]
[eerie music]
♪
Hello, Logan.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
♪
[hums]
[laughs]
[playful spooky music]
♪
Home sweet home.
Hm.
It's just darling.
[giggles]
- Not bad
for our first rattrap, huh?
- Nothing a few throw rugs
can't fix.
- [laughs]
- Maybe some wallpaper.
We could get a plant.
Hey, uh, Tiff,
I'm feeling kinda hungry.
Wanna order a pizza?
I think that's a great idea.
[both laughing]
[upbeat electronic music]
♪
You like it?
- Deep dish is good,
but I miss Jersey pizza.
- I don't know, I kinda
like the mess it makes.
[laughs]
Mm.
- [sirens wailing]
- ♪ The blacker it gets
♪ The lower we go
♪ A lonely mess is
the best of it all ♪
[laughs]
♪
- We should stop
at the next gas station.
- Yeah, it's my turn to drive
anyway.
I got it.
- You've been driving
for, like, six hours.
I'm good.
What?
- You're scared
to let me drive.
No.
I'm not that bad.
Come on!
- It's not your fault
you're a bad driver.
You've had a lot
to be worried about.
I'm not a bad driver.
There's a gas station.
Let's make it fast though,
all right?
We don't know who's looking
for us.
[New Bum's
"The Killers and Me"]
[unsettling guitar music]
- ♪ There we were sitting
in a circle ♪
♪ The killers and me
♪ Dressed for Halloween,
Catholic girls ♪
♪ Circa 2143
♪ I'd have hit the road
long before ♪
♪ But Elsa took my keys
♪ So I laid down and listened
to the wind in the trees ♪
I said no cigarettes.
- I'm gonna need them
if you're driving.
- Those things are
gonna kill you.
Seriously?
You're worried about this?
- Really?
- All right.
Look what I got us.
Oh.
Nice, thank you.
- You're welcome.
- ♪ I tried to paint
♪ As usual Elsa posed
♪ Laying in drag
on my sleeping bag ♪
♪ Bitching about her nose
♪ I felt I was in too deep
♪ And in need of repose
♪ Fell asleep in Elsa's arms
♪ And woke up in my clothes
♪
It's locked. Open it up.
Ha ha, very funny.
Open the door.
Open the fucking door!
Come on, Andy!
Andy!
[sighs]
Shit.
♪
Hey!
- Oh, oh, no, I'm just--
I'm just taking it
for a little while.
No, Caroline, stop it!
No, no!
Caroline, as your sister,
I'm doing this
for your own good!
[gasps]
[laughing]
[both laughing]
[unsettling music]
♪
[sirens wailing]
[knock at door]
Hey.
I'm sorry, your aunt said
that you were down here, so.
- I thought we said
we weren't gonna--
I'm not here about Chucky.
I'm here for you.
I'm worried about you.
- You don't have
to worry about me.
I'm not gonna be around
much longer.
What do you mean?
- I'm only staying
with my aunt for, like, a week.
She can't take care
of me forever.
Where you gonna go?
- I don't know, where all kids
with no parents go.
Some foster home.
I don't know if I'll stay
in Jersey.
- I'm sure there's
some place that you could stay.
You know,
maybe I can ask my uncle,
maybe Lexy or--
Jake...
I'm scared.
I was thinking.
Maybe I should just leave,
you know?
On my own.
Maybe then I'd get
to decide where I go.
You know...
I've thought about
running away.
Yeah?
- Lots of times
after my mom died.
[somber music]
What stopped you?
You.
I stayed because I didn't like
the idea of not seeing you
every day.
Don't, Jake.
Just...
Being around you hurts.
All I can think about
when I see you
is what she looked like,
lying there.
♪
Oh.
Um, maybe I can come back
another time or...?
No.
I'm sorry.
Uh...
It's okay, I'll go.
♪
You okay, Dad?
- Shouldn't hit your cousin
like that.
Coaches find out
you're a hothead,
they'll kick your ass
to the curb.
Dad, who was that woman?
What?
[unsettling music]
The one at the wake.
She kissed you.
- I don't know, maybe she was
a friend of your mother's.
♪
Going out for a bit.
[foreboding music]
♪
- Our police department has
a suspect in custody now
whom we believe is
the individual responsible
for the murders
of Oliver Hayden,
Megan McVey,
and Detective Sean Peyton.
[crowd shouting]
I can't go into further
detail at this time.
But I can assure you
that justice will be swift,
and it will be served.
- Madame Mayor?
- Yes?
- Last week the lead detective
on the cases
you just mentioned,
Kim Evans, died tragically
in a supposedly
accidental fall.
This is on the heels of several
other "freak accidents"
that have been in the news
over the last month or so.
Do you think these have
anything to do with the murders
you've just mentioned,
and it is possible
you've arrested
an innocent woman?
James.
This is a good--no,
great day for Hackensack.
We need to focus on the future.
Our only task now is to put
this whole ugly affair
behind us and to start healing
as a community.
And what better way to do that
than with an event
that will not only bring
our beloved city together,
but will also
do tremendous good.
So our charity matinée
of the universal classic...
"Frankenstein" will still take
place tomorrow as planned!
A fun-filled afternoon
of G-rated horror
for the whole family,
the proceeds of which will go
directly to...
[eerie music]
Better Days
Children's Hospitals
all over the country.
Oh, we only have
a few tickets left,
so I encourage everyone
to get yours now.
And, as an added treat,
a very special celebrity guest
will be joining us tomorrow
to host an auction prior
to the screening.
So get those tickets
and support Better Days!
- Well then, Madame Mayor,
since this is obviously such
a big deal for Hackensack,
where the hack is
the First Husband?
Oh, I'm so glad you asked.
He's at home.
It's laundry day.
But he will be at the benefit
tomorrow.
Next question?
[reporters clamoring]
- Caroline, do you wanna be
mayor one day,
just like your mommy?
[chuckles]
- He asked you a question,
Caroline.
Chucky told me to kill Mommy.
- Uh--
- Who is Chucky?
- Um, thank you--
- I'm sorry. Kids...
So much for coming.
Thank you all.
- What did Chucky tell you
exactly?
Kill them all.
Mommy, Daddy, and you.
♪
[engine roaring]
[unsettling music]
♪
Sperm donor of the year.
- Mom always said
he was trying his best.
- And look what happened
to her.
Kid, the guy's an asshole.
I always knew he was, I just
never said anything.
Now it's too late.
It's never too late.
My mom's dead.
Your dad can be too.
♪
- He kissed some lady
at the wake.
My mom's wake.
What?
That's so disrespectful.
Makes you wanna just...
Just...
Go on, go on.
♪
- I don't know,
maybe I'm just losing it.
You're fine, Junior.
You got me.
You know that, don't you?
Like I said before,
some people just deserve
to die.
Dads, ex-girlfriends,
cousins.
Everything was fine
till Jake moved in.
Your mom was fine.
♪
- I don't know if I can do it,
Chucky.
Jake said the same thing.
But you're better than him,
aren't you, Junior?
Prove it.
♪
You got guts, kid.
[dark electronic music]
♪
- ♪ Grit your teeth,
hands clenched ♪
♪
♪ Fever forms to the ends
[indistinct conversation]
[laughs]
♪ Tool of the hatred
♪ Lost by sunrise
♪ Pray for it to end
♪
♪ I'm cutting you down
♪ We're cutting you down
♪
♪ And there won't be a sound
♪ We'll cut you down
♪
♪ And there won't be a sound
♪ You've got the fear
in the number ♪
♪ The fire in the color
♪ Take what you can't win
♪
♪ We'll cut you down
♪ Cut you down
♪
♪ There won't be a sound
Here in Hackensack,
the mayor likes to say
the saints are always watching
over us.
Guiding our destinies
and keeping us from harm.
And if I'm being
totally honest,
I have to admit,
this town was a pretty decent
place to grow up in,
and I really did have a saint
watching over me.
My mom.
So to my very favorite
detective out there,
if you're listening,
I just wanna say,
no matter how hard life gets,
your mom still sees you.
And so do I.
[somber music]
Chucky, I'm home!
Making your favorite,
Swedish meatballs.
- [grunting]
- [screams]
- Chucky?
- [shouting]
[screaming]
[grunting]
[laughs]
[screams]
[suspenseful music]
How could you?
It was easy.
You're killing without me?
Believe it or not, Tiff,
I got a life outside of you
and this dump.
But killing is an "us thing."
- Nag, nag, nag,
nag, nag, Tiff.
- When was the last time
that you took me out
for a nice dinner and a murder?
♪
We never kill anybody together
anymore.
[sighs]
- Where the hell do you think
you're going?
I'm going out.
Don't wait up for me, Red, huh?
♪
[car horn honking]
Hello?
Oh.
Hellooo.
Is it Junior?
Hi, Junior.
You don't know me yet,
but I wanted
to bring you something
to help you through
this difficult time.
[unsettling music]
It's Swedish meatballs!
Your father's favorite.
I know you.
[giggles]
Aren't you a little young
to have seen "Bound"?
- No, you were the--
the lady at my mom's funeral.
Oh.
There...
There.
Don't worry.
It's gonna get a lot better,
I promise.
Is Jake home?
You know,
he's been through this before.
He knows how important it is
to have a woman in the house
to take care of you.
You mustn't ever
let circumstance
take that away from you.
- What were you doing there
with my dad?
[gasps]
Oh, my God, he didn't tell you?
Oh, no, no,
I've said too much already.
I...
Don't tell anybody,
okay, Junior?
It'll be our little secret,
okay?
♪
[whispering]
I was never here.
[giggling]
[foreboding music]
♪
- [phone chirps]
- You've arrived
at your destination.
♪
Oh!
Who is that?
Hello?
Hello? Help me!
Help me, please!
♪
[indistinct PA announcement
plays]
[ominous music]
♪
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, excuse me.
Hey!
What the hell, kid?
What're you doing with that?
The doll!
Fucking Jersey, man.
Hey, look, I need that doll.
[sighs]
Listen, I don't give a shit
what you need, okay?
Someone paid for this doll,
and I'm kinda late
delivering it,
which is gonna piss
my boss off.
I'll pay you.
More. Look, how much?
350 bucks.
Okay.
Plus a tip.
both:
Okay.
Wait, where you taking that?
I can't tell you that.
987 Sherwood Lane.
♪
Talk to me.
Talk to me!
Hi, I'm Billy.
Wanna play?
[sinister music]
♪
I'm in here!
[eerie music]
Is anybody there?
♪
[panting]
Hello?
Who is that?
[gasps]
Could you please help me?
What happened?
- Please, I think she's gonna
come back soon!
Please, please,
please untie me!
Hurry!
She's gonna be back,
please hurry!
- She?
- Yeah, she's crazy!
Please hurry! Please hurry!
[sobs]
[grunting]
[laughs]
- Let's get you some water.
- [laughs]
My name's Devon, by the way.
What's yours?
♪
Oh, it depends.
Right now,
it's Chucky.
[taser beeping]
[taser crackling]
[cackles]
♪
[door clicks open]
[door slams]
[sighs]
What the fuck is that?
I thought we said we were done.
We were. Chucky wasn't.
- Why the hell
did you bring him here?
Don't worry.
He's cool.
You going somewhere?
Not anymore.
You were?
Do you know how selfish
that is?
Leaving your family behind
like we wouldn't notice?
What family?
Me.
Devon. The family you chose.
Do you think we wouldn't care?
I thought it'd be better.
Why?
- Everything bad
that's happened
happened because of me.
I thought that maybe
it would stop
if I wasn't around anymore.
[somber music]
- I shouldn't have ditched you
like that yesterday.
♪
So where's your real family?
Checked into the Plaza.
Think they're trying
to save their marriage.
Um, anyway,
where did this come from?
- Um, I ran into some guy
at the bus station
on his way to deliver it.
- Okay, did you get the address
for delivery?
Please tell me you brought it.
It's 987 Sherwood Lane.
Okay.
God, did Chucky murder
the Wi-Fi too?
Have you talked to Devon?
Um, no.
I don't think he wants to talk
to me anymore.
Or see me.
Ever.
- Well, we should grab him
before we do whatever this is.
You two can work out your
relationship problems later.
But he's not home.
Look at his Snap story
he posted.
He's on a walk or something.
Lemme check.
♪
- Why is some random guy
delivering a Good Guy doll
to Charles Lee Ray's old house?
[phone chimes]
♪
I found Devon.
He's there.
What?
- Devon's at Charles Lee Ray's
house.
[crickets chirping]
[sinister music]
♪
- [cackles]
I can hear him.
He's coming.
I think he's drunk.
[cackles]
This is gonna be great.
Gonna be great.
Okay.
I'll just follow your lead.
♪
Junior.
We need to talk.
What are you doing
with that thing?
♪
Hi.
I'm Chucky.
And I'm your friend
till the end.
Hidey-ho!
Ha ha ha.
Look, uh,
hey, um...
I don't know why your mom did
what she did.
But I do know she loved you.
I like to be hugged.
- How do I turn
this thing off?
- Hidey-ho! Ha ha ha.
What's wrong with you?
Junior, I asked you a question.
You sure drink a lot.
Just like Uncle Lucas.
Just like your brother.
Knock it off.
Logan, Lucas.
Lucas, Logan.
They sound the same to me.
Logan and Lucas,
the loser twins!
Stop it!
- Stop it!
- Glug, glug, glug.
Get your fucking hands off me.
♪
What'd you say to me?
You heard me, Dad.
How you doing that?
- [laughs]
Tell you in a minute.
But now that I've got
your attention, Dad,
let's talk about
that bitch at the funeral.
What are you talking about?
Cancer wasn't enough, huh?
You had to cheat on her too.
Real classy, Dad.
Don't, Junior.
I would never do anything
like that.
You know I wouldn't.
No wonder she jumped.
Shut your goddamn mouth.
Give me that!
[groans]
Look at you.
You can't even talk to me
like a man.
If your mom saw you,
she'd be ashamed.
She killed herself.
Because of you.
No, no, no, no, no.
She killed herself
'cause she's a quitter.
Just like you.
- [screams]
- [grunts]
Oh!
[groaning]
♪
[thunder booms]
Whoa!
Whee.
[gurgling]
[suspenseful music]
Where's the Uber?
Four minutes.
Shit.
♪
Jake.
I found out something today.
About Chucky.
What?
♪
- He tried to get my sister
to kill too.
First me, then you.
Now Caroline?
And why is Chucky
murder-whispering everyone?
It doesn't make any sense.
- He doesn't exactly need help
killing people.
No, he doesn't.
So why bother?
What's he getting out of it?
I don't know.
[spooky upbeat music]
♪
Kid, thank you!
Finally!
You have no idea
how hard it's been
getting one of you little shits
to step the fuck up and play.
- ♪ See the people walking
down the street ♪
♪ Fall in line,
just watching all their feet ♪
♪ They don't know
where they want to go ♪
♪ But they're walking in time
- [singing along]
♪ 'Cause we got the beat
♪ We got the beat,
we got the beat ♪
♪ Yeah!
♪ We got the beat
[The Go-Go's
"We Got the Beat"]
♪ We got the beat
♪
♪ Everybody,
get on your feet ♪
♪ We got the beat
♪ We know you can dance
to the beat ♪
♪ We got the beat
♪ Jumpin'
♪ Get down, we got the beat
♪ Round and round and round
♪ We got the beat
♪ We got the beat,
we got the beat ♪
♪
♪ We got the beat,
we got the beat ♪
♪
♪ We got the beat
[tires squealing]
Way to go, playa.
Now, thanks to you,
the real fun can start.
♪
[doorbell rings]
- ♪ We got the beat,
we got the beat ♪
♪ We got the beat,
[playful spooky music]
♪