- Previously on "Chucky"...
- Hey, Dad, check it out.
- Hi, I'm Chucky.
- Andy Warhol once said
just because something's
been thrown away
doesn't make it garbage.
- Wasn't Warhol gay too?
- What is going on?
- Lexy's new GoFundMe.
- Here you go, Wheeler.
Don't spend it all
in one place.
- Okay if I sit here?
- Yeah.
- I'm in
the talent show tomorrow.
You should come.
- I'll check it out.
- And is that Jake Wheeler?
Now's your chance to tell Dev
and his mom
what you really think.
- You just care
that they know I'm a fag!
[dramatic music]
- I'm your friend till the end.
You get that now, Jake.
We all have our secrets.
- I really need to see you.
Can I call you tomorrow?
- Right, Bree?
[laughter]
- Dad?
[electricity crackling]
- What are we calling it?
- Death by misadventure.
For now.
- You really are
Charles Lee Ray.
- Now, let's talk
about that bitch Lexy.
♪
[The Kac-Ties' "Mr. Werewolf"]
- ♪ Mr. Werewolf,
Mr. Werewolf ♪
- ♪ Please don't get me,
[wolf howls]
- ♪ Mr. Werewolf,
Mr. Werewolf ♪
- ♪ Please, Mr. Werewolf,
let me get by ♪
- ♪ Mr. Werewolf
- Charles, time for bed.
- ♪ Werewolf, go outside
- ♪ Mr. Werewolf
- ♪ Yeah
- ♪ 'Cause I got a date,
and I can't be late ♪
♪ Please, Mr. Werewolf
- [gasps]
- ♪ Mr. Werewolf
- ♪ Yeah
- ♪ I got a sweet girl
who wants to be my wife ♪
- ♪ Mr. Werewolf
- ♪ Yeah
- Ah...
[eerie music]
♪
- ♪ Yeah
- ♪ Mr. Werewolf
♪
- Good morning,
Hackenslashers.
It's October 31st.
In most cities,
Halloween means
ghosts and goblins,
candy and costumes,
a night when
young and old alike
can give free expression
to their inner ids
from magical unicorns
to slutty zombies.
But here in Hackensack,
Halloween also means
bloodshed and butchery.
That's because,
historically speaking,
violence in our fair city
has always spiked
on Halloween.
Maybe it's because
we celebrate it
all day long here.
[indistinct chatter]
Remember the year a group
of deranged trick-or-treaters
broke into
the Candy Emporium downtown?
It wasn't pretty.
And who can forget
just last year,
when Ms. Fairchild sliced
her hand carving pumpkins?
She ended up with 15 stitches.
Plus, this year,
Halloween just happens
to fall on a full moon,
another sign of doom
and destruction.
So tonight, Hackenslashers,
be on the lookout
for all kinds of shit
to really hit the fan.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- You okay back there, buddy?
- Yeah, it's just--
my seat's hot.
- Oh, Jake, I'm sorry.
You can turn that down.
There's a switch over there
on the right.
- You know,
long periods of exposure
can cause second-degree burns.
It's called
Toasted Skin Syndrome.
- That's ridiculous.
- Look it up.
It happens.
- Not in a Lexus, it doesn't.
Jake, don't pay any attention
to him, sweetheart.
- Remind me, what's your
protein intake this week?
- Uh, 50 grams a day?
- Oof, you should bump
that up to 75.
- But Dad,
state's not till the 15th.
Plus, I'm not a sprinter,
and I only weighed 105
this morning.
- We don't want you
getting injured
a week before the most
important race of your life.
Just have a Clif Bar
before lunch, okay?
- Okay.
♪
[school bell rings]
- Have a good day
at school, Junior.
- Still with the nightmares?
You can take another week
if you need it.
- No, I actually think,
at this point, that it's better
that I get out of the house.
- Jake, aren't you
comfortable with us?
You can be honest.
- No.
I mean, I am comfortable.
Anyway, you guys
have been really great.
I appreciate it.
I should go.
- Hey, Jake?
- Yeah?
- For lunch.
Have a good day.
- It's gonna take
more than that.
[indistinct whispering]
- Why is he back at school?
- What happened to his dad?
- Did you see
what he did with that doll?
- Hey, Jake,
good to see you back.
How you doing?
- Hey, Oliver.
I'm okay.
- You didn't miss much.
Ms. F dropped a pop quiz,
and then Junior's pissed
about what you said
about me and Lex.
- You mean what Chucky said.
- Right.
That shit was hilarious.
Look, Jake, I just wanted
to express my condolences.
- Thanks.
- And I wanted to apologize
for every time
I ever gave you shit.
That was not cool.
I'm really sorry.
- Okay.
- I'm having a party tonight,
and I think it'd be really good
for you if you came.
- A Halloween party?
- Yep.
Costumes, Coronas, and candy,
and we're not talking M&Ms.
My parents are
in London for the weekend,
so it's gonna be sick.
- I don't have a costume.
- It's all right.
Just bring Chucky.
- They should have suspended
his Walmart ass.
And they totally would have
if your idiot uncle
hadn't stuck his finger
in the freaking toaster.
- He was a drunk.
He was like an accident
waiting to happen.
It's actually really sad.
- Yeah, it really is.
So sad.
But, you know,
fuck Jake Wheeler
with a chainsaw.
- You're not
the only one, okay?
I mean, what about what he said
to my mom--"you got a secret"?
That's some creepy shit.
- Anyway, McVey told him
he can't bring that thing
to school anymore.
It's disruptive,
so I guess that's something.
[school bell rings]
I just can't believe
Oliver's actually inviting him
to the party.
- So what are you
wearing tonight?
- You'll see.
- I don't know.
What if I'm not into it?
- I wasn't aware
I had to get your approval.
- Did you get
Oliver's approval?
- I might
if you keep pushing me.
- Sorry, sorry.
So what is it?
Hot Hermione?
Hot Hit-Girl?
Hot harlot?
- Down, bae.
It's a surprise.
But I promise you
it's gonna be hot.
- Hi.
- Jake.
I'm sorry.
- Thanks.
I really appreciate it.
- I've been thinking about you.
- You have?
- About what you've
been going through.
You know, my dad died
when I was nine.
- Yeah, I remember.
- I think the worst part is
what it did to me and my mom.
When I was little,
we were super close,
but now we barely even talk.
I think I remind her
of him, you know?
♪
Look, the point is,
I would have never
gotten through it
without my friends.
Look, we don't know
each other very well.
- We don't know
each other at all.
- You going
to Oliver's party tonight?
- I think so, yeah.
- Awesome. Bringing Chucky?
- I don't know.
- Why not?
You two really killed
the other night.
♪
At the talent show.
So where is he, anyway?
[school bell rings]
[vacuum cleaner humming]
♪
- [humming melody]
[continues humming]
- [chuckles]
[glass shatters]
[eerie music]
♪
- Ugh.
[humming melody]
- [breathing heavily]
- Hm.
- Oh.
Whew.
- [breathing heavily]
[soft footfalls]
♪
- [screams]
- [laughs]
[playful spooky music]
♪
[spooky dramatic music]
[keypad beeping]
[keypad buzzes]
- Oh, Logan changed the code.
It's "bell lap" now.
[keypad beeping]
[eerie music]
♪
Hey, you want a popsicle?
- No.
Thank you.
- What?
- Nothing.
It's just, I don't need you
offering me popsicles
in my own house.
You know what I mean?
Annie's been making those
for me
since I was three years old.
- So?
- So could you just stop
trying so fucking hard?
Okay?
♪
- Oh, no.
Call 911.
- What are you doing?
- Call 911!
♪
Shit.
[indistinct radio chatter]
- Oh, God.
Where are the boys?
- It's okay.
They're all right.
They're with
the grief counselor.
- Forgive me.
- Not at all.
- It's just,
I know it's a cliché,
but Annie really was
a part of this family.
- Bree, I'm so sorry.
What was her home address?
- Oh, this is embarrassing.
Um, she lived
on the south side?
She always took the bus in.
- Okay.
What about next of kin, family?
Anybody we should notify?
- I don't think she had
anyone besides us, did she?
- She has a brother,
I think.
He lives in D.C.--Baltimore.
- Okay, we'll check it out.
- How could this happen?
♪
- Well, turns out it happens
more often than you think.
Happened to a woman
up in Vancouver just last year.
- Some people will load
the knives blade up
'cause they think
it'll get it cleaner.
It's a fallacy, by the way.
- All it takes
is one little slip.
- Or one little push.
- Sean.
- What are you saying?
- Well, I'm just saying,
this is the second
"freak accident" in this town
in less than a week,
and your nephew has had
a ringside seat for both.
- Sean.
- What?
- But we know
from all the door cam footage
that no one set foot
inside this house
before the boys
got home from school.
Annie must have been dead
before they came
through that door.
- Unless they're covering
for each other.
- Sean, please,
let me handle this, okay?
- Handle what?
- Yes, what exactly
are you saying?
[soft dramatic music]
- Look, I'm sorry
to have to ask you this,
but did Jake have
any issues with Annie?
- What?
- No!
- That's ridiculous.
He barely even knew her.
I mean,
they just met last week.
- Well, I don't know.
Maybe she resented having
to deal with someone new.
- No.
Annie was a saint.
She welcomed him with open arms
like she did everyone.
- What about Junior?
- What?
- Bree, I have to ask.
- Junior loved Annie!
- She practically raised him.
[siren blaring]
♪
- What the fuck did you do?
- I didn't do it.
- What?
- Swear to God
I didn't kill her.
- What do you think,
I'm a complete moron?
- Come on, Jake,
you gotta believe me!
I'm your friend to the end.
- Get fucked with that shit.
I'm not six years old.
Give me that.
- [sighs]
Gotta say,
writing's not your forte.
Stick to sculpture.
- Fuck you.
- You should just call it
"Devon, Devon, Devon."
[laughs]
- Shut up.
- You know, I have a queer kid.
- You have a kid?
- Genderfluid.
- And you're cool with it?
- I'm not a monster, Jake.
- No, you are.
You killed Annie!
- Come on, man.
Think.
Why would I kill Annie?
You and me, we only kill people
who have it coming.
- No.
No, I don't kill anyone.
And I don't want you
to kill anyone else.
- It wasn't me!
Accidents happen, Jake.
More often than murder,
and way more often than murders
committed by
supernaturally-possessed dolls.
That's just basic math.
And let me remind you
that I could have killed
anybody in this house
during the last week
at any time,
including you.
- So why haven't you?
- I told you.
I'm trying to help you.
Look around, kid!
Take a good look
at where you are.
A long way from that shithole
you used to live in
with that shitheel who liked
using you for a punching bag.
I'm the one friend
you got, Jake.
And I'm telling you,
I did not kill
the damn housekeeper.
I got my sights
set on bigger game.
- Chucky, no.
- You of all people should know
some people deserve to die.
[eerie music]
♪
- You heard what they said.
It was an accident.
- No, what I heard was that
it was
an astronomical coincidence,
the chances of which
actually happening
are about a billion to one.
- We watched him grow up.
He's not a violent kid.
He's just traumatized.
- We're all traumatized.
I mean, are we even qualified
to look after a boy like this?
- A boy like what?
[soft dramatic music]
- Okay.
You yourself said many times
that you were worried
that your brother
was a bad influence on him,
especially after Mary died.
Logan, we don't have a clue
what's going on in his head.
- We could say the same
for Junior.
No one knows what's going on
inside their heads.
Bree, they're teenagers.
- You know exactly
what Junior is thinking,
24 hours a day,
consciously or unconsciously,
and it's pleasing you.
- You say that
like it's a bad thing.
- You're pushing him
too hard, Logan.
I'm worried about him.
- Bree, I'm just trying
to help him succeed.
♪
[shower running]
- What the hell are you doing?
- Was gonna ask you
the same thing.
♪
- Wait, no, that's--
that's not--
- Stay away from her.
- I didn't do that.
♪
What the hell?
Chucky, I told you, back off.
I'm not letting you.
What are you gonna do about it?
[heavy thud]
Ugh!
[spooky dramatic music]
♪
- I'm sorry.
Did you say dishwasher?
Jesus.
What did Evan say?
Look.
Okay.
Was there any press this time?
Good. Let's keep it that way.
Okay, I've got to go.
Got to go.
Take this.
Look. Look, look, look.
Oh, honey, that's so good.
I'm speechless.
It's incredible.
All that detail
after seeing him
for, what, five minutes?
- Eidetic memory.
- Yeah.
- Baby, can you
remember his name?
- Chucky.
- Yes, that's right.
Caroline, would you maybe
like to meet Chucky sometime?
I bet your sister
could make that happen.
- What?
- Oh, no, I'd be too scared.
- Why, honey?
- What if he doesn't like me?
- Why are you encouraging this?
That thing belongs
to Jake Wheeler.
And I'm sorry,
but did you not hear him
talking shit about me
at the talent show?
- Honey, you're overreacting.
It was a joke!
In a way,
you should be flattered.
The whole thing
was all about you.
- Oh, Dad,
that's fucking awesome.
I'm just so thrilled
you all found it so amusing.
As usual, you both totally
ignore what's going on with me.
It's called bullying.
He's a bully.
- Who's a bully?
Chucky?
- No.
No, honey, he's not.
- Give me a break.
- Will you take a look at this?
Here, sweetie.
- It's hideous.
- Lexy, your sister has a gift,
and she's better at this
than you've ever been
at anything
in your entire life.
- Michelle!
- No, I'm sorry.
I just can't take
her attitude anymore.
It breaks my heart.
Your sister adores you.
- She barely knows I exist.
And it's obvious
neither do you guys.
- Where do you think
you're going?
- To get ready
for Oliver's party.
- No, you're taking your sister
trick-or-treating.
- I have a costume.
It was expensive.
- And I have
the Hacky Halloween Ball,
and your father
has to be with me.
- "The Daily Voice"
is doing a story
on Hackensack's
very first first husband.
- Besides, Dr. Mixter
says that Halloween
is the perfect opportunity
for you girls to bond.
- Bond?
She doesn't even like
to be touched.
[eerie music]
♪
- Annie?
Their housekeeper?
What happened?
- An accident.
Another accident.
- She used to make popsicles
when we were
at Junior's after school.
She was really nice.
- I know.
It's very sad.
Look, I have to head back
to the office for a while.
Did you eat anything?
- I'll have something
at the party.
- Junior going?
- Yep.
Lexy too.
- What about Jake?
- How would I know?
It's not like we hang
in the same crowd.
- Even now that he's
living at Junior's?
- No.
- Dev, did Jake ever say
anything about his father?
About his father hurting him?
- What do you mean?
- Like, maybe because he's gay?
- How would I know?
- I don't know.
- Mom, what are
we talking about?
- I'm just doing my job.
- As a mom or a cop?
- A bit of both, I guess.
[chuckles]
Have fun at the party.
- Later.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
[upbeat music]
[indistinct chatter]
♪
[phone chimes]
- Hey, hang on, hang on.
You're not still going
to the party, are you?
- Why not?
- Well, I just thought
after everything
that happened today,
you'd want to spend
some time with your family.
- I just need to get
out of the house, okay?
- Wow.
You look great.
Are those my medals?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
what's Lexy going as?
- It's a surprise.
- Oh.
You know, I think you two
make a terrific couple.
- Thank you.
Uber's here.
I gotta go.
See you guys later.
- Oh, what about Jake?
- Hey, Jake, your Uber's here!
Jake?
Wow, Jake.
You look incredible.
- That looks so real.
- Yeah.
Who you supposed to be, though?
- Victim of circumstances.
- Huh. That's great, Jake.
I think Junior
already took off.
You want a ride?
- Actually, I changed my mind.
I don't think I'm up
for a party tonight.
- I understand.
- Okay.
- Got some stuff to do
in my room.
Shit!
[door slams]
[dramatic music]
Where is he?
Did Junior take him?
- What are you talking about?
- Chucky.
He's gone.
[indistinct chatter]
[spooky dramatic music]
♪
- [laughs]
Jesus Christ, you all look
like a bunch of damn idiots.
[doorbell rings]
all: Trick or treat!
- [laughing]
Oh.
Aren't you girls a little
mature for this type of thing?
You know, when I was your age,
I was high as a kite.
You have a good time.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Oh.
- Hi. I'm Chucky.
Want to play?
- Oh, Hello Kitty!
[chuckles]
- If you tell me
what I need to know,
I'll give you a treat.
- Oh, well,
what do you need to know?
- I'm looking for a party!
- A party.
Aren't you a little young
for that type of thing?
- If you don't tell me,
you might just get a trick.
- Well, I don't think
that will be necessary.
Let me think.
Oh, I know.
The Haydens have
a big Halloween party
every year.
Well, at least
their son Oliver does.
You can hear it from here.
- Oliver.
- It's just two blocks over
on Claremont Street.
- Thanks, lady.
[hums melody]
Here's your treat.
- Ooh, thank you.
- [laughs]
[heavy techno music]
♪
- Where's Lexy?
- Up there.
♪
- Hey.
- Are you--you okay?
- Of course I'm okay.
How else would I be?
- You know that I can't.
- Why not?
Daddy's not here to stop you.
- Do me a favor.
Be careful with Jake, okay?
He's got issues.
- I'm not afraid of Jake.
His creepy doll
just creeps me the fuck out.
- Me too.
- So...
- Whatever happens,
I'll protect you.
- Junior Wheeler, my hero.
Will you catch me if I fall?
- Lex, I'm serious.
- Sad but true.
- Would you catch me?
- What do you think?
- Probably not.
So what are you supposed to be?
- Just you wait.
- What if I can't wait?
- Well, then come on, Jun-Jun.
Come to Daddy.
[Electric Youth's
"Modern Fears"]
[dreamy pop music]
- ♪ They can
♪ Say what they say
♪ But you need a heart
♪ To have heart like you do
♪
♪ You're too
♪ You're too careful
♪ To truly not care
- Have you seen Lexy?
- Why is everybody
looking for Lexy?
- [scoffs]
Let's go.
- Hey.
Where's your doll?
- We want Chucky.
- Chucky?
You've seen Chucky?
- Dude, you lost your doll?
- Jake.
- Oh, Devon.
You look great.
- I didn't think
you were coming.
It's cool that you're here.
- I've gotta find Lexy.
- Is something wrong?
- I just--I've gotta find her.
- Why?
- I just--I need
to make sure she's okay.
- Why do you care?
- Oh, Oliver,
have you seen Lexy?
- Who?
- Lexy.
- Oh, yeah, she's in there.
- Wait.
- Seven minutes in hell.
[all chanting]
Hell, hell, hell, hell, hell!
Hell, hell, hell, hell,
hell, hell, hell, hell!
[all cheer]
- Jake.
Jake, your eye.
It looks so real.
- Oliver, let us out.
Oliver, let us out!
[blood splattering]
- You're good at this, Chucky.
- You too, Caroline.
You got potential.
I always say
killing's good, clean fun
for the whole family.
You can kill the housekeeper.
You can kill the babysitter.
You can even kill your sister.
- Mommy says
real killing is bad.
- Yeah, well,
Mommy's full of shit.
- Mommy says
it isn't nice to swear.
- Mommy's working
her way up my list
pretty fucking quick.
[soft dramatic music]
[game character screams]
But first things first, kid.
where's Lexy?
- Probably kissing
Junior somewhere.
- Well, at least she's gonna
die doing what she loves.
♪
- You're not doing it right.
- I haven't done anything yet.
- No duh. I noticed.
Just--you know what?
Forget it.
- We can hug.
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
What are you, my mom?
- Tell me
what you want me to do.
- Well, you're supposed
to know what to do.
- [grunting]
- Stop.
Did you feel that?
- Did you do something?
- The mattress moved.
- [grunting]
- "We can hug."
- I didn't mean it like that.
- Hug.
- What are you two
doing in here?
- Absolutely nothing.
- Lexy, wait.
[eerie music]
- Oy.
- How much time?
- 30 seconds to go.
- What's going on with you?
- Nothing.
- It's not nothing.
I can tell.
- If I told you,
you wouldn't believe me.
- Yes, I would.
- Why?
- I just don't think
you'd lie to me.
♪
- Leave my friends alone!
- Dude, you have
a serious doll problem.
- If you only knew.
- [imitating kissing noises]
- Kissy-kissy.
- Lovebirds.
[all cheering]
- Is he a good kisser?
[people chanting]
Lexy, Lexy, Lexy, Lexy!
- Lexy is here.
- Move.
- I just don't get
why you care.
[people chanting]
Lexy, Lexy, Lexy, Lexy, Lexy!
- Oh, oh, oh!
[laughter]
[upbeat music]
[grunting]
♪
[laughter]
[electricity crackles]
♪
[grunting]
- What?
♪
- She's my dad.
- I'm sorry.
That's so fucked up.
- It's not your fault.
- Okay, I don't know
what Lexy's problem is.
- I can't let her
get away with this.
- You don't have to do that.
- Yes, I do.
I'm gonna show her
what it's like to get hurt.
- [muffled]
It was this terrible
redheaded child.
I hold him responsible.
- I'm sorry.
I didn't get that.
- I said it was
this horrible redheaded child.
I hold him responsible.
- Red hair?
- Yes.
Hello Kitty mask
with tennis shoes
and denim overalls.
They had something
stitched on them.
- Do you remember
what it said on the overalls?
- "Good gay."
"Good guy."
- Red hair.
- Yeah, exactly.
Does he sound familiar?
- Yes, he does.
[spooky dramatic music]
♪
- I don't want to go!
- Caroline, come on.
- I have a new friend.
- That's great, Care,
but we still
have to get out of here.
Come on.
- My new friend!
- Care, I don't know what
you're talking about, but--
♪
What?
- Aha.
- No!
- Jake, wait!
- [sighs]
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- His creepy doll
just creeps me the fuck out.
♪
- How you doing?
- Not good.
- Look,
sorry about the eye, kid.
I promise
I will never do that again.
- Heard that before.
♪
- That was some party.
- It sucked.
- Like I said before, Jake,
some people
just deserve to die.
♪
Look at the world.
It's the Super Bowl
of slaughter.
And you can't just sit
in the stands, you know?
We all gotta get out there
and get in the game.
It's kill or be killed.
Whose team
do you want to be on?
Because sooner or later,
everybody's gotta choose.
[eerie music]
♪
Make the right choice, Jake.
Kill the bitch
before she kills you.
- I don't know
if I can do that.
- Man the fuck up.
♪
What did they all do tonight?
They laughed,
just like Lexy wanted.
They were all laughing at you.
I told you,
I'm the only real friend
you got in the whole world.
♪
Take the knife, Jake.
You know you want to.
Take it.
♪
Congrats, kid.
[laughs]
You're going to the Super Bowl.
[dramatic music]
♪
[playful spooky music]