- Another three bodies
were found
by the Hackensack Mall
last night.
That brings the total
body count to 11.
Police are still searching
for the mass murderer.
- ♪ Oh, the days
in Hickory Meadows ♪
♪ A beautiful place to live,
not die ♪
♪ Oh, the day
in Hickory Meadows ♪
♪ Why
- [breathing heavily]
[gasps]
[menacing music]
♪
- [gasps]
[Billie Eilish's "Copycat"]
♪
- ♪ Don't be cautious
♪ Don't be kind
♪ You committed,
I'm your crime ♪
♪ Push my button anytime
♪ You got your finger
on the trigger ♪
♪ But your
trigger finger's mine ♪
♪ Silver dollar
♪ Golden flame
♪ Dirty water
♪ Poison rain
♪ Perfect murder
♪ Take your aim,
I don't belong to anyone ♪
♪ But everybody
knows my name ♪
♪
- Hi, Jake.
20 bucks for that.
Sound fair?
- 20 bucks?
- It's got to be worth
20 bucks, right?
- Hey, where'd you get this?
- I have no idea.
Must've been my daughter's,
I guess.
Honestly, I don't remember.
You into vintage?
- No, I'm into retro.
- Oh, what's the difference?
- About 10 bucks.
- [chuckles] Fair enough.
♪
- Well, thanks, Mrs. Jolly.
- Tell your dad I said hello.
Oh.
Someone took the butcher knife.
- ♪ Call me calloused
♪ Call me cold
♪ You're italic, I'm in bold
♪ Call me cocky,
watch your tone ♪
♪ You better love me
'cause you're just a clone ♪
- What's up, detectives?
It's me, Devon Evans.
Here in Hackensack,
the mayor likes to say
the saints are always
watching over us,
guiding our destinies
and keeping us from harm.
Well, I call bullshit on that.
The mayor wants us to think
we're all living
on Main Street in Disneyland,
but the truth is, Hackensack
is a haven for the bizarre,
the fucked-up,
and the straight-up
criminally insane.
In the past year alone,
our murder rate
has spiked 25%.
In fact, we haven't seen
this kind of violence here
since the Ray family murders
in '65,
a bloodbath that gave birth
to one of the most notorious
serial killers in history,
Charles Lee Ray.
Back in the day,
he was one of us,
growing up right over
on Sherwood Lane.
You won't read about it
in the "Times" dispatch,
but you can hear all about it
right here, every week.
Until next time,
fellow detectives,
this is Devon Evans
bringing you...
"Hackenslash."
Binxie?
[clicking tongue]
Here, Binx.
[ambient music]
♪
[cat meows]
How you doing, Binxie?
[disturbing music]
[cat meows]
♪
[cat hisses]
[cat screeches, growls]
Two heads are better than one,
right?
♪
[cat growls]
[distant siren wailing]
♪
[cat meows]
Let's see what you're really
made of.
♪
- Jake!
Jake, I'm home.
- Hey.
- [gasps]
- Wanna play?
- Jesus Christ, Jake,
another frickin' doll?
- Hi, I'm Chucky,
and I'm your friend
till the end.
Hidey-ho!
[laughs]
- It's voice-activated.
Hey, I was thinking about using
his head for the sculpture.
What do you think?
- I don't know.
I'm no art critic.
- Well, I'm not asking
for a review, Dad.
I just want your opinion.
- It's cool, Jake.
Still think you're spending
too much time on it.
Wouldn't hurt you
to get out of this room
every once in a while.
Maybe you could, uh,
ask a girl to a movie.
See a friend or something.
- Friends come and go,
in my experience.
The work lasts forever.
- So does student debt.
You know it's almost
impossible to make a living
as an artist?
- Mom did.
- That wasn't a living.
That was a lifestyle,
and it certainly
didn't pay the bills.
I did.
- [sighs]
- You know you're looking more
and more like her every day?
Speaking of which,
I looked into that art camp,
and I don't think
it's gonna work out.
- Why not?
- It's 1,000 bucks, Jake.
I'm sorry.
Maybe next year.
Besides,
you don't wanna be away from me
for a whole month,
do you?
[rock music
playing over stereo]
You remember
to take your pill today?
- Not yet.
- Well, you should take it.
You're gonna need it.
We're at Defcon 1 tonight.
- Why?
- Your cousin's coming over
for dinner, remember?
- Oh, shit.
- "Shit" is right.
[cat growls]
[suspenseful music]
♪
[cat hisses]
[playful spooky music]
♪
- So this is fun.
Can't remember last time
we just sent out for pizza.
- Hey, Luke,
you got a little something
on your, uh...
Other side.
There you go.
So how's business?
- It's not worth talking about.
- Sure, it is.
- Things could be better.
I'm drowning.
[menacing music]
- Uh...
I could throw you
a little business.
Bree put a dent in her Lexus.
- That'd be great...
if we handled bodywork.
♪
But we don't.
- There's no shame in getting
a little help now and then.
- Who's ashamed?
- You're my brother.
You'd do the same for me.
- Come on, Logan.
When have you ever needed help?
♪
- Well, Junior has some news.
- Mom.
- Guess who made regionals.
- Holy shit.
Oh, that's great, Junior.
Isn't that great, Jake?
Huh?
- He's the best distance runner
at Perry Middle since...
well, since his father.
- [whispering] Yeah!
- But regionals
is on the 10th.
It's the day I'm painting
City Hall with the Scouts,
remember?
- You already made Eagle Scout,
which reminds me,
you're gonna need
another extracurricular.
Harvard's gonna want three.
If anyone can handle it,
you can.
- You know, Jake, the, uh--
the Scouts are taking gays now.
You should totally come
check it out.
- Junior.
- What? It's true.
- So what does that mean,
exactly, Eagle Scout?
Did you, like,
sell the most cookies?
- No, while you were up in
your room playing with dolls,
I organized a whole book drive
for the homeless.
- Yeah, because keeping up
with Harry Potter
is the most pressing issue
facing the homeless.
- So, Jake, how is
the sculpture coming along?
Can we see it yet?
- Soon.
- Where do you get the dolls?
- Thrift shops, yard sales,
eBay, trash cans.
Andy Warhol once said,
"Just because something's
been thrown away
doesn't make it garbage."
- Wasn't Warhol gay too?
- Junior, stop it.
- What?
It's the 21st century.
It's cool to be gay now.
Right, Jake?
- It's a nonissue.
- Yeah, it's like
being left-handed or vegan.
- Would you give it a rest?
He's 13 years old.
He doesn't know what he is.
[menacing music]
- 14.
- Excuse me. Lucas,
where's your powder room?
- It's upstairs
where it's always been.
♪
[eerie music]
[cell phone beeps]
- Hey, it's me.
[sighs]
Sorry. I only have a minute.
I'm with my family.
I just...
[rustling]
I just needed--
[sighs]
Can you hold on a minute?
♪
[dramatic musical flourish]
[sighs]
[cat screeches]
Oh, my God!
[cat growls]
[sighs]
Sorry, I thought someone
was in here with me.
I really need to see you.
Can I call you tomorrow?
Okay.
[engine turning over]
- Binxie!
Here, Binx.
- [grunting, groaning]
[objects crashing]
[menacing music]
[grunting]
♪
[Madalen Duke's
"How Villains Are Made"]
- ♪ Time to
♪ Put my medal on
♪
♪ Whose blood to spill
♪ I don't know
- No more dolls, Jake.
Ever.
- ♪ Whose side I'm on
♪
♪ Two armies
are coming at me ♪
♪ Their flags and weapons
look the same ♪
- [breathing shakily]
- ♪ One tells the truth,
the other's lying ♪
♪
♪ And they're both
calling my name ♪
♪ This is how villains
are made ♪
♪ This is how
villains are made ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh, oh, oh
♪
♪ No one ever
starts that way ♪
♪ But this is how villains
are made ♪
♪
- Binxie?
[crows cawing]
[suspenseful music]
♪
[keyboard clacking]
[distant siren wailing]
♪
[keyboard clacking]
- 1,500 bucks?
Holy shit.
[Kim Petras' "Personal Hell"]
♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah
♪ Summer sun,
don't feel a thing ♪
♪ Overthink 'bout everything
♪ When I think of you,
you give me chills ♪
♪ Baby, come on,
got what I need ♪
♪ Hands all over me, oh
♪ Save me
♪ From my personal hell
♪ Yeah, yeah
♪ Exorcise my demons, yeah
♪ Tainted love
could get me there ♪
♪ I've been saving
all of this for you ♪
♪ Baby, come on, over to me
♪ Come set me free
♪ Baby, come on
♪ Got what I need
♪ Hands all over me, oh
♪ Save me
♪ From my person--
[horn beeps]
- Hey, what up?
- Still don't understand why
you're still into this stuff.
It's so freaking weird.
- I think it's a better hobby
than running.
- ♪ Save me
♪ From my personal hell
♪ Yeah, yeah
♪ Break me,
break me out of myself ♪
- Hey, Jake.
Awesome Good Guy.
I'm into vintage too.
- Oh, he's retro.
Wanna buy it?
- No, thanks.
Hey, uh, can I ask you
a question?
- Yeah, sure.
- This is really awkward,
but do you think that you can,
like, maybe introduce me
to your cousin?
- [sighs] Junior?
- Yeah.
- I get that a lot.
I'm flattered, really,
but, um, it's not my thing.
- Oh, sorry, I didn't know.
- Yeah, since cotillion.
Don't you follow my Insta?
- Your bed buddy, Jake?
What's his name?
- What's your name?
- Hi, I'm Chucky.
Wanna play?
- Oh, my God, that's adorable.
Say, "Cheese."
- Chucky cheese.
- You're not tearing him apart,
I hope.
- Anything for art, right?
- No, you can't.
- Well, actually,
I'm gonna sell him.
- Oh, you're selling
your stuff now, Jake?
I didn't realize
it'd gotten that bad.
- No.
- I mean, do you need
to borrow any money?
- No.
- Seriously, it's no problem.
Right?
- You know I don't carry
cash on me.
- You can Venmo.
- I'm fine.
- Being financially
disadvantaged
is nothing to be ashamed of,
Jake.
Right?
- I'm not.
[bell rings]
- Well, see you later.
- Yeah, see you in class.
- I just had
the most amazing idea.
- Maybe you should
give the guy a break.
- Don't go soft on me, babe.
[bell rings]
- E.B. White said
that explaining a joke
is like dissecting a frog:
you understand it better,
but unfortunately,
the frog dies in the process.
Jake, are you okay?
- Uh, yeah, I just--
I don't--
I don't think I can do this.
- Do you have
a religious conflict?
- No, I just...
I can't stand
the sight of blood.
- Pussy.
- Oliver,
mind your fucking business.
all: Ooh!
- Look, you can do this.
Just make a vertical incision
down the length
of the abdomen,
like I showed you.
Sometimes the heart
will go on beating
for a few minutes after death.
[ominous music]
♪
- [hyperventilating]
[tense music]
♪
[heartbeat thumping,
clock ticking slowly]
♪
- Oh.
Oh, no, Jake,
that isn't quite right.
- No, I didn't do that.
[cell phones buzzing, chiming]
[laughter]
- What is going on?
- Lexy's new GoFundMe.
- Oliver, let me see that.
- Here you go, Wheeler.
[coin clinks]
Don't spend it all
in one place.
[bell rings]
- Hey, for homework tonight,
read chapter 12
of your Zoology book.
We do have a quiz tomorrow.
- Don't forget your boytoy.
- Oliver,
get the hell out of here.
Jake.
- Hey, Ms. F,
can you maybe keep this
until I sell it?
It won't fit in my locker.
- Of course.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
Just a moment, Lexy.
I'd like a word.
You can close the door.
Have a seat.
- Thank you.
- I want you to take
the page down, right now.
- But, Ms. Fairchild,
I've already raised $75.
I'm just trying to help
a fellow student
who's in need.
- Lexy, you're not very funny.
- Poverty's no laughing matter.
- What has Jake Wheeler
ever done to you, anyway?
- Nothing.
- You know,
I was a lot like you
when I was your age.
Entitled, arrogant,
and secretly terrified.
- And what is it I'm supposedly
so afraid of?
- The creeping realization
that real life is gonna be
a lot more challenging
than middle school
and that no matter how pretty
or popular or important
you might think you are
right now,
in the end,
nobody gets everything
they want in life.
- Don't worry about me, Ms. F.
I'm pretty sure
I'm not going to end up
teaching eight grade biology.
- Just take the page down,
Lexy,
and you can report to detention
right after school.
[dramatic musical flourish]
- What I'm doing is admirable,
and if you try to stop me
or penalize me in any way,
my parents will sue the school.
[playful music]
Can I go now?
- You know, I think Mrs. McVey
should be part
of this conversation.
You can repeat your threat
to her.
- Happy to. She and my mom
are in the same Pilates class.
- [sighs] Wait here.
- Crime is complicated,
especially in the eyes
of the victim,
the marginalized.
It's not just murders
and robberies.
There are silent crimes,
socially accepted crimes,
systemic crimes
against humanity,
crimes happening every day,
all around us.
You can't always hear
the victims screaming.
They are, though.
You just have to listen
hard enough.
- Okay if I sit here?
- Uh, yeah.
- What are you listening to?
- Nothing.
- Well, you were listening
to something.
Every day I see you here,
you're totally wrapped up
in whatever it is.
- Uh...
I was watching
"Vampire Diaries," actually.
- [chuckles] For real?
Is it good?
- It's sort of
a guilty pleasure.
- What's it about?
- Uh, well, it's about
the unbreakable bond
between brothers.
Strong enough
to survive anything,
even their worst mistakes.
- But it's also, like,
super hot vampires, right?
- [chuckles]
Yeah, they're super hot.
- I'll check it out.
- Coolio.
- Uh, hey, I'm in
the talent show tomorrow.
You should come.
- I'll check it out.
- Coolio.
- [laughs]
Uh, anyways, listen, um,
I wanted to ask you something.
This is kind of awkward.
Um...
- What?
- Well, first of all,
I know you listen to my show.
- That's not a question.
- Well, I mean, I know
you were listening just now.
I saw.
- [chuckles] Okay.
- So I was wondering
if maybe...
well, I was wondering
if maybe you'd be interested
in coming on my podcast.
- What?
- I wanna do a whole series
on bullying, Jake.
- I thought you were
into true crime.
- Bullying is a crime, Jake.
I mean, just here
in Hackensack,
we have Lexy, Oliver...
- Junior.
- No. Junior's a good guy.
- Junior's my cousin.
Believe me,
he's not a good guy.
- It's Lexy, all right?
I don't know what
he sees in her.
But, Jake--
- Hey, do I look like
the poster boy for losers
to you?
- No, I just thought that--
- No, I'm not interested.
I got to go.
- Loser.
[foreboding music]
♪
- [giggles]
- [gasps]
♪
[ominous music]
- [breathing heavily]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
- [sighs]
Lexy, what's going on?
- Nothing.
I have to go.
I have rehearsal.
- Not so fast.
I want you to tell Mrs. McVey
what you told me.
- I'll take the page down,
okay? I have to go.
I think I lost my phone.
Just keep an eye out for it.
I got to stop smoking
so much weed before class.
- Yeah, good idea.
Okay, well, that was way easier
than it should've been.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- [breathing heavily]
[dog barking]
[message swooshes]
[cell phone buzzes]
- Hello?
- Yeah, I'm calling
about the doll.
- That was fast.
- What condition is he in?
- He's good.
Really good.
Mint, actually.
- Is he there with you now?
- No, he's sort of in storage.
- Is his name Chucky?
- Yeah, as a matter of fact,
it is.
How'd you know?
- Listen to me carefully.
I know this is
gonna sound strange,
but has anything weird
happened lately?
I mean, with Chucky.
- Well, this conversation
has been pretty weird.
- Be very careful
with that doll.
Do you understand?
- What?
- Have you checked
his batteries?
- What are you talking about?
- Wait, hold on a second.
Hello?
Is somebody there?
- Hello?
[suspenseful music]
♪
[ambient music]
Dad, are you okay?
- Yeah.
I was up late doing payroll.
- Dad, we need to talk.
- I agree.
- I like to be hugged.
- Found this in the bathroom.
I thought we got rid of that.
- Yeah, I'm working on it.
[eerie music]
♪
[dramatic music]
[soft piano music playing]
♪
[applause]
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
♪
- That was so beautiful,
Devon.
Was it meant
for anyone special?
- Only for you, Lexy.
- [giggles]
- I think you're lying.
Okay, I see some familiar
faces in the crowd tonight.
Hey, Mom.
Hey, Dad.
Hey, brat.
[laughter]
Oh, and I think
I see Devon's mom.
Mrs. Evans,
you must be so proud.
- Yes, I am.
all: Aw.
- And is that Jake Wheeler
sitting right across from you?
- Loser!
all: Boo!
- Hey, Jake, enjoying the show?
- Uh, yeah.
- What did you think of Devon?
- It was good.
- Just good?
Come on, Jake, don't be shy.
Now is your chance to tell Dev
and his mom
what you really think.
- Hey, Lexy!
Lexy.
Why don't you pick on someone
your own size?
[foreboding music]
- Who is that?
[unsettling music]
♪
- Little help here, Jake.
Here...
[whispering indistinctly]
- Okay.
[foreboding music]
♪
- What are you doing?
- Hi, I'm Chucky,
and I'm your friend
till the end.
You get that now, Jake, right?
- Yeah, I get it.
- Now, I said "friend," Jake.
Nothing more.
[soft laughter]
Not that there's anything wrong
with that.
[laughter]
- Hey, look what I found.
- My phone!
- Boo!
- Ah!
[laughter]
- Lots of pics of Junior.
Lots of pics of Oliver too.
[crowd chattering, whistling]
Uh-oh.
Guess that was a secret.
[laughter]
- Jake, stop it.
- I'm not doing this.
- We all have our secrets,
right, Bree?
Here's Lexy's search history.
Apparently,
she's Botox curious,
she's into Pokémon porn,
and look
what she keeps Googling.
- "Why do my farts smell
so good?"
[laughter]
- Adorable.
[cackling]
[eerie music]
♪
[laughter continues]
It's contagious, isn't it?
Laughing at people.
Well, guess what, dickheads.
- Okay, that's enough.
- Now the joke's on you.
- Fun's over. Let's go.
- You're all a bunch
of fucking assholes.
- Let's go.
- I'm out of here.
[cackling]
- Come on, come on.
[cheers and applause]
[mysterious music]
♪
- Your teacher called.
You proud of yourself?
- I'm sorry,
if that's what you mean.
- You're not sorry.
You were suspended.
- It wasn't my fault.
- You insulted your friends
and your family
in front of the entire school.
- They deserved it.
And they're not my friends.
- They used to be.
You used to have friends, Jake.
What happened to you?
It doesn't bother you
that everybody thinks
you're fucking weird, huh?
- You don't care
that they think I'm weird.
You just care
that they know I'm a fag.
- [grunts]
Listen to me. Listen to me.
You say that again
and I will kill you,
you hear me?
You hear me?
- Should've been you inside
that car instead of Mom.
♪
Get off of me.
- Go to your room, Jake.
Give me that.
- No, Dad, I don't think
you wa--
- Go to your room!
Go!
I don't wanna see you anymore.
Get up there!
[woman screaming over TV]
- I hate you!
I fucking hate you!
- Yeah?
[dramatic music]
♪
- [weeps]
- [sighs]
[mysterious music]
♪
Who drank my whiskey?
What the fuck?
Ah, son of a bitch.
[lock clicks]
[foreboding music]
♪
[switches clicking]
[light bulb buzzes]
[dramatic music]
♪
- [retching]
[electricity crackling]
♪
- Ah...
- Dad?
- [groaning]
[electricity crackling]
♪
- [shouts]
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
[sirens wailing]
- Jake?
I'm Detective Evans.
This is my partner,
Detective Peyton.
I think you're in
the same class as my son.
- Devon.
- That's right.
- Look, Jake, your uncle's
on his way over.
He's gonna take you to stay
at his place tonight.
I cannot imagine
what you're going through.
You sure you don't wanna
see the grief counselor?
- No, thanks.
- Okay.
I just have a couple questions,
if you're up for it.
Is that okay, Jake?
[eerie music]
♪
Did you know
that there was a break-in
at the school last night?
- No.
- No real harm done.
God knows I did worse
in my day.
The funny thing is, the only
thing missing was a doll.
- Your teacher said it belonged
to you, Jake.
- I caught your act
at school today.
You were incredible.
- I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have lied.
I've never done anything
like that before.
- Don't worry.
You're not in any kind
of trouble.
I just wanna
get something straight.
So you broke into the school
in the middle of the night
just to get your doll?
- Uh, I needed him to practice
for the talent show.
♪
- Hey.
You're all right.
♪
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- It was an accident.
It's not your fault.
You okay?
Was he drinking?
- Looks like it. Yes.
- Thank you.
Come.
- Oh, Jake.
What happened to your nose?
- I fell.
- Oh. Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Wheeler.
Thank you, Jake.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
- So what are we calling it?
- "Death by misadventure."
For now.
♪
[thunder booming]
- Hi, Jake.
[sighs]
So you're gonna come stay
with us now.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Can I get you anything?
Are you hungry?
Do you want something to drink?
It's important
to stay hydrated.
- No, I'm okay.
Thanks.
- Why don't you show Jake
to his room?
- Shit.
♪
- So this is yours.
Make yourself at home.
The bathroom's down the hall.
Wi-Fi password is "EAGLESCOUT,"
all uppercase.
Is there anything else
you need?
- I think I'm good.
- I want you to know
that we're here for you, Jake.
All of us.
You're not alone.
- Thanks, Aunt Bree.
- Jake.
What did you mean today?
At the talent show, you know,
about me having a secret.
- Um, I was just trying
to be funny.
I didn't--I didn't mean
anything by it.
I'm sorry.
- Okay.
Get some rest.
♪
- Talk to me.
I said talk to me, damn it.
All right.
I'm gonna make you--
- Hi, I'm Chucky,
and I'm your friend
till the end.
Hidey-fucking-ho.
[laughs wickedly]
- Holy shit.
- I know.
- You--you killed him.
You really did it.
- We did it, Jake.
- I didn't want him dead.
- What did you think
I was gonna do,
ask him for a hug?
He got what he deserved.
- He--he wasn't always
like that.
When I was younger,
he was really cool.
- I know an asshole
when I see one.
- After my mom died, he just--
he couldn't deal.
- Oh, I thought we were talking
about the cat.
- You really are
Charles Lee Ray.
- But my friends all call me
Chucky.
Now, let's talk
about that bitch Lexy.
[chilling music]
♪
[thunder booming]
[ominous music]
♪
- [gasps]
Charles.
[The Exotics' "Come with Me"]
both: ♪ When you see me start
to look at you ♪
♪ And, babe, you know
I'm gonna be lonely ♪
- ♪ On my way
both: ♪ If you see me
start to fall ♪
♪ Unless you wanna
see me crawl ♪
♪ Then tell me
that you're here ♪
- ♪ Stay with me
♪ Come with me
both: ♪ Come with me
♪ Come with