- Previously on "Chucky"...
- You dressed up
as his dead dad, my uncle.
- It got, like, 400 likes.
- I wish I could, like,
protect you or something.
- You hate her?
- Of course I hate her.
What--what if
I'm not a killer?
- Everybody's a killer
if you push 'em far enough.
- I want to apologize.
I'm sure you want to know
what you can do for me.
- I want Chucky!
- Chucky.
- Chucky?
- Give her what she wants.
- Chucky!
- She can have him?
- Yeah.
- [squeals]
- I don't want you to think
we're, like,
friends or something.
Hey. Sorry, it took forever
for my parents to leave.
- Hey, kid.
I'm gonna go kill your sister.
[growls]
- [gasps]
- Chucky, when did you
become a killer?
- Let me tell you the story
of my first time.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- I helped.
- You got guts, kid.
I'll give you that.
[eerie music]
♪
[sirens wailing]
- Battalion 12, fire is
across the mansion right now.
It can change, but
it's nowhere near contained.
♪
- Copy that, Battalion 12.
I'll work on getting
a secondary battalion
out your way,
along with a transport wagon.
An ambulance is on its way
as well.
[sirens wailing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[sinister music]
♪
[elevator dings]
- I'm very sorry
to have to tell you this...
- No! No.
[sobbing]
- [screams]
[sobbing continues]
♪
[somber music]
[soft indistinct chatter]
[chatter loudens]
- Anybody tell us
how long he has to be in here?
Huh? Does anybody know?
♪
I would just like to know
how long my son
is going to be here.
- Shortness of breath? No?
- No, I'm okay.
- Okay.
- Just my throat's
a little scratchy.
[gentle music]
- [sighs]
♪
[monitors beeping,
respirator hissing]
[ominous music]
♪
- Jake!
- [gasps]
- You're here.
- Chucky did it.
Did he kill your dad too?
[gasps]
Holy shit!
I mean, fuck.
- Yeah.
- How?
- I don't know.
- Well, when did you find out?
- Talent show.
- So that was him talking?
For real talking?
- Yeah.
- What a dick.
- Where is he?
- Well, last time I saw him,
he was in my room,
surrounded by fire,
after he tried to kill me.
- But you didn't see him die?
- No, but I mean,
half the house burned down--
- No, it doesn't matter.
Okay, I have to find him
and make sure he's dead,
'cause if he's not,
he's gonna
come after you again.
- Why?
Jake,
why is your doll
coming after me?
- 'Cause I--I told him to.
- You gave that thing
to my sister.
You knew what he was and you
put him in my house anyway.
- I didn't mean--
- You told him to hurt me.
Jake, did you tell him
to kill me?
Oh, you freak!
- Lexy, I--
- You're so dead.
- Where are you going?
- Get off of me.
- You can't tell anyone.
- Watch me.
- Look, anyone who's
told the truth about Chucky
has either been put away
or worse.
Mostly worse.
No one's gonna believe you.
It's just us.
I know you're pissed me right
now, but you're still alive--
- Oliver isn't.
- What?
- He's dead.
He died in the fire.
A fire that wouldn't
have even happened
if you didn't
send that thing after me.
Maybe I'm still alive,
but that doesn't mean
you didn't kill anybody
at that party.
Stay the hell away from me.
- Lexy.
[solemn music]
♪
[sighs]
- Sorry.
How you feeling?
- Like a chimney.
- Well, drink that down.
- Hey. I'm okay, Mom.
- I know.
You're a very lucky boy.
- I shouldn't have gone
to Lexy's without telling you.
- No, you shouldn't have.
- [sighs]
I don't mean to make you worry
all the time.
- There's not much
you can do about that.
I'm a mom.
I'll be worried
the rest of my life.
- Sounds awful.
- It is awful.
But it has its perks.
- Did you talk
to Oliver's parents?
- Who else was at the party?
- The usuals.
- Jake?
- No. No, he didn't come.
- What about Jake's doll?
- Chucky?
- Yeah.
- What about it?
- Well, did you see it
at Lexy's?
- Yeah, actually. Why?
- How did it get there?
- I think he gave it
to Lexy's sister or something.
- Why would he do that?
- I don't know.
He's nice?
- You sure he wasn't there?
- Yes, I'm sure.
Are you saying that Jake
started the fire?
Because--
- This isn't about the fire.
- Then what?
- Honey,
Oliver didn't die in the fire.
Someone killed him.
♪
[playful spooky music]
[monitors beeping]
- We're gonna go ahead
and check
her oxygen saturation levels.
We just need
a little space to work.
- Okay.
Have you eaten anything?
- No.
- Okay. Let's go.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[somber music]
♪
- Is Caroline gonna be okay?
- Suddenly you care about your
little sister's well-being?
That's funny.
- Why is it funny?
- Do you have any idea
what you've done, Alexandra?
Can you even grasp it?
- I told you that--
- Your sister's in the ICU,
a boy is dead,
and our house--
which, by the way,
is an historic landmark
that belongs to the city--
is partially destroyed
all because
you decided to throw a party
and set the place on fire.
- No, I didn't. Dad--
- No, Lexy.
Your mother's right.
- No, she's not.
Look, none of this is my fault.
Jake--
- Jake?
Lexy, Jake wasn't even there.
Haven't you tortured
that poor boy enough?
- Mom--
- [breathing heavily]
[chuckles darkly]
[eerie music]
♪
[footsteps tapping]
- Look, baby.
- Hey.
- I found your ball.
- How's Junior doing?
- I--I think he's okay.
How are you?
- No permanent damage.
Just gonna be stuck with this
sexy smoker voice for a while.
My phone got it worse than me.
Dropped it
running out of the house.
Camera's busted.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey, it's okay.
I can still use it.
- No, I mean the fire, Oliver.
It must have been so scary.
- Yeah, it was.
I was kind of bummed
you weren't there at first,
but I'm just glad you're safe.
Hey, can I tell you something?
- Yeah, of course.
- I'm not really supposed to.
No one knows yet,
but I can't not tell anyone,
and I know
you won't say anything.
Oliver was stabbed to death.
[dark music]
During the fire
or right before.
I mean, someone murdered him.
- Really?
- My mom told me.
- Do--do they know
who did it?
- No clue.
Could have been an intruder
who snuck in
or someone at the party.
Either way, there's a killer
out there right now
running around Hackensack.
I don't mean to freak you out.
- Oh, no. No.
You--you don't freak me out.
- My mom also asked
about your doll.
- What about him?
- She asked
if I saw it at the party.
You gave it
to Lexy's sister, right?
- Right.
- I don't know why she asked.
Just be careful
around her, okay?
She has these ideas about you.
She just doesn't know you
like I do.
See ya.
- See ya.
♪
- Can't stop thinking
about the Haydens.
Can you imagine going out
of town and getting that call?
- I know.
- It really puts things
in perspective.
- [sighs]
- Come on.
- Life's so short, sweetheart.
It just feels silly to go on
pretending like everything's
okay when it's not.
- Damn it!
What?
- Hi there, friends.
- How's Caroline doing?
- Oh, she's--she's stabilized,
but they're keeping her
on the ventilator for now.
- She'll pull through.
She's a tough little girl.
- Yeah.
How's--how's Junior?
- He's okay.
- He's not okay.
Doctors say he can't run
for at least a month
thanks to the damage
to his lungs.
- Now's not the time
to have this conversation.
- No, Bree, it's fine.
He has every right
to be upset.
This was a horrible,
tragic accident.
- Accident?
You let Lexy have free rein
for whatever the hell
she wants.
It was a matter of time before
something like this happened.
- We don't know
how the fire started.
- Oh, Jesus.
- There were a lot of kids
there, including your son.
- Yes, but Junior would never
be that irresponsible.
- Oh, no.
I didn't say he did anything.
But he has been under
a lot of pressure lately.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You put that much stress
on a kid,
sometimes he acts out.
- You know what? Fuck you.
- Hey, what's going on?
- I don't appreciate that.
- Oh, you don't appreciate?
Well, I apologize.
- I don't deserve this, okay?
My daughter
is in the ICU right now.
- And the Haydens' son is dead
thanks to your negligence.
- Oh, my.
- None of you knew
where your kids were,
but somehow,
I'm the negligent one?
I'm the only bad parent here?
- Jesus, Michelle.
Nobody's saying that.
- Her kid's
the one with that podcast.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
But it's just
a little disturbing
for a kid to be so obsessed
with crime.
- Are you gonna blame
everybody but yourselves?
- Just back off
a second, okay?
- Oh, shit.
Look who decided to show up.
You know, to be considered
a stay-at-home dad,
you gotta actually
parent your kids.
- Forcing your son
to compete so you can
relive your glory days,
it's not parenting, Logan.
It's pathetic.
- Hey! Hey, hey!
- That's assault.
Bree, get him.
Arrest him!
- Can we all just talk?
- No, no.
I want to press charges.
- Michelle.
- I'd like
to press charges too.
- Everybody shut up!
The medical examiner
has determined
the cause of death
for Oliver Hayden.
Severe blood loss as a result
of multiple stab wounds.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- His death has been ruled
a homicide.
I'm gonna need you
to make yourselves
and your children available
for questioning.
Don't stray too far.
- Oh, my God.
- Wake up.
- What's wrong?
Did something happen?
- Yeah, a psycho kid
told a little ginger doll
to murder me.
- So you're here
to yell at me some more?
- No.
I don't really want
to spend the rest of my life
being scared
of getting killed by a toy.
Since no one else
will believe me,
I'm stuck with you.
So what do we do?
- I say we go back
to your house,
see if he's still there.
- Fine.
It's not like my parents
will realize I'm gone anyway.
God, I need a shower.
- ♪ Lose control
[industrial rock music]
♪
- Wait.
- ♪ Here we go, here we go
- Ready?
- ♪ We're gonna lose control
- ♪ Tear it down,
tear it apart ♪
- ♪ We're gonna lose control
- ♪ Oh, we can't get enough
- ♪ Let go, let go
and lose control ♪
[dramatic music]
- What's it called again?
- Bronchoscopy.
They stick a little camera
down your throat,
take a look at your lungs.
- It's okay, Jun-Jun.
You're not gonna feel anything.
- I know.
- Junior, you like
cross-country, right?
- What?
- You're not just doing it
'cause I want you to?
- No. No.
- 'Cause I wouldn't want that.
You gotta do it
'cause you love it.
I wanna hear it.
- I love cross-country.
- Attaboy.
This is just a little setback.
I'm gonna do whatever it takes
to get you back in there, okay?
I promise.
- Okey dokey.
This shouldn't take very long.
If you don't mind
waiting outside,
I'll let you know
when we're done, okay?
- Okay. Thank you, Doctor.
You'll be okay.
- We'll be right outside,
okay, buddy?
- All right, Junior,
I'm just gonna have you
open up your mouth.
This is gonna numb your throat.
- Okay.
- Perfect.
- All right,
you're gonna feel funny
in a few seconds, okay, Junior?
- Okay.
♪
♪ See the people
walking down the street ♪
♪ Fall in line
just watching all their feet ♪
♪ They don't know
where they want to go ♪
♪ But they're walking in time
♪ They got the beat,
they got the beat ♪
- ♪ We got the beat
- ♪ Everybody
get on your feet ♪
- ♪ We got the beat
- ♪ We know you can dance
to the beat ♪
- [breathing heavily]
- ♪ Jump back
- You're okay.
- ♪ Round
and round and round ♪
♪ Whoo, we got the beat
- ♪ We got the beat
♪ We got the beat
- ♪ We got the beat,
we got the beat ♪
♪ We got the beat
[gentle music]
♪
- "After the brutal murder
of his parents
"at the hands
of an unknown assailant,
Charles Lee Ray was placed in
a boys' home in South Jersey."
- "The boys on the island
vary, of course,
"in numbers according
as they get killed and so on.
"And as they seem
to be growing up,
"which is against the rules,
Peter thins them out."
- You are so good
with kids, Charles.
How's the story, boys?
- Fucking fantastic.
- Language, young man.
Where did you learn that?
Well, I don't want
to hear it again, understood?
[ominous music]
- Hey, Miss Janie.
- Watch out!
You little brat.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
- Sorry.
Hey!
This is my only pair.
- [mockingly]
Sorry.
- "Charles Lee Ray spent
a few relatively quiet years
"in the boys' home
"until another
violent incident
changed the trajectory
of his life."
- Is everyone ready?
all: Yeah!
- Weapons, sound and true?
- Wait, wait, wait.
Don't you need a sword?
- Don't worry.
I've got it covered.
Come on, boys, let's get
that scoundrel, Captain Hook.
Onward to Neverland!
[all cheer]
[all groan]
- Uh, are we there yet?
- Come on.
Can we stop, man?
We're tired.
- We're close now.
Look.
There.
Come.
Our adventure is at hand.
all: Yeah!
[distorted music]
♪
- [shakily]
Who's that?
- It's Captain Hook.
We got him.
[music swells]
[all scream]
♪
You got guts, kid.
[chuckles darkly]
[door creaks]
[sinister music]
♪
- Shit.
- Oh, my God.
Zoloft?
- Effexor.
- Anxiety or depression?
- Both.
You okay?
- Seriously?
Okay, the last place I saw him
was up in my room.
- All right.
Let's go.
- What are you waiting for?
- I don't know
where your room is.
- I'll give you directions.
Just go.
- All right.
[step creaks]
- Go!
- Shit.
[tense music]
♪
[rattling]
- Jake.
- What?
- Just be careful.
- Okay.
You okay?
- Stop asking me that.
- I'm just trying to be nice.
- But you're not nice, Jake.
All of this happened
because of you.
You happy now?
- I'm not happy.
I can't remember
the last time I was.
- Me neither.
[wood snaps]
[gasps]
[debris crumbling]
Shit!
- Come on.
- Did you really
want me to die?
Did it really get that bad?
- Yeah, it did.
- Why didn't you
just say something?
- Because I didn't think
it would make a difference.
- But I'm not a mind reader.
How was I supposed to know
how upset you were?
- Well, usually when
you treat people like shit,
they get upset.
- But you didn't
just get upset.
You wanted to kill me.
- I didn't know
what else to do, all right?
- So you went straight
to murder?
- You dressed up as my dead dad
in front of everyone.
- I know, but still,
there's gotta be something
really wrong with you
to want to kill someone--
- But I didn't want
to kill somebody, all right?
I wanted to kill you.
- Jake.
- Because you're a bad person.
You treat everyone around you
like they're nothing
and you just expect them
to take it.
- Stop it!
- I wanted you to die
but not because there's
something wrong with me.
It's because
you fucking deserved it!
- [screams]
- Lexy!
- [screaming]
Jake.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- [chuckles darkly]
- Chucky?
- [screams]
- It's the easiest thing
in the world, Jake.
Just let go.
This ain't a coincidence, Jake.
This is a crossroads.
This is life giving you
a second chance
to be the man
you know you wanna be.
Not the scared little pussy
she tried to make you.
- Jake!
- Just let go.
The world's gonna be better off
without her.
Just one less little vicious
Karen on training wheels.
- Please. Please.
- Let go.
Then you could go
break the news to Junior,
and everybody will get
to see him cry.
[chuckles darkly]
You can do it, Jake.
Just let go.
- Jake! Jake, please!
- No, I'm not like you, Chucky.
I'm not a killer.
[both grunting]
- You're pathetic, Jake!
I'll do it myself, then.
[grunting]
- Please.
- [laughing darkly]
♪
- Police.
This is Detective Peyton.
Anyone here?
- We're up here.
- You're not allowed in here.
- I live here.
- Not now, you don't.
It's gonna take weeks
to clean this mess up.
What in the--
Is this your sister's doll?
Your dad asked me
to bring it back for her.
Ugly fucking doll,
if you ask me.
- No, don't!
- No!
- He will fuck you up.
- Let's go, you two.
- No!
- No, don't!
- Shit.
[heartbeat thumping]
- Look, please, I promise you.
You do not want to do this.
- Shut up!
[tense music]
♪
- Wait, wait. No.
- No, no.
- Just wait here.
- Hey.
[car beeps]
No!
- Wait.
- Hey!
- Stop!
- Let us out.
Let us out!
- Hey!
[car beeps]
Thank you.
- Not so fast.
I need a word, in private.
- Go get him.
- Thanks for not letting go.
- Let's go.
[elevator dings]
[ominous music]
♪
- Our little secret, okay?
[dramatic musical sting]
[tense music]
♪
- Excuse me. Hi.
Has anyone been in here
in the last two minutes?
I don't know, maybe
brought a doll for my sister?
- No, I haven't seen anyone.
- Okay. Thank you.
[sirens wailing]
[monitors beeping]
[dramatic musical sting]
- Lexy.
- [gasps]
Don't do that.
- Hey, have you seen Jake?
- Your mom's got him.
- Shit. Okay.
- Wait. Hold on.
What's up?
- I need to talk to him.
I found out some stuff
about his doll.
- His doll?
What is it?
- It'll sound crazy.
- Devon, just tell me.
- Come back to my room.
We can talk there.
- Okay.
- [sighs]
[monitors beeping]
[quirky music]
♪
- [laughs softly]
[shouts]
[flesh squelches]
- [groaning]
Oh, God.
[groans]
[spine crunches]
I can't move.
- That's because
I hit your spinal cord.
[spooky rock music]
♪
[dramatic musical sting]
You might feel a little prick.
[shouts]
- [groans]
- Sorry, asshole,
but I just couldn't take it
for one more second.
From the minute
I first saw you, you know,
I couldn't stand
your fucking face.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm just projecting.
Time for another cocktail.
Let's make it a double.
[grunting]
- [groaning]
[sinister music]
♪
[laughing darkly]
God, I love hospitals.
- Where could he be?
[indistinct radio chatter]
[eerie music]
♪
- What?
- Shh.
It's a gift.
Promise me that you
won't tell a soul.
- I cross my heart
and hope to die.
[upbeat country music]
♪
- ♪ I need song,
I need love ♪
♪ I don't need the things
people tell me I need ♪
♪ I need you, I need me
♪ The morning to tell me
what a great day it'll be ♪
♪
- What are you doing up?
Andy Caputo, go to sleep.
- ♪ I don't need a tie
and shirt on ♪
♪ Just something simple
to keep a smile on ♪
♪ I think our time
can get better that way ♪
♪ Ah
♪
[indistinct radio chatter]
- Charles Lee Ray, the famous
serial killer from Hackensack.
- Who?
- Wow. Do you read anything
other than "Teen Vogue"?
Well, anyways, Charles Lee Ray
was a serial killer
who died in the '80s.
I mean, He terrorized Chicago
for years. Prolific.
They call him
the Lakeshore Strangler,
but he never really
strangled anyone.
I mean, he was more of, like,
a mangler or a butcher--
- Devon, the point.
- Fine.
Do you know the website
Urban Legend: Fact or Fiction?
- Do I look like a nerd?
- Well, there's this urban
legend about Charles Lee Ray.
It's crazy, but who knows?
Maybe not.
It's about a Good Guy doll.
- Like Chucky.
- Exactly.
You see, Charles Lee Ray
was shot and killed
in a toy store in Chicago,
but supposedly,
right before he died,
he transferred his soul
to a Good Guy doll,
and that doll is still
out there killing, supposedly.
- It's not a legend.
You have to believe me.
Chucky is alive.
- Come on.
- No, no.
I know it sounds crazy, but...
it's not just alive.
He is trying to kill us.
- You see my problem?
You don't even have an alibi.
I'm sorry.
This must be very hard.
I just have
a few more questions.
- And then we'll be done?
- Yeah.
Tell me about Oliver.
I heard
there were some problems
at his Halloween party.
Was he bullying you?
- No.
- Do you know
how serious this is, Jake?
I can actually help you,
but only once
you start telling the truth.
So tell me, Jake.
What do you know
about Oliver's death?
- I don't know.
But it's not what you think.
- Well, tell me
what I should think.
And what about your father?
Was he hitting you?
- I--I don't understand
what you're trying to ask.
- Did you need your dad
to just stop hitting you
and you didn't know
what else to do?
And Oliver, did you need him
to just stop bullying you?
- I didn't do anything.
I swear.
- Then who did?
Because for some reason,
all roads lead back to you.
Or more precisely,
to your doll.
- My doll?
- Chucky.
He's been
at multiple crime scenes now.
Do you know why that might be?
- I said I didn't do anything.
- Then who did it?
Tell me, Jake.
Tell me,
and this can all be over.
- It...
It was...
It--it was...
[eerie music]
[monitors beeping rapidly]
It--
[alarms blaring]
- Code White.
Resuscitation teams and defib,
priority one.
- Hey!
- Caroline. Hey.
- Oh, my God!
- We need help in here!
- Please take a step back
so we can help your daughter.
- Oh, my God.
Please hurry.
[frantic music]
- Oh, my God.
- Tell us what's happening.
- Please hurry!
- Why isn't there a signal?
- Oh, my God.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- Help her!
- What's going on?
- Tell us what's happening.
- Please hurry.
- Just let the doctors
do their job.
That's the best thing you can
do for your sister right now.
- [gasps]
[blood rippling]
[dark music]
♪
[screams]
[music swells]
- [screams]
- Doctor!
- Oh, my God!
[wailing]
♪
[sinister music]