narrator: Previously
on fucking "Chucky."
- Nica,
sometimes when we're together,
you looking at me--
and I know it's you.
It's not Chucky.
And I live for those moments.
[muffled gasp]
[tense music]
- Okay, so there's just
one left, right?
One doll left.
Open the fucking door!
Shit.
- Our charity matinee,
"Frankenstein,"
will still take place tomorrow
as planned.
- Mom or mayor?
- Excuse me?
- Choose. Because Lexy didn't
sign up for all of this,
and neither did I.
- Why is someone random guy
delivering a Good Guy doll
to Charles Lee Ray's old house?
- Devon's at
Charles Lee Ray's house.
♪
[panting]
My name's Devon, by the way.
- What's yours?
- It's Chucky.
- I love you.
I just want to protect you.
- It's over.
We're done.
My dad kissed some lady
at the wake.
My mom's wake.
Real classy, Dad.
- No wonder she jumped.
- Shut your goddamn mouth!
♪
- She killed herself
because of you.
♪
- Kid, thank you!
Finally!
You have no idea
how hard it's been
getting one
of you little shits
to step up and play.
[laugh menacingly]
♪
[cocks gun]
Now, the real fun can start.
[doorbell chimes]
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Shit.
- Who is he?
- Someone who never had
the balls to be one of us.
- Or the height.
Dude's almost as short as you.
- I know, right?
[laughs]
♪
[doorbell chimes]
What do we do?
What do you think?
♪
I'm looking for Jake Wheeler.
- And you are?
- A friend.
- Jake's sure got
a lot of new friends.
Is he here?
Nope.
What about your mother?
♪
- She died.
- She died? How?
- Not that it's any
of your business,
but she killed herself.
Jesus.
Well, is your dad home?
- Yeah, actually, he is.
This way.
♪
So how do you know Jake?
- We met in an online
chat group.
For Good Guy doll collectors.
Said he has one for sale.
- I didn't know he was
getting rid of Chucky.
- Is Chucky here?
I'd love to take a look at him.
I mean,
if he's as mint as Jake says.
- I don't think
you'll be disappointed.
♪
Huh.
He was just here.
♪
- Your dad or the doll?
- Both, actually.
Uh...
Dad?
♪
My mistake.
I guess he went out.
- With the doll?
- I guess.
♪
Where'd he go, your dad?
- Probably out
with his girlfriend.
Mm-hmm.
[thump in another room]
♪
- You don't mind if I take
a quick look around, do you?
just in case he's here?
The doll, I mean.
I don't mind.
♪
[tense musical crescendo]
- Look, I'm sorry.
I know how weird this is.
What's your name?
- Junior.
I'm Jake's cousin.
Andy.
You said your dad
went out with his girlfriend.
You really think
he brought the doll with him?
- I'd rather not think
about that at all. Thanks.
Why don't we call him?
♪
What, now?
- Yeah.
Let's try his cell.
- And ask if he has Chucky?
- Humor me, okay?
♪
[phone line trilling]
[phone ringing
in another room]
♪
[phone ringing]
You having a bath?
I was about to.
[phone ringing]
♪
[chuckles]
He always leaves it.
♪
[water gurgles]
Be careful.
It's freezing.
♪
Do you have any idea where
your father and his girlfriend
may have gone?
Nope.
- What about Jake?
Where's he tonight?
- Sorry.
I have no idea.
Lot going on.
I'll let myself out.
♪
But if you see Jake,
tell him to call me.
And Junior, if you see
the doll, stay away from him.
Okay?
♪
[dramatic music]
[grunts]
I knew he'd never look in here.
The guy's got serious issues.
♪
- Why didn't you kill him?
- He had a gun.
I hate guns.
They're like my Achilles heel.
Along with axes, fire,
and those big,
industrial-size fans.
[shudders]
I just wanted to fuck with him.
I got other plans
for Andy Barclay.
What'd you do with my dad?
Down the laundry chute.
[chuckles]
You hungry?
♪
[playful spooky music]
[suspenseful music]
♪
- He doesn't exactly need
help killing people.
No, he doesn't.
- So why bother?
What's he getting out of it?
Seriously, why has Chucky
been trying to get one of us
to kill somebody?
What would that accomplish?
- Maybe it's part
of some voodoo spell.
Maybe it has something to do
with that doll you got
at the bus station.
I left it in the kitchen.
[whistling]
♪
[screams]
[tense dramatic music]
[laughs]
♪
[gasps]
Here's Chucky!
[gunshot]
♪
[gunfire continuing]
- Who are you?
- I'm Kyle. I'm with Andy.
[suspenseful music]
- Okay, how many
freaking Chuckys are there?
- That's a good
freaking question.
We need to kill all of them.
- We need to find Devon first.
- Who's Devon?
His boyfriend.
- He's not my--
he's at Chucky's old house.
Okay.
Well, trust me, if we're going
into the lion's den,
we're gonna need help,
and we're gonna need Andy.
And we're gonna need
a lot of coffee.
♪
- Where's Andy?
- Don't worry, he's on his way.
Okay, so Chucky can, like,
splinter himself
into other dolls?
Only Good Guy dolls.
It has to be
an identical vessel.
Except for Nica.
- Who's Nica?
- Poor girl at the asylum.
Chucky possessed her, too.
I know.
Whack. [scoffs]
Fucking voodoo, man.
A few weeks ago,
there were three dolls.
Jake, we thought
you had the last one.
But here's the thing.
If Chucky can corrupt
an innocent,
if he can get just one kid
to kill someone,
he can make an entire army.
Either of you kill
anyone lately?
♪
- Will you please
just let it go?
Somewhere here in Hackensack,
I fear some poor kid
is Chucky's friend to the end.
- It's not Devon.
Devon's fine.
And they've probably
got him as bait,
so what are we waiting for?
- Don't worry.
I have a plan.
♪
I'm really sorry.
I feel terrible.
But Andy would kill me if
I let anything happen to you.
This is all I could think of
to keep you safe.
♪
No.
- I promise to do everything
I can to save your friend.
Everything's gonna be okay.
And now...
you are, too.
♪
[door opens]
- [gasps]
Hi, honey! I'm home!
Nica?
Ooh, where did Nica go?
Where is she?
Oh, I see a little foot.
Ha!
- [gasps]
- [laughing] That was fun!
Please don't hurt me.
- One thing you should know
about me, Nica.
I would never, ever hurt you.
- No, please.
I'm scared of needles.
- Don't be scared.
It's just a little.
You won't feel anything.
- [grunts]
- [shouts]
♪
- Oh, I'm disappointed in you,
Tiff.
♪
[cackles]
Here we are again, huh?
This will make--how many times
have I killed you?
- [stammers]
- Is it three?
No, four. Four, if you count
human bodies and doll bodies.
This--this will be
the last time, babe.
I promise.
- You can't kill me, Chucky!
You need me!
You need me,
or the plan won't work!
♪
Think about it.
- Oh, thinking is for losers.
- [screams]
Think again.
♪
She's right, bro.
We need her.
And I'm kind of used
to having her around.
Sweetface.
Help her up.
Yeah, help me up, asshole.
- [chuckles]
Get up.
Fuck you, Chucky.
Thank you, Chucky.
Come to Mama, come to Mama!
- Who's a good little Good Guy?
- [giggling]
Who's a good little Good Guy?
Aww!
- Looking good, doll.
- [giggles]
You're not looking so bad
yourself, Sweetface.
Mwah!
[chuckles]
- So where are they?
- They're right downstairs.
- Follow me.
- Okey-doke.
- Come into my inner sanctum.
[chuckles]
Watch your step. We wouldn't
want to have any accidents.
[cackling softly]
[dramatic music]
Chucky, it worked.
♪
- Thanks to my pal here,
Mr. Patricide.
Proud of him.
Now, he's gonna do his friend.
- That's you.
[chuckles]
♪
You want me to kill Devon?
- Not yet.
He could still be useful.
Good thinking.
- Are you ready to meet
the troops, Chucky?
[suspenseful music]
[chuckles]
♪
- Pretty soon, the good guys
are gonna come for him,
and then, we're gonna
party like it's 1999.
[laughter]
What does that mean?
We're gonna fuck 'em up.
- Oh.
- And then, vaya con Dios.
Kill 'em all.
[chuckles]
Any questions?
Um, uh...
is there an age limit?
On potential victims?
Good question.
No babies.
We're not savages.
And they make better stooges
anyway.
Anyone else?
Uh, yeah.
Could you define "baby"?
I mean, they can get pretty
wily once they start walking.
- Well, let's just say nobody
under the age of five or six.
Fair enough?
What about twins?
Those freaks
will gang up on you.
- I mean, two against one?
That's not a fair fight.
Am I right?
♪
[cackling]
[ominous music]
♪
[all cackling]
- See you tomorrow night
at the theater.
- Don't be late.
- You got it.
All right.
♪
[rock music playing on stereo]
- No cookies
for bad little boys.
[chuckles]
There you go, Sweetface.
- Don't get me started
on Andy Barclay, bro.
You should have seen
the look on his face
when I whacked his babysitter.
[laughter]
- Chucky!
We did it!
- We--
- [laughing]
- Chucky, Chucky,
Chucky, Chucky,
- In a minute.
- Ah, Jesus Christ, huh?
So what's all this been like?
- You wouldn't believe the
amount of tail I get like this.
- Fuck.
[laughter]
Dick, too.
♪
[chuckles]
- You know, Chucky, you really
need to get over yourself.
You are the most
self-involved man
I have ever met
in my entire life.
- Are you talking to me?
- Or me?
Well, strictly speaking,
neither one of you
is a man at all.
A real man would know
how to treat a lady!
♪
[tense music]
- But I don't see no lady.
[cackles]
- [shouts]
- Oh!
♪
Oh, no.
[yelps]
No!
- Oh, shit.
- Please.
- At least she treats me
with a little respect.
- Okay. Tiff, you're right.
I'm sorry.
And maybe I should
just get over myself.
And sometimes that takes
real sacrifice.
♪
Kill her.
- No! No! No, no, please!
Please!
I'm sorry?
- You know what
that does to me.
[cackling]
- Chucky,
she's a part of you, too!
- Plenty of me
to go around nowadays.
There's 72 more of me
on that truck.
Now kill the bitch.
- [sobbing] Okay, Chucky.
I'll do it for you.
But I don't want to do it.
- Who is it you're afraid
of losing, Tiff?
Me or her?
♪
- Please! Please!
Please! Please! Please!
Junior, do it.
♪
- [sobbing]
I'm sorry, Chucky.
[sobbing]
I'm sorry.
♪
[tense music building]
Chucky, I mean, who is she?
She's your goddamn trophy.
Now do her,
or I'll do the three of ya!
♪
[both screaming]
[panting]
[laughs]
You fucking hag!
You're upside-down.
[laughing]
Back off, Junior!
Who are you gonna trust to get
you out of this shithole town
before they find
your father's corpse?
Me?
Or that?
- [grunts]
- [laughing deliriously]
[dramatic music]
♪
I'm done with you, Chucky!
I'm done with your petty shit
and your massive ego
and your tiny fucking dick!
[gasps]
Tell me something, Sweetface.
Did you ever wonder
how those cops found you
that night in Chicago?
[suspenseful music]
We never kill anybody
together anymore.
♪
Where the hell
do you think you're going?
Going out.
♪
Don't wait up for me, Red.
Eh?
[blows smooch]
♪
- I'd like to speak to
Detective Mike Norris, please.
I have some information
on the Lakeshore Strangler.
- I'm gonna get you for it!
- [laughing]
- I'm gonna get you!
- One of me's gonna get you!
No matter what!
- You'll do no such thing.
You need me, Chucky.
Besides, it's like
my mother always said.
If you love somebody,
set them free.
Well, I'm setting us
both free, Chucky.
Vaya con Dios!
See you in hell!
[grunts and groans]
- Mic drop.
[giggles]
All right, Junior, look alive.
Make yourself useful.
I'm gonna make her
go nighty-night. [chuckles]
- No! Tiffany, stop!
Please don't! Tiffany, don't!
- [gasps]
- [laughing]
So noisy.
All right.
Here, honey.
Help me with your auntie, Nica.
I have more important
things to do.
[humming to self]
- What's that?
- Isn't it cute?
My darling Glenda
gave it to me.
They have exquisite taste.
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music]
♪
A little something to welcome
Andy Barclay with a bang.
[chuckles]
♪
All right.
You took one?
Can I keep him?
[sighs]
Okay, you can keep him.
But you gotta
clean up the mess.
[laughs]
[remote beeps]
♪
[laughs]
[laughter continuing]
♪
Get up!
Kill the twink.
[dramatic ominous music]
♪
No!
[crunching impacts]
♪
[suspenseful music]
Andy.
The front door's
booby-trapped.
Yeah, I figured.
- They delivered
the dolls in a truck.
Andy, they're all alive.
- Just get out.
Now.
♪
Another goddamn head.
Why not?
♪
[lighter clicks]
Where are the dolls, Chucky?
- I'm not telling you,
short stack,
so don't even bother.
- Oh, you're gonna tell me,
all right.
Where the fuck are you?
I'm everywhere.
Andy?
♪
- [in child's voice]
Help me! Please, help!
♪
Andy?
[dramatic music]
Kyle, no!
♪
[device beeps]
[sparse ominous music]
♪
Lexy, wake up.
Wake up.
♪
- [gasps]
The bitch drugged us.
- [sighs]
How long were we asleep?
♪
- Mom sent like 100 texts
from the hotel.
She's actually
worried about me.
- Devon's still
at Charles Lee Ray's old house.
Jake.
What?
Check your alerts.
♪
- No.
No, not Devon.
[Jeremy Zucker's
"You Were Good to Me"]
Jake, I'm so sorry.
♪
- ♪ Lying isn't better
than silence ♪
♪
♪ Floating
♪ But I feel like I'm dyin'
♪
together: ♪ Still,
no matter where I go ♪
♪ At the end of every road
♪ You were good to me
♪
♪ You were good to me, yeah
♪ I know it's easier to run
♪ After everything I've done
Jake?
- Devon.
I thought you were dead.
- ♪ And I'm so used
to letting go ♪
- I was looking
for you everywhere.
- ♪ But I don't wanna
be alone, oh ♪
♪ You were good to me
♪
[chuckles]
- So what happened?
- That woman.
She was at Bree's wake.
She planted a bomb.
What about Andy and Kyle?
I got out, but...
they were both inside.
[suspenseful music]
♪
We're on our own.
Again.
Kyle said that
Chucky needs to convince
an innocent to kill somebody.
If he does, he'll have an army.
But who's the innocent?
And who did they kill?
He killed his dad.
- Who?
- Junior.
Oh, shit.
- There was a room
full of Chuckys,
living ones, at the house.
There was dozens of them.
But they took them away
in a truck.
- Those dolls
could be anywhere.
♪
The mayor's benefit is today.
Some fundraiser
for children's hospitals.
- Chucky's gonna hit
the benefit.
We gotta get to the theater.
[applause
and shutters clicking]
I'd like to thank all of you
for coming
to this important event,
a benefit not only
for the children of Hackensack,
but for children in need
all over the USA!
[laughs]
[audience murmurs]
What better way to celebrate
the occasion
than to announce the identity
of our special
celebrity guest--
and I know this will come
as a wonderful surprise--
Oscar-nominated actress
and professional poker player,
Jennifer Tilly!
- [cheers and applause]
- Hi! [laughs]
Hello, Hackensack.
Hello!
Lexy!
[tense music]
Help me.
- Hello!
You look ravishing.
Thank you for coming.
Oh, please, sit down.
I love you all.
[indistinct chatter]
- Junior?
- Lexy!
♪
- Every Better Days hospital
in the country
will receive a priceless gift
from her personal collection...
of vintage Good Guy dolls!
[laughs]
- "Hi. I'm Chucky. Wanna play?"
That's right.
72 authentic Good Guy dolls
that will be transported
immediately after the show
to Teterboro Airport,
and from there to needful
children from coast to coast.
Let's hear it
for Ms. Jennifer Tilly! Whoo!
Thank you.
- Chucky!
I want Chucky!
- Okay. So let's all go watch
"Frankenstein," all right?
- Yay!
- Let's go.
- Chucky wants to watch
"Frankenstein" too!
- No, sweetheart,
those are for sick children
who need someone
to take care of them.
- Well, I'm sure one measly,
little, sick child
can take care of himself.
Here, sweetheart.
Your very own Good Guy doll.
Be careful, you two.
Don't get into
too much trouble.
[suspenseful music]
♪
Lexy!
Junior?
♪
[metallic clanking]
- Look, it's moving.
[thunder booms]
It's moving.
It's alive!
Junior?
- It's alive, it's alive,
it's alive, it's alive!
What did you do to Junior?
In the name of God!
See for yourself.
- Now I know what
it feels like to be God!
[thunder booming]
♪
I'm Maria.
Will you play with me?
See how mine floats?
[gasps]
[chuckles]
This is my favorite part.
- No, you're hurting me!
No!
[laughing loudly]
[gasps]
Hi.
Thank you.
[tense music]
[the Monster gasps]
♪
- Chucky?
Where are you going?
- I'm gonna get some popcorn.
- Oh, yeah?
You want some?
♪
[tense music]
[cackles]
♪
Hey.
[chuckling]
♪
Please, Junior.
- I think we should
get back together.
♪
You do?
It's incredible.
What is?
♪
I used to be so afraid.
Afraid to compete,
afraid of my dad.
♪
I was even afraid of you.
- That's--
- But Chucky
changed everything.
♪
How's that?
He taught me how to be a man.
♪
- The brain which was stolen
from my laboratory
was a criminal brain.
What'd I miss?
- After all, it's only
a piece of dead tissue.
- Here you go.
- Only evil can come of it.
Your health will be ruined if
you persist in this madness.
[Michelle chucking]
- I'm astonishingly sane,
Doctor.
- You have created a monster,
and it will destroy you!
♪
Nathan?
[gasps and shudders]
[screaming]
What's going on?
[screams]
[cackling]
[screaming]
[all screaming]
[dramatic music]
♪
[cackling]
- [grunts]
- Ha!
♪
[chuckles]
- One of us, Lexy.
That's who you are.
You're a winner.
And you know what winners say.
Fuck the losers
who can't take a joke.
[audience screaming]
Come with us.
Come with us, and it'll be
better than it ever was before.
You and me.
Together.
♪
I'm not like that.
Bullshit!
You're exactly like that,
and you know it.
You and Junior are made
for each other.
[tense music]
♪
[indistinct chaos]
Caroline.
Hey.
Care?
Devon's gonna get you
out of here,
but you have to hold his hand
the whole time.
- But the movie's not over yet.
- I know. We'll watch it later.
But right now, Devon's
gonna get you out of here.
But what about Daddy?
♪
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music]
♪
[dramatic music]
- He's coming!
Go!
♪
Chucky!
Here I am, asshole!
Come and get me!
You know what, Jake?
Once I hack you to pieces,
the world's gonna forget
all about you.
Eventually,
they're gonna forget the names
of everybody who
died here tonight.
All they'll remember is
the number of people I killed.
My body count.
And they'll remember my name.
And from now on,
when they think of Hackensack,
they won't think
about families,
they won't think about kids
growing up
to be doctors or CEOs
or Instagram influencers.
They won't think about
pathetic losers like you, Jake.
They'll think of Hackensack
as ground zero
for the army of me
that invaded America.
Not if we stop that truck.
Not if I kill you first.
♪
- [knife rips]
- [screams]
[laughs]
♪
[shouts]
[straining]
You're thinking,
"How could a little doll
possibly be so strong?"
Doesn't make any sense!
- You're nothing
against the power
of the great, almighty
Damballa!
[cackles]
♪
Elizabeth!
- I loved you, Junior.
I honestly did.
[soft dramatic music]
Because you were kind,
'cause you were loyal,
'cause you forgave me
every time I screwed up.
I was a bitch.
God, I was such a bitch.
And you were
the sweetest boy ever.
♪
I think I'm gonna be sick.
He's not a boy,
he's a man.
No, Junior, you're a boy.
And you will never be the kind
of man he wants you to be.
[soft tense music]
♪
Kill her now, Junior!
But if you fall...
this time I'll catch you.
I promise.
Bullshit!
Kill her!
Or I will!
[dramatic music]
♪
[Chucky groaning]
Leave her alone.
♪
[groaning]
She's not like us.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
[rasps]
♪
Lexy.
Junior! No! No!
No, Junior, please don't.
Oh, my God.
Tell everyone...I'm sorry.
- [sobbing]
No, no, no.
[the Monster bellowing]
[cackling]
- [tense music]
- [straining]
♪
[screams]
- There he is!
The murderer!
[snarls]
♪
Sacrilege!
You dare defy
the almighty Damballa?
- Yeah. I've been doing
some pushups lately.
[straining]
Look at you now, Chucky.
You're pathetic.
You're nothing.
[groaning]
- You're just
Teddy Ruxpin without a knife.
♪
I don't need that shit.
All I need are my bare hands.
♪
All that anyone's
gonna remember tonight
is that we kicked your ass.
- The world won't believe you.
They never do.
Admit, Jake.
When I killed your dad,
you were thrilled.
I saw it in your eyes.
- I knew he'd never be able
to hurt me again.
And this is how you thank me?
♪
Then I was pissed.
I'm still pissed...
that we never got the chance
to work it out,
or to be friends again.
I was your friend.
I accepted you.
Your father never would have.
Yes, he would have.
If he only got the chance
to meet Devon.
Oh, that is so gay.
♪
[raspy gagging]
[soft dramatic music]
♪
Watch your fucking mouth.
That's my boyfriend
you're talking about.
♪
[dramatic music]
[siren wailing distantly]
[sniffling]
What--what about Daddy?
- Sweetie.
- [crying]
♪
Junior?
- Good job, good job.
The plane leaves at midnight.
Don't be late.
Or I'll kill you.
[laughs]
Just joking.
Actually, I'm not.
♪
[engine grinding]
[engine turns over]
♪
It's Andy.
♪ Limitations lifting
♪ Up from the underground
♪
♪ Can't bury me,
can't cover me up ♪
♪ Can't hold me down
No!
He did it.
♪
[dramatic music stops]
[gun cocks]
- Andy, I don't think
we've had the pleasure.
I'm Tiffany, the doll,
not the person.
It's complicated.
- You're not as cute
as I thought you'd be.
Just drive.
If you know
what's good for you.
♪
[soft dramatic music]
Morning, sleepyhead.
♪
I really like you, Nica.
After all we've been through.
Just one snag.
I couldn't run the risk that
Chucky would sneak back in.
[chuckles]
Who knows what that little shit
would do to me?
[chuckles and sighs]
Sometimes a girl's just
gotta advocate for herself.
♪
So I fixed it.
[chuckles]
♪
[soft ominous music]
[gasping]
[screaming]
♪
[Billie Eilish's
"The End of the World"]
♪ It's a beautiful day
♪
♪ I wish this moment would
stay with the Earth ♪
- Hackensack's motto
is "defendit numerus,"
Latin for "safety in numbers."
But what happens
when we feel outnumbered?
How do we fight back?
How do we stand a chance
against an enemy
who disguises himself
as our friend?
Maybe the best way
is to know the difference
between friend and enemy.
And that means digging
deep enough to find out.
Sometimes bad things happen.
[soft dramatic music]
[sniffles]
We try to stop them.
Sometimes we can't.
♪
If people die,
it's up to us to remember them.
♪
Junior wasn't born
with evil in his heart.
Chucky put it there.
♪
Like he tried to do with me.
But you guys stopped him.
♪
Thanks for saving my life.
♪ If the end of the world
♪ Was near
♪ Where would you choose
to be? ♪
♪ If there was
five more minutes ♪
♪ Of air
♪ Would you panic and hide
♪ Or run for your life
- We can never tell anyone
what really happened.
Not even Ms. Fairchild.
- ♪ If we had
five more minutes ♪
- But the three of us
are enough.
Even though believing
in one another is not easy,
standing together
does not come naturally.
But when we do,
united like that,
that's how we fight back.
That's how we win.
[tense music]
[humming to self]
[classical music]
Oh.
Hello.
I didn't see you there.
I'm Chucky, and I hope
you enjoyed my new show.
You were probably wondering
how it all turned out.
Who lived, who loved, who died.
The eternal questions,
explored by authors
such as Austen,
Shakespeare,
Mancini.
And speaking of who died,
let's review, shall we?
I scored one electrocution...
[bell rings]
one decapitation...
one defenestration...
[bell rings]
one exsanguination...
an explosion...
[bell rings]
an awesome dishwasher mishap,
a neck break,
and one beat down
I'm sure you agree
the victim 100% had coming.
And let us not forget
the good,
old-fashioned stabbings.
[bell ringing repeatedly]
And exactly how did
I kill the cat?
Probably better I leave that
to your imagination.
Making for a grand total
of 21 victims.
Well, at least the kids
got their happy ending.
True love, BFFs,
and a whole bunch
of dead parents!
[cackles]
But what about Andy and Nica,
and that truck full of Chuckys?
What kind of ending
do they get?
And now,
a word from our sponsors.
[playful spooky music]
♪