Previously on "Chucky"...
You knew what he was, and you
put him in my house anyway.
- You can't tell anyone!
- Watch me.
- Do you have any idea
what you've done?
Your sister's in the ICU,
a boy is dead,
and our house
is partially destroyed.
- Who's gonna believe you?
It's just us.
Life's so short, sweetheart.
I just feel silly to go
on pretending like
everything's okay
when it's not.
- Um, how's--how's Junior?
- Doctors he can't run
for at least a month
thanks to the damage
to his lungs.
- We don't know
how the fire started.
- Oliver didn't
die in the fire.
His death has been
ruled a homicide.
All roads lead back to you.
Or more precisely,
to your doll.
- You might feel
a little prick.
- [grunts]
- [screams]
[screaming
- Charles Lee Ray
was a serial killer
who died in the eighties.
Supposedly,
right before he died,
he transferred his soul
into a Good Guy doll.
- You have to believe me.
Chucky is alive.
He is trying to kill us.
[chuckles]
[upbeat synth music playing]
♪
Ooh!
Oh.
Oh!
What the--what--
hey, hey, hey.
[grunts]
What the fuck, Delilah?
- Oh, come on, don't be
such a pussy, huh?
I said give it to me, now.
Not like that.
Fuck off, Dwayne!
Hi.
Want a smoke?
Thanks.
Well...
It's a shame your friend
had to run off like that.
Maybe that's my problem.
Maybe I'm not looking
for a friend.
- Well, maybe
you haven't found one.
Maybe.
Thanks for the light.
Hey, where are you going?
- I'm looking for something
very specific.
[chuckles]
Try me.
You guys are all the same.
- I promise you,
I'm not like anybody else.
[machinery beeping]
[apprehensive music]
♪
Caroline, Caroline.
I like to be hugged.
Where's Chucky?
- Oh, sweetie,
Chucky's had a few boo-boos
and needs to rest up.
Maybe you could see him
in a little bit.
I want Chucky.
I want Chucky!
- Okay, but Chucky looks
a little different now, honey.
[screaming]
[shouts]
Ah.
[mumbling]
[laughing]
Ah, what a fucking rush!
That's the good shit.
[laughing]
God, I love hospitals.
[playful spooky music]
♪
Oh, my baby!
Look at you!
- Excuse me.
- Mm.
Oh, sweet pea.
- Hey Care, um,
where's Chucky?
I was thinking
maybe I could take him
to go get a Snickers
or something.
He must be starving after
taking such good care of you.
- I hate Chucky.
I hate Chucky! He's bad.
Jesus, Lexy.
It's all daisies
until you dampen the mood.
I was just trying to help.
Your mother and I both know
that you want
what's best for Caroline.
I don't know that.
I don't.
But Caroline's decided that
she doesn't like
Chucky anymore,
so we took care of it.
I threw him in the garbage.
[suspenseful music]
♪
Follow me.
This way.
[metallic crash]
Come on.
What are the chances
he burned to death?
Okay.
Ah.
♪
Uh-uh.
No way, this is disgusting.
We have to be sure.
- I don't know what's worse,
stabbed with a butcher knife
or a used needle.
I'll do it. It's my mess.
We're in this together.
- Together.
- That's what I said.
[machinery churns]
- Maybe we--you know,
we could wait for him
to come for us.
He can't stay
down there forever.
He can't?
What exactly are the rules
for supernaturally
possessed dolls?
Hey, guys, I have an idea.
I'll get him out.
Lexy, dig.
Devon, keep watch.
- Uh-uh. No, absolutely not.
There's like seven diseases
down there.
- Did you not just say
"together"?
- You do it.
- Fine by me.
Ready to take him down
if he jumps out?
Ugh, fine.
Just follow my lead.
Oh, shit.
Three, two, one.
Go!
Over there.
Jake, over there.
Eat this, Chucky!
Ugh, so gross!
♪
- A few days ago, you were
probably feeling shock, denial.
That's normal.
All of this is
so much to take in.
At this point, you might be
feeling pain and guilt.
That's still normal.
Your feelings are valid
and expected.
Everyone will heal
at their own speed,
and if you need
anyone to talk to,
please know my door
is always open to you guys.
I, know, probably think
I'm just the biology teacher,
but feelings do start
on the molecular level.
Okay, let's pick back up
where we left off.
Chapter Three:
Biotic and Abiotic Factors.
What are living and non-living
beings of life?
[knock at door]
[inquisitive music]
Why don't you guys get started
on the chapter questions.
I'll be back in just a minute.
♪
- How does he even
move around so fast?
He's a freaking doll.
- Maybe he left Hackensack.
- No.
He's a psycho back
in his hometown on a mission.
He's not leaving.
What do we do about Junior?
We should tell him.
No.
No, we can't
bring him into this.
He doesn't have
the imagination.
It's just the three of us.
Guys, we have to think.
No one's reported any
weird shit since the hospital
so he must be itching
to kill by now.
- Maybe we're going about this
the wrong way.
Maybe it's not where
he's going next, its...
It's who.
Devon,
you know serial killers
better than anyone.
What are you thinking?
- Well, most of the time
it's opportunity,
but sometimes they fixate
on a certain kind--
- What're you guys
talking about?
Nothing.
- Have you guys seen
"Westworld?"
It's a crazy theme park
with these hot robots
and you can, like,
do anything you want to them.
It's really cool.
- I haven't.
Been a little busy.
- Haven't really had time
for that this week.
- Guys, can we get
back to work please?
Less chat, more science.
All right,
who can give me an example
of one of the biotic factors?
Lexy?
[phone buzzes]
Biotic factors? No?
[bell rings]
Devon, this is all my fault.
Oliver would still be alive
if it wasn't for me.
[solemn music]
- Pain's a lot easier if you
let someone feel it with you.
Hey.
Close your eyes.
- What?
- Just do it.
Okay.
- Now, think of
everything you're feeling,
deep in your gut.
Unfiltered.
[soft exciting music]
- You ever have those dreams
where you're running in place?
It feels like I'm running,
just like that.
The world is crashing down
because of something I did.
But I can't run to fix it.
Can't run from it.
Just stuck somewhere
in the middle,
watching it all burn down.
There's nothing I can do
but pump my arms faster.
♪
[rapid indistinct chatter]
Oh.
All right,
this smell is disgusting.
- Don't worry, Marta's
is gonna make this dump
camera ready again in time
for the New Year's Eve ball.
- How much is that
gonna cost us?
Nothing.
It's on the good people
of Hackensack.
- How are the people gonna feel
about their tax dollars
paying to clean up our mess?
- They'll be happy
to help restore order
and grateful for
the sense of security.
The people of this town
need to know they're safe.
And the town hall tonight
will be the perfect way
to convince them.
You mean "reach them."
You mean "lie to them."
Excuse me?
- Whatever.
I gotta get outta here.
I don't think so.
You're grounded.
What?
- You caused all this.
You have to live in it with us.
You're grounded
until I say you're not.
Where are you going?
Uh-uh.
[tense music]
Exactly.
- Honey.
- Ugh.
I won't with her anymore.
Every time she speaks,
it's cheap silver
on a mass produced
dinner plate.
Show her some compassion.
You know, maybe get through to
her a little more effectively.
- She nearly burned the
whole damn house down, Nathan.
I'm running a little low
on compassion at the moment.
Which I understand, but look,
do we care more
about how our life looks
or how it feels?
You know, Lexy's hurting too.
- Touchy-feely Nathan
is my least favorite Nathan,
just so you know.
How cool would it be
if you got to sleep down here
in Mommy's office?
- There's no bed.
- Well, it's a sofa bed.
Nana slept here, remember?
- Nana's dead.
- Well, now.
Yeah, but she didn't--
hey, look.
What do you think of that, huh?
I want my bed, I want my bed.
- I want my bed!
- Honey! Honey, honey.
Guess what? Guess what?
I have a surprise for you.
Close your eyes.
Open 'em.
Where did that come from?
- Hi, I'm Tommy.
Wanna play?
- Dad, where did you get that?
- I got it online.
- From who?
- "From whom."
I like to be hugged.
[unsettling music]
- Tommy hugs too,
just like Chucky.
Oh.
Hey, Care,
do you think that Tommy
would give me a hug too?
♪
[breathing heavily]
- Lexy!
Sweetie, what are you doing?
- Stop hurting him. Stop!
- Stop it!
Do something!
Lexy, stop it right now!
- Stop it.
- Stop!
[panting]
[camera clicks]
Uh...
[thunder crashes]
So I have some good news.
- You do?
[thunder rumbles]
I made a few phone calls.
Thanks to a favor owed,
Junior, you're still going
to nationals next month.
Is that really the best idea?
The doctor did say
that Junior was--
- I missed regionals
'cause I was in the hospital.
I didn't qualify for nationals.
Isn't that kind of unfair?
[thunder rumbles]
- Let this be
a teaching moment, kid.
In life,
when you get advantages,
you have to take 'em.
So in a week or two,
you're gonna--
[phone buzzes]
In a week or two,
we're gonna have you
back out there running.
I even got you a trainer.
That guy, Dobbs. He's the best.
That's okay, right?
- Logan--
[phone buzzes]
Jake, please,
no phones at the dinner table.
What's she doing texting you?
She hasn't returned
my texts all day.
Okay. Phone, now.
- Sorry, I--I can't do that.
- You can have it back
after dinner.
[phone buzzes]
- Yeah, hand over
the phone, Jake.
- No.
- [scoffs]
Boys.
What are you doing?
- Give me the phone,
you assbag!
Boys, seriously!
Hey!
Drop it.
[tense music]
♪
You give 'em everything
and at the end,
all you can do is
hope for the best.
- Logan,
I think we need to talk.
About?
- Just--
Maybe now is not the best time
to have an extra son
in the house.
I just feel like everything
is falling to pieces
and I'm not entirely sure
that what you're doing
is helpful.
I'm not my brother, Bree.
That's not what I mean.
Then what did you mean?
Oh, what was I saying before?
[indistinct conversation]
[thunder rumbles]
- ♪ The itsy bitsy spider
crawled up the water spout ♪
♪ Out came the rain
and washed the spider out ♪
♪ Out came the sun
and dried up all the rain ♪
♪ And the itsy bitsy spider
crawled up the spout again ♪
[eerie music]
♪
- Start. What the--?
- Tried--so, okay.
- Move.
[dishwasher humming]
- Oh.
- What the hell?
Where did that come from?
Lexy, this isn't funny.
Hasn't your sister
been through enough?
- No, that's not fair.
There's no way--
- Michelle,
it's not a big deal.
I was just gonna throw it out.
Please do.
And Lexy, now just--
just get outta my sight.
Go to your room.
- She doesn't have
a room anymore, remember?
And whose fault is that?
- Jesus, Michelle,
would you just give it a rest?
[door slams]
- Okay, so I'm
the bad guy here.
♪
What are you thinking, Jake?
- I figure we kick his ass
till he's dead.
Hell yeah!
Nathan,
don't ever
undermine my authority
in front of the kids.
We talked about this.
It's hard enough--
Pick a lane, Michelle.
I despise sports metaphors.
Pick a lane.
Talk to me like a grownup.
A man, for example.
All right. Mom or mayor.
- Excuse me?
- Choose.
Because I'm not so sure
you can do both anymore.
- Oh, that's crazy
and you know it.
- Oh, is it?
- It's also impossible.
Lexy didn't sign up for this,
and neither did I.
How about mom and mayor?
Did you think of that?
Because that's the best
I can do,
and I do it pretty damn well
if you ask me.
Nathan?
Nathan!
[clattering]
Stay.
Sh--okay.
Oh, shit!
[clattering]
Hey, okay.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Um, get--get the sack.
- Okay.
- Mm, okay.
- Shit.
- Are you sure
this is gonna work?
- No.
- Are you serious right now?
- What do you mean, no?
- It'll work.
It has to, right?
Okay. All right, ready?
Three, two, one.
- [hissing]
[all shout]
[gasps]
Okay!
[hard rock music]
- I like--I like--
I like to be hugged.
Get him in!
♪
Yeah!
I like to be hugged.
[voice stuttering]
[sound falters, fades]
- Okay.
- [breathing heavily]
[clattering]
Oh, my God.
The little fucker's dead!
Oh, yeah!
[laughs]
- Yes!
- [chuckles]
Holy shit!
- What about
Caroline's new doll?
What about Tommy?
No, I checked. Totally cool.
Tommy's just a dumb doll.
Take the win, Jake.
Chucky is dead!
[Lauv's "Modern Loneliness"]
♪
- Hey, man, hurry,
the sun's coming up.
Okay.
[both chuckling]
♪
- ♪ I've been thinking
'bout my father lately ♪
♪ The person that he made me
We did it.
- Yeah, Chucky's gone.
He's really gone.
- Kicked his ass
just like you said.
What do we do now?
- I don't know.
Go back to normal, I guess.
Right.
- Except that--
- Except what?
- Sometimes I'm not sure
what normal feels like anymore.
- I feel like that
all the time.
You do?
What are you thinking, Devon?
I'm thinking...
This is a problem
we can solve together.
Okay.
- ♪ The baggage in my heart
is still so dark ♪
[chuckles]
♪
[both chuckle]
[laughs]
Bye, Jake.
See you, Devon.
♪ La, di, da, di, da, yeah
♪ You get what you give
and you give what you get ♪
♪ Modern loneliness
♪ We love to get high
♪ But we don't know
how to come down ♪
[upbeat pop music playing]
♪
See anything you like?
As a matter of fact, I do.
♪
Hey, Red, what's new?
- Is there something
I can do for you?
[unsettling music]
Yeah, maybe there is.
[Modern Art's
"Hello / Goodbye"]
♪
[chuckles]
[both sighing]
- [necklace snaps]
- Ah! [laughs]
[metal scrapes]
- ♪ I walk back
into your life ♪
♪
♪ You ask me
where I've been to ♪
Hey.
♪ I don't know what to say
Do it.
Do it to me, now.
♪
Charles, what the hell?
Hello! What the hell?
[grunting]
[gasping]
Hey, Red, wanna play?
[chuckles]
[grunting]
[crying out]
[laughs]
Wow, it's never happened
like that before.
[chuckles]
Is that me?
Oh, it's definitely you.
[both moaning]
[chuckles]
Boy, you really know
how to show a girl a good time.
[both chuckle]
I'm Tiffany.
I'm Charles.
Know what, Charles?
You should be Chucky.
You know what, Tiff?
You should be blonde.
- My secret.
It's all I think about.
I know it's wrong,
of course it is.
I think about Logan
and the look on his face
when I finally say the words.
Every time I try to tell him
I just can't.
But I don't think I can
keep this a secret anymore.
- Have you thought about
telling Junior first?
Junior is just a boy.
He'll find out soon enough.
Besides, with Jake
coming to live with us,
he's been through a lot,
you know?
And as if Logan
doesn't put enough pressure
on Junior as it is.
He just won't let up.
- Did you know that last night--
- Bree.
Your illness?
Stage four cancer.
[contemplative piano music]
♪
You know, I say the words
and it still doesn't feel real.
I just wanted to protect
everyone for as long as I could
so I made a decision;
I didn't tell them.
You spared them.
You took all that weight
and put it on your shoulders.
How does that feel?
Lonely.
No wonder.
I have to tell them.
I will.
I don't want
to go through this alone.
No matter
how I treat my illness
or what's going on at home.
Bree...
Let the people you love
back into your life.
Yeah.
[eerie music]
♪
[both groaning]
[chuckles]
- What's the matter,
little fella?
Are you not enjoying the show?
[muffled groaning]
What about that, Chucky?
We put on a really nice show
for this young man
and all he does is
moan and complain.
What do you want, little fella?
[blows puff of air, chuckles]
Mmm, I need a snack.
Yeah, does look kinda yummy.
- I'm thrilled you've expanded
your palette, Chucky,
but I was talking about
a real snack,
like Swedish meatballs.
Wait, you're hungry?
- Yeah.
- Now?
- Yeah, I'm hungry.
I wanna eat something.
- Jesus Christ,
you're always hungry.
Yeah, I'm always hungry.
- You know, I'd say you were
turning into your mother,
but that would be
an improvement.
- You know, my mother
always told me,
"Never let a man cockblock you
from what really
makes you happy."
And eating makes me happy!
- Go get fat then!
- Maybe I will.
Go!
[metal scrapes]
[sighs]
You know, if killing with Tiff
is the best time
I ever had in my life,
how come I feel like
strangling her
with my own bare hands?
Huh?
You wanna know why?
Because love...
Is strange.
- [groans]
- [chuckles]
[eerie music]
[cries out]
[groans]
Oh, what?
Where am I?
Oh! Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
[grunts]
I'm sorry, my legs--
I'm paraplegic.
[gasps]
Please don't kill me,
please don't kill me.
What?
Oh, my God.
What day is today?
- What?
- What is the date?
- November 8th, I guess?
I don't know.
- It's been two weeks.
- Please don't kill me.
No, no, no, no.
I'm not a killer.
You don't understand.
- Are you fucking serious
right now?
I watched you murder him!
- [sobs]
No!
Look, you don't understand.
My name is Nica Pierce and--
Oh, no.
Is there
a Good Guy doll around here?
A Good Guy what?
- Chucky murdered
my whole family.
[shouting]
[screams]
Who's Chucky?
He framed me for the murders
and put me
in a mental hospital.
[gavel bangs]
I'm still alive!
I can honestly see that.
Two weeks ago, Chucky,
he split his soul into pieces.
Ade boku Damballa.
Give me all the power,
I beg of you!
[dramatic music]
- But one of those pieces
is inside me and I--
- but I'm still here too.
- [grunting]
I can save you.
I can fight him.
[grunts]
Chucky!
My stomach
is growling like a lion
- and this lion needs to eat.
- [groans]
- And if you ever compare me
to my mother again,
I will cut your heart out
and feed it to a stranger.
What are you doing
on the floor?
- That was weird.
- What's going on?
[grunts, sighs]
I dropped my knife.
Well, don't do it again.
You want to eat? Let's eat.
Wet work for dessert.
My favorite.
Hey.
Best if we keep this
Nica bullshit between us, huh?
[gurgling]
- It'll be our little secret.
[chuckles]
- Mrs. McGee, can't wait
for Rock the School Block.
Hey, can we expect those famous
everything but the sink cookies
this year?
Great.
Hey, Adrianna,
you ready to kick
some Manchester butt
this Friday?
Okay.
Phyllis, so glad you made it.
Thank you.
- Tommy ran away.
- He did?
- I want Tommy back.
- Okay.
I bet Tommy will be waiting
for you when you get home.
No, he won't!
- You know, we could just
tell them about Chucky.
Tell 'em he's dead.
- My mom's not going
to believe that.
Nobody will believe us.
- What--what if they do?
Move.
Lexy, what the hell?
Jake's doll Chucky was alive
and he killed his dad,
and he killed Oliver,
and the cop at the hospital,
and your housekeeper too,
and he wouldn't stop killing,
so we broke him into pieces
and now he's dead,
so everyone can stop
worrying about it.
You can stop worrying
about it too.
- If you don't want to tell me
what's going on, fine,
but making up stupid shit
like that is just embarrassing.
Grow up, Lexy.
Asshole.
Told you.
Good evening, everyone.
Thank you all
for coming tonight.
As your mayor,
I wanted to take this
opportunity to speak to you
about the recent series
of unfortunate
accidents in this community.
First,
thoughts and prayers for anyone
who has lost an acquaintance
or loved one.
[audience murmuring]
Second, I am here to tell you
that Hackensack
has never been safer.
[audience booing]
We are still the best darn
big little city in America.
Third, you're an idiot!
- Fourth, it's important
that you understand
that I am doing
everything in my power
to keep you all
happy and healthy.
Because nothing
is more important to me
than family.
Boo!
- Thank you.
- You're the murderer!
Thank you so much.
- You killed that cop!
- Have a wonderful evening.
- What about the fire
at your house?
- Psycho!
- Please.
Quiet, please.
This is about
the ongoing investigation
into every one
of these recent deaths.
This is about the curfew,
which goes into effect tonight.
But most of all,
it's about getting
to the bottom of this
so that we can all
live our lives
without living in fear.
[apprehensive music]
♪
Now, before I answer
your questions,
and I'll stay long enough
to answer every one of them,
Principal McVey would like
to say a few words.
[audience whispering]
Principal McVey?
[Yeah Yeah Yeah's
"Heads Will Roll']
♪ Off with your head
[screaming]
♪ Dance till you're dead
♪ Heads will roll
♪ Heads will roll,
heads will roll ♪
- [chuckles]
- ♪ On the floor
♪ Glitter on the wet streets
[crowd screaming]
♪ Silver over everything
Oh, my God.
♪ The river's all wet
- But we killed him.
We killed him!
♪
♪ Dripping with alchemy
♪ Shiver stop shivering
♪ The glitter's all wet
♪ You're all chrome
♪
♪ The men cry out,
the girls cry out ♪
♪ The men cry out, oh, no
♪ Oh
♪
You look like a tuna melt.
No one's gonna love you
looking like this.
♪
♪ Oh, looking glass
♪ Take the past
Ade due Damballa,
give me the power I beg of you.
[thunder crashes]
[eerie music]
♪
Hi, I'm Tommy.
Wanna play?
♪ Off with your head
♪ Dance, dance, dance
till you're dead ♪
♪ Off, off, off
with your head ♪
♪ Dance, dance, dance
till you're dead ♪
♪ Off, off, off
with your head ♪
♪ Dance, dance
till you're dead ♪