Tiffany:
Previously, on "Chucky"...
Move.
Now, there's a lot going on,
so pay attention.
Jake's doll chucky was alive,
and he killed his dad,
and he killed Oliver,
and the cop at the hospital,
Junior's housekeeper, too,
and he wouldn't stop killing.
- [screaming]
- I like to be hugged.
- Making up stupid shit
like that is just embarrassing.
- Meanwhile, the mayor
went all Megyn Kelly,
until the principal
lost her head.
[screaming]
We killed him!
- Hello?
- Yeah, I'm calling
about the doll.
Have you checked
his batteries?
My name is Nica Pierce.
Chucky murdered
my whole family.
He split his soul into pieces.
One of those pieces
is inside me.
Who's Chucky?
- What are you doing
on the floor?
- Uhh--
- Have you thought about
telling Junior first?
- As if Logan
doesn't put enough
pressure on Junior as it is.
Re: your illness?
Ade due Damballa.
Give me the power,
I beg of you.
I'm Tommy. Wanna play?
- Best if we keep this Nica
bullshit between us, huh?
Ooh, did I mention
I took over the life
of my favorite celebrity?
I wanna be Jennifer Tilly.
I wanna be a star.
Ade due Damballa. And switch.
And switch.
Switch, switch, switch.
[exhales]
Anyhow, lots to get to.
Television is so exciting.
[upbeat music]
♪
[doorbell dings]
Can I help you?
- Is this the
Morrison residence?
- Yes.
- Hi.
We're from the U.S. Census.
Can we have a few minutes
of your time?
- Well, we were just about
to sit down to eat.
Oh, this won't take long.
We just want to make sure
everyone is counted.
It's important
to be represented.
All right, come on in.
- So, the Census is pretty
straightforward these days.
We're just gonna ask you
a few questions
and we'll get out of your hair.
Happy to do our part.
- So, how many members
in the household?
- Just the three of us?
- Ages?
- 39.
- 38, and Becky here
just turned seven,
didn't you, Becks?
I'm a grownup.
- I bet you are.
I bet you're really smart too.
Any recent property damage?
No, not that I can think of.
- We should move on
to the occupations.
Any fires or major injuries?
Freak accidents?
God, no. Nothing like that.
We have to ask.
Um, so, you were saying?
Your occupation?
Any new dolls in the house?
Dolls?
- What kind of census
are you taking exactly?
- It's a new thing we're doing
at the Bureau.
You know, we ask
a few questions
to get the kids excited
about the Census.
That's wonderful.
Becky, why don't you go get
some of your friends
from your room?
- Uh, it's so important
to start them early.
Mm.
[eerie music]
♪
- Here's Binty and
Mrs. Fluff and Jojo and--
- Sweetheart, are these
all your friends?
'Cause it's really important
that we count everyone.
This is everybody.
Mrs. Fluff and Jojo
and Monkey Beans
and wait, I forgot Charlie.
- Oh.
- Well, go get him. Go get him.
[both laugh]
That is her favorite.
♪
Hi. I'm...Charlie.
Wanna play?
♪
You made me do this.
Do what?
[gasps] Ah!
- Ah!
- [girl screams]
Oh! Oh!
- Oh, oh, oh, oh!
- [screaming]
Fuck you, Andy!
♪
- Thank you
for your cooperation.
♪
[tires screeching]
[playful spooky music]
♪
Ohh.
Those people today,
what if they talk?
- You and I both know
nobody's gonna believe 'em.
- That little girl,
she's gonna be traumatized.
She's never gonna be the same.
She'll be alive.
Besides, you and me
went through a lot as kids.
Come on!
[thrilling music]
- [gasps]
- Uh!
We turned out okay.
You did, at least.
- Reminds me,
why didn't you tell me
you were keeping a living
Chucky head locked in a safe?
Yeah.
Thanks for taking care of that.
- You didn't answer
my question.
Why did you keep him alive
for four years?
What difference does it make?
- I don't know.
Doesn't sound like
very rational behavior.
- There's nothing rational
about any of this!
It's something I picked up
in military school.
Get to know your enemy.
You can learn a lot from a POW,
if you persuade him
hard enough.
What did you learn?
- He scream
the loudest at fire.
[screaming]
Those screams were my favorite.
Even louder than my own.
- Okay, so there's just
one left, right?
Yeah.
One doll left.
- Okay, what aren't you
telling me?
- Well, Chucky broke his soul
into pieces,
but the last piece,
it didn't go into a doll.
Where did it go?
- Let's just say that murder
isn't the worst thing
Chucky can do to you.
The female wildebeests
begin to give birth
to their offspring.
all: Eww!
- The calves fall
to the ground
along with the afterbirth.
- Okay, let's simmer
down, guys.
- Others take a bit more time.
[knock on door]
- Rachel Fairchild,
you're under arrest
for the murders
of Megan McVey, Oliver Hayden,
- and Detective Sean Peyton.
- What?
What? Are you joking?
Mom.
- She didn't do it.
- Lower your voice.
How do you know
she didn't do it?
I just do.
I'll see you at home.
No, stop! Please!
Devon's right.
We know she didn't do it.
All right, let's go.
- Go ahead and get back
in the classroom.
- We should have told 'em
about Chucky.
- Yeah, brilliant.
Because I've always wanted
to be institutionalized.
How about you?
- Lexy's right.
We can't just tell anyone.
We have to find him
and kill him.
- But we did kill him.
I mean, we were all there.
- We all saw what happened
to McVey.
He's still out there.
Shit.
It's gotta be Tommy.
What, your sister's doll?
I thought you said
you checked him out.
I did. Now he's missing.
What? Since when?
- Well, how's that
even possible?
- This is serious.
We have to find him.
I have an idea.
Andy Barclay.
Who's Andy Barclay?
- He was this kid in the '80s
whose babysitter was murdered.
He always said Chucky did it.
The whole Charles Lee Ray
connection, everything,
it all comes back
to Andy Barclay.
- Well, you think he'll know
how to find Chucky?
Maybe.
- Let's do it.
Let's talk to him.
- My house, after school.
Come as soon as you can.
[straining efforts]
I can't close it!
It won't close.
It won't close!
- You never were good
at packing light.
- Oh, very funny.
I don't see you helping me.
- You're the body
disposal expert.
Dispose.
- I am disposing as best
as I can!
[panting]
- Shoving a full-grown man
into a suitcase that size?
Shut up, Chucky.
It's amateur hour.
You're not helping.
- The key is smaller pieces
for optimal packing.
- Oh, so now you're
a packing genius.
Smaller pieces.
Is that what you suggest?
- It's like
rolling your t-shirts
instead of folding 'em.
- Shut up, Chucky!
- [laughs]
Get your leg off my suitcase!
You want smaller pieces?
you can cut 'em yourself.
[eerie music]
♪
- Uh!
[grunts]
Oh, fuck!
Uh! [inhales]
Oh, no.
[whimpers]
- 1960 Pontiac Parisian
four-door wide-track.
Back when bigger
was unapologetically better.
Comfortably seats six.
perfect for the growing family,
by the way.
389 V8 engine topped
with Tri-Power carburetor,
making it the ultimate cruiser
of its day.
Superior handling
and just the quietest purr
from this pussycat.
And I love the color.
Coronado red.
Just put on a fresh coat
last month.
Chucky, it's perfect.
- You heard the lady.
How much?
1,000 bucks.
- Check okay?
- Fine.
Oh, though there is
one thing that legally
I am bound to disclose to you.
What's that?
- Um, unfortunately, this car
was--there was an accident.
- What happened?
- Young couple got killed.
How exactly?
Well, if you must know,
I believe they
were decapitated.
Ooh.
Both of them?
More or less.
We'll take it.
- Really? Great! Good for you!
[laughs]
It's a stunning automobile,
and a true classic
never goes out of style.
What'd you say?
- I said you got
a real classic here.
Liar.
- Pardon?
- Technically,
it isn't even an antique.
[chuckles] Well, sure it is.
It's vintage, retro.
- It's not vintage
or retro
or an antique.
it's just old.
Kinda like you.
But don't worry,
we're gonna give you
another paint job, too.
[laughs]
♪
[gurgling]
Here you go.
- That's 1,000 bucks.
- [laughs] That's cute.
Ahh.
I just love that color.
- Yeah, it matches
your lip gloss.
[starts engine]
What's that?
It's a hobby.
♪
[crying]
[somber music]
♪
I'm gonna call him in.
Are you ready?
- I don't know how anybody
could be ready for this.
I know.
Junior.
Can you come in here
for a minute, please?
Hi.
Come have a seat for a sec.
Mom, what's going on?
- Um--
Your mother is--
Your mother--
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
Um, there's something
I have to tell you.
And there's no easy way
to say it.
I'm sick.
- Sick?
- Hey.
I don't want you to worry.
Mom?
What's going on?
♪
- It's, um--
It's cancer.
- You're--you're gonna be okay,
right?
You're gonna be okay?
- We're gonna get through
this together, Junior.
Please don't worry.
Come here, buddy.
Come here.
Oh.
I love you, buddy.
Oh, my boy.
You ready? Look. Huh?
I guess today
is my lucky day, huh?
[laughs]
Funny.
I don't remember you
being dumb enough
to chase an inside straight,
even if you are lucky enough
to get it.
[laughs]
Another beer?
No, I'm okay.
- Ah, cuttin' back,
are you, Chucky?
You know what this motel
reminds me of?
It reminds me
of that night in Niagara.
- All those fond memories.
- [laughs]
It's why I chose this dump.
Tell me, do you
remember Niagara, Chucky?
- You know, I'm more of
a live-in-the-present
kinda guy, huh?
Humor me.
What was your favorite part?
Come on, Tiff.
That was a long time ago.
Raise you 100.
I call.
Too long to remember
your own honeymoon, Chucky?
Come on.
- You know, my favorite part
was just being with you.
Aww, shucks.
- [laughs]
- I never figured you to be
the sentimental type, Chucky.
- I'm all-in.
- All right. I'm all-in too.
[chuckles]
Hello, Nica.
Long time no see.
Nica? I'm not Nica.
Why do you think I'm Nica?
I'm not--
[tense music]
♪
Is it Chucky doesn't bluff?
Ohh, Chucky bluffs.
But he doesn't chew
on his fingernails.
[laughs]
Besides, I stabbed you
in the thigh ten minutes ago.
You didn't feel a thing.
Ooh, if it'd have been Chucky,
he woulda screamed
like a banshee.
But not you,
being paralyzed and all.
What are you gonna do to me?
- I don't know.
that's an interesting question.
You see, the thing is, Nica,
I spent some with you,
I spent some time with Chucky,
and I gotta say,
I like you better.
[chuckles]
You do?
Do you wanna know a secret?
Sure.
- Sometimes,
when we're together, I--
I see you looking at me,
and I know it's you.
It's not Chucky,
it's you, and...
I live for those moments.
I want to have those moments
all the time.
- Mm-hmm.
- I--[sighs]
Guess what?
I have a surprise
for you, Nica.
I bought us a house
right here in Hackensack.
You know, they say the saints
look over everybody
that lives in Hackensack,
even non-traditional couples
like ourselves.
The only problem is...
How do I keep you
in the driver's seat
- instead of that rat Chucky?
- [laughs]
[humming]
Ahh!
He's not on Insta.
Not on Snap.
Not on Twitter.
- Well...
- What?
- I Googled Andy Barclay and
got an article
from two weeks ago.
"Violent Patient Escapes
Harrogate Psychiatric Hospital
Manhunt Underway"
[sighs] Great sign.
[doorbell dings]
Be right back.
- Wait, Harrogate,
where is that?
- Rhode Island.
- Rhode Island?
Wait, I got a call from Rhode
Island about a month ago.
Holy shit,
that must be Andy Barclay.
God.
Junior, I'm so sorry.
- I just feel like everything's
falling apart right now,
you know?
My mom, my uncle.
Even you and me.
No. No, not us.
I'm always here for you.
Hey, Lexy, he's on Facebook!
- I just feel like you're
somewhere else these days.
I'm sorry, what?
You see what I mean?
The fuck, Lex?
It's like I don't even
exist to you anymore!
- No. No, that's--
that's not true.
I'm always here for you.
I love you.
And it's like you said,
everything has just been
such a mess lately,
and I just want to protect you.
No.
No?
It's over.
We're done.
No.
No, Junior, please.
Please don't do this.
We can fix this.
I just did.
[door opens, shuts]
- Wait, how old's
this guy again?
Um, 40.
God help us.
- Hi. This is Andy Barclay.
Leave a message.
[beep]
Shit.
[phone ringing]
- Uh--
Andy Barclay?
Jake Wheeler.
Where are you?
In a kitchen in Hackensack.
Hackensack. Figures.
- You know about Chucky,
and you're still alive.
Makes you one of the lucky few.
It's a shitty club to be in,
but welcome.
- At first I thought
I was going crazy.
- Well, you haven't told
anyone, have you?
No. No one.
- Look, you feel like
you're going crazy?
That's exactly what everyone
will think if you tell them.
Speaking of crazy, Chucky's
not with anyone, is he?
A woman? Two women?
- Uh--
No, I don't think so, but
listen, Andy, I have, like,
a million questions.
We're out of time,
and we need your help.
How do we find him?
- Oh, you don't have
to find Chucky.
He'll find you.
And if he can't find you,
he'll go after your
whole family to get to you.
- He killed
our foster parents, Jake.
He'll stop at nothing.
- Oh, and Jake, it'll be
somewhere he's familiar with,
and you're
at your most vulnerable.
That's exactly
where he'll find you.
Junior's house.
- Not a bad place
to spring a trap.
Well, text me the address.
We're on our way.
♪
[laughs]
[humming]
Gladys! Big day!
- Congratulations, Miss Tilly.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Well, you know, the house
has beautiful bones.
- Mm-hmm.
- It just needs a little TLC.
- And someone like yourself...
- Yes.
- With a vision to restore it
to its mid-century glory.
- Yes. We have big plans
for this place.
- We?
- Yes.
Me and my fiancée
will be moving in immediately.
- Oh, congratulations!
That's wonderful!
Thank you. Yes.
- What brings you
to Hackensack?
- Well, my fiancée
grew up here, actually.
Right in this very house.
- Oh!
- Mm-hmm.
- I--it's just been empty
ever since--
- Ever since the murders.
Yes.
- Yeah.
- Oh, so it was
your fiancée's parents that--
[laughs] Yes. Yes.
So many memories.
- Okay. You know,
I almost forgot.
You've already started
getting some mail.
Oh! [gasps]
Oh!
There you go.
- I have an online
shopping addiction.
- Okay. Well, you have
a good night, Miss Tilly.
- Oh, would you
like my autograph?
Next time!
Okay.
Weirdo.
[humming]
I'll put you
right here for now.
And...
♪
[whimpering softly]
Welcome home!
[sighs]
[grunting]
- Hold still!
Hold still! Hold still!
It's for your own good.
There, that's better.
That didn't hurt, did it?
You're such a baby.
[laughs]
Look how sweet you look.
Oh, oh. Ohh.
Goodbye, sweet face.
Don't wait up.
[laughs]
Don't do anything
I wouldn't do.
- [grunting]
[door shuts]
[muffled]
Help! Help!
[screams]
I want my lawyer.
Someone's on their way.
Besides, I don't
need you to talk.
Just listen.
Here's what we got.
You were the last person
to see Principal McVey alive.
You were next in line
for her job.
We found your fingerprints
everywhere in the office
and the crime scene and...this.
- Of course my fingerprints
are everywhere.
I work at the school.
- I haven't even gotten started
on Oliver Hayden.
He was your student, wasn't he?
Oh, and then there's
your juvenile record.
Maybe McVey found out
about your delinquent past?
So, yeah, wait for the lawyer.
You're gonna need one.
- Rachel Fairchild,
a biology teacher
at Perry Middle School,
has been charged
with three counts of homicide
by Hackensack police.
The recent murders are part
of an alarming trend
in local violence,
which have threatened
reelection prospects
for Mayor Michelle Cross.
- Do you want me to leave you
the keys
in case you want
to listen to the radio?
Okay, I'll leave them
just in case.
- Mom?
- Mm-hmm?
- What do you talk
about in there?
[sighs]
All the things we don't
talk about at home.
- Why don't we talk
about them at home?
I don't know.
You talk about me?
All the time.
You know, your my favorite
topic of conversation?
Come here, buddy.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'll be right back, okay?
♪
[laughter]
I told them.
I was honest.
About the cancer,
and my chances.
It's all out in the open now.
That's good.
I imagine it was unburdening
to share your truth
with people close to you.
No.
It was horrible.
- I didn't need to share my
pain,
or my fear, or my worry.
Some things aren't meant
to be shared.
So, I've made another decision.
I'm refusing treatment.
- Bree, we've talked
about depression before.
It's very common for people
with your diagnosis
to feel hopeless.
- Dr. Mixter, I don't feel
depressed or hopeless.
Literally,
for the first time in weeks.
I just wanna live my life
with my family,
with whatever time
that I have left.
Because every day is a gift.
For all of us.
That's true.
- I could walk out
of this office right now
and get hit by a bus.
Who knows what could happen?
- Could be something
very special.
- The important thing is for me
to savor what time I have left,
and welcome whatever's waiting
around that corner
with open arms.
♪ I've been having dreams
♪ Splashin' in
the summer stream ♪
♪ Trip and I fall in
♪ I want it to happen
♪ My body turns to ice
♪ Crushin' weight
of paradise ♪
♪ Solid block of gold
lying in the cold ♪
♪ I feel right at home
♪ Wait if I'm on fire
♪ How am I so deep in love?
♪ When I dream of dying
♪ I never feel so loved
[laughs]
♪
♪ I never feel so loved
[laughs]
[grunts]
[screams]
♪
♪ Wait if I'm on fire
[kisses]
- ♪ How am I so deep
in love? ♪
♪ When I dream of dying
- Ah!
[crashing]
[gasping]
Mom?
[panting]
- ♪ How am I so deep
in love? ♪
♪ When I dream of fire
Ahh!
Mom--Mom!
[screams]
[dark music]
♪
- I know it's a lot
to process right now.
- She didn't seem--
I don't understand.
She made it sound
like everything was fine.
That she had it under control.
She didn't say anything to you?
You're her fuckin' therapist.
You didn't see any signs?
- It's normal to feel angry
at times like this.
When faced with
their own mortality,
some patients try
to regain control
the only way they can.
So, that's it.
She just decided
to hell with all of us.
She just gave up.
Her cancer had metastasized.
Her prognosis,
even with chemo, was grim.
She didn't want her treatment
to overtake your lives.
You must understand your
mother loved you all very much.
Thank you for coming by.
- If you ever need to talk,
don't hesitate to call.
I'm so very sorry
for your loss.
Take care of yourselves.
- Junior, I don't think
your mother killed herself.
♪
Stay the fuck away from me.
We were fine
before you came along.
["Cape Fear" theme playing]
♪
[knock at door]
- Hey. I have to head back
to the station.
I have a busy night
ahead of me.
If you're hungry,
I left some soup in the fridge.
Thanks.
Curfew is still in effect.
Promise me you'll stay inside.
Devon, I know I've been
hard on you lately, and...
I know that
I was wrong about Jake.
And I'm sorry.
I should have trusted you.
Hey, Mom.
Can I ask you something?
Shoot.
- How do you know
if you really like someone?
When I first met your father,
I couldn't stop
thinking about him.
I had butterflies in my stomach
whenever he was around.
[laughs]
Is that how you feel?
About Jake?
Yeah.
You know, I was worried you
wouldn't look at me the same.
- Honey, this doesn't
change anything.
You're my son.
And I'll always love you. Okay?
I love you, Mom.
Thank you.
I miss your movie nights.
Maybe next week
we could do a double feature.
You could invite Jake.
- Maybe.
- Okay.
[rewinding video]
♪
What is that?
- Well, it's
a monofilament line.
Got it from
Sam's Fishing Gear.
See, what I do is I stretch it
across the windows
and the doors, and attach it
to Andy's teddy bear here.
If the bear moves 1/4 inch,
I'll know if the Holy Ghost
is sneaking in.
♪
[beeping]
[electricity crackling]
[tense music]
♪
- We'll know if the Holy Ghost
sneaks in.
What?
She's our alarm.
- They have an alarm,
and it's from this century.
- Well, we don't
want the cops here.
I don't want my mom here, okay?
- Where's Junior
and your uncle?
Funeral home.
Why aren't you with them?
They need to be alone.
And so do we.
Best vantage point is upstairs.
My room.
- Rock-paper-scissors?
Seriously?
[sighs] Jesus.
- Just don't touch
any of my stuff, all right?
[phone buzzing]
[thunder rumbles]
Hey, I talked to my mom.
Told her I'm into someone.
- [chuckles]
- You.
- Um, how--how'd she take it?
- Now that she knows you're not
a psycho, she's cool.
Yeah. Well, maybe,
you know,
when this is all over,
maybe we could go on a date?
You know, one that doesn't
involve hunting a killer doll.
Definitely.
Okay.
- What kind of movies
are you into?
Um, horror movies.
Well, I mean,
I used to, anyway.
Favorite final girl?
Laurie Strode, hands down.
- Jamie Lee's gonna win
the Saturn this year.
- Dude, she's gonna win
an Oscar. She's magnificent.
She's fabulous.
Uh, anyway.
I have a feeling
it's gonna take a lot more than
"Goosebumps" and Pennywise
to scare us.
[both gasp]
♪
Chucky's here.
[tense music]
♪
[crashing]
[Chucky laughs]
♪
Oh, shit.
That never happened
in "Cape Fear."
Of course not.
De Niro could have
never fit down that chimney.
- No, dude.
He was totally ripped in that.
- Hey, make sure he
doesn't double back.
♪
[gas hissing]
Hey.
- Where is he?
- I don't know.
He's--he's messing with us.
♪
Jake?
Jake!
[screams]
I got you now, bitch!
But I'll let you go
on one condition.
[panting]
What?
- All you gotta do
is kill Jake.
Everybody's gotta die sometime,
so--
That's true.
- I mean, I've died myself
many times,
so it's no big deal.
- You want me to kill Jake?
Why?
- Don't tell me you've
never thought about it.
You get off on hurting Jake.
Yeah.
Okay, fine, I'll admit it.
I have thought about it.
You're right.
I do wanna kill Jake.
I knew it.
You wanna know I'd do it?
Duh!
I'm all ears.
[beeping]
Okay.
I'd beat him to death...
with this.
Can I watch?
[floorboard creaks]
Aha!
Do it, Lexy!
Kill him!
Damn it!
- Ha ha!
- Ahh!
- [Tazer crackling]
- No! [screams]
Jake!
♪
Shit!
- [beeping]
- Come on, come on, come on!
♪
[groans]
I'm too old for this shit.
[laughs]
[beeping]
- Guys.
He's headed back downstairs.
- Okay.
[grunting]
- He didn't even try
to kill me.
- Me neither.
- What the hell?
- Hello?
[police radio chatter]
Devon, are you here?
Mom?
Ahh!
Hey, Devon, watch this!
[screams]
Mom! Mom!
[screaming]
- Whoa! [laughs]
Ahh!
[screaming]
Mom!
[bones cracking]
[Chucky laughs]
♪