- Previously
on fuckin' "Chucky"...
- [screams, gags]
- I'm not a monster, Jake.
[chuckles]
Hi, I'm Chucky,
and I'm your friend
till the end.
- Caroline, would you maybe
like to meet Chucky sometime?
- What if he doesn't like me?
- I'm Detective Evans.
Do you know
that there was a break-in
at the school last night?
The only thing missing
was a doll.
- I'm sorry,
I--I shouldn't have lied.
I've never done anything
like that before.
- Your sister adores you.
- She barely knows I exist.
She doesn't even like
to be touched.
- Where is he?
Did Junior take him?
- What are you talking about?
- Chucky.
He's gone.
- Hi, I'm Chucky.
I'm looking for a party.
- I--I've gone to find Lexy.
I just, I--I need
to make sure she's okay.
- Seven minutes in hell!
[crowd cheers]
- Where's Lexy?
- Probably kissing Junior
somewhere.
- Well, at least she's gonna
die doin' what she loves.
[knife slashes]
[sudden musical flourish]
- Leave my friends alone!
- You have a serious
doll problem.
- If you only knew.
[crowd chanting, cheering]
[ominous music]
[laughter]
♪
[electricity zapping]
- Some people just
deserve to die.
- I--I can't let her
get away with this.
- Kill the bitch
before she kills you.
You know you want to.
♪
[owl hooting]
[eerie music]
- So, Jake, are you more
of a stabbing kind of guy
or a strangulation kind of guy?
'Cause I see the appeal
of both.
- I--I don't know.
Neither.
I--I don't know
if I can do this.
- Oh, sure you can.
Easy.
You want hard?
[chuckles]
Try choking someone with these.
You hate her, don't you?
- Of course I hate her.
- She's definitely
got it comin'.
- Yeah, and--
and I want her dead.
But what if I'm not a killer?
- Everybody's a killer
if you push 'em far enough.
And I think Lexy's pushed you
right over the edge.
- Chucky?
How did you end up like this?
- Great question.
In a lot of ways, it was your
standard voodoo soul transfer.
My big innovation
was using the doll.
You see--
- No, I mean,
when did you become a killer
in the first place?
- Oh.
[chuckles]
Oh, I get it.
All right, kid,
let me tell you the story
of my first time.
You never forget your first.
[creepy laughter]
Step one, picking your prey.
Could be a total stranger.
Could be someone close to you.
- I want cake now!
Charles, hurry up
and cut the cake!
- Or maybe someone you just
want to shut the fuck up.
But no matter
how you slice it,
you got to find
that special someone.
- ♪ Everybody wants
to be different ♪
- ♪ Just be you
- ♪ I know it's true
- ♪ But, baby,
please don't change ♪
♪ Just be you
- ♪ Don't you do it,
please be true ♪
♪ 'Cause you're mine,
just be you ♪
- ♪ Don't look
through everybody ♪
[ringing crescendos
over music]
[cheers]
- [grunting]
[music fades]
- A mass murderer continued
his reign of terror today,
leaving two more dead
in his wake.
As violent crimes
continue to rise,
we urge all citizens
of Hackensack
not to go out alone at night.
[knife whooshes]
[playful '60s music returns]
[people cheering,
noisemakers tooting]
[playful spooky music]
♪
[school bell rings]
[students chattering
indistinctly]
- Kim, you here for Devon?
I don't have him till fifth.
- No, actually I'm--I'm here
officially, Ms. Fairchild.
- Oh.
- I'd like to talk
about Jake Wheeler.
- Well, I'm sorry,
but I'm not really comfortable
talking about my students,
especially one that's been
through what Jake has recently,
Detective Evans.
- Look, I appreciate
your concern for these kids.
It's my job
to be concerned too.
But not just for them,
for everyone in the community.
- Great, then you understand
my position.
- What I understand is
everywhere Jake Wheeler goes,
death seems to follow.
Now maybe his father
and housekeeper
were just accidents,
but I think Jake knows more
than he's saying.
- I'm sorry,
but are you suggesting--
- And if he does
know something,
who's to say one of these kids
won't be the next to be hurt?
- I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
- Can't or won't?
- [sighs]
[school bell rings]
[students chattering
indistinctly]
[soft ominous music]
- [sighs]
♪
Oh, um...
- Am I too late to say "boo"?
- I'll allow it.
- Hey, you doing okay?
- Yeah, I'm totally fine.
It's--it's no big deal.
- Well, I think
it's a big deal.
I mean, what Lexy did to you,
that was cruel and disgusting.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
I can't imagine
how much that hurt.
- Well, thanks.
- I wish I could like--
[sighs]
Never mind.
No, it's stupid, no.
- No, tell me.
- [sighs]
Well, I wish I could, like,
protect you or something.
- [laughs lightly]
I mean, I guess
it does hurt a little.
[tender music]
- I still can't believe
she did that.
You must have been so angry.
- Well, I mean,
of course, I was angry.
You know,
Lexy can be a real bitch.
You know what she's like.
I mean, no, no, no,
we're cool now.
It's--no, but she was
just messing around.
[sighs]
[phone buzzes]
Oh.
[phone buzzes longer]
[phone chimes]
Oh, um,
I got to go do a project--
homework, and--
I--I got to go.
- Uh, see you later?
- I don't know.
Uh, I mean, maybe.
See you, Devon.
[eerie music]
♪
[crows cawing]
[phone chimes]
- Jake, perfect.
We need to chat.
- Uh--
I mean, I'm--
I'm meeting some friends
and I'm kind of late.
- It'll just take a minute.
I just wanted you
to hear it from me.
I've asked your aunt and uncle
to come in for a meeting
with me tonight.
- What, why?
Did I do something wrong?
- No, no, no, no, Jake,
you haven't.
I'm also inviting
Lexy's parents.
I think this whole thing
between the two of you has
gotten a little out of hand,
and I think getting
the parents--um, I'm sorry,
the--the guardians
together will help
to diffuse the situation.
- You don't have to do that.
You know, me and Lexy are
really cool now.
It's--
it's all good.
- I saw the pictures
from Oliver's party.
They're all over school.
- [sighs]
- You don't need to pretend
like everything's fine, Jake.
[phone chimes]
- Um--
you know what,
this whole parent--
guardian meetup thing,
it's--it's--it's great.
Yeah, it's a really good idea.
Yeah, um--
- Okay.
[phone chimes]
- Um, yeah, see you later.
- Uh, listen.
[phone chimes]
I want you to know
that if you're ever
in any sort of trouble,
I just want you to know
that you can always come to me,
yeah?
You can trust me.
[tender music]
- Thanks, Miss F.
- Okay.
[phone chimes twice]
[sighs]
[phone chimes repeatedly]
[creepy music]
♪
- The next thing you got to do
is really get to know
your victim.
What they like, where they go.
But eventually, you got
to get your victim alone.
[phone chimes]
Keep it intimate.
Really set the mood.
Timing is everything.
You're looking for that magic
moment, just the two of you.
[phone chimes]
[suspenseful music]
♪
[phone chimes]
- [breathing heavily]
- [panting]
[heartbeat thumping]
[bird calls]
[frantic music]
♪
- Whoa!
The hell are you doing?
- I--I wasn't doing anything.
I was--
- What's your problem?
Why the hell are you
following me?
Whatever, creep.
- The moment
isn't always right,
but I promise you,
the right moment always comes.
[birds calling]
- [panting]
Hey, babe.
Oh, thanks for grabbing it.
How'd you like my playlist?
Jeez, moody much?
What's your problem?
- It's Jake.
- Oh, God.
- You really went
too far this time.
- It was funny.
It got like, 400 likes.
- You dressed up
as his dead dad--
my uncle.
- Hold your breath
for my apology.
- It was fucked up, Lex.
You crossed a line.
And now--
- And now?
What?
- [sighs]
You need to apologize to Jake.
- [laughs]
Also fucking no way.
Never.
- I'm serious.
You need to talk to him.
- Yeah?
And what if I don't?
What's Jake gonna do?
- Honestly...
[sighs]
I don't know.
Look, I'll talk to you later,
okay?
[tense music]
♪
- No.
- [sighs]
Sweetie, come on.
- No.
- Come on.
- [screams]
- Oh, my God,
why is she acting like this?
- [shushing]
- No.
- She likes her blankie.
- Mom, the sunglasses
or the blankie.
- No!
- What about her sunglasses?
- I looked in the drawer,
Nathan, they're not there.
[sighs]
Why does she always do this
when I'm heading out the door?
- No. No.
- Sweetie, it's okay.
- No.
No.
- It's all right, you're okay.
Look, look, look, look.
- No.
[groaning]
- Here.
- No.
- Here, hey.
- Hey, what can I get you?
- I want Chucky.
Chucky is my best friend!
I want Chucky!
[creepy music]
♪
[ominous music]
- [grunting]
- Hey, freak show.
Whoa, that looks sharp.
- Junior's not home.
- Who cares?
I'm here for you.
What's that for anyway?
- It's for gardening.
Actually,
for my new sculpture house--
- Whatever, don't care.
[building suspenseful music]
You know, Dad took us
to a wax museum once.
Totally sucked.
But they had this
"Chamber of Terror,"
torture stuff.
- [breathing shakily]
- All these insane tools
on a wall just like this one.
It was actually pretty cool.
[music ends abruptly]
You look even weirder
than usual right now.
- W--Why are you even here?
- I'm here because
I need to talk to you,
if you can fit me into
your busy gardening schedule.
- Okay, talk.
- I want to...apologize
for the whole dead dad
Halloween costume thing.
I guess I can sort of see why
you'd take that the wrong way.
- There was a right way?
- [sighs]
All right, okay, um...
Sometimes when I'm upset, I...
hurt people or something.
And it--
[sighs]
Look, I'm sorry
I hurt your feelings.
I am.
Even though you're like a weird
social tumor who's creepy AF
and you thought you could mess
with me at the talent show.
[tense music]
I just thought since
maybe I was a little harsh,
I should be the bigger man.
You know, I think people really
underestimate my humility.
[laughs lightly]
Anyway,
now that I've done this,
like, act of charity,
I'm sure you want to know
what you can do for me.
- Wasn't really thinking that,
but, uh,
hey, Lexy,
what could I do for you?
- Chucky.
- Chucky?
- Yeah.
Can I, like, have him?
Not for me.
I think he's totally creepy.
For Caroline.
- N-no, no, absolutely not.
No.
- Excuse me?
- You can't have him
for any reason.
You--you can never have him.
- You mean, I came all the way
here to apologize,
and this is how you repay me?
- Yeah, that's exactly how.
- [sighs]
You are a waste!
[scoffs]
Ugh!
[intense, dark music]
♪
- So you had the chance
to kill her and you choked.
And not in the good way.
[music intensifies]
♪
It's called
"completion anxiety."
- [sighs]
Look, I wanted to do it.
I just couldn't.
And besides,
with my dad and Annie, I...
couldn't just kill Lexy
in the garage.
It's too risky.
- Pussy.
And that means once again,
I got to do your dirty work
for you.
- I--I don't know.
- Oh, come on, Jake.
Let me fix your Lexy problem.
- How?
- We give her what she wants.
[chuckles]
♪
Shiny.
Mm-hmm.
[suspenseful music]
♪
[audio rewinding]
- You know,
Lexy can be a real bitch.
I mean, no, no, no,
we're cool now.
It's--no, she was
just messing around.
I got to go and do a project.
[audio rewinding]
You know,
Lexy can be a real bitch.
I mean--
[audio rewinding]
You know,
Lexy can be a real bitch.
I mean--
- Hey.
- You know, Lexy can be a--
- How's it going in here?
- Super.
Thanks for knocking,
by the way.
- Devon, tone.
- Tone?
What about privacy?
- I didn't know
you had anything to hide.
- Of course not, Detective.
- My roof, my rules.
- Copy that.
- I need to talk to you
about Jake.
- What about Jake?
- I think it's best if you
stay away from him from now on.
- Mom, I told you,
I barely know him.
And what,
you're picking my friends now?
- No, of course not.
But I think I have to draw
the line at certain people.
- Certain people?
That's crazy.
What did he do?
- Well, for one, people seem
to drop dead around him.
- Jake's dad died and now
you're making Jake the bad guy?
- This isn't about Jake's dad.
This is about my son.
- Yeah, this feels very caring.
- Either Jake is trouble,
or trouble seems to follow him,
and I don't want you
mixed up in it.
- You're wrong, okay?
Jake wouldn't hurt anyone.
And I'm going to prove it.
- You know what?
This isn't a debate.
It's an edict.
Stay away from him.
[somber music]
♪
[door creaks]
[audio rewinding]
- No, she was just mess--
[dramatic, eerie music]
♪
[knocking on door]
- Why are you here?
- I just--
I thought it was cool of you
to apologize the way you did.
- I know.
- I--and I just
thought that you should
have Chucky.
- Chucky?
Chucky!
- She can have him?
Really?
- Yeah.
- [squealing]
- This means a lot to her.
Thank you.
But just to be clear,
I don't want you to think
we're, like,
friends or something now.
- No, no.
No.
- Come on.
- When it all comes together,
it's like fireworks.
- Not friends.
- And, God, I love
to watch the sparks fly.
[playful spooky music]
♪
[ominous music]
- Here you go, Chucky.
- Mom, have you seen
my biology book?
- Uh--
[shushes]
- Great, what's
the little genius doing now?
- Shh, look.
[eerie music]
- [child's voice]
I like to be hugged.
♪
- Can I give Chucky a hug?
- He likes to be hugged.
- Okay.
Okay, come here.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Thank you, Chucky.
That was a good hug.
- [indistinct whispering]
- He wants to give you a hug.
♪
- Lexy, he's waiting.
[tender, eerie music]
♪
- I like to be hugged.
- Every killer needs a cover.
Personally, I like hiding
behind an innocent face.
- Hackensack continues
its streak
as one of the top ten
safest cities in America.
Mayor Michelle Cross cited
a high priority
on safety
and citizen involvement.
- Okay, brat, you gonna be okay
in here for a while?
- Mm-hmm.
- I thought you were
watching "Westworld."
- Chucky says life's too short.
He wants to watch the news.
[TV drones in background]
[ominous music]
♪
[suspenseful music]
- [growls]
- Hey.
Sorry.
It took forever
for my parents to leave.
- How long will
they be gone for?
- Oh, as long as it takes
for everyone
to finish crying
over poor Jake Wheeler.
- I brought your favorite.
- Ooh.
- Courtesy
of my parents' stash.
- Ooh!
Thanks.
[sultry rock music]
- Let it go, Junior.
He isn't worth it, all right?
She isn't either.
- Why didn't you ask me
to bring something?
- [laughing]
Oh, my God.
You're kidding, right?
If your dad caught you stealing
his liquor, he'd be pissed.
Oliver's parents
don't give a shit.
- Never mind.
What are you doing
with Jake's doll?
- He brought him over
for Caroline.
Oh, and I talked to him
like you wanted me to,
so you can stop giving me shit.
- Thanks, Lex.
I appreciate that.
- Caroline,
come get your stupid doll.
- There you are!
- You won't mention that Junior
and our friends came over
to Mom and Dad, right?
It'll be our little secret,
okay?
Cross your heart.
- Cross my heart.
[eerie music]
- [sighs]
♪
- Thank you for caring enough
about our daughter
to meet with us, but...
[scoffs]
I just need to ask.
How long is this going to take?
Oh, we have theater tickets,
and, you know,
people notice
when the mayor shows up late.
- [chuckles]
- Hi, hi.
Sorry I'm so late.
Traffic was just terrible.
Hi, Michelle. Hi, Nathan.
Hello, ladies.
- Hi.
- Mrs. Wheeler.
- Thank you for joining us.
Okay, so now that
we're all together, uh,
Ms. Fairchild and I would like
to discuss with you
recent events
with Jake and Lexy.
We want to ensure
that each student feels safe
here at Perry Middle School--
- And I assure you,
we want that too.
One of my first moves as mayor
was allocating funds
to school safety programs.
- We believe that bullying
is unacceptable.
- As do we.
- It's come to our attention
that Lexy has been
bullying Jake.
[both laugh]
- Our daughter
is not the bully.
If anything, she's the victim.
Did you see what that kid did
at the talent show?
He humiliated her.
- This has gone far beyond
typical name-calling.
- Look, excuse me,
Jake's been through
a lot lately.
- That is not an excuse
for his behavior.
- I'd actually like
to bring this back to Lexy.
- We don't need to sit here
and listen
to these baseless attacks
on our daughter.
- A student brought this
to my attention.
[dance music playing,
laughter]
[tense music]
♪
- [grunting]
- What is this?
Her Halloween costume?
- She's dressed up
like Lucas...
My brother.
Why would you let her do that?
- Okay, look,
we all know that communicating
with teenagers is a challenge.
I think we can all agree
the best thing is to go home,
talk to your kids,
find a way to move forward.
[dramatic music]
♪
[crow cawing]
[wind whooshing]
[bird calling]
♪
- Mom, you always said
it would get better,
but it never did.
Everything just got worse.
I don't expect you
to forgive me.
And I'm--
I'm sorry I'm not the person
that you wanted me to be.
[crickets chirping]
- [sighs]
Hey, it's time for bed.
Did you brush your teeth?
- And Chucky's too.
- Good job.
- Okay, go to sleep.
- You didn't do it right.
- What?
- Bedtime.
You have to sing to me.
Daddy sings to me.
- [laughing softly]
- If you tell anyone
about this, I'll kill you.
- I won't say a word.
- [sighs]
[sighs]
Um...
♪ La, la, la, la, la
♪ All our time has come
♪ Here but now they're gone
♪ Seasons don't fear
the reaper ♪
♪ Nor do the wind,
the sun, or the rain ♪
♪ We can be like they are
♪ Come on, baby,
don't fear the reaper ♪
♪ Baby, take my hand,
♪ We'll be able to fly,
don't fear the reaper ♪
[soft dramatic music]
♪
Okay.
Snug as a bug.
- What about Chucky?
- Snug as a bug.
Now go to sleep.
- Hey, kid.
I'm gonna go kill your sister.
Wanna come?
- I'm sleepy.
- You snooze, you lose.
[grunting]
Snug as a fuckin' bug.
[intense, spooky music]
♪
[electronic dance music]
- ♪ Let it happen
♪ Oh
♪ Let it happen
[people whoop, laugh]
♪ Oh
♪ Let it happen
[music playing
through headphones]
[quiet laughter, whooping]
♪ Stand up
from a higher place ♪
♪ Closing my eyes
♪ And I still
know the taste ♪
♪ The touch of your skin
♪ When the sun
hits your face ♪
♪ And if you're ever lonely
[music playing softly
through headphones]
[camera shutter clicks]
♪ With you
♪
- [sighs]
- ♪ Ooh
[dance music changes]
- Oh, my God, I love this song!
Come on!
- I don't dance.
- Yes, you do.
Come on.
[laughing]
♪
Come on.
[laughing]
Whoa!
- I won't let you fall.
[dramatic musical flourish]
[ominous music]
♪
- Why aren't you in bed?
- Chucky's gone.
- Are you sure?
Maybe he fell under your bed.
- He said he's going
to kill you.
- Caroline,
why would you say that?
- I didn't say it.
Chucky did.
- [sighs]
Come on.
[dance music playing
through headphones]
♪
- Attention,
citizens of Hackensack.
A murderer is on the loose.
We urge you
to stay in your homes.
Another body was found today--
[glass shatters]
- [gasps]
- Bringing the body count
to 19.
[footsteps, glass shattering]
- We urge you
to remain in your homes--
[person yells out]
- [panting]
- [grunting]
- Mom?
Dad?
[ominous music]
[grunting]
[glass shatters]
[gritty electronic music]
♪
- [sighs]
What a pain in the ass.
Stupid doll.
♪
[sighs]
Where the hell
is this stupid thing?
[door slams]
[spooky gritty
electronic music]
♪
- [gagging]
[flesh squelching]
- [grunts]
- [gags]
[both grunt]
- Dad?
- Ugh!
[flesh squelching]
[partygoers cheering]
- Hey, Lexy.
- Ah!
Ugh!
[groaning]
- Shit, my bad.
I thought you were Lexy.
- [whimpering]
- Eh, fuck it.
- No!
[screaming]
[flesh squelching]
[dance music building]
- [panting]
- [grunts]
Charles, run.
♪
- Charles?
[gasps]
Charles, come on.
Okay, in here.
It's okay, it's okay.
Shh, shh.
[flesh squelching]
- [gagging, gasping]
[screaming]
[unhinged music]
♪
[coughing, gagging]
- [panting, grunting]
[ominous music]
♪
- Caroline, I can't find...
[dance music fades in]
Never mind.
♪
[door slams, music stops]
[tense music]
♪
[eerie music]
[curtains rattle]
- [shouts]
- [gasps]
[coughing]
- [growling]
- [screams]
[both grunting]
[frantic, suspenseful music]
♪
[glass shatters]
[wind whooshes]
[sinister music]
- [cackling]
- [coughing, grunting]
- [gagging]
- [cackling]
- [shrieking]
- [yelps]
[fire whooshes]
♪
- [whimpering]
- This is for Jake,
you fucking little [bleep].
- [screams]
- [laughing]
[dance music playing
through headphones]
[eerie music
mixing into dance music]
♪
[explosion whooshes]
[fire crackles]
♪
- [laughing diabolically]
[tense music]
- [panting, shushing]
- I can't breathe.
- Okay, okay.
Shh.
[whimpering]
[gasps]
Shh.
[crying]
[siren wailing]
- [breathing shakily]
[gulps]
I'm sorry.
[crying]
[sniffles]
[dramatic music]
♪
[dramatic musical sting]
- I helped.
- You got guts, kid.
I'll give you that.
Here.
You want to do this right?
You've got to cover
your tracks.
[lips pop]
See you around, kid.
[upbeat retro music]
- So to answer your question,
Jake, some killers are made,
but the best of us are born.
Sometimes we just need
a little push.
- ♪ Everybody wants
to be different ♪
- ♪ Just be you
- ♪ I know it's true
- ♪ But, baby,
please don't change ♪
- [laughing diabolically]
- ♪ Just be you
♪ Don't you do it,
please be true ♪
♪ 'Cause you're mine,
just be you ♪
♪ Don't look
through everybody ♪
- ♪ Just be you
- ♪ Like they're
a windowpane ♪
- ♪ Just be you
- ♪ They're all
just like you and me ♪
♪ Please be you
♪ Don't you do it,
please be true ♪
♪ 'Cause you might just be