Poppy, can we take a photo with you?
Sure, but please take this leaflet.
Let's go to the backdrop.
Guys, move over.
We're taking a photo here.
You stand here, and you here.
Bota!
DRAMA CLUB
Come take a photo for us.
Will you sign up for our Drama Club?
You have to!
Ready?
Squeeze in.
One, two...
Got it.
Thank you.
Don't overact!
Please take our leaflet.
Sign up over there.
Look at that. Is he from another planet?
My prince charming.
Come and wake me up
from the eternal sleep with your kiss.
Did you just peck me?
Hot latte with no foam, please.
Same for me.
That's Non's favorite drink.
Who's Non?
That architecture student.
Did you hear?
Non and I have the same taste in coffee.
Same as me too!
Just me. Not you.
You know what?
The other day when I brushed past him...
I was so nervous I couldn't look at him.
But I felt like...
He was sneaking a look at me.
He must have feelings for me.
Poppy, if you didn't look at him,
how could you know he was looking at you?
It's all in your head!
Bota!
Stay here.
Hello.
It's me, Mom.
Hi, Mom.
Thought you worked so hard
you forgot your daughter in Thailand.
Of course not,
but it's pretty hectic here in Seoul.
Hold on.
An envelope, in the wardrobe.
Found it.
A big brown envelope?
Yes.
Check the document inside.
-Is it a title deed?
-I'm looking.
Yes, it is.
Can you drop it off at your aunt's?
Sure. I'll do it before class.
Good.
Miss you, love.
Miss you too.
I have to go.
Call me more often.
Okay.
Bye.
DALAH PHIPHATKUL
TANIL CHAISAMUT
How are you? I miss you so much.
It's raining a lot here. What about there?
How romantic!
Everybody has their own love story
kept in a memory box
and stashed away in a corner,
waiting for it to melt into thin air.
These love letters
are so sweet and tender.
Mom's first love has been kept here.
Hear that, kitty?
You're Kajorn, right?
Yeah.
I'm Tanil, from Class C.
Okay. Hi.
Beautiful poems.
They say you can write love letters
that win over girls.
You must have a way with words.
Please write one for me.
I tried but it sucked.
Her name is Dalah.
An MP's daughter
my dad wants me to marry her.
Please help me out.
WEEKS EARLIER
Hey, Kajorn.
How many fish shall we catch today?
How about four?
Why four?
So they're in pairs.
So, whoever catches no fish
has to buy sweets for everyone.
For real?
Yeah.
Right on.
Look, that's Mr. Kham's beautiful niece.
She goes to school in the city.
An angel is out of your league, man.
She's waving at me.
Not at you!
-At me.
-Hi, there.
-My name's Yod.
-Hello.
-I'm Chai.
Hello. I'm Yod.
Kajorn, let's go catch some fish.
Get it, Chai.
I can't.
Chai, move your ass!
Trap it!
-Easy, easy.
-What are you doing?
Damn!
These boys always sneak in
to steal our fighting fish.
You've got some nerve
stealing from my grandpa's orchard.
If he finds out, you're finished.
Please don't tell him!
It's just some fish.
Fine. I won't tell him.
But you have to do something for me.
Of course! I'll do anything for you!
You know the haunted house
across the river?
Take me there.
Don't go. The demon will break your neck!
Or Grandpa will give you hell.
Noi, if you're so scared, stay here.
But don't tell anyone.
I'm definitely going there.
What do you say?
Ghosts or Grandpa, what scares you more?
Meet me tomorrow at the river.
Sure.
So, what was that?
Yod.
Find me a boat.
Okay.
Chai.
Teach me to row.
Me?
I can't row a boat.
-Hi.
Please get in.
Take my arm.
Well, my name is Dalah.
I'm Kajorn.
Are you sure you know how to row?
Piece of cake,
though it's my first time today.
The haunted house is that way.
Oh, that way.
Take the flashlight. I won't need it.
Damn it!
Don't hold it like that.
It's spooky.
Don't!
Old folks warn us not to call out
to unusual things.
Let's get out of here.
Still want to see a ghost?
It's going to rain.
We'd better hurry.
Don't worry, let's find a shelter first.
We'll come back when the rain stops.
Are you hurt?
I've sprained my ankle.
Let me help you.
So, there are no ghosts.
Isn't that a good thing?
Why did you want to see ghosts?
I'm curious...
I want to know
what happens when people die.
So, you go to school here?
I'm from around here,
but I study in the city.
Me too.
I only come back to visit Grandpa
during school breaks.
Hungry?
Be careful.
Don't worry. Almost there.
Watch out.
Are you hurt?
You're okay?
Wait here.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Slowly.
Thanks.
Look.
So beautiful.
You've done a lot for me today.
But I haven't done anything for you.
You don't have to.
I had so much fun today.
Thank you, Kajorn.
Miss Dalah!
-There she is!
-Be careful.
I'm sorry I got you in trouble.
It's all right.
My dear, are you all right?
I'm fine, Grandpa.
Kajorn! You damn boy!
I'm in so much trouble because of you!
Please, Miss Dalah.
Let's go home.
THE PROBABILITY THEORY
The least likely event
can in actuality happen.
The probability of an event
is a number that shows
how likely it is that a random event
will happen.
The probability of any given event is
equal to the ratio
of an event of our focus...
-But it can or cannot happen...
-Bota!
Why are you here? This isn't your class.
I'm here to deliver good news.
Move over.
The story I proposed
will be performed by the club.
Really?
Congratulations!
Which story, anyway?
The one you told me about.
Which one?
Your mom's love letters!
No! Not that one!
You can't do that.
It's personal and I trusted you!
If my mom finds out,
she's going to kill me.
Bota, calm down.
Your mom lives in Korea.
How could she find out?
You have to help me write the script.
No, I'm not going to,
and no one can make me.
You have to.
You two! Take your business outside!
Now!
The director said he loves the story.
He promises to let me play the lead.
You know that's always been my dream,
being a female lead!
This is my big break.
Won't you help make my dream come true?
Why did he choose you, anyway?
Dear Dalah,
while I was writing
this letter by the window,
a gentle breeze came through.
So I put it in the envelope
along with my words.
I hope the wind of love
will make you feel wonderful.
SCENE 1
A MAN IS SITTING BY THE WINDOW
After she came back from Grandpa's,
she was ill for weeks.
I don't know what she had.
But when she left the hospital,
she became bright and happy.
She'd had a sad air about her
since she lost her mother.
It hurts me having to write
the love letter for Tanil.
There are so many things
I wish I could tell her myself.
But at least this letter gives me a chance
to talk to her again.
Done.
Man, so sweet.
Sugary, impossibly sweet!
You're so damn good, like it's all
coming straight from your heart.
Don't flatter me.
I have something for you.
-You don't have to.
-Come on. Here.
Thanks.
"To the end of the Earth,
to the edge of the ocean
My love knows no bounds
Beneath the ground,
or under the magical stream..."
Kajorn.
She wrote back!
Thanks, man. Your letter
truly works wonders! Awesome!
She wrote me back, ma'am!
She invited me to go see her school show.
Sent me a couple of tickets.
Wanna come along?
There'll be lots of cute chicks.
Dalah plays beautifully.
That was so beautiful.
Thank you.
You're wonderful.
Thanks, Dad.
Come join us for lunch.
My pleasure, sir.
Let's go, Dalah.
Time for lunch.
Hi. I didn't expect to see you here.
I have to run back.
I snuck out.
Right.
Dalah.
Will I see you again?
Fantastic!
Let's take ten. We'll do the next scene
when we come back.
Non, can I have a word with you?
Take a look here...
Hey!
I'm so happy Non accepted the role.
He rejected every play
they offered him before.
But he likes this script
and wants to have a go.
But, in fact, he accepted
because he knows I'm the lead actress.
Poppy.
You didn't tell anyone
I wrote the script, right?
Of course not. It's your mom's life story.
And this is just college theater.
Anyway, what's with the makeup?
I've never seen you with makeup.
-You're pretty.
-I had stuff to do.
What stuff?
Well...
Non!
This is Bota, my best friend.
Bota, this is Non.
Hi.
Poppy.
Let's discuss the next scene.
Coming.
Excuse me.
Wait!
Do you know who wrote the script?
No, I don't.
In case you bump
into the writer, tell her that...
it's a fantastic script.
Right.
Are you all right?
Aren't you feeling well?
Your cheeks are kind of red.
-Got a fever?
-No! Nothing!
I'm totally fine.
I have to go check the next set.
Bota!
You forgot your bag.
Thank you.
-Wait up!
-No.
It's pretty crowded.
I've never been to this kind of party.
You think Dalah's here already?
She'll be here soon.
Here she is.
Dahla, this is Kajorn.
Good evening.
Nice to meet you.
You guys are friends?
We're best pals.
This is Tubtim, my best friend.
Hi, nice to meet you.
I'll get you some drinks.
I'll come with you.
Kajorn is so cute.
I miss you.
I miss you too.
CHARITY DANCE
I didn't know you're Tanil's friend.
Now we meet again.
See you guys later.
It was nice meeting you.
Good luck.
Let's go.
This is my first time at a dance party.
On the floor I felt like
a storybook princess...
dancing with a prince.
One day when I actually meet my prince,
I will...
Kajorn!
I had a great time today.
-I want to--
-Thank you for today.
All right. I'm leaving now.
Bye.
Non is such a gentleman.
Popular and nice.
Strange that he's never dated a girl.
Maybe he's waiting for the right one.
That's me! I'm definitely his right one.
It must be my destiny and you're my cupid.
Let's drop the subject.
Where shall we go tomorrow?
Tomorrow after class
Non will give me a birthday treat.
He asked for you to come along.
I happened to tell him
that we have the same birthday.
So he wants to treat you too.
Bota, rehearsal time!
Okay. That's all for now.
Poppy.
Can you try on the costume now?
If it doesn't fit,
we'll have time to fix it.
Right.
That was good, but can you be more--
Director,
I need two people on stage
to set up the light.
You, there.
Dance with him, would you?
Me?
I can't dance.
It's just for marking.
Just follow Non's lead. Come up here.
Come!
Repeat the same routine,
but you have to lead her.
Ready?
May I?
Don't be nervous.
Ready! Music!
Bota.
What?
Your foot.
I'm sorry.
So sorry.
It's all right.
-Here you are.
-What?
Come on.
-What's up?
-Let's continue.
Okay.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
Just twisted my ankle.
Thais are peace-loving
but do not fear to fight
They will never let anyone
threaten their sovereignty
Sacrificing every drop of their blood
for the nation
Hail the nation of Thailand
Long last the victory
Hurrah
Tanil!
-Take him to the nurse.
-Yes, sir.
Can you walk?
What are you doing?
She hasn't replied to my letters lately.
Usually, I'm not anxious
about something like this.
I want to give her a present
that makes her feel special.
Help me pick something.
Do it yourself.
You don't need me.
I do because you're my best friend.
You know my feelings more than anyone.
Right?
Kajorn.
This? It looks like her.
Or this?
This is perfect.
See? You know me best.
How much is it?
Happy Birthday to you
-I'll put it on a plate.
-Thank you.
Thanks.
I have presents for both of you.
I'm taking this one.
Thanks.
What is it? A bomb?
Actually, I meant to give you this one.
Thank you. It must be something special.
Obviously.
Poppy.
I'm going home.
Have some cake with us first.
I'd better go.
Thank you for the present.
Can you take me home later?
Yes.
I don't want it.
Look, it's not my dad's idea.
I want to give it to you.
I really like you.
That brooch. You chose it, didn't you?
Didn't you care
about how Tanil and I would feel?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to buy it for you.
But I couldn't afford it.
Tanil saw me holding it.
He took it and went to pay for it.
Tanil is an idiot.
No.
He's a good guy.
He's an idiot.
Because he's too good.
He's perfect for you.
We shouldn't see each other again.
Our love will only hurt everyone.
I won't see you and Tanil again.
When the sun shines in the morning,
I think of you.
When the moon sparkles at night,
When the sun shines in the morning,
I think of you.
When the moon sparkles at night,
Wait, Dalah.
Can we talk?
Please.
Can we just be like we used to be?
Between us, it's impossible.
No.
There's got to be a way.
Why are you doing this?
You'll die of pneumonia.
I'm doing this...
because I love you.
Hi, there.
Hi.
Wait.
Where are you going?
To the library.
But the library is that way.
It's not that far.
If we hop around the buildings,
we won't get soaked.
I'll walk with you.
I have a magic umbrella.
Ready?
One, two, three.
It's still there and has never changed
Still beautiful and valuable in my heart
The memory of someone I once knew
Ready?
Even though we said goodbye
But I still remember everything
One promise
I could tell by looking into your eyes
My heart does not need any reason
Holding your hand
I still remember that day
There are words that
only two of us would understand
It's still there and has never changed
Still beautiful and valuable in my heart
The memory of someone I once knew
Even though we said goodbye
I still remember everything
Thank you so much.
No problem.
I'd better go.
See you again.
I've made up my mind.
I'll confess
that I didn't write those letters myself.
She's now sick in a hospital.
What's wrong with her?
The flu's got her again.
No idea why she likes
to go out in the rain.
How long have you been sitting there?
A long while.
I didn't want to wake you up.
Why are you covering your face?
No.
I haven't washed my face.
I've got sticky eyes, I look horrible.
You look as beautiful as always.
Nothing horrible about you.
How did you know I was here?
Tanil told you?
Are you very sick?
I'm sorry.
I always do stupid things.
Apart from loving you...
I'm not good at anything at all.
That's not true.
You're good at many things.
Especially writing romantic letters.
This afternoon,
Tanil came to tell me everything.
I was stunned.
But I'm happy too...
to know that those words
have been coming from you.
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to tell Tanil everything.
That's only fair to everyone.
Don't worry.
Get well soon.
What's up with you?
Make a fist.
Why?
Hit me. Hit me hard.
Do it. Do it now!
Why are you doing this?
Because I'm a terrible friend.
I like Dalah.
I met her and liked her before
you asked me to write the letters.
But I didn't have the guts to tell you.
I remember that necklace.
It belonged to her late mother.
I've suspected you and Dalah
might have feelings for each other.
At first I courted her
just to please my dad.
But when I got to know her,
I really fell for her.
That shouldn't be a problem.
A handsome guy like me
can always find a new girl.
If you keep writing to her,
put my name down on the envelope as usual,
so her family won't get suspicious.
I thought I knew love.
Now all I know is loss.
Do you really need so many of them?
Not really.
Just in case.
-Thank you, sir.
-You're welcome.
I miss you.
If I missed you more my heart would break.
Please say hello to the river
and the fireflies for me.
Tell them I miss them so much.
And that I'm doing fine here.
-Your letter.
-Thank you.
I'm jealous of the sun for it gets
to wake you up in the morning.
I'm jealous of the water
for it gets to kiss you every day.
Whenever you look out the window
and see tree branches
dancing with the wind,
please remember
that the one you love is loving you too.
It's school break now.
Couples go out, walking hand in hand.
But I can only write you letters.
I miss you so much.
Please wait for me.
I'm going to ask my dad
to let me visit Grandpa's.
I long for the day
I'll see your face again.
On a long and lonely night,
close your eyes
and put your ear to the pillow.
You'll hear our song in your dream,
singing, "I love you."
Bota.
Here's Non's umbrella.
Can you give it back to him?
Why are you asking me?
Remember that day when it rained so hard?
Did you bring your umbrella?
Guess I didn't.
It really is a magic umbrella.
I'll return it to him.
It's still there and has never changed
Still beautiful and valuable in my heart
The memory of someone I once knew
Even though we said goodbye
I still remember everything
Poppy.
What's wrong?
I just told Non...
I liked him.
He didn't say a word back.
He must have someone else.
All this time I thought he liked me.
Why is it like this?
It's okay.
Everything will be all right.
Hello?
I don't think I can help you
with the play anymore.
My grades have dropped.
I need to focus on my studies.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Bye.
When the sun shines in the morning,
I think of you.
Kajorn and Dalah are so much in love.
I tried but she never even saw me.
Because you're a good-for-nothing.
Never once did you succeed
in what I asked you to do.
She's the daughter of a bigshot MP.
Do you realize that you're
jeopardizing our family business?
Please don't hit me, Dad.
I'll make her like me. I promise.
Please don't, Dad! I'm sorry.
Don't hit me.
That's enough.
See? Because you're so weak.
The boy's a total failure.
Don't hit Mom. Please.
It's all my fault. I'm so sorry.
You're a curse to the family.
I shouldn't have a son like you.
-Dalah.
-Yes, Dad.
Good morning.
You'll arrive
during the Songkran festival.
I'll be waiting at the station.
BAN DIN LAN
-Take him to the nurse.
-Yes, sir.
Tanil!
Help! He's hung himself!
Help!
Tanil!
Why are you doing this? Tanil!
Tanil! Wake up!
Help!
Why did you do this?
Wake up! Tanil! Wake up!
TO EVERYONE I LOVE - TANIL
Go and sit by the bed.
When he opens his eyes...
and you're the first person he sees,
he will be very happy.
Come on, you'd better wake up soon.
So we'll go out
and have fun together again.
Remember when we went dancing?
Next time I'll you teach you a new move.
Kajorn!
FIRST LOVE
Listen up, folks!
We must stand united
to fight the imperialist nations
that are using their influence
to take control of our country.
-We will never give in.
-Never!
-We will never give up.
-Get out!
-Never give in.
-Never give up.
-Get out!
-Never give in.
-Never give up.
-Get out!
-Never give in.
-Never give up.
-Get out!
Come this way.
Come!
Run! Quickly!
Give me some water!
Are you okay? Get up.
Get back there!
This way.
Over here.
Sit down.
-Wash your face with this.
-Thank you.
Keep running!
Go this way!
You okay now?
Tanil...
You look much better.
Mature, serious, like a different person.
After what happened,
I decided to grow up
and turn myself around.
What about you?
What are you doing here?
I just finished college
and am looking for a job.
Today I came for a test
at the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
Maybe I won't get it.
I'm sure you will.
Back then, if I hadn't been so stupid,
I would've had a degree by now
instead of ending up a permanent dropout.
And... have you heard from Kajorn?
The trucks are leaving!
Excuse me.
Kajorn!
Do you hear me?
Look at me!
Kajorn.
What have I done wrong?
Look at me.
Kajorn!
-Kajorn!
You have to come back.
Take care of yourself.
Kajorn.
I've missed you.
Make it back, pal!
Shit!
Medic!
-Medic.
-He's dead.
Medic!
Pull out!
Run. Hurry.
Go!
Kajorn!
Kajorn.
Cover him!
On the right!
Over here.
It's been ages.
You're still as beautiful as ever.
Not really...
I'm getting old.
You still look good too.
How have you been?
I haven't heard from you for a while.
I'm so sorry.
I've been busy.
Are you doing well?
Yes.
I have something to tell you.
Tell me, then.
I got married.
Congratulations.
Why haven't you married yet?
You must have many admirers.
I'm a workaholic.
So I haven't been thinking of marriage.
I have so many things to tell you.
But when I see you,
I forget about everything.
Look at that little piano.
It brings back the memory of that day
when I heard you play so beautifully.
I wish I could hear you play again.
It'd be a shame if I don't get a chance.
It's funny thinking about us...
We were so naive.
We let emotions get the better of us.
When something happened...
we laughed...
and we cried too.
But the past is the past.
I know I have to endure
How do I look now?
Not to fall for you again
You look cheerful and happy.
But I want to see you look even happier.
I will let you go
Kajorn, I'm crying.
Don't you see my tears?
How long do you think
you could hide it from me?
I'm ready to forget everything
I'm ready to stay away
Let our memories fade away
I know I can't do it
I'm willing to get hurt
When I think of our past
I almost did it.
No.
But you were so convincing.
I almost believed you.
I know you won't come
I don't want to think too much
Truthfully
I didn't think it would be hard
I came to return this to you.
Thinking that you're no longer with me
But it is so difficult
I'm ready to forget everything
I'm ready to stay away
Let our memories fade away
I know I can't
Keep it.
I'm not ready for the agony
It's been yours...
since the first day we met.
I'm ready to stay away
Let our memories fade away
I know I can't
I'm not ready for the agony
When I think of
Our past
It's strange that my story
and my mom's are remarkably similar.
We choose what we think is best
for the man we love,
but in exchange for pain.
Her letter has taught me
a deeper meaning of love.
But I don't want my love
to end the same way as hers.
Now, I don't know what will happen...
but I've decided to try
saving this love in my own way.
I hope I've made the right choice.
Poppy. Non.
It's not raining.
What's with the umbrella?
I have something to tell you.
I...
I've liked Non...
from the very beginning.
Hold on.
I...
Why didn't anyone tell me?
Bota.
What the hell?
Poppy, wait!
I'm learning to play the guitar.
I'm still not very good at it.
But I wanted to play this song for you.
Please listen.
Love comes with the wind
Nestles closely
With care
When I first met you
Everything became so beautiful
We met because of destiny
I know you think the same
Two hearts united as one
This is our eternal love
Play with me.
Come on.
Stay here.
What's that?
I WANT TO BE THE LOVE OF YOUR LIFE
Toom.
Still here?
Your date won't be waiting for you.
Toom's just left.
She asked you to look after the shop too?
She didn't tell me.
Get to work, then.
Why do we always have the same taste?
It's you...
who copies my taste.
So you and Non...
Did you do it?
Stop it!
I heard you auditioned
for professional theater.
How was it?
I got a supporting role.
That's awesome.
My friend's going to be a star.
I was lucky to be in the play you wrote.
They saw my potential there.
It wasn't really my play.
It's all my mom's story.
You know what?
I thought your mom's letters
were a trick of destiny
to bring me and Non together.
With you as my cupid.
Turned out I was the bad guy
who got in the way of the leading couple.
Don't be such a drama queen.
What can I do?
I'm on my way to become a famous actress.
It's nice here.
Pretty windy.
You could get blown away.
After that day...
did they ever meet again?
No, my mom didn't meet Kajorn again.
Then, after he passed away...
Miss Dalah.
Thank you for coming.
Do you remember me?
I'm Kajorn's friend.
And also...
his brother-in-law.
You were in the gang
that snuck into Grandpa's orchard.
Yes.
Before Kajorn died,
he asked me to give this to you.
Here.
He wanted you to keep it.
After you got married,
he married my sister.
They have a son.
Please, excuse me.
Mommy, look at the rainbow.
I still remember that rainbow.
It was the biggest
and most beautiful one I've ever seen.
I remember that rainbow, too.