Phoon, aren't you going to apply for a creative position?
I'm scared I might be dreaming.
You're definitely not dreaming.
I'm right next to you, Mr. Ray.
Really.
Pierce is getting to produce Jedi's new single!
I don't care if you're together or not.
But if you want to work here,
you have to demonstrate your skills to me.
Jedi, you're here...
(Previously)
Huh?
(Close Friend 2)
("The Drunkard and the Indoor Cat")
All right. Is everyone ready?
The thing is, I want something new and positive.
I want a love song that doesn't use the word "love".
Like what you said just now, Pai.
A ship pairing.
Do anything to convince the listeners
that Milin and Jedi
are really in a relationship.
Huh? But...
Did you just come up with a creative idea, Typhoon?
No.
If you have any new ideas, just share them with us.
We're a team after all.
Okay.
You have to keep what's going on between me and Jedi top secret.
But before that,
you have to tell me first how you...
and Jedi got together.
It's a long story.
I'll tell you later.
I don't want to talk about it here either.
Okay? I'll call you later.
What about you? What are you doing here?
Today's my first day on the job.
What? Really?
Well, my boyfriend works as a producer here.
He's getting to produce new music for Jedi and Milin too.
Milin...
What's wrong?
Oh, Phoon.
- Hi. - Pierce, this is Ray. He's a friend
from high school. I've told you about him before.
Ray, are you crazy?
Which no-name's cutout did you bid for? It's like 5,000 baht!
Keep it down, or my mom will hear you.
More importantly, he has a name.
This is Jedi. I'm a huge fan of his.
But anyway,
it shouldn't have cost 5,000!
Well, I love him.
Even if he's not famous or does something lame,
I'll be his fan forever.
Right. You're his only fan.
Here. Catch.
One, two...
- Hup. - Did you catch it?
Here.
Pull it up.
Who's there?
- Mommy! - Hi, Mom!
Jedi!
Oh!
Mommy...
Jedi...
Did it snap?
No.
Oh, hi.
You won't believe this. Ray is the boy...
A fan.
A fan of Jedi.
Oh.
- Jedi Army, right? - That's right.
I'm not sure if Jedi can come out and meet his fans today.
- Anyway, we'll see. - Oh, okay.
Ray just dropped by to see me.
Oh, okay.
Phoon.
Can I have a word with you?
- Right now? - Mm.
I'll call you later.
See you.
- Bye. - Bye.
Why didn't you tell me?
I wanted to surprise you.
I also wanted you to see
that I can stand on my own two feet.
Well done.
But you heard what Pai said, didn't you?
Now that you're on the team,
you have to be professional.
We can't act like a couple like when we're at home anymore.
You know that, don't you?
Why?
Like this, for example.
Okay. Noted.
From now on, I won't go near you when we're at work.
I'll stay two meters away from you, okay?
You're going to get it when we get home, drunkard.
- I have to go back to work now. - Mm.
I'm staying at the condo tonight.
Mr. Ray,
you're okay with being alone, right?
Staying the night at the condo again.
That's today's outfit.
It means the photo was just taken.
You didn't tell me you were going somewhere else after work.
It's okay.
I can't unsee it now that I've seen it.
So how can I stop myself from overthinking?
Darn it!
Whose car is that in front of our place, Pierce?
Dad?
Mom?
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
Oh? Why should we?
I asked Dad to drive me over.
You're always working and haven't visited us at all.
I've missed you.
And it's almost the end of the durian season.
So I suggested to Dad to come to your new house.
Are you happy?
- Yes. - Give me a hug.
- You really missed him, didn't you? - My dear son.
Mom.
Did you grow taller?
I'm still at the same height.
Did you bring something?
Oh, heaps.
That's right. Heaps. Fruits and all.
- Okay. I'll take care of them. - They're all your favorites.
- Come and give us a hand. - I'll help you.
Here.
Can you open up the trunk?
Phoon,
can you help bring the stuff in?
- Come on. - Okay.
Take this.
- Here. - Thanks.
- And this one. - This one's a little heavy.
Uh...
This is Typhoon, Mom.
We're housemates.
He's one of my colleagues.
Oh.
You're his housemate?
That's right.
And why did you bring so much stuff?
I won't be able to finish everything.
There's a lot.
I brought them over so you can give them to your colleagues too.
Oh.
- But... - Here.
- I'll put it away. - Take them into the kitchen.
- Okay. - Go on.
Come on, Mom.
- The longan can last long. - That's good.
Phoon?
Here. Dig in.
They're all your favorites, Pierce.
Phoon, try this.
It's curry, Mom's recipe.
Authentic Gang Tai Pla tastes like this.
- Oh. - Oh dear.
Sorry. I forgot to tell you the flavor is quite strong.
Really, Pierce. Look at him. He's coughing.
- Drink some water. - Are you okay?
Drink some water.
Are you okay?
Oh? Dad, that's beer!
Well, it is.
- Isn't that okay? - No, Dad.
- There you go. - Thank you.
Drink some water.
You didn't give us a heads up at all, Dad.
I guess you can't really eat spicy food?
No, ma'am.
- Are you okay? - I'm okay.
So you can't eat spicy food at all?
No, ma'am.
- Are you okay? - I am.
Have some clear soup then.
And is it okay for you to drink beer?
Don't you have to drive?
Oh, it's fine.
We're not going home just yet.
Oh, really?
Why?
And where are you staying tonight?
At Aunt Pin's?
Why would we stay the night at someone else's house?
My son has a house, and it's a big one.
But...
Are you going to let us
visit you for just one day?
Drink some water.
- Okay. - Don't you agree?
Mm.
Dad and I can stay in Pierce's room.
We won't bother you.
- Is that a good thing? - Don't you like it?
Hey.
Where are you going?
You don't have to go. You can sleep in the smaller room.
I should've been sleeping in that room right from the start, right?
Because I'm just your junior who pays the rent.
Come on, Phoon.
You know I haven't told my parents about us yet.
How can I tell them everything?
Then I should be understanding
and shouldn't feel anything about suddenly becoming your junior again.
It's different.
Phoon,
it's not that I'm not going to tell them.
But it needs to be the right time.
We might have to go with the flow for the time being.
I'm sorry.
Do I have any other choice?
Pierce?
Mom asked me to bring the stuff upstairs.
She's worried I might get drunk and fall asleep soon.
Typhoon?
- Goodbye, Dad. - Mm.
Phoon!
Why aren't you picking up?
Where are you going?
I'll sleep at a friend's.
Which friend?
I don't know. Whoever answers my call.
You don't have to go. Get inside.
It's you who should hurry up and get inside,
or your mom will find out.
Hello, Ray? Can you send me your location? I'm heading over.
Mm.
Call me again when you're in front of the gate.
Call me if you can't find it.
Phoon!
Pierce, Dad wants to watch a Chinese movie.
How do you turn on the TV?
Can you come and help me?
Okay, Mom.
Shoot. How did Phoon know I want him to come over?
He definitely has a special sense.
I'm getting goosebumps.
But the person I want to know about this doesn't care about me.
(Happy 1st Anniversary)
Are you feeling unwell?
No.
Someone's...
probably missing me.
Oh.
It's nothing.
Thank you for letting me carpool with you.
It's okay. We're heading in the same direction.
I bothered you at work,
and now you're giving me a lift too.
I told you it's okay.
We still have to work together for a while.
We should help each other in any way we can.
Thank you.
I'm going now.
Drive safe.
Hello, Mom?
I've sent you some money.
It's my first paycheck.
Check to see if you've received it.
(Invoice)
Aren't you too hot-headed, Phoon?
I don't think so.
This time, I'm being as cool-headed as I've ever been.
I didn't cry or cause a scene in front of Pierce's folks.
I've learned my lessons.
I don't understand! We're only colleagues? What is that?
What do you want him to tell her? That you're his boyfriend?
He doesn't have to say that.
But shouldn't he have at least thought
that I'm in a position where we can be open?
Have I ever existed in his life?
Has he ever told his family about me at all?
Calm down.
Look at me.
Let alone our families.
No one knows I'm dating Jedi apart from you.
But in my case, it's been more than four years.
And am I wrong for hoping that he's serious about me?
Come and sit here.
Come on.
Here.
Your anchor for the past four years.
It's been since college.
The ring hasn't darkened at all.
Pierce, do you know I've been waiting for ages?
Why did you just arrive?
Merry Christmas Eve
and happy birthday,
Shorty.
You didn't have to get me flowers.
Do you know how long I've been waiting for you?
Phoon.
Pierce?
Give me your hand.
Thank you, Pierce.
I love you.
I love you too.
I love you very much.
From what you've told me, he sounds like a good guy.
You should give him some time.
There might be something on his mind.
That's why he hasn't told his parents yet.
But his mom seems very kind.
His dad does too.
I think it's work that's more worrisome.
Why did I have to face two problems in one day?
What's up with work?
Once they found out that Pierce and I are together,
our boss had me under scrutiny right away
even though I haven't even done anything.
Pierce also told me to behave appropriately
and that we can't act like a couple at work.
If I'd known, I wouldn't have applied to work at the same place.
But that's in the presence of high-ranking people.
Pierce has a point.
Manners are important.
Besides, you should be on Pierce's side.
Don't whine so much or force him to make a choice.
Otherwise, you'll be the troublemaker.
Wow.
I can't believe that such a thoughtful message
would come out of your mouth.
You've changed a lot.
Ever since I started dating Jedi,
I have to ask myself this every day.
Oh.
By the way, how did you guys start going out?
It's such a wonder.
I know.
It really was a wonder, initially.
But then after we actually started dating,
things have been cruel.
Why?
Does Jedi whip you?
Moron!
What?
What's more painful than being whipped
is getting to be with someone you really like,
but having to keep it a secret.
And it's not just an ordinary secret.
It's a secret at the national level.
There's lobster too, Jedi?
Do you like it?
If you do, then go ahead and order it.
But it comes as a set.
I won't be able to finish by myself.
Jedi, can I take a selfie with you?
Of course not.
Of course I won't refuse.
Can I take one with you too?
- Can I take one too? - Sure.
- Me first. - Yes, you first.
Jedi is very close,
but I feel even more distant.
- This place is beautiful. - Mm.
By the way,
why did you bring me here?
I've bought this house.
- You're not kidding, aren't you? - No.
Is this the real you?
So where's the reward?
I can't go back to being his fan anymore.
Because I don't know how long I'll get to be happy with him.
Maybe my time is about to be over.
I might just be having a sweet dream
and will have to wake up soon.
But...
you get to live in this house with him.
He must be serious about you, right?
I feel like he lets me stay here
because he's scared someone will find out he's with me.
I'm the secret.
I'm like... a mistress.
No, no, no! A mistress sounds too cliché.
I'm like...
an indoor cat.
Meow.
You understand me, don't you?
He comes and goes whenever he pleases.
He plays with me for a bit and then leaves.
And then I become a cat waiting for his owner
without knowing when he's going to return.
Aw. My friend...
has become a cat.
Come on. Let's drink.
Let's drink to our secrets.
Secrets never die.
The expression is "there are no secrets in this world."
Oh, okay.
We're going to drink and forget everything.
Forget about Pierce and Jedi.
Huh?
I have a better idea.
Whoa.
If Pierce finds out,
he's going to complain that I reek of alcohol.
So what? Who cares?
Right. So what? Who cares?
Uh-uh.
No, Jedi's very possessive about the top shelf.
So what? Who cares?
I care.
Let's have this one.
One, two, three!
And now you're with Ray.
I'd like to show you a trending dance move.
I can't sleep.
I can just drink the water here, right?
Sure.
Phoon, what's wrong?
You look like you see a ghost.
It's...
What's up with your top?
He's confused about my top.
You're about to...
You're a sloppy dancer.
What about this?
- Okay. - Where's the music?
- Yes! - You can't take it anymore.
- Yes! - You should go to sleep.
Cut.
What is this? Why did you have to be this close?
Ray, you're my miracle.
Pierce, do any monks come by to receive offerings?
I can do it.
Let's give it a listen.
Do you know what kind of work a creative team does?
It's not just dressing up in chic outfits.
A promoter?