The concept I'm presenting to you today
is a mood that is currently popular.
So the genre of my music is easy-listening.
Anyone can listen to it regardless of age and gender.
Our artist is...
You said you weren't going to drink.
Don't do this again, okay?
I'm worried about you.
Typhoon, listen to me. What's wrong?
Why are you walking away from me?
Did you forget that today is our anniversary?
I'm sorry.
You're only focusing on work right now. I understand that.
I'm just a silly crybaby
who isn't going places.
I haven't changed a bit.
Then can you act as if we're still in love?
I don't want to break up with...
"You've received an exclusive reward for participating"
"in the fan trivia competition of the hottest idol, Jedi."
There, there. Give us a hug.
Oh well. I'll settle with a virtual hug.
If you were granted a wish,
what would you wish for, Mr. Ray?
Is it okay to wish for you
to become a reality for me?
I'll make it for you.
- Jedi, do you remember... - Oh.
I forgot to tell you that I'll have it here.
I'll swap the cups for you.
It's okay. You don't have...
I'll help you wipe it off.
No need.
It's okay.
I thought you said you'd recognize me.
You're Ray,
who won the trivia
and got this VR headset, right?
Are you even real?
Of course. Here.
The stain from the coffee you spilled just now.
What are you doing?
So?
It's better than VR, isn't it?
Mr. Ray?
(Close)
(Friend)
(Close Friend 2)
("I want to tell you about a really awesome surprise.")
(One Year Later)
Pierce?
(Ohm - Thitiwat Ritprasert)
(Fluke - Natouch Siripongthon)
What do you think of my outfit? Does it look okay?
Whoa. Are you going to a wedding or something?
Phoon, aren't you going to apply for a creative position?
Just dress in your own style.
I'm just scared that they'll think I'm too young.
They won't.
Anyone would want to hire
someone like you, Phoon.
Will they even want to hire me?
Of course.
A typhoon is predicted to sweep over all the companies in the nation.
Come on. Hurry up and eat.
It's an auspicious day.
Don't start any trouble elsewhere, okay?
I'll give you a lift.
Don't.
I can go there myself.
Oh? The company's not that far away?
We've moved to a place close to your company
so you won't have to stay the night there.
I'll be fine.
They might not hire me after all.
All right. It's up to you.
I hope you get the job.
As for me, I have to come up with a new project.
A new song for Jedi.
Jedi?
The Jedi?
Wow! That's awesome, Pierce!
It is.
But you have to keep this a secret, okay?
Come on. Energize me.
Hold on. Let's wait until I get a new job.
I was going to give you a lucky charm.
Pierce!
Mr. Ray,
working as a barista.
A die-hard fan.
I wonder what he's like in real life.
Hi!
Huh?
What's up with my Mr. Ray today?
What a grumpy face.
I know now
that this Jedi is fake.
The real one isn't even remotely interested in me.
Huh?
You're from the VR headset?
You're not dreaming, Mr. Ray.
Should we let you rest?
(Kimmon - Warodom Khemmonta)
(Copter - Panuwat Kerdthongtavee)
You look so handsome even in your sleep.
Is this the real you?
The real deal. The original me.
I had a nightmare.
I dreamed that you were the fake one from the VR again, Jedi.
I'm going now.
I'm probably dreaming.
You're shaking.
Are you really that scared?
I'm scared I might be dreaming.
And then everything might disappear once I wake up.
You're definitely not dreaming.
I'm right next to you, Mr. Ray.
Really.
It's good!
It's so good that I got scared.
It still feels incredible.
I don't even know
if I'd get to be with you without the help of the VR.
Of course you would.
I'd obviously go
to the ends of the earth
to find Mr. Ray.
Okay?
The real deal.
Oh, what time is it now?
- Nine. - Oh.
I have to get going.
I have a meeting about my single.
Are you going to come and stay the night here or at the condo?
Let me think about it.
I'll let you know, Mr. Ray.
- I'm going now. - What?
You didn't even give me a kiss or anything.
It's like you read my mind.
Okay?
Jerk.
It's nice to be together like this.
No one knows the real Jedi likes to sing out of tune in the shower.
How long do I have to hide love?
Close your eyes and open your heart
Who do you see?
Tell me
He sleeps with his mouth open.
He doesn't snore but drools.
And he always pays respect to everything.
He believes that there are guardian angels all around us.
I'm the only one who knows about these things.
But the guy named Ray doesn't exist in his life.
How long will this be kept a secret?
Who's calling at this hour?
Ugh, really.
Are you awake? I have a really awesome surprise to tell you.
Mm. What is it?
Pierce is getting to produce Jedi's new single!
Mm. Really?
What? Aren't you excited at all?
You're actually the first to hear about his.
Or have you quit being his fan?
Well, I already know about it.
Oh, that's no fun.
Anyway, what are you doing?
I'm thinking of looking for a job.
Huh? You haven't done that already?
Mm.
I'm waiting for the studio I used to teach at to open again.
They're closed for renovations at the moment.
Oh. What about the cafe you used to work at?
I've already quit.
The owner closed the shop because of an illness.
By the way, I'm about to go and apply for a new job today.
Guess where.
Typhoon, I have to hang up now. My mom's here.
Hey.
What's up with you, Ray?
Dressed for a wedding, you say?
- What is this? - Did you just hit me?
- I did. - You hit me, didn't you?
- There! - Hey!
- Take that! - Jedi! Stop it.
I thought you were in a rush to go to a meeting?
I am.
- I'm going then. - Mm. Hurry up and get dressed.
Come on. See me off.
I can't breathe.
Pierce.
Just a second. I'm trying to concentrate.
Hello, Pai.
What's the matter?
I'm making you the producer of a new face in the company.
This project has to be kept secret.
Because no one has seen her face before.
But I'm going to push her to become number one this year.
And she's going to push you to another level.
Her name is Milin.
I want everyone to be devoted to Jedi and Milin's new project.
It has to top at least three major charts.
Pierce,
I'd like you to be the music director.
You've proven that you can make a song appeal to the masses.
Tina, you're the promoter.
I'd like to see your idea within next week.
- Pai. - Hm?
I have someone else who wants to join the team.
Go ahead.
Hello? You can come in now.
Hello.
I'm Typhoon.
Phoon?
Hm? You know each other?
Well...
Are you Pierce's boyfriend?
I remember seeing you at the party last year.
Typhoon?
I thought you said you don't like drinking.
Is this what adults do at work?
Uh...
That's right.
I don't care if you're together or not.
But if you want to work here,
you have to demonstrate your skills to me.
I will.
Hm?
What about Jedi?
Didn't you come here together?
Oh? That's true.
- Where is he off to? - I don't know.
He's probably gone to the bathroom.
Typhoon, go and get Jedi.
Sure.
What am I going to do now?
- Oh, what should I do? - Right?
What should you do now?
Jedi?
What are you doing here?
This is where I work.
I should ask you why you followed me here.
I was feeling posses...
I mean worried... oh!
I've missed... No, I can't control myself!
What should I do? What should I do?
- Ray, Ray, Ray... - Come here, you.
I can't find the bathroom.
Jedi, you're here...
Ray?
Typhoon.
Surprise! Hey there.
Hi.
Okay. Cut.
- All good. - You can go and get dressed.
Cut.
A slate can go in.
We can go back to sleep now.
Good.
To the ends of the earth to find Mr. Ray.
Where are you going?
I'm going. I'm dreaming.
I'm definitely dreaming.
Really!
- Cut. - You can slate now.
How long till we can show love?
How long do I have to hide love?
Close your eyes and open your heart
- Good. Cut. - Thank you.
Next, eat the fruit.
Okay. Cut.
Okay.
- Just a little bit. - Thank you very much.
Okay. Stop.
- Take that! - Jedi! Stop it.
- Jerk. Go away. - I'm sorry.
Let me see your mouth.
Hm? Let me see your mouth.
I thought you said you were in a rush...
I can't find the bathroom.
Je...
Ray?
Surprise!
Hi.
Cut. Check and wrap it up.
Oh, I should move.
Slate.
(Next Episode)
- Who's there? - Hi, Mother!
Jedi!
Do whatever it takes to convince the listeners
that Milin and Jedi
are really in a relationship.
Huh? But...
Did you just come up with a creative idea, Typhoon?
You have to keep what's going on between me and Jedi top secret.
You heard what Pai said, didn't you?
Now that you're on the team,
you have to be professional.
We can't act as a couple like when we're at home.
- Dad? - Hi.
Mom?