(Previously)
You don't want to accept the truth,
or are you embarrassed about our relationship?
It's neither.
Wait for a little bit longer.
I'll find the right time to talk to Mom.
But not right now.
How did these photos get out?
What do you have to say, Jedi?
Nothing.
It's not wrong for people to have secrets.
He didn't murder anyone.
Why do we have to hide this?
I don't care who's the one for you.
I'm okay with just...
being close to you, Jedi.
Have you come to a decision?
I probably won't have the courage to love anyone again.
(Close Friend 2)
(Is There an Expiry Date for Love?)
Oh?
Who said I'm going to get it just now?
Are there going to be any more visitors?
Come on, Phoon. We're home.
Five more minutes.
Five minutes? It's not morning.
Pierce? How did I get here?
I picked you up and drove you home.
You're way too drunk.
Turn on some music. Turn it on.
Gently. Take it easy.
I wonder if it was a mistake or a deliberate move
Your every smile and gesture make me feel suspicious
I wonder
If it was a mistake or a deliberate move
The more you look at me the more I tremble
Every word, every greeting...
I'm thirsty.
Thirsty...
Here. Drink some water.
- Drink slowly, okay? - Okay.
I can't open it.
Here.
Hey, Phoon! Phoon!
Phoon.
All right. Let it all out.
- Nothing's coming up. - What?
Look at you. Your face is all greasy.
Here.
I'm going to dress you up as Santa.
- Come on. - What?
Don't squirm.
Why did you bring me back?
I didn't ask you to.
You didn't. But the owner did.
Jedi called to ask me to pick you up.
Jedi?
What about Ray?
He's heartbroken right now! Gosh!
Come on, Pierce!
He's as wasted as you are.
But you don't have to worry about him.
Jedi's looking after him now.
Let's head inside. It's late.
No!
No? You're not going inside?
Then where do you want to go?
I'm going to stay the night at Mom's.
I can call a taxi.
At this hour?
Won't she punish you if you go there?
She won't.
My mom always understands me.
I tell her everything, unlike someone.
Everything?
Yes.
Including this?
Pierce, what are you doing? I'll hit you! Let go of me!
I'm not scared of you.
You're tiny.
What are you doing?
Teaching a naughty kid a lesson.
Pierce! Pierce!
I'm almost at my limit!
Just a little more.
Pierce!
I can't take it anymore!
Hang in there.
- I have had enough. - A little bit longer. Come on.
- You got this. - My abs hurt.
Almost there.
- Close? - Yes.
- Gosh! - What are you doing, boys?
Oops.
Excuse me.
Mom! Mom!
Mom! Listen to me!
Listen to me, Mom! I can explain!
There's nothing else to explain. I understand everything.
And I've seen everything.
What have you seen, Dad?
And if you understand,
why did you walk away from me?
Well, I was shocked.
Mom. Dad.
Phoon and I...
have been together for four years now.
I love him.
And there's no way I'll change my mind.
Phoon has to be a part of my life in the future.
I want you to understand.
Pierce,
Mom and I have known about this for a very long time.
We were just waiting...
for you to tell us yourself.
And can you...
accept this?
Even if we couldn't,
would we be able to change anything?
Would we be able to force you to break up with each other?
Technically we could.
But if it meant that you would be unhappy,
I wouldn't do it.
But Mom and I don't agree with you entirely.
We need time to adapt
and take it in as well.
I'm not an old-fashioned person.
And you're a grown-up now.
But as parents, we're afraid that you might have to struggle.
We were terribly worried.
I want us to communicate with each other
so that I don't have to make assumptions.
Mom.
Give me a hug.
Typhoon, come here.
Thanks, Dad.
See? Easy-peasy.
Are you okay, Jedi?
You keep staring at me.
I'll never get bored
staring at someone as cute as you.
Silly. Stop staring already. Don't you have work to do?
I don't want to go.
I'm scared you might overthink things if you're alone.
I won't anymore.
Ray,
don't listen to what other people say.
Just remember...
that I love you very much.
Don't forget...
how we first met each other.
Miracles only happen...
with soulmates.
Don't you agree?
Whatever you say.
It's only been a second, but I already miss you.
(What were these two doing at Jedi's place?)
(Probably shared by the same person, but they changed the profile.)
(Carrying the boy at Jedi's)
It's nothing.
It's okay.
(Why were there drunk kids at your house, Jedi? Who are those two?)
Here.
Where did you find these photos?
Someone sent them to us.
We only have until noon.
If we don't pay them 100,000 for each photo,
they're going to leak them.
Nonsense.
Don't transfer them any money.
And go to the police.
Good thing Pai isn't here.
What about you, Pierce and Typhoon? What were you doing at Jedi's?
Typhoon is Ray's friend.
They were just hanging out for a bit.
I don't think that's "a bit".
What about Pierce?
Pierce just went there...
to pick Typhoon up.
He has nothing to do with me.
But this is stirring up suspicion,
and the problem won't be over.
It won't...
if there's someone harassing us
and taking candid photos like this.
So? Can we get to the root of everything?
It's too late.
Oh dear! How did the photos get leaked?
I thought they said we have until noon!
By now, Pai's probably seen all of them.
I think...
the person who leaked the photos isn't after money.
That's why they've set the price so high.
They probably want to see
how the company and Jedi would react.
So?
If you can't give me an answer, you can pack your things and leave.
(Pai)
Hello?
I'm willing to resign.
I just started working here. I'm still on probation too.
But it's not fair.
You didn't do anything wrong.
But it involves work.
It can't be helped, right?
It's okay.
I'll find the time to talk to Tina.
I feel bad.
Well, I think...
if I try to reason with her,
she'll probably understand.
Excuse me.
Typhoon, Tina wants to see you.
Tell me what you know
about Ray and Jedi.
What's wrong? Are you stressed about the leaked photos?
No.
I can tell. No need to hide it from me.
Do you have a lot of time on your hands?
Is that why you're taking a stroll around here?
I'm looking for some inspiration.
Mr. Producer, let me tell you something.
Where there is love, there is suffering.
And where there is content,
there is a song to be written.
It's not funny?
No.
Seriously though.
It's impossible to be in love and not suffer.
Because everyone has expectations.
And therefore, everyone will change.
If you want to be in love without suffering,
then you have to be able to accept and understand changes.
Don't let love revolve around you,
and don't let yourself be the center of your life.
I came across it. It's the concept behind my new song. So?
You like it?
Yes, I do.
I kind of understand.
- So does that mean you don't? - I do.
Anyway,
I get it a lot more now that I've told you about it.
Thanks so much. Cheers.
What's up with him?
Boo!
Teddy's back!
Teddy actually hurried back home today!
Let's see. Is there anything to eat?
Teddy is starving right now!
Mr. Ray?
Ray?
He's not here?
Where did he go?
Ray?
Miracles only happen with soulmates.
But I guess it'll eventually expire.
Getting to be with you
and be loved by you
felt incredibly amazing.
I don't dare to ask for more.
But I think my time is up.
I don't want to be the cause of your troubles.
I have to go now.
I'm sorry that I didn't give you a proper goodbye.
I don't think I can handle it.
Thank you for the time we've spent together.
I love you.
I will always be part of Jedi's Army.
You have reached the voicemail box of...
The number you have reached is not available.
Please leave a message after the tone.
The flowers reminded me of you.
Us meeting each other
is a miracle.
What do you think?
This is better than the VR, right?
This Jedi is fake.
(BEHIND THE SCENE)
Oh, sorry. It's my fault. I heard it wrong.
- You got it right. - It's me. My bad.
You already got it right.
- That's why they've set... - Set the price so high.
- All right. - From the top?
What? Nobody's pranking you.
(Next episode)
Goodbye, Jedi.
If Ray is interested in doing something, he'll do it
and become entirely focused on it, especially when it comes to Jedi.
Ray, wake up.
- What? - What?
A fan's love for their favorite artist
isn't the same kind of love most people would usually think of.
Let's see how far it can go.