(Previously)
I love Phoon.
And there's no way I'll change my mind.
Give me a hug, Mom.
It's only been a second, but I already miss you.
I'm willing to resign.
Boo!
Teddy's back!
Teddy actually hurried back home today!
Is there anything to eat?
Teddy is starving right now!
I'm sorry that I didn't give you a proper goodbye.
I don't think I can handle it.
(Close Friend 2)
("Close Your Eyes and Open Your Heart. Who Do You See?")
Goodbye, Jedi.
Should I give you a hand?
I was going to remove them a while ago.
But I left them there since you seem to like them.
Mom.
You're not going to throw them away anymore?
I've changed my mind. I'll keep them. It's a waste.
Really.
Hasn't he seen any movies?
They say it'll be easier to forget if you throw everything away.
Oh dear.
Hi, everyone.
I'm sorry
for not announcing in advance I'll be live streaming in Meta VR.
I really want you to see me.
There's an urgent matter
that I have to tell you,
my Jedi Army.
(Cheer up. I'm rooting for you.)
(I'm so disappointed. This sucks.)
You've probably seen the news about me two days ago.
I'm sorry
for upsetting
or disappointing all of you,
including...
Ray.
He's the guy in the photos.
I hurt his feelings.
He's important to me.
I don't know
if Ray's watching this live stream.
But I want to let him know
that I'm very worried about him.
That's right.
Ray and I
are really in a relationship.
(- I'm so disappointed. This sucks. - Massive fail, Jedi.)
(Grabs popcorn...)
But please don't be angry with him.
If you're going to be angry with
or take it out on someone,
let it be me.
(- Oh, no... - Who is he?)
(I hate it %^#+*&!?)
I'm admitting to all my faults.
I understand
if you don't want to support me anymore.
But I won't lie to myself any longer.
In this life,
I can't live without Ray.
But now,
I'm about to lose him.
Tell me what you know about Ray and Jedi.
Ray and I have been friends since high school.
He's a lovely person and is unbelievably serious.
If Ray is interested in doing something, he'll do it
and become entirely focused on it,
especially when it comes to Jedi.
I think he's one of Jedi's first fans.
Since before Jedi was famous.
He actually went as far as taking a barista course
because he wanted to make Jedi's favorite coffee.
But I still don't understand. Does such a person actually exist?
He actually expected to be in a relationship with a celebrity?
Well, no.
I don't think Ray expected something like that.
Jedi probably inspired him
to try new things
and to do something different in his life.
A fan's love for their favorite artist
isn't the same kind of love people would usually think of.
It's about giving
without expecting anything in return,
except for getting to see your favorite artist be happy,
have a job, and be successful. That's all.
And how come there's still drama?
Like when a celebrity does something
but it doesn't go along with their fans' expectations.
That's it. There are no expectations.
But then again, there still are.
I think it's similar to parental love.
Parents expect their kids to be happy.
And they feel disappointed
when their kids misbehave.
But they probably won't stop loving them. They're just shocked.
It might take some time for them to understand
and adapt in order to accept.
Apart from his obsession with Jedi, does this guy have special skills?
He's good at dancing. He even used to teach it.
Tina, there's trouble. Jedi's doing a live stream in Meta VR.
By the looks of it, he seems to be doing it on both social media
and the fans' VR.
Jedi!
What's going on?
What is Aun doing?
Why is he letting Jedi do this?
I'll call him.
Right. Typhoon,
can you try calling Ray?
- Okay. - No need.
Just let him be for now.
And let's see how far it can go.
- Pai. - Pai.
Ray, check out the front of the house.
- Mom? - Take a look. Have you seen it?
- See? - What?
Who's that?
Ray!
Can you come out and talk to me?
- Hey! - What's wrong?
Why did he come here?
Is he really at the front of the house?
What is he doing?
Oh my gosh! What's up with him?
Why is he here?
Mom, did you lock the door?
- Yes. - Okay.
How strange.
Come out and talk to me.
Please? Pretty please?
Please? Okay?
Please, Ray?
Please? It won't take long.
Please? Please? Please?
Ray?
You're really watching.
Can you come down and talk to me?
It won't be long. Okay?
- Okay? I want to talk to you. - Stop the live stream first.
- What? - I don't know if it's actually you.
- Stop the live stream first. - What did you say?
Stop the live stream first, or I'm not going to talk to you.
Okay.
Were you followed?
I didn't see anyone.
How did you find out where my mom's house is?
I know everything when it comes to you, Mr. Ray.
You're obviously a stalker.
That's right. I'm a stalker.
Come inside. We'll get in trouble again if someone sees us.
Sit.
Sit down!
Okay.
What's up with you, causing a scene in someone else's front yard?
- Hello, ma'am. - Hello there.
I remember you. Jedi Army.
Don't act like you're a man of the people.
Have a seat, okay?
Well, I'm happy to see you.
Shut it.
I told you. It's over between us.
But it's not over for me.
It has to be over.
Otherwise, you won't have a career, future, or fans left.
I don't care.
No, you have to.
Come on, Jedi. Can you stop acting like you're crazy in love already?
What's up with you?
You said we have to keep it secret because you're worried about work.
So why don't you care now?
Because it has always been what you want,
and...
I'm scared to lose you.
Even if I have to give everything up,
I'm happy to do so.
Jedi, can you not say that?
It's too much.
I won't be able to bear the responsibility.
Then don't.
I can't stand
not being myself either.
If I can't be with the person I love,
then why should I bother having everything else?
All that's left in the end
is just emptiness.
What about your fans? Jedi Army?
I don't want them to be disappointed.
That's why I don't want to lie to them anymore.
I'm sorry
for making you lie as well.
You've probably been feeling uncomfortable
and...
lonely because you were left alone so often.
Ma'am.
I'm Jedi.
I'm Ray's boyfriend.
I'd like to take him back to my place.
I promise
that I'll take good care of him.
And I won't hurt his feelings again.
Jedi, why did you say that to her?
Do you want to go, Ray?
You'll probably have to talk it out with him yourself, Jedi.
This guy's name is Ray.
Hey! Jedi, why did you start streaming?
No! Turn it off!
He's my boyfriend.
He's short
and has squishy cheeks. When he smiles,
you can see his dimples too.
Let me tell you. He's very cute.
I just found out today
that he gets his cuteness from his mom.
Isn't that right, ma'am?
You're embarrassing me.
Come on.
Stop live streaming already.
He's timid.
But he really loves to dance
and is a very good dancer too.
I've also told him
that he makes very good coffee.
But I lied.
He actually sucks.
But what I like
is him.
He always thinks that he's my true fan
and knows everything about me.
He really does.
But what he doesn't know
is that...
I'm also a fan of his.
I used to think
that I...
love him the most.
But today, I realized
that I can love him even more.
He always says
that I'm crazy in love.
That's right.
I'm very crazy in love...
with Ray.
I hope I've made it clear.
(Jedi and Ray)
(Ray Jedi)
(Je&Ray. I like that.)
That's mean.
You're meaner.
I didn't know you had this photo.
I haven't seen it in ages.
Cute, right?
Mom's here.
It's been a year, I think.
What photo album is that, Mom?
Photos of you when you were young.
Hey! No! You can't see those!
Then can I take a selfie with him?
I'm also part of Jedi Army.
Since when?
You've always left merchandise around the house.
He's quite lovely,
so I started following him.
Okay? Come. Let's take a selfie.
Well then. Let's take a photo of the three of us.
All right.
- You're so lovely. - One more?
- One more? - Yes.
What about me?
Will I be removed from this project?
Calm down, Milin.
Let's listen to the team's PR plan first.
The ship has sailed.
The spotlight is on Jedi and Ray now.
No one cares about me anymore.
I agree.
If we keep promoting Milin and Jedi,
it'll be detrimental.
But Pai...
I mean Jedi and Ray's popularity.
Aun, you should plan to promote the real couple
rather than Milin and Jedi.
We haven't promoted Milin much. We can still turn her around.
But the popularity of Jedi and Ray
is on the rise now.
Jedi's popularity
is winning the hearts of his fans internationally.
All right, Pierce.
You haven't finished with the song, have you?
I haven't. I only proposed it during our last meeting.
Well then. Change it to a solo for Jedi.
I also heard
that Ray's good at dancing, Tina?
That's right. I've already worked it out with the team.
We're ready to present the idea to you.
We're very lucky that Typhoon has all the insights.
So we were able to plan it swiftly.
After yesterday, Ray has gained almost 20,000 followers.
As for the comments, they're mainly positive.
People are showing him support and want to know him better.
As for the hashtag, #JediRay.
It's been the most trending on social media for several hours.
And it's still in the top ten.
We should turn this crisis into an opportunity.
Good. Let's come up with a fun beat that people can dance to.
And let's get Ray in the music video, Aun.
But...
What about me?
It's a ship pairing project.
Who is going to pair with me?
Excuse me. I dozed off.
I'm sorry.
Here.
We'll come up with a new song.
Milin feat. Marc.
His songs are famous.
This is Marc?
That's me.
I like your music.
I think I've heard that somewhere before.
Who was that?
- Milin! - Milin!
Oh, Milin!
Milin, you forgot your bag!
Marc's got terrible timing.
People often take it out on him.
Then it's settled.
Well done, everyone.
Are you up for working on two projects?
Let's get started and not waste any more time.
I need the concept behind the new song this evening, Pierce.
Sure. I can tell you now, actually. I already have an idea.
I have an idea as well.
I came up with it when I talked to Typhoon yesterday.
Pai and Pierce, what do you think
if this song is about the love
between the fans and the artist.
Love
and expectations.
Secrets
and acceptance.
With love,
a person has a goal in life
and wants to become a better person.
Tell me. I'm waiting.
- Hi! - Jedi?
What did the company say? Were you chastised?
No, I wasn't.
Mr. Ray,
do you have any dance shoes for rehearsal yet?
- Dance shoes? - Yes.
Why are you asking?
If you don't have them, then we should go shopping.
From now on,
you have to rehearse every day, you know?
Every day?
- Yes. - But why?
Well...
You're going to be in a music video with me.
- What? A music video? - Yes.
Congratulations.
What? I'll be in a music video.
No, I can't dance that well.
What should I do, Phoon?
You can do it. Just believe in yourself.
But I'm not that good at dancing.
That's right. I saw you dancing in the video Typhoon took.
You've definitely got some cool moves. Well done.
I thought you were SV5.
How did you get your hands on that video anyway?
Hey.
Come on. Is this your poker face?
It's the video where you were drunk.
You sure can move.
If it was Phoon, his joints would be cracking with the tiniest movement.
Pierce.
Just kidding.
Well then.
Let's go home.
Gosh, look at the lovebirds.
It's so sweet ants are going to haul you away.
You obviously don't have a sweet tooth.
I prefer low-fat.
Come on. Let's hurry home,
or they might become more lovey-dovey than us.
Should we watch an Ohm-Fluke TV series tonight?
- It's popular right now. - It's so sweet you'll get diabetes.
Wow, this is so beautiful.
Good.
It's pretty.
You're so lucky, Winn.
Seonmin is good-looking
and extremely talented.
He's the epitome of perfection.
Yes, I think so too.
Yes, that's right.
I'll get back to work.
Oh.
That's very nice.
- Amazing. - Okay. Good job.
Okay. Thank you.
What's this?
Jedi's newest music video.
And who's this guy?
His name is Ray. He is Jedi's boyfriend.
Are they actually in a relationship?
They just went public.
But people are really into them.
It was trending on social media in Thailand for days.
Cool.
Are you thinking of going back to Thailand now?
The photographer said he's going to shoot the next set.
Let's do it.
Please handle this for me, Mr. Manager.
(Close Friend 2)
You can put the phone down for now.
- Just let the viewers see, Ray. - No.
All right. I'll put it down.
- Why? Isn't it enough? - No.
- Just like at the cafe. - Keep talking.
Are you really that mad?
- Gosh. - Are you mad?