Where are you going?
I'll sleep at a friend's.
Thank you for letting me carpool with you.
It's okay.
What's up with work?
Once they found out that Pierce and I are together,
our boss had me under scrutiny right away
even though I haven't even done anything.
Let's drink to our secrets.
Secrets never die.
The expression is "there are no secrets in this world."
Oh, okay.
We're going to drink and forget everything.
(Close Friend 2)
("You can be jealous if you want.")
I can't sleep.
I can just drink the water here, right?
Of course.
Hey, what's wrong, Phoon?
You look like you just saw a ghost.
It's... It's...
Hi.
How come you're back? I thought you said you were staying at the condo.
I've changed my mind.
I'd rather come home and cuddle with you.
- What are you doing? - Am I dreaming?
Hey, you're not! Silly!
You're seeing what I'm seeing, right?
You're being silly.
Ray?
What is this?
Why did you have to be that close to each other?
Here.
Listen, Ray.
There's nothing between me and Milin except work.
We're just helping each other promote the new single.
The company's hoping she becomes an artist.
So they asked me to give them a hand.
And is the ship pairing even necessary?
Well, it's just an act.
If there's a ship pairing, the fans will pay us more attention,
and people will get to know Milin faster too.
Does the company think Jedi Army will accept this?
I'm not sure.
But I believe
that long-time members of Jedi Army
will understand
and be welcoming of Milin.
But you don't have to understand.
You can be jealous if you want.
Oh? Why?
I know I can't stop you from feeling that way.
Jealousy is normal for people who are in love.
But I want to prove to you
that there's nothing going on.
You're the only person I love.
Do you know
that us meeting each other
is a miracle?
It's you.
I'm just a regular guy.
Everyone in the country knows you.
Actually, no. The whole world does.
Do you know
that if someone told me I'd get to be with you three months ago,
people would call them crazy.
Do you believe me now?
No.
- Do you believe me now? - No.
- You're not going to believe me? - No.
You're not going to believe me? No? No?
- Come here! - Jedi!
You're not going to believe me? Do you believe me now?
- Do you believe me now? - Enough! No!
You're back.
It's still early.
Why didn't you come home a little bit later?
I couldn't fall asleep after I sobered up.
So I thought I should just head home.
I told you you didn't have to go.
What a naughty kid.
Pierce, do the monks come for alms? I want to make an offering.
Oh, I think so. I'll go out and take a look.
- Oh, Typhoon? You're up. - Good morning.
Good. Help me prepare the alms.
Okay?
Yes, ma'am.
The song mainly tells
the story of a couple.
The woman
is an introvert
suffering from depression.
The man is an extrovert.
He has a big mouth and a snarky attitude.
But he tries to help with her depression.
The genre of the song
will be easy listening
with a slight hint of jazz.
It's in the same style as Marc's.
What do you think, Milin? Do you like it?
It sounds all right. But I don't want to be depressed.
But I'm okay if it's cute and endearing.
- Pierce, handle it for her. - Okay.
But...
I'm not sure about the easy listening part.
I think it's boring.
Let's do a mix between pop and R&B.
Can you add a bit of rap
for Jedi to show off his skills?
Well... pop and R&B?
Is that going to work?
Pierce's strength doesn't lie in those genres at all.
Are you saying he's not talented, Tina?
Oh, no.
I can do it.
Good.
Let's give it a listen.
But personally,
I don't really enjoy being a big-mouth and snarky guy.
But if that guy, the guy in the lyrics,
really believes so
and says things without lying, then I'm...
He never lies.
Then I'm okay with that.
What about you, Typhoon?
Do you have any creative references to show me?
Oh? The thing I told you to find yesterday.
Uh...
- I... - I've got a rough draft.
Go on. Play the slideshow.
I'm sorry.
It's so exciting. I want to hear the demo soon.
It's okay. I'll do it.
You can sit down.
Phoon,
do you know what a creative team's job entails?
It's not coming to work dressed in chic clothing,
jotting down silly notes.
I understand.
I know you asked me to find references.
But I didn't think we were going to need them today.
I've actually found some.
I just haven't created a presentation yet.
You're lucky Fah had your back today.
I'll let this go because it's the first time.
Don't repeat the same mistake.
Let this be a lesson for you.
And you have to learn to help yourself from now on.
You can't just wait for someone to save the day.
I can't help you either.
And if you want to learn something, check out our previous projects.
Okay.
I promise to do better.
Here you go. Take a look at some of our previous projects.
Thank you so much, ma'am.
Hey, no need to call me that. Just call me Fah.
We're of the same age after all.
I only started working here three months before you.
- Really? - Mm.
But you seem to really know your way around here.
How do you do it?
I just do what I'm telling you to do.
Initially, I actually had it worse than you do right now.
I cried so many times.
I almost quit.
Was the workload really that bad?
The workload wasn't the problem.
But you have to be...
mentally tough.
You have to be able to
accept criticism.
And you have to fix your mistakes.
Tina might seem to have that attitude,
but she's actually a very skilled promoter.
I want to be as good as she is.
What about you?
Did you decide to work here
because you want to become a promoter in the future?
A promoter?
I don't know if I'd like it or not.
Pierce's music?
A promoter?
I'm so bored!
You have to make her famous, Pierce!
I'll try.
Thank you.
And these are the song lyrics.
Please tell her to memorize it.
Sure. I'll tell her to practice a lot.
Oh, Jedi?
Can you keep Milin company?
Hey, Jedi.
How have you been doing lately?
We need moments like this to fuel the ship pairing.
So that she'll be trending
when we release the music video.
Anyway, please help her practice.
This is very important.
Of course.
Smile.
It sounds all right.
Okay. Let's take a break.
Jedi,
do you have to be anywhere after this?
Not really.
Would you like to have dinner together?
Um, well...
I've been working hard recently.
So I just want to head straight home.
Really?
What a shame.
There are so many things I want your advice on.
Okay, guys.
Can I get some photos of you together?
Jedi, scoot closer to Milin.
Sure.
Okay.
Uh, Jedi? Scoot a little closer to her.
Closer. A lot closer.
That's good. Can you look into her eyes, Jedi?
Jedi.
Can I talk to you for a bit?
Sure.
Should I come out and talk too?
You don't have to.
I just want to talk to Jedi.
Milin, let's take some photos.
Yes, alone. That's totally fine.
Thank you.
What's the matter? Why did you want to talk to me?
You seem tired.
Very, in fact.
High notes are usually
a piece of cake for you.
Well,
I probably haven't been getting enough sleep.
That's why I'm a little off.
Get some rest, okay?
You need it even more
during the recording process.
You're in front of a camera nearly all the time.
That must be exhausting.
What do you think
about this project?
Do you think it's going to be successful?
I can't force fame.
But when it comes to making good music,
it's already a success
if everyone on the team is on the same page.
But anyway,
I'm going to give this song my all.
Because my boyfriend is a fan of yours.
What is it called, again?
Jedi Army, right?
Yes.
That is
the most important thing.
Oh, Marc?
Hey, how are you doing?
Marc?
Whoa.
That's Marc.
He's the artist I'm taking care of.
Excellent.
What's the matter? You're so quiet.
Are you tired?
During the meeting today,
was I really that bad?
No.
It's your first time. How were you supposed to know?
Tina didn't brief you on the details either.
But I should've known how to do my job.
Now that you know,
don't make a mistake next time.
Just keep giving me advice.
I can't do that.
Our line of work is different.
Oh? But we're on the same team.
We should be able to help each other, right?
I'll help you, of course.
But our duties and responsibilities
are different.
If you really need advice,
I think you should ask Tina,
not me.
Pierce, Typhoon, have a seat.
You guys are still here?
I want to have a word with you.
Are you upset that we're still here?
No, not at all.
Come on, honey.
We're going home tonight.
Mom, don't be like that.
I just want you to tell me in advance that you're coming.
So I can plan things
for when you're here.
Well, you haven't come to visit us.
If I didn't come all the way here,
would I get to see you?
I want to know
how you're doing
and if there's anyone looking after you.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, now that we've mentioned it...
Honey, I don't think you should say it.
You've graduated and have been working for a while now.
It's time to think about starting a family.
Or are you two
in a relationship?
Honey!
Don't you want to know?
You've been nagging me about it all day.
Pierce is here now.
You can ask him yourself.
So what's going on?
Do you like Typhoon?
Can you tell me?
Don't pester him with questions.
He'll let us know when he's ready.
Let's talk about this later.
Excuse me.
Did I upset Typhoon?
I'm sorry.
You didn't, Mom.
Excuse me.
Calm down.
Jedi?
Special delivery.
Why did you buy flowers?
The beautiful flowers reminded me of you.
You're such a pain.
Thanks, Jedi.
What should I do next?
I don't know.
I'll just keep drinking.
- Okay. Cut. - Cut!
Cut! The door is open.
Get the door.
Cut.
I didn't even get to go scuba diving and see the coral reefs.
Keep mumbling and pacing around.
I can't go out to eat either.
I can't even leave the house.
There's always a problem.
- All right. Cut. - Cut. Get the slate.
Cut!
(Next Episode)
You don't want to accept the truth,
or are you embarrassed by us?
I think you have to break up with this kid now.
Milin.
I'm okay with just being close to you, Jedi.
Are you sure that the person who was embarrassed is Tina
and not yourself?