(Yoo Jun)
(Hur Hyun Jun)
(Color Rush, Episode 3)
No, show me right now.
You jerk.
You got your preview.
So should the tutoring continue?
Forget it.
(Nurse's Office)
What?
Here. Take it.
Don't you ever show me this color chart again.
Choi Yeon Woo, you're pretty when you're angry too!
Remember that the beneficiary of my life insurance policy is you.
Are you off to your death or something?
I'll be at an island for a month to cover a story.
- A month? - Yes.
There's enough money in your account for expenses.
- I'll get going. - Aunt Yi Rang, wait.
What is it?
Be safe out there.
- I'll come back in one piece. - Got it.
Take care.
Darn it!
Forget about the class leader and call me the class servant.
Shouldn't they at least provide some snacks...
when they give me such a task?
Grandpa said you'd be craving snacks today.
Thanks.
Yeon Woo, have one too.
Right. Thanks.
It'd be rude of me only to accept this,
so milk will be on me.
Where's mine?
"Twisted doughnuts become round doughnuts,"
"and round doughnuts become twisted doughnuts."
"Macbeth."
Don't change the subject.
Is Joo Haeng your only friend? Give me one too.
Are you kissing up to him because he's the class leader?
Shouldn't you be at practice?
I'm back from it.
That's for Min Jae!
You've known me since elementary school...
and have been friends with Min Jae since last year,
but all you care about is Yeon Woo right now.
Yeon Woo is special...
unlike the two of you.
I guess I'd rather quit being friends with you...
than wait for you to care for me.
Yeon Woo, join me at the science lab later.
Me? Why?
You'll know once we're there.
(Safety first)
Seriously. Talk about a stupid joke?
Wait, do you have a fear of blood?
- Yes. - Since when?
I'm just nervous when I'm with you.
- Because I'm a probe? - No.
Because you'll talk rubbish.
That's something I never do. I'm nothing but serious.
Trust me and follow my lead.
It's nice and cozy here...
like a hideout.
Hideouts are only as good as the experiments done in secret.
What are you about to do?
First, take a seat right here.
Look at me.
Wait, are you...
Are you awake now?
I wanted to show you a rainbow,
but it wouldn't rain.
Made by a prism.
Can I touch it?
Me?
Sure.
It's all yours.
I know what it was...
since I had seen a gray-colored rainbow before.
But looking at one with all its natural colors...
was a first for me.
Red,
orange, yellow, green,
blue, navy, and purple.
Changing the angle of the light...
will have one end of the rainbow seem longer.
It's so pretty.
What are you doing?
Let me see it again.
Go Yoo Han!
I will only wait until this week.
Was this another 10-minute preview?
Why do you want me to agree to this deal?
You already see enough of my face!
The colors of this world...
are yours to enjoy...
only when I let you see them.
Go Yoo Han.
Then you should know that I'm more than that to you.
A mono and his probe.
That's what I am, aren't I?
I want to see the colors.
You got your preview.
So should the tutoring continue?
They're yours to enjoy.
It's so pretty.
When a mono meets a probe, it leads to an obsession.
Would it be any different for me?
(Aunt Yi Rang)
Hello?
Yeon Woo,
the family on the news today committed plain suicide.
It has nothing to do with one being a mono.
The husband is one, but his wife isn't a probe.
The initial media report got it wrong.
On the news?
Yes, so don't be bothered by it.
(Breaking News: Murder-suicide of a Mono Husband in His 40s)
(Kills His Probe Wife and Family)
Where's Myeong Hun?
I'd like to know myself.
The reporter got it wrong.
It'll take some time to correct the error,
so don't let it get to you in the meantime.
Aunt Yi Rang, when did I ever let things like this get to me?
Just turn the TV off.
(Speaker)
Don't look up the case online.
The murder didn't happen because he was mono,
so don't be bothered by it.
It's nothing that you need to worry about anyway...
since you don't have a probe yet.
(Mono Murder Case)
(Another Mono Kills Yet Again)
Aunt Yi Rang,
I met my probe.
His name is Go Yoo Han and is nothing but unpredictable.
Yeon Woo.
Yeon Woo?
Yes?
The wife stepping out on the husband...
is only a speculation, so don't believe it.
So what about you? Is your story coming along?
Yes, it's great here. The food is especially delicious.
I had mulhoe yesterday and black pork today.
She can send me all these photos,
but I still know that she went there to find clues about Mom.
Enough with the photos of food. It's like you're teasing me.
Right. Well, I'll buy some omegi rice cake on my way home.
Bye.
If Mom's disappearance is related to other mono cases,
investigating the case will be just as dangerous.
Still, her priority always seems to be my well-being.
I am a mono and I doubt I'm different from other monos.
Why won't you run away from me though?
A probe should run away after meeting a mono, you idiot.
This darkness, this boredom...
Maybe just living this way...
(Yoo Han)
Yeon Woo.
What.
- Where are you? - Home.
I didn't save his number for I never wanted to get close to him.
But it turns out that I already know it by heart.
Yoo Han's calling me.
I shouldn't answer. I should decline.
Yeon Woo, I'm outside your house.
Want to come out for a bit?
(Color Rush)