(Yoo Jun)
(Hur Hyun Jun)
(Color Rush, Episode 4)
Why am I putting on my jacket?
Why are you here?
Because I missed you.
I can't believe he's here.
I shouldn't see him today.
So why am I already wearing my jacket?
Get home safely.
Wait, don't hang up.
I failed to show you a rainbow the other day,
so I thought I'd show you something else.
Which is what?
The night view.
This will be it.
After seeing the night view, I'll say I've had enough.
That I don't want to be with my probe.
Yeon Woo, this will be your last preview.
I see.
Last night, I looked at it with sunglasses on.
- Sunglasses? - I got to realize...
that maybe you'd be better off not seeing its colors.
You might collapse due to the color rush again.
Still, you should get at least one chance to see this view.
To know that having colors isn't always beautiful.
What's the name of this color?
Lemon.
Yeon Woo,
lookout in front of you.
This is what a night view looks like.
The night view here...
is one that felt the loneliest to me.
You're right.
It does feel lonely.
Why on earth did you show me this though?
Because you're adamant...
against learning about colors.
When did I ever say that?
You show the colors to me...
and I help you to identify faces. Right?
- That's right. - Tell me what I need to do.
Just look at me when I tell you to.
Like this?
So what now?
Do you want to learn the colors?
Yes.
No. No way.
No way. Not a chance.
I must've been out of my mind to have said that.
Like this?
I blame it on Yoo Han's eyes that went from a shade of gray...
to a mesmerizing shade of caramel brown.
That's the reason for saying what I didn't mean.
So what now?
Do you want to learn the colors?
Yes.
I'm doomed.
How am I supposed to go to school now?
- Boo! - What on earth?
Are you all right?
Not even my mom has ever hit me,
but Yeon Woo did.
Hold on. Let me see.
I'm fine.
Let's go see the school nurse.
I see she's not here.
Have a seat.
Here's a mirror, so apply the ointment.
I thought you'd do it for me.
Fainting from a color rush will only cause more nuisance.
No, that will hardly be the case.
Then, let me help.
So this much of a color rush doesn't have me fainting.
I can take it off if you want me to.
This might hurt.
Does it hurt a lot?
Soothe it for me.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Yellow.
(Missing Person)
(Yoo Yi Ri, mono)
Yeon Woo?
(Nurse's Office)
Are you all right?
Wait.
What happened to me?
You cried your eyes out.
Pain suddenly swept over you...
and you started crying.
You didn't seem to be conscious though.
What exactly did I do?
I can't remember.
The colors...
I can't see them.
Decoloring happened. Don't you remember?
You needed to see the color of the headband.
You didn't want the image to fade away.
I already...
experienced it?
It's one of the phases mono experiences...
while adjusting to one's probe.
The color rush gets extended,
you forget what happened, you pass out a while later,
and your subconscious can surface.
The fact that he's adjusting to the color rushes...
is a good sign, right?
Don't do it at school for the time being.
We don't want him to wither away even more.
Got it.
I'm glad that you're getting used to it.
You scared me a little back there.
I'm getting used to it? As in what way?
Me getting used to my probe?
To Go Yoo Han?
Yeon Woo...
And what comes after that?
Obsession, kidnapping,
and murder.
Look at me.
You should wash your face.
You're still just as pretty with puffy eyes,
but it seems too obvious that you cried.
I'm the mono here.
So why are you trying to keep me next to you?
Go Yoo Han.
Why are you crying when I'm the one who blacked out?
I thought something bad had happened to you earlier...
and got scared.
I get it, so let go of me.
No. Since it's raining...
Just for a little while.
What does the rain have to do with anything?
I'm fully aware of it now.
The difference between what my brain logically wants...
and what my heart desires.
I like being with my probe.
I want to see the colors.
Do you wish to see the colors that I see?
Yes.
What?
Can he even tell what I'm thinking now?
Yeon Woo, look ahead.
Being your probe...
means that the colors I know will become the colors you know.
We'll be seeing the same colors.
What on earth?
Then how you describe the sea...
will be the color I'll learn.
Yes, that's exactly how it'll be.
That's absurd.
But when I felt a moment of happiness,
I saw the happiness draining out from my view.
Loss.
Only having moments of happiness...
that leaves me all alone in a land of gray...
terrifies me.
Could there be a way to never let this go?
If only I could...
Choi Yeon Woo!
Let go of me!
What's your problem?
It just crossed my mind...
that I want to keep you forever.
(Color Rush)