(Yoo Jun)
(Hur Hyun Jun)
(Color Rush, Episode 6)
Yeon Woo.
Are you all right?
Doesn't your head hurt?
It does.
Yeon Woo, get behind me.
Aunt Yi Rang?
Your aunt?
Who is this kid?
So that's what my aunt looks like.
- You... - No, don't!
You know I'm against violence.
Tell me who you are.
I'm his classmate.
A friend?
I see. A friend?
That's right.
We're not...
See? We have the same school uniform.
- I'm his one and only... - My Yeon Woo doesn't have friends.
- So tell me who you are. - It's true that he's my friend.
He is.
I'm the closest friend he has.
See? Wasn't it the right choice to change schools?
You got yourself a friend.
I heard you're a TV show director.
Yes, one for a show called "Hunt for the Truth"...
that airs at night.
I see. Then...
I, Go Yoo Han, Yeon Woo's closest friend,
will get going.
All right, get going. Your parents will be worried.
- Yeon Woo. - Yes?
Aren't you going to walk me out?
I see you're not that close.
You must be the only one who thinks so.
Right. Well, then I'll see him out.
Okay, but don't take too long. I'm hungry.
That reminds me.
Ramyeon...
- It's nothing. I'll be right back. - Sure.
That was odd.
You seem overly excited.
Are you happy that your aunt's back?
- Your mask. - What? Oh, no, I forgot.
It's been off for a while now.
- Are you okay though? - Yes.
- I was worried for a second there. - Hey, my hair.
I can still see the colors.
- Decoloring hasn't happened. - Really?
You must've grown accustomed to it then.
Your feelings for me led to you getting used to it.
That's not the case. It isn't.
That sign is in blue.
And...
- that's in yellow. - Yes, yellow.
And that...
- That's neon. - Neon?
Yes, fluorescent versions of primary colors.
That's the fluorescent version of the color blue...
which makes it neon blue.
Yeon Woo,
what's the color of that cafe sign?
Well... Yellow?
(Ultramarine Special Collection)
Back in the day, ultramarine blue was expensive to buy.
European countries had to import lazurite to make it.
Being made by lazurite that was imported overseas...
gave it the name ultramarine.
Before artificial dye-making became common,
the color was loved for its bright blue pigment.
In today's currency,
it would cost 15,000 dollars per kilogram.
What?
Due to its high price, nobles watched over the painters...
to check if they are using it correctly.
It sure is expensive.
In this painting,
the color was only used to paint in the Virgin Mary's clothes.
See that over there?
The sky isn't clear or blue...
because they couldn't waste the paint.
However, lapis lazuli is no longer expensive.
- Lapis lazuli? - That's lazurite in Latin.
Quite a large amount was needed to mix the ultramarine color,
but it was only expensive because it needed to be...
extracted and shipped from Afghanistan.
These days, it's hardly considered a gem.
Just a mineral.
I have one at home. Want to see it?
Yes, I do.
Then come to my house sometime.
Hey, your bus is here.
- Is that a promise? - You don't want to miss it.
Promise!
(Royal Embroidery and Sewing Work Shop)
(Ultramarine Special Collection)
I must get away from here.
Despair swept over me and I feel listless.
Without Yoo Han,
it's like being abandoned in a lifeless world.
So you met your probe.
Go Yoo Han...
is your probe, isn't he?
Yes.
- You should transfer again. - No.
- We'll move out too. - I don't want to!
What do you plan to do then?
I'll try my best to handle it.
I'm different. I'm not like the other monos.
I'll rise above the urge. I will.
Are you not aware of the loss you'll experience?
How can you possibly handle that?
I already lost my sister. I can't lose you too.
- So Yeon Woo... - No. I said, no!
Don't say things like that.
I'm sorry, Yeon Woo. I was wrong.
(Sangsang High School)
Yo Han won't make it today either. He has a test to complete.
Once he makes the debut squad, his phone will be confiscated...
and he'll have to move in with other members.
He might not be coming back then.
You're right. That might be the case.
What if I kidnapped Yoo Han?
How do you think he'll react?
You're being ridiculous.
Are you willing to become a monster yourself?
A monster took my mom away from me.
So why can't I turn into one myself...
and keep Go Yoo Han by my side?
Guys, come on. You're making it sound too real.
So much for it being a joke.
You know how Yoo Han is.
He'll stand guard by the door if you kidnap him...
just so that you wouldn't kick him out.
What's with the mood today?
Kang Min Jae saw right through me.
I'm now close to becoming a monster.
Yeon Woo, don't get any funny ideas.
My phone got busted, so I bought a new one.
You remind me of someone, you know.
- Who's that? - My sister.
Your mom seemed exactly the same...
right before bringing home your dad.
What are you talking about?
I could tell that she was up to something,
but I couldn't figure out what.
I'm not up to anything.
(How to tie a hangman's noose)
(Sangsang High School)
Yeon Woo.
Are you all right?
I see you came to school today.
I missed you so much that I came early.
What happened? Did you injure yourself?
I wonder how this scar will seem to him.
Are you sure you're all right?
- Was it your aunt... - No, of course not.
Then what happened?
You should be worried about yourself, not me.
It's like I've been saying.
I'm a mono and you're a probe.
A mono can only hurt a probe.
Because monos never want to lose...
what probes can show them.
(Color Rush)