(Yoo Jun)
(Hur Hyun Jun)
(Color Rush, Episode 2)
At least, my breathing is better now.
Before, I felt like I was suffocating.
I don't like being touched by just anyone.
Then you should know that I'm more than that to you.
A mono and his probe.
That's what I am, aren't I?
I'm sorry to say this but...
You don't look like you're sorry.
Fine, I'm not sorry.
I never wanted to meet my probe.
It never crossed my mind and it never will.
Because it turned out to be me?
That isn't the case.
All I want is to live in peace.
Let go of me.
Are you all right?
You still need to rest.
Look at me.
I said, look not glare.
Do you want me to show you my face?
So that you can see colors.
I don't need this!
You're better off not getting involved with a mono.
- What's that? - Because...
monos have kidnapped probes,
killed those in their lives,
and have also killed probes...
to eat their flesh.
Oh, that.
Don't you get how serious this situation is?
No, not really.
I just like the movement of your eyes when you see colors.
Let's make a deal.
I'll teach you the colors of this world.
In return, you'll show me the colore moving of your eyes.
What do you say?
I'm not interested.
What are you doing next week?
Are you a mono?
- Yes. - I knew it.
We told the others that you fainted after seeing a ghost.
A ghost?
We figured it'd be better than everyone knowing you're a mono.
Then the old man Min Jae knows...
That's right.
It's the spirit of an old man that possesses Min Jae.
Some bullies accused Min Jae because they thought...
Min Jae was a mono last year.
Min Jae went,
"Don't you ride that motorcycle!"
to one of the guys.
Then to those standing beside and behind him, he went,
"Don't you stare at that tree..."
"and don't you get on the back of that bike."
Like that.
It got them all worked up at the time,
but while riding the bike...
that very weekend, they collided...
with a truck at the intersection.
One ended up under the truck,
but one was nowhere to be seen.
Their friends and the police looked everywhere for him.
A little later, one of their friends fainted from shock.
It turns out that the one riding on the back...
flew straight into...
a tree.
His tongue was hanging long.
That's why our school doesn't have bullies anymore.
If anyone bothers you, the spirit of Min Jae's Grandpa...
I told you that isn't the case.
My grandpa has the ability to see the near future, that's all.
That's what he said.
How powerful can an old ghost be, right?
Still, if anyone annoys you,
we'll be there to fend them off.
Why though?
Because we're friends. Isn't it obvious?
Yeon Woo doesn't have any friends.
Shut it, will you?
- Wait, did your grandpa say that? - Yes.
I'm grateful for you guys not being judgmental,
but it's easier for me to be alone.
But still... Hey.
Leave him be.
Monos are known to be loners.
White, snowy white,
light gray, silver gray,
moonlit gray, cement gray,
dolphin gray, shark gray,
charcoal gray, and black.
Again, my world is in the shade of gray.
Aunt Yi Rang, this is urgent.
I need to transfer schools again. My probe goes to this school.
That's the color of the ocean.
The color of the ocean?
The oceans I saw were of a different color.
This is the color of that water.
(Missing Person)
(Yoo Yi Ri, mono)
This is the portrait of my mom that my dad drew before dying.
He said her lips are red.
Unfortunately,
I don't know the color of her sky-blue dress,
the color of her brown shoes,
or what he meant by her lips being red.
I wish to see the colors used in this painting.
Mom said she couldn't forget the feeling of the color rush...
when she first met Dad.
She injured both her knees from falling to the ground,
but she still loved the rush.
That's probably when she first realized...
that she looked good in a sky-blue dress,
that she looked even nicer in brown shoes,
and that red lips suited her.
For the first time in my life today, I saw colors.
And I loved it.
The female mantis is eating the male mantis.
That is how it ends for male mantises...
who risk their lives trying to mate.
Female mantises...
eat male mantises during mating season.
Male mantises try to mate knowing they'll lose their lives.
Female mantises eat them entirely without leaving anything behind.
(Self-studying)
You must think your good looks give you a free pass for everything.
Arriving after the first class ends?
All right, I hear you.
- Yoo Han, take your seat. - Sure.
- Hurry up. - Got it.
Yeon Woo. Choi Yeon Woo.
I'm here.
Hey!
Choi Yeon Woo, look at me, will you?
What about your mask?
I still have it on.
Did you just poke me with that?
No, the art supply shop closed up early,
so I went by there this morning.
What for?
To buy this.
Even academic tutors give previews before getting the job.
I offered to teach you about colors...
without giving you one myself.
That's why... Ta-da.
Come on. Take it.
This is what is called a color chart.
Okay, now let me explain.
Everyone starts with the basics, right?
Come on.
Seriously?
Hey.
How are these different?
Let me teach you.
All right. The number three...
refers to this being the third card.
Y stands for the color yellow.
And GY stands for green yellow.
- I'm not interested. - R stands for red.
YR stands for yellow red which is also orange.
Y stands for the color yellow.
B is blue.
PB is purple blue which is also navy blue.
P is purple.
Lastly, RP is red purple.
You're up.
That was a dirty trick you pulled. How could you take off your mask?
Hardly. I was going to put my mask back on,
but you looked before I could.
You'll pay for this.
Oh, sorry.
Does this still not intrigue you?
I want to see the colors.
No...
Yoo Han, take off your mask.
- I should take it off? - Right now!
I will if you want me to,
but only later.
No, show me right now.
You jerk.
You got your preview.
So should the tutoring continue?
(Color Rush)