(Yoo Jun)
(Hur Hyun Jun)
(Color Rush, Episode 5)
Yoo Han won't make it today.
Why are you telling me that?
He wanted me to.
He didn't say it in a way...
that made me want to relay the message,
but that's what he wanted you to know.
He could've told me himself.
Why go through Joo Haeng?
- Choi Yeon Woo! - Let go of me!
What's your problem?
It just crossed my mind...
that I want to keep you forever.
He must be avoiding me.
He realized the danger of mono.
It's not like I wanted to know,
but he orders me around because I'm the class leader.
I honestly didn't want to know.
Having the wrong kind of friend can be such a nuisance.
Yeon Woo, can you grab this for us? Come on.
Come on over.
- Like this? - Yes.
Let me see.
What do you think? Perfect, right?
Yes, it is.
This is what makes Joo Haeng class leader material.
Of course.
Attention, everyone.
Today, we'll study Korean poems.
Please turn to page 171.
Joo Haeng, wake him up, will you?
Forget it. Turn to page 171.
Joo Haeng, go ahead and recite this poem.
- Talk about loyal friends. - Sure.
(Sangsang High School)
A day without Go Yoo Han...
was quiet and peaceful.
Actually, it was boring.
When he'd spew nonsense,
all I wanted was for him to go away.
I must've grown accustomed to it...
considering how I was bored today.
When I walked around the schoolyard...
during lunch break,
the quietness surrounding me felt odd.
I felt nervous as if...
I had put off something important to do.
Yeon Woo. Choi Yeon Woo.
My Yeon Woo.
My Yeon Woo's the softest.
Have you ever had fun with colors?
No. Why do you ask?
(No. Why do you ask?)
How can one even play with colors?
I hated the feeling of loss when the colors fade away...
more than not being able to see them at all.
How can Go Yoo Han leave me after forcing his way into my life?
(The World of Radiant Colors)
(Yoo Han)
Let's see an exhibition.
I wanted to see this with you.
It's a media art exhibition.
Where flowers become you and you become flowers.
Let me escort you to that very world.
What on earth?
Yeon Woo, we'll now enter a starlit space.
(Recording Time)
Will you be able to handle the blackout today?
I won't.
I'll stay strong no matter what.
Fine.
Where flowers become you and you become flowers.
Let me escort you there.
It's beautiful.
Even if I become dependent on my probe,
even if I follow in the footsteps of other monos...
who turn into criminals,
I still want to see the colors.
That is what I desire.
- How will you get home? - Me? I'm taking the bus.
Thank you for inviting me to this exhibition today.
For finding this exhibition, bringing me here,
letting me see the colors, and explaining them to me.
Get home safely then.
Can probes read their monos' minds?
Hey, let me come home with you today.
Darn, he's irresistible. No way.
Pretend like you didn't hear him.
- Is your aunt home? - No.
What the... What did I just say?
Then, what about your dad?
- He's not home either. - It'll be just you and me then.
He already knows that I don't have a mother.
How much do you know about me?
Yoo Han.
Go ahead.
If I let you come home with me,
will you grant me a wish?
It'll be my command.
Hurry up, will you? I'm starving.
Let's eat ramyeon for dinner. It's what I'm craving.
- What is he saying? - Come on!
- Ramyeon? Are you kidding me? - Hurry.
Is this fair lady...
your mother?
What are you doing?
Chill out. The painting called for me.
Yeon Woo, take a seat.
Let's look at it together.
My mom...
Yes?
She disappeared four years ago.
Truth be told, I saw the missing person flyer.
She looked familiar in a way.
It was you I saw in her.
I want to take a proper look at it.
I want to see the colors my dad used to paint it.
That's my wish.
Don't cry.
I'll let you see it. It's what I'm here for anyway.
Yeon Woo.
Stay strong.
Come on.
Sky-blue...
A sky-blue dress.
Mom...
Brown shoes.
Red lips.
Yellow...
Your headband was in yellow, Mom.
I can finally see your true smile.
This is the aura you have.
Where are you, Mom?
I can tell you everything now.
I can teach you all the colors.
Mom said that she and I saw the world...
in the same way.
She told me that the world isn't just a shade of gray,
but consisted of many beautiful colors.
I'll be the key to your colors.
I'm right here for you.
Why are you...
so handsome?
Yeon Woo.
Are you all right?
Doesn't your head hurt?
It does.
Yeon Woo, get behind me.
(Color Rush)