(Yoo Jun)
(Hur Hyun Jun)
(Color Rush, Episode 1)
My aunt doesn't recall...
Mom was wearing the headband the day she disappeared.
But I do.
However, I suffer from monochromacy,
so I have no way of telling what color it was.
Everything is in a shade of gray to me,
so I just can't say.
What color...
"What color..."
Yellow.
No!
A man in his 40s kidnapped a woman in her 30s...
and held her captive against her will.
According to some acquaintances, the suspect is a monochromat.
He appears to have taken her...
after her presence led him to identify colors.
Those like me with monochromatic vision...
who see the world only in gray are called Mono.
We're different from those who have total color blindness.
Our cone cells aren't impaired,
but our brains can't distinguish the colors.
However, looking at the face of a certain someone...
lets us see colors.
And that person...
who opens the world of colors to us are known as Probe.
The only issue is that...
there is only a rare chance of a mono meeting a probe...
and quite a number of them don't get to meet theirs at all.
Worried that they'll lose the ability to see colors again,
monos become obsessed with their probes.
And their obsession...
leads to them to break the law.
Monos and probes should never meet one another.
Why are you watching something like that?
(Application for Student Transfer)
I'm moving schools again?
Yes. To a boys' school this time.
Not a coed school?
Why? You think you'll be missing out?
It's not like you ever date anyone anyway.
I beat up a boy who teased me of my condition...
and now I'm once again transferring to a new school.
Darn it. I don't know who did this,
but someone threatened me again to stop looking into the mono case.
Aunt Yi Rang, you need to watch out for yourself.
You don't know who you're up against.
That's more the reason for me keep digging.
I'll dig, dig, and dig.
I must keep digging.
Four years ago, my mom's disappeared.
Since then, my aunt has been searching for her...
by investigating all related cases.
Just like me, my mom's also a mono.
("The 6 Missing Are All Monos")
(All six missing victims are known to be monos.)
(They disappeared after attending the same gathering.)
White, snowy white, light gray,
silver gray, moonlit gray, cement gray,
dolphin gray, shark gray, charcoal gray, and black.
("All 6 Missing Assumed as Monos")
("The 6 Missing Are All Monos")
Those are the 10 colors my mom taught me.
Colors from the gray color palette.
Even in the world of gray, different colors exist.
Attention, all.
Today, we have a new student joining our class.
Say hi.
I'm Choi Yeon Woo.
- Is that it? - Yes.
Right.
See that empty seat next to the class leader?
You can sit there.
5, 6...
Hi.
Hold on. Class leader.
- Yes? - One's missing.
Oh...
Asleep like always.
Just when is he set to make his debut?
Why does he even bother coming to school?
Unbelievable.
You all seem to be here, so I'll skip the roll call.
Don't make any trouble today and don't chat in class. Got it?
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
That'll be all.
Hi, I'm Kang Min Jae.
I hope we get along.
Sure, me too. I'm Choi Yeon Woo.
Are you also a K-pop idol trainee?
- Also? - You're that good looking.
Him too, you know.
Hey.
Okay, fine. I'll cut it out.
Anyway, my name is Jung Joo Haeng.
It's probably obvious, but I'm class leader.
Who Joo Haeng just referred to is him.
Go Yoo Han, the one taking a nap.
He denies it since it isn't official yet,
but he's a K-pop idol trainee.
Anyway, ask Joo Haeng if you have any questions.
Why me?
No, he's right. Come to me instead of going to Min Jae.
What?
The old man in him could take up your time, you see.
Grandpa Min Jae will only bore you silly,
so refrain from asking him anything.
Matching a black face mask with his school uniform.
He's trying to get that to trend.
Are you sure he didn't remove a mole?
So what's with him and the old man?
The spirit of one takes over Min Jae sometimes.
By the way, you're quite pretty.
- I'm not. - Actually, you're stunning.
I've seen my fair share of K-pop idol trainees...
while jumping from one agency to another,
but you're worth noticing.
Yoo Han, it's not like you can remember faces anyway.
I may not be able to, but I can still feel one's vibe.
He's a pretty boy for sure.
Life must be tiring for you. So which agency are you with?
I know which ones you should avoid.
I'm not a trainee.
- Why? - What?
What?
I've never been interested.
Go Yoo Han, this is the first time...
you've shown interest in anyone but us.
Have you always been this friendly?
Doesn't he seem like the type to suddenly give up on college...
and announce his debut?
Right, Min Jae?
Should I ask the old man later on?
Just who is this old man?
The first class is about to begin.
Hey, Jae Seong, let's go and grab a snack.
(With Friends, Paint Yourself with Colors)
(Love Your Nation Festival)
(Organized by Sangsang High School)
"With Friends, Paint Yourself with Colors".
I still can't get over how pretty you are.
- You must have a death wish. - Want to join the agency I'm in?
Are you sure you're not a K-pop idol trainee?
I'm not.
Crush. Crush on you.
Then what? Are you an athlete?
I'm not.
The sooner, the better.
When did you take that?
You'd better get it done quickly.
Then what do you plan on doing with that pretty face?
Live a normal life.
With that face?
Talk about aiming low in life.
Whatever.
(Choi Yeon Woo)
Mom said that the color rush she experienced...
when she first my dad was very romantic.
I never dreamed of a color rush or meeting my probe for that matter.
Yeon Woo.
Choi Yeon Woo.
His eyes seem to be closed but moving.
Is it because of the color rush?
I'm not sure. I can't say for sure...
since it's my first time witnessing a case.
But I'm right. It's proof that he's experiencing a color rush.
Be a doctor yourself if you're so sure.
I need to step out to collect some materials,
so keep an eye on him for me.
Call me if his eyes start to pop out or is about to die.
Got it.
Choi Yeon Woo, you can open your eyes now.
Do you want something for your headache?
- Yes. - Then sit up.
No. I'm too dizzy.
Why? Is it because you can see colors now?
Still, you should take the medicine.
That's the color of the ocean.
- The color of the ocean? - Yes.
What is it?
The oceans I saw were of a different color.
How the moonlight could shine on the water always fascinated me,
but this is the color of that water.
Gosh...
What is it?
The colors...
I'm losing them.
Decoloring?
Are the colors disappearing?
Yes.
At least, my breathing is better now.
Before, I felt like I was suffocating.
I don't like being touched by just anyone.
Then you should know that I'm more than that to you.
A mono and his probe.
That's what I am, aren't I?
(Color Rush)