You spoiled brat! You brat, where are you?
You think you can escape from me?
Help me!
It's okay, my child. Don't cry.
Look at your brothers and sisters.
They are such good kids.
Hey, Pom, are you sure that Chaba
was the one who abducted the kids?
You're sure about that?
She looks so frail.
She can barely walk.
I heard Pang's voice coming from in here.
Where could Chaba be?
The house is this small.
Be still, my child.
So you won't be afraid to look
at me anymore.
Don't worry, it won't hurt.
I'll be quick.
-Get out!
-Hey!
-Mom, help me!
-Who did this to you?
Don't you mess with my kid!
No! Stop!
My child.
Stop! Don't touch my kid!
Crazy bitch, your kids
were burned to death!
My child.
Come here, you bitch!
-Damn you, Chaba!
-Take this!
How could you do this to my child?
Die, you bitch!
Pang.
-Do you wanna die?
-Go to hell!
Look at my face, bitch!
-Kill her!
-Crazy bitch!
-Let her die!
-Die, you bitch!
-Die!
Go to hell!
-Crazy bitch!
-Crazy!
Just die already!
Die!
Hey, Toh,
why are you sitting here?
You don't want to go back in
to see your work?
I watched it once last night.
So how was it? You don't seem happy.
Yeah.
I'm going to edit the scene
where Chaba was hanged.
Hello. What's up?
Yeah.
Pang!
Pang, what happened?
-What happened, Pang?
-Don't! It's here!
It's here. Chaba is here!
Don't be scared, Pang.
You just had a bad dream, that's all.
Who is that? Is that you, Toh?
Toh?
A.C. MILAN
Hey, Shane, the reel is running out.
Hey, this is the ghost movie that's going
to show in theaters next week, right?
Where did you get these reels?
The production team
had a private screening.
Is it scary? I really want to see
this movie.
I don't know. I don't like horror movies,
so I didn't watch.
You're trying to be cool.
But I know you're too scared to watch it.
It's nothing like that.
I just don't like watching stupid movies.
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
PART 1-3
Is it ready yet?
No, not yet. I just got around to it.
So just swap these reels in for now.
They're outside, waiting for the film.
HAUNTING HELL
Yod,
will we get in trouble for this?
You pussy. It's too late to back out now.
If you want your money now, just say so.
This is your share. Here's half now.
As for the rest,
I'll give it to you later.
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
Hello, is this Joe?
Tonight, I want in on three matches.
On Calcio.
Okay, yes, Cagliari,
Milan, and Palermo.
Bye, Shane.
Palermo! You idiot, not Palamo Picasso.
Yeah, 1,000 baht.
Yes, 1,000 on all three matches.
Are you leaving now?
Hello.
Thanks.
I didn't think you would remember
my birthday.
Yes, okay, bye.
Hey, Som, happy birthday.
Hey!
Hey, am I interrupting something?
Hey, Yod.
What's wrong with you?
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
Yod!
Shane!
Hey, Yod!
Oh, Yod!
Yod, are you all right?
It fucking hurts, man.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
Som, did you really have to hit me?
-I didn't know it was you.
-Yod.
I finished everything.
I want some cake.
Can I eat it?
So, I might gain some weight.
I didn't think you would remember
my birthday.
I didn't.
But your guy here did.
-Bottoms up.
-Fill it up.
-Down it.
Hey, try not to drink too much.
You have to work tomorrow.
Som, you're my sister, not my mother.
It's just a little, I will be fine.
All right.
I've got to go now.
Hey, why? What's the hurry?
I won't be able to wake up.
Your choice, man.
A girl like you going back alone,
do take care. It's very dangerous.
I told you to move in with me.
Right.
Yod's room is as dirty as hell.
Who the hell would be able to live in it?
-Where?
-It's extreme.
-Even the rats have to leave.
-You're overexaggerating.
-You can leave now.
-I'm leaving.
-Bye. Be safe.
-See you.
Go!
Go.
Isn't the weather
good tonight?
Hey, Som,
-about the watch I took--
-Forget about it.
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
Shane,
you have the worst luck, man.
I really think Som hates your guts.
Hey.
Yod.
Yod, are you sure security
is not going to walk in?
Shit, man, you know I got your back.
Don't you need the money
to get Som's watch?
Just hurry and get it done.
Die!
Go to hell!
All right, we're now
in the 73rd minute of the match.
A.C. Milan is being attacked
feverishly by Inter Milan.
TAWEESUP PAWNSHOP
Javier Zanetti is now in possession
of the ball in midfield.
ONE WOMAN WATCH
He is swooping to the left
and switching to the right.
He is now passing the ball to the center.
Shane, what are you doing?
Why are you taking my watch?
I just need to borrow it, Som.
Are you trading it for drugs again?
-Come on, just for a while.
-You can't have it!
-I'll return it soon.
-Give it back.
Give it back.
Let go!
Som...
Inter Milan has the upper hand so far.
The ball is kicked off
from A.C. Milan's side.
A.C. Milan is mainly playing
from the left wing today.
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
ANNOUNCEMENT: DEAR CUSTOMERS
RECORDING OF MOVIES IN THE CINEMA
IS REGARDED AS PIRACY
Damn it.
Shit.
Who is that?
What are you doing?
Here? I was looking for my stuff.
I must've dropped something
while I was here yesterday.
Okay, have you seen, Yod?
No. I just came.
Where the heck is he?
Do you have something urgent for him?
If I see him, I will let him know.
Yesterday, Yod returned the wrong print.
Now everyone is scrambling to find it.
They are worried that the film
will be pirated.
Som, where are you?
Go get the posters at the entrance for me.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Pang, what happened?
No!
Are you jacking off?
Why is the door locked?
Oh, I accidentally locked it.
Dude, do you know the result
of last night's games?
You won all your bets!
A.C. MILAN OVERTHREW INTER
Does your shift end in the afternoon?
-Yes.
-Can you do me a favor?
Go collect my winnings for me.
Then take my share of the winnings
and this money,
and go redeem my stuff for me.
-I'm leaving then.
-All right.
Don't forget.
Yod!
Yod.
Fuck!
Hey, Shane,
where is your supervisor?
No one answered when I called.
I really don't know.
The both of you think
you can screw me over?
So, where's that movie
that I asked you to copy?
Right now, all the theater staff
are on the lookout.
About the money, I'll find a way
to pay you back.
I don't want your money.
Find a way to copy that film.
I want to sell the pirated DVDs
before the movie release date.
Hey, Pom, are you sure that Chaba
was the one who abducted the kids?
I heard Pang's voice coming from in here.
Pang!
Pang, wake up!
CALLING YOD
Phong!
What is it, Pom?
Hurry, take her with you and run.
Ghost.
Chaba's ghost is back to get revenge.
Everyone else is dead.
It's done here.
Hurry! Grab your sister. Go, Phong!
Get out of here.
Pang!
Pang.
Yod.
Who the hell is it?
CALLING SOM
END CALL
VOLUME
Shit!
Were you on duty yesterday?
Yes, I was.
When you were on your way out,
did you see Yod?
No, I didn't.
Did you see the film then?
What film?
The film Revengeful Spirit.
No, I didn't.
And do you know where the print
could be sent to?
Hey, Shane.
Are you free? Please come and help us
assemble this standee.
Let's go.
-Som.
-Yeah?
Ever since the two of you broke up,
you never thought of talking to him?
If I have nothing to talk about,
why should I talk to him?
You knew that Shane was high on drugs.
He didn't mean to hurt you.
Who knows,
one day, he might not be there anymore,
and you're going to regret it.
BASED ON A HORRIFYING TRUE STORY
No!
-No!
-Pang!
Pang, what happened?
Pang!
Why are you doing this?
Do you want to go to jail?
Don't tell me that you need
the money for drugs.
Is Yod part of this, too? Where is he?
Where is Yod?
Yod, he is...
Yod is dead, Som.
What are you talking about?
This might sound ridiculous.
But this movie,
there's something about it.
The ghost in the movie,
I think she is for real.
Shane, are you high?
No, Som.
Som, take a look at this.
No!
Last night,
-No!
-I was screening the movie again,
and...
I noticed Yod's corpse in the movie.
In the movie?
Ever since I've watched this movie,
I've been seeing her all the time.
Don't watch the movie,
or else you will end up like me!
Why? If I want to watch it,
what are you going to do? Hit me?
Thanks.
YOD
DIALING YOD
REDIALLING YOD
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
Shane, what the hell
are you sitting here for?
I thought you already went home.
Here is the stuff you asked me
to get for you.
Luckily, I redeemed it on time,
or else it might have been sold.
Hey!
Open it!
Help, please!
Fucking open it!
-Hey.
-Hey, Shane!
Shane, what's wrong?
Shane!
Shane! Could you help me out here?
Hey!
Shane, what's wrong?
What the hell is going on?
I have no clue what's scaring the shit
out of him.
But this time, I think he's really
in bad shape.
What else could be causing this?
Except for him getting high
and overdosing again?
Som, you know what?
Ever since you broke up,
he stopped using drugs.
-See you tomorrow, Som.
-All right.
-Bye.
-Bye, Som.
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
PRODUCTION CREW OF REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
FELL UNDER THE CURSE.
CREW LIT INCENSE AS A FORM OF ATONEMENT
CHABA
CHABA - WIKIPEDIA
CHABA CHINESE ROSE
HOW TO GROW CHINESE ROSE
HANGING
EYE-GOUGING
AN INSANE WOMAN WHO CAPTURES CHILDREN
AND GOUGES THEIR EYES OUT.
DO YOU STILL REMEMBER THIS HOUSE
AN INSANE WOMAN CAPTURED CHILDREN
AND GOUGED THEIR EYES OUT,
BELIEVING THEM TO BE HER OWN.
30 YEARS AGO, MRS. CHABA NGAMSRI
CAPTURED CHILDREN
AND GOUGED THEIR EYES OUT,
BELIEVING THEM TO BE HER OWN.
THE VILLAGERS FOUND THE HOUSE
AND BROKE INTO IT
AND SUBSEQUENTLY HUNG HER.
Thank you
for taking care of me, Som.
Shane,
you know that story you told me...
about Yod
and the ghost in the movie?
At first, I wasn't sure if it was true.
But...
I came across what you told me
on the Internet.
It was exactly as you told me.
If everything that's been happening
to you is exactly like the movie,
then how will the movie end?
In the end,
the hero dies.
He breaks into an abandoned house
to find and burn Chaba's body.
But he doesn't make it.
What if...
we can make it?
Chaba's body might still be in this house.
AFTER CHABA'S BODY WAS HANGED,
UNTIL NOW, HER BODY
STILL HASN'T BEEN FOUND.
BANGKOK NONG RAHAN
Shane!
Look!
This can't be it.
There should be another room here.
Shane, everything might not be exactly
like the movie.
-Som!
-Shit!
Shane!
How are you, Shane?
Can you hear me?
Shane!
Shane, I'll be back in a moment.
Shane, are you all right? Are you hurt?
I'm all right.
Let's get out of here.
Shane!
Shane. Come up, quickly!
Shane, what's wrong?
Come with me.
I'm telling you to come with me!
Come with me!
Shane!
Shane, I'm telling you to come with me!
Shane, come here!
-Get lost!
-Shane!
Shane, it's me.
It's all right.
I will end up like Yod.
Som, I brought your watch back.
But I accidentally broke it again.
I don't think I can fix it
for you this time.
Shane, don't talk like that.
You're going to be all right.
Mr. Rashane, please go
to the examination room.
From what I can see,
you have a fracture in your left arm.
I will give you some medicine
for the pain,
then you can go home.
So, what were the two of you doing
in that house?
We were looking for more information
to do a news story about Chaba's death.
What are you talking about?
Chaba is not dead.
Doctor, what do you mean?
PSYCHIATRIC FACILITY
Right after Chaba was taken
by the villagers to be hanged,
the police arrived just in time to send
her to the hospital and saved her life.
However, all the villagers
believed she died.
So the story was forgotten.
There. That is Chaba.
Are you sure that old lady
is really Chaba?
Yes, I'm sure.
So if Chaba is not dead,
then...
SAKDA TOUR COMPANY LIMITED
...who was that woman you saw?
Who is she?
Is it possible
that everything is just a figment
of your imagination?
SRI SIAM CENTER
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
NONG RAHAN - BANGKOK
Shane.
Som,
the person I've been seeing
is her.
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
Shane, you mean this actress?
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT STARRING INGCHAN
PHROM PONG FILM
Thank you.
Are you looking for somebody?
Nobody has come to work
at that company for over a week.
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
FORMS FOR LOCATION MAPS
ID CARDS, NAMES, AND FINANCE FORMS
TEAM NAME LIST
MOVIE CREW FOR "REVENGEFUL SPIRIT"
THITA KANJANACHAIROJ BUM
BACKGROUND IMAGES OF VILLAGERS
LOOKING FOR PANG
NO. 25 BEHIND THE SCENES
PANG
Sorry--
BUMJOOM PAPOOM TOH
THE HANGING SCENE OF CHABA
Hey, cameraman. Over there.
-Okay.
-Move towards the end a little.
-We're ready now.
What was that?
Are you ready?
The director is getting impatient.
Okay. Where is it?
Make way, please.
-Are the lights ready?
-Make way, please.
What is that rope?
All right.
-Okay?
-Yes, we're ready.
Action.
-Kill her!
-Go to hell!
Cut.
-Come.
-Action!
-That's right! Pull the rope!
-Kill her!
-That's right!
Cut!
-Action.
-Hey.
Hey!
-Help, please.
-Cut.
Take 25.
Action!
Hey! Help me. I can't take it anymore.
-Help, please!
-Cut.
Shit. Just this and you can't even do it?
Jeab.
You call this acting?
Hey, your foot position is wrong.
-You know what I mean?
-Okay.
What are you afraid of?
You're tensing all the wrong body parts.
I don't know. It's just...
you looked like you were dancing,
and not dying.
Try and focus this time, okay?
Action!
-Pull the rope!
-Go to hell!
Cut!
You don't even have any lines.
All you have to do is act
like you're dying. You can't do it?
Action.
-That's right! Pull the rope!
-Kill her!
-Hey!
-Cut!
-Damn it!
-You can do better.
Damn, why is it so difficult?
Can we try it again, one more time?
If she can't get it this time, then Jeab,
you go change and take her place instead.
What are you scared of? I don't get it!
What's not safe? See? It's safe. Okay?
How many times are you going
to repeat the same mistake?
Everybody is waiting for you.
Can we film already? Damn it!
We're ready.
Okay, ready, everyone?
Just one more time, okay?
Get out of my way!
Help! Help!
What the hell? Fuck.
Hey, Jeab.
Jeab, come have a look.
-Come have a look.
-What?
-Come and see!
-Shit.
-Look, the sling's broken.
-Holy shit.
Oh, damn! Stop! Everybody stop!
-The sling broke. Toh, the sling broke!
-What the fuck?
Get her down. Get her down first!
Cut! Get her down, quickly!
-Come on help her down.
-Get her down.
-Quickly!
-Toh, get her down first!
Get her down first! Shit!
It's okay. Don't die!
Is she okay?
Sorry--
Shane!
Shane, where are you going?
Som,
if I don't make it back tomorrow,
please don't go to the theater.
Don't watch the movie.
Why?
The scene where Chaba died
in the movie is for real.
Ingchan's death was for real.
And whoever watches that scene...
will die.
Shane, what are you going to do?
Where are you going?
Shane!
I'm sorry, Som.
Hey, Shane.
Keeping to yourself lately?
Where are you going in such a hurry?
I've been waiting for you for many days.
Don't tell me you're going to try
to skip out on me again?
The exit is to your right.
Yeah, the movie just ended.
I'm leaving now.
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
Hey, Shane.
Keeping to yourself lately?
Where are you going in such a hurry?
I've been waiting for you for many days.
Don't tell me you're going to try
to skip out on me again?
The exit is to your right.
Yeah, the movie just ended.
I'm leaving now.
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
Hey, Shane.
Keeping to yourself lately?
Where are you going in such a hurry?
I've been waiting for you for many days.
Don't tell me you're going to try
to skip out on me again?
Shithead!
What the fuck!
Som!
Shane!
Shane?
Som!
Som.
You really want to see me die?
Look at me!
Do you really want to see?
Shit!
Shane!
Yod.
Shane.
Shane!
RESENTMENT NEVER DIES
REVENGEFUL SPIRIT
Dear customers who are here for the film
Revengeful Spirit, you can catch it
at 12:15 a.m.
The movie is about to start.
Do you really wanna see me die?