Papa, I want one.
No, I don't want to hear
your mom complain.
Let's go somewhere else.
-It's too loud. The baby is crying.
-Come here.
Let's go. We'll miss the countdown.
Let's dance.
Are you tired already?
Cee.
Say something.
I'll send your brother a clip.
What?
Hey, Sun.
-Ten, nine, eight, seven,
-six, five, four,
-three, two, one.
-Six, five, four, three, two, one.
Damn.
I got the key copied.
I'll swing by Rite Aid first.
Okay?
Wait for three minutes.
Is that a kid or instant noodles?
I'm clueless. What does it mean?
I told you. I'm not pregnant.
No kid!
I have good news too.
Cool, right?
So Dad will stop threatening
to cut me off.
It would be cooler
if it wasn't misspelled.
What?
It's "business," not "busyness."
How do I spell that?
You're busy?
You should save energy to help me unpack.
I am unpacking.
What a waste of time.
Well?
Fabio slept with someone else.
How did you know?
He said a cat scratched him.
What kind of cat bites nipples?
Chill out.
Herbal remedies can take the edge off.
Babe,
let me take you to heaven.
He's funny.
Por bought a new mattress.
Selling weed must make him a fortune.
-Want to sell some?
-What?
Are you crazy?
Come on.
Mr. Famous wants to see us.
What?
NYPD, my ass.
Why are you painting your room?
Are you renovating?
Not renovating. I'm moving out, bitch.
What?
If I don't paint the room...
See? Jose won't return my deposit.
Are you moving far?
In case I miss you and I want to visit.
Not far.
Just back to Thailand.
Do you want to come?
Do you?
Do you want to come with me?
I'm hungry. Feel free to tag along.
Hey, Por.
Are you going back for good?
Why are you in a hurry?
I have my reasons.
Can you not be nosy for once?
Who will I buy weed from when you're gone?
-Are you craving for some?
-Yes.
You're looking pale.
Sorry, I'm turning over a new leaf.
What?
I'm clean now, dude.
There.
See for yourself. Take a look.
Did you throw away all the good stuff?
See, amigo?
Finito.
I stopped buying.
I stopped smoking.
I even stopped selling.
Isn't that amazing?
Did you hit your head or something?
Hey, Jack.
You should stop too.
It's a new year. You should start fresh.
Quit all the bad shit.
Quit getting high. Trust me.
Life is short.
Give me the dealer's card.
I'll deal with him.
You asshole.
Didn't you hear me? If you want it,
get it from someone else.
Don't get me involved.
Why are you so worked up?
Are you having a midlife crisis?
I'm on my period.
I'll take this.
I've been eyeing it for a long time.
Hey.
You look familiar.
Have we met before?
We've probably
run into each other in the building.
No.
Are you an actress in Thailand?
Hey, dude. What's this?
A nail gun.
It's too heavy to take back.
It's so cool. Can I have it?
Go ahead.
Don't blame me
if you shoot yourself in the balls.
Shit.
It's missing one digit.
Damn. Is that your breath or your dog's?
You bitch.
What the hell is that?
The dealer's name card.
Por stopped dealing,
so I have to call him myself.
Drug dealers have name cards too?
Cool.
But the last digit is missing.
There are ten possibilities. Take a guess.
Which number do you like, babe?
Three.
Why three?
It's the new year.
If you add a three, it will be 2013.
That's so dope.
How about four? So it will be next year.
You're not even helping.
Jack.
-Jack!
-What?
Are you seriously counting down the hours?
Looks like you need a fix. Come here.
Make yourself useful.
You know it's no good
for a sinner like me to do good deeds.
Shit. What is this?
-Your dog's blood?
-It's your mother's.
-My mother's, my ass.
-You're an ass.
Haven't you ever had blood pudding?
It's a sacred dish.
You'll go to hell for calling it that.
Hell can't handle me.
Anyway,
will you go make merit with me tomorrow?
I'm staying up for the countdown.
I want to sleep in.
-Come on, man.
-What?
Bee.
Can you go with my aunt for me?
She's your aunt, not mine.
Jerk.
Jack, when will the dealer arrive?
He said he'd come around nine,
which is in...
Ten, nine,
-Damn. He's a person, not a microwave.
-eight, seven,
six, five,
four, three,
two, one.
Feliz año nuevo, señor.
I'm Jesus.
What the hell is he saying?
"Jabba Pizza Hut"? What the hell is that?
I don't know,
but he's making me hungry.
Taiwan, my ass.
Up your father's ass!
Puta madre.
Margarita. El Niño.
Come on. Don't be upset, Jack.
Hang in there.
Fuck you. I'm going to pee.
Do you want to give me a hand?
Shit!
Holy shit!
Do you remember Fai?
She saw Fabio and his new girl
at the Circle.
Look at her.
She looks like a lizard even in photos.
Do you think I'm beautiful?
The most beautiful.
I told you Italians just bone you
and dump you.
You know it all, don't you?
I'm a Buddhist.
Thanks for saving me from a very sad
and lonely countdown tonight.
Sharing is caring.
Hey. It's free. Why don't you try it?
Are you a youth ambassador?
Why are you so uptight?
You've had enough, Pam.
You have to go
to the temple early tomorrow.
God, how many sins
have you committed since this evening?
It's not that. We don't know
if he put drugs in there.
Didn't you learn a lesson
after we lost 1,400 dollars?
Don't tell him, Jack.
We don't know him. How can we trust him?
That's right. How can we trust someone
we don't know? Take you for example.
What do you mean?
Can I trust you?
I don't know a single thing about you.
You never tell me anything.
Stop it, Pam.
Shit, a cockroach!
You scared me.
Fuck you, cockroach.
I'll have my dog, Chanel, eat you.
It's freaking funny.
You know, Chanel likes to chew things.
She chews on everything she sees.
One time, I left my Chanel bag
in the room.
Just imagine,
Chanel chewed on the Chanel bag.
You're talking so fast.
I can't catch anything.
What did he say?
What the hell is up with him?
Are you possessed by the Holy Spirit?
We should give him the money,
so he can leave.
Why did you squeeze so damn hard?
I'm building the suspense.
Bathroom.
Shit.
Hey. Why are you flushing it?
He said the cops are coming.
Come here to help, Jack. Hurry.
Jesus!
You ordered pizza?
Does it look like pad thai?
Why didn't you tell me?
You should have seen Jesus' face.
He ran as if a tsunami was coming.
He's a grown-up man,
but he's such a pussy.
He's about to cry.
Stop laughing at him.
Jack, give him the money, so he can go.
Damn.
You played rough.
My ears are ringing.
It's not number three.
Shit.
Are you out of your mind, Jack?
What kind of wallet is that expensive?
Wouldn't it be better
to give that money to a beggar?
Get up here!
Your dad sent you money for school.
What did you spend it on?
Did you spend it on weed?
That hurts!
-On stupid earrings?
-That hurts!
Why are you like this?
Do you have any tattoos?
-Show it to me.
-That hurts.
Won't your parents be devastated
if they find out?
You asshole. Take this.
You're hurting me. Stop!
That's enough! Stop it!
Turn around!
Your dad's factory went bankrupt,
so he sent you abroad to study.
Who the hell are you?
Did my dad send you?
What's wrong with you?
Are you thinking
with your brain or your feet?
What kind of father would send someone
to beat up his kid?
Why won't it pause?
Why won't it pause? Come on.
What's up?
Won't you laugh anymore?
Well, this isn't funny.
I see.
I'll fix that.
Is this funny?
Laugh, bitch.
I said laugh.
If you don't laugh,
I'll beat him until his spleen explodes.
I said laugh!
Laugh.
You're crying. I said laugh.
Laugh now.
Laugh!
Do you remember the story about my dog?
Do you want to know the ending?
Time passed by for, like...
three months,
and it stopped biting.
Because I pulled out all its teeth.
Creative, right?
I'm so sorry
for laughing at you.
You can take whatever you want.
I see.
What if I said I want you,
can I have you now?
Why are you so violent?
Come here.
I haven't done anything to you!
Come here. Where are you going?
Come here.
That's enough.
What are you doing?
That tickles.
Come here.
Shit. He can't breathe.
Wait, Jack.
Wait for what? He will die.
What if he wakes up?
What?
What do you want me to do?
Jack.
Go!
Leave!
I said go! Go now!
Fuck!
Open up! Help!
I'm tired.
Don't make me use force.
Would you open the door?
I'll give you three seconds
to decide.
Please don't hurt my dog.
Three!
Mommy.
Please help me.
Please don't hurt my dog.
I'm begging you!
Two!
Open.
Mommy, please open the door for me.
Don't you love me anymore?
One!
Damn it. Open.
What?
Are you all awake?
I have a question for you, guys.
What do death row prisoners do
before they die?
The cops are coming.
What did you just say?
The neighbors already heard me.
The cops are coming.
Here.
You didn't answer my question.
Death row prisoners confess their sins
before they die.
Why?
To cleanse their souls
before going to heaven.
My bad.
Before their souls get damned to hell.
Who wants to go first?
Pam.
Do you have anything to confess?
If you don't hurry,
I'll start counting down.
-Mister.
-What?
Please don't hurt me.
There's money in my room if you want.
Jack and Bee, I am sorry.
Sorry for what? Say it.
I was the one who stole the money.
Tell your friends what you did with it.
Don't be ashamed.
They have the right to know.
I spent all the money my mom sent me
on clothes at Woodbury.
Fabio said I wasn't pretty.
I didn't want him to leave me.
I didn't want to be alone.
Stupid bitch.
It's your turn, handsome.
I want some real drama, okay?
No basic shit like banging a girl
and dumping her.
I am a bad son.
Louder.
Louder!
I'm an ungrateful son.
Louder, or I will shoot you dead
right now!
I'm an ungrateful son!
I've been lying to my parents!
-I just want to say sorry!
-There.
That wasn't so hard.
I didn't need to yell.
Here.
Now is your chance.
Don't act stupid. Take it.
Dad, help...
What's wrong with you?
Why do you have to yell?
Nothing, Dad.
I just want to talk.
Dad! I have something to confess.
Can you hear me?
What is it?
All the money you sent me last time,
I didn't use it to pay for my tuition.
I spent it all on partying.
I haven't been accepted to college yet.
Jack.
You've been there for three years,
and you still haven't been accepted?
I sold my factory to send you to school.
Do you know that?
-Do you?
-I'm so sorry, Dad.
Enough.
You can talk to him on Skype later.
You're wasting his money.
Pam. Jack.
Look at me when I talk to you!
Are you sure that what you just confessed
are the worst sins you've committed?
Do you have anything else to confess?
Come on.
Maybe you didn't get my question.
I'll get to the point.
Do you two have anything
to confess to Bee?
Jack, just say it.
-Right.
-Just tell Bee.
You're a girl. You tell her.
You're a man. You tell her.
Enough!
I'll tell her.
Two days ago,
these two got drunk and slept together.
Isn't that right?
Bee.
I'm sorry.
It's your fault, Jack.
I was really drunk that night.
Bullshit. You weren't even drunk.
You seduced me. I didn't start it.
-Cut it out.
-Damn it.
I said enough.
You're pointing fingers now,
but when you were doing it...
"Jack, hurry. Bee is coming back soon."
"Hold it. I'm about to cum."
Your sins aren't that bad.
Her secret is the most shocking.
She has a lot to tell.
Turn around.
Turn around and have a chat with us.
Do you have anything
to confess to your friends?
Spit it out.
Shit.
Stay still.
Jackie.
Hey.
Jack.
Are you in there?
Crap. Your face is messed up.
What happened to you?
I had a fight with my girl.
Is your girl here?
She's the reason I'm here.
I wasn't sure at first
because she cut her hair.
So I got proof for you.
I dug up old newspapers at Namtarn's.
I think...
You should read it yourself.
Go take a shit.
Wait. I forgot my sour sausage.
Is she in there?
Why didn't you tell me?
Bee.
I was just joking. I...
I was just messing around.
I'm really high right now.
Bee, are you mad?
Now.
Let's see if there's any interesting news
happening in Thailand.
Let's see.
"Townsfolk seek lucky numbers
from a two-headed calf."
Typical.
"A pervert fakes a ritual to rape victim."
Happens every day.
"A millionaire kills five people
when ex-wife refuses to make up."
"A female speedster kills a whole family
in a crash on New Year's Day.
The car crashes at high speed,
then a pretty girl
was seen fleeing the scene."
Please stop.
"The reckless driver was identified
as the daughter of a famous politician.
Four dead. The son flies back from England
-to take the bodies home today."
-Stop.
"Dad fabricates a false confession
and insists on his daughter's innocence,
but an eyewitness confirms she's at fault.
-The case has gone quiet
-I said enough!
after the scapegoat took the fall."
What?
A RECKLESS DRIVER KILLS FOUR PEOPLE
AND FLEES ABROAD
-Shit.
-Please stop.
Bee, you're so famous.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm a fan of your work.
Can I have an autograph, please?
Leave me alone!
It was an accident.
What do you want from me?
Is this what it's about?
Their family sent you here, right?
You guys called me!
Stop asking me this question!
You scum are so hard to kill.
Luckily,
I always come prepared.
There.
I didn't mean to.
Thailand is a Buddhist country, right?
Do you know the five precepts?
Have you learned them?
Let me take a piss.
Okay.
I'll give you guys another chance
to get out of this.
You should clean your toilet.
It's gross.
You have to recite all five precepts.
If you get them right,
I will let you live.
But if you get even one word wrong,
I will kill all of you.
Or do you want my help?
I can blow your brains out right now!
I observe the precept
of abstaining
from the destruction of life.
That's very good.
You can recite it,
but you don't practice it.
What is the second precept, baby?
Please don't do anything to me.
I really don't know.
Please don't hurt me.
Okay. Come here.
It's okay.
Take it easy.
It's okay if you don't know.
Just repeat after me.
I observe the precept of abstaining...
I said repeat after me! Do it!
"I observe the precept
of abstaining..."
From taking that...
"From taking that..."
Which is not given!
Now.
The third precept is for you.
It hits right home.
Recite the third precept
for your punk-ass friends.
I observe the precept
of abstaining from sexual misconduct.
Wow. Excellent.
Did you get an A
when you studied Buddhism?
It's your turn.
What's the fourth precept?
You idiot.
I'll recite it for you,
and you should remember it.
I observe the precept
of abstaining from falsehood.
of abstaining from falsehood!
Do you remember now?
Do you?
And now,
it's the final part of our show.
The three contestants
need to recite
the fifth precept altogether.
Are you all ready?
If you are,
let's hear it!
-I observe
-the precept...
Let's start again. Recite it together,
loud and clear.
-I observe
-the precept
-of abstaining--
Wrong!
I will give you
one last chance.
-I observe
the precept...
I observe...
The precept...
Of...
Abstaining from intoxicants...
Easy now.
Let's discuss this.
Fuck.
Fuck you.
Let me go!
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
Please!
Stop it, please.
Please let me go.
I can't take this anymore.
Just let me go.
Please let me go.
Tell me then.
Why should I let you live?
Give me one good reason
why you should continue living
in this world?
You can't, can you?
But I have
four reasons
why I shouldn't let you live!
Do you have anything else to confess?
Bee?
What else do you want me to say?
Anything you haven't said yet.
So you'll have no regrets once you die.
That girl...
She wasn't dead yet.
When the car crashed,
the girl...
She was still alive.
You left her there to die?
You left her lying there?
She's a person, not a dog!
If you had rushed her to the hospital,
-she wouldn't have died!
-I know!
Enough! Just shoot me!
Shoot me now!
Okay. I'll give you an out.
I'll let you choose between
killing me
or
shooting yourself in the head.
Grab the brass ring. Come on.
What's so hard about it? Just shoot me.
Once the cops arrive,
you can say I killed those three.
You just defended yourself.
Your parents can hire a lawyer
to clean this up.
You can flee to another country
and start over,
walking away unpunished
like you did before.
Sounds good?
Stop overthinking.
Here. Okay?
Just pull the trigger,
and it will all be over.
It's so easy to kill a person.
You're a professional.
This special chance expires
on New Year's Day.
Damn.
You just won't die.
Humans and cockroaches are the same.
They are so damn useless.
They just try to get by.
Jack.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Bee.
What the hell happened last night?
It happened to all of us, right?
Did it happen to you too?
Jack.
I went to Chinatown to eat.
I got food for you.
What took you so long?
Are you watching porn?
Your nose is bleeding.
Did I call you last night?
No, you didn't.
Are you okay?
Mom.
Yes? What is it?
I have something to confess.
I spent all my pocket money
on a shopping spree.
I haven't gotten accepted yet.
I stole my friends' money.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I didn't mean to.
Bee.
Where are you going?
Home.
What do you mean by "home"?
Juvenile home, maybe.
I don't know either.
Are you sure about this?
I already bought the ticket online.
Damn, Pam.
Your snot is dripping on my back.
Asshole.
Come on, Jack.
I'll have to tell Jose
about this elevator.
What about it?
It moves slowly,
and it's missing a button.
Do you know
what death row prisoners do
before they die?
They confess their sins.
Subtitle translation by Joey Vajrabukka