NEW YORK
I know that it's a lot of money.
Please believe me,
I'll pay back every single dime.
Please.
I…
I really need it.
Please. I'm begging you.
What!
So you'll let Rachel go blind?
Am I going to be blind?
No, honey.
I'll never let that happen.
You'll have a surgery.
And you'll be able to see like before.
Don't worry.
Hi, Ruja. It's me, Wichai.
Your dad's friend.
Remember me?
There's something important
I need to tell you.
I think you should come back to Thailand.
How did you find me?
Don't…
Don't go back!
Ruja.
We're here.
Let's get inside.
CHIANG MAI
Grandma's house is so big.
What's this room, mommy?
Dining room, honey.
Let's go.
Mommy, are we moving here?
No.
We're here just for a few days.
Hi, Da.
Welcome home, ma'am.
This is Rachel, my daughter.
Ruja.
Come to the studio with me.
Da can look after Rachel.
Now?
Yes. I'll have to leave soon.
It won't take long.
Can you stay with Da? I'll be right back.
But I want to come with you.
Kids are not allowed
in the studio, Rachel.
Stay here with me.
I'll show you your bedroom upstairs.
Want to see it?
Come on.
Wait.
Rachel has eye problems.
Please be very careful.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go.
Ruja.
Come in.
Look here, Portrait of a Beauty,
Number One and Number Two.
Your father painted them
over 20 years ago.
Painting Number One
was sold to one of his fans for…
several million.
But it was returned to this studio…
because…
the owner killed all his family members
and then killed himself.
He left a note under the painting.
It said…
''I'm returning you to your creator.''
So, we got it back for free.
As for Number Two,
Pakorn kept it in good condition.
Said it wasn't for sale.
But now,
a millionaire is willing to pay a fortune
to buy both of them.
I need your permission first.
When will we get the money?
Are you not even going to ask
how your father died?
Yummy, Rachel?
Yummy.
Let me ask you something.
How's your grandma Vipa doing?
Grandma died, from cancer.
Did she?
She didn't hang herself?
Pakorn, your father…
hung himself here.
From that beam.
What is "hang herself?"
Never mind. Forget it.
Forgive him, Ruja.
Think of these expensive paintings
as his redemption.
Are we done?
I want to get out of here.
Rachel, where're you going?
I want to see mommy.
Where did you get that?
You gave it to me just now.
Let me have it back.
I'll wash it for you first.
You wait for your mommy here.
She'll be back soon.
One more thing.
The paintings have some cracks.
I want them fixed before we sell them.
My son is an art restorer,
he can take care of it.
If you think it's necessary, do it.
One more thing…
After his funeral,
I want to sell this house too.
Please see to it for me.
Mommy?
Rachel!
What are you doing?
Please don't hold it against me!
Mommy…
Grandpa's paintings. Why can't I see them?
They're scary.
How scary?
So scary that you'll have nightmares.
You don't like nightmares, do you?
Aren't you scared, mommy?
Why does dad paint you like that?
It's just an act.
Like in a play.
It helped dad create nice paintings.
But you cried.
It's nothing, Ruja.
But you must not go
into dad's studio again.
He needs to focus on his work.
Promise me, dear.
I miss your grandma, honey.
Don't cry, mommy.
Don't cry.
Rachel.
Mommy.
Mommy!
Rachel!
Rachel.
What's going on?
Have you seen Rachel?
Rachel.
Rachel!
Da.
Let's split up.
I'll look in the forest.
Rachel!
Are you in there?
I'm not playing with you!
Come out now!
Rachel!
Where were you? You scared me to death.
I took a walk and I met him.
Are you Ruja?
My name's Tim.
I'm here to fix the paintings,
my dad must have told you.
Where did you go for a walk?
Tell me where.
By the stream back there.
It's dangerous.
Don't do it again.
What would I do
if something happened to you?
I wasn't alone.
I went with the woman with a red scarf.
Stop lying.
I'm not lying.
Rachel.
I'm sorry.
Please don't do it again.
I'm sorry, honey.
Here.
Thank you.
Da,
what happened to your ankle?
Just a sprain. Nothing serious.
Excuse me.
What were you doing in the woods?
I paint landscapes.
My dad said there's a beautiful stream
behind the house.
So I went to look.
And luckily, I bumped into Rachel.
Rachel has eye problems.
It's not safe for her to wander around.
I see.
But thank you anyway.
Look…
I'll show you my sketches.
Even better, I'll draw you.
You don't have to please her.
It's okay. I really want to draw her.
Here we go.
Done.
Want to see it?
It's ugly.
I think it's pretty.
How about this?
Next time I'll draw you
like a princess. Okay?
I'm sorry.
How long will it take
to fix the paintings?
I need to see them
before I can answer that.
But I've heard the damages
are minor. Right?
Mommy, when will the rain stop?
I want to play outside.
Rachel.
Listen to mommy.
From now on, when you want to go outside
you have to ask me first.
Understand?
Can I go with Tim?
No, you can't.
But I like him.
I want him to draw my picture.
Ruja.
Tim.
Hi, Rachel.
How's it going?
Let me talk to your mommy for a second.
You should come see
something in the studio.
Can I come too?
Whatever it is,
you don't need my permission.
It's not about the restoration.
Believe me, you have to see it.
This.
I had no idea it was this bad.
Look at these cracks.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
What are you doing?
You'll ruin it even more.
I have to fix it anyway, right?
Put it back right now.
Don't you want to see what's underneath?
No.
It could be a big discovery,
may raise the value
of your father's paintings artistically--
I don't care. Okay? Put it back.
You should care.
If you want to sell it.
Or…
Do you think it's haunted?
Nonsense.
I'm kidding.
But I don't get it.
People always think of ghosts
when they see unexpected things.
But everything can be explained.
Listen…
You know the Mona Lisa?
You do.
They say when you lock your eyes with hers
her gaze will follow you
no matter where you walk in the room.
But it has nothing to do with ghosts.
The same with this painting.
Let's test it.
See for yourself
so you'll stop being afraid.
Let's try.
Look her in the eyes.
And walk this way.
Is she following you?
See? I told you.
What's wrong?
Just fix the damn thing.
Is this your dress, mommy?
Can I try it on?
Da!
You shouldn't let her play
with dirty clothes!
Burn them all. Come here.
Rachel.
Are you okay?
There's someone under the bed.
It's just you and me here.
Fine.
I'll look.
Mommy, I can't see.
Rachel!
Rachel.
Ruja! What's the matter?
Get me out of here.
-What's wrong?
-Just get me out of here!
It's pouring outside.
But I need to get out of here!
You have to help me!
Calm down.
Take it easy.
Have some tea.
Rachel.
This anklet has a magical power.
I'm giving it to you.
Let me put it on.
It came from a tribal village
in the hills.
They believe that
if you walk around wearing it,
the jingling sound can chase away demons.
Try it.
Thank you for the anklet.
You can paint, right?
How come you chose to be a restorer?
It pays well, so why not?
I wanted to be an artist.
Even had an exhibition once.
All my paintings were sold out.
Because my dad hired people
to buy them up.
It made me realize
that I could never
run away from his shadow.
So I decided to work with him instead.
I'm no different.
You're doing it for your daughter.
I'm sure Rachel is so proud of you.
Rachel likes you a lot.
I know.
Because I'm handsome.
Sorry, honey.
We have to go.
Tim.
Ruja.
I was about to come and get you.
You have to see this.
I don't want to go in there.
The rain's stopped, let just go.
Take a look first and then we can leave.
I don't want Rachel to go in there.
It's okay. I'm here with you.
Just a quick look.
Don't look.
Wait for me here.
Don't look at the paintings.
Promise?
Promise.
Good girl.
Did you rip it off?
I'm sorry.
I really wanted to know what's underneath.
You know what? This man--
Was the one who committed suicide.
How do you know?
You father told me.
I've been wondering
why he did what he did.
If we peel off the whole thing,
we might know the truth.
There is no truth whatsoever!
And it's none of my business.
Get me and my daughter out of here now!
Rachel!
Where are you?
Ruja.
Mommy.
Wait for me, mommy.
You're hurting me.
Da!
Ma'am.
Let her go.
I have no choice.
If I don't do it,
she won't leave me in peace.
What are you talking about?
Let her go right now.
No.
No. I can't! I have to do this!
Mommy, help me!
Mommy.
She's a just a kid,
she has nothing to do with this.
In that case…
you jump instead,
and I will let her go.
What are you talking about?
Please don't do this. I'm begging you.
No.
I have to do it.
I have to!
Please don't hurt me.
I'll do anything for you.
Kill them all.
I have no choice.
Jump!
Da…
Da.
Calm down, please.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry!
Help me, mommy.
Da!
Rachel!
Are you hurt?
You wait here. I'll be right back.
What are you doing?
I'm going to rip it to pieces!
Are you crazy?
It's all because of these damn paintings!
You think you can save me
by destroying the paintings?
Rachel, what's wrong with you?
What did you just say?
Rachel.
I'm not your fucking daughter.
Because of you and your evil family,
I have become like this!
Rachel.
Rachel!
Ruja.
What happened?
Get me and my daughter out of here.
What the hell's going on?
Please, get us out of here!
Boring.
I'll do anything…
to make you love me again.
Love?
How corny.
I can make you happy.
Like before.
Want to make me happy like before?
Rachel.
Don't move. It'll hurt more.
Want some?
Who are you?
Who the fuck are you?
Your mother was sexy.
Where's Rachel?
An artist's party can get pretty wild.
Tell me about these paintings.
Okay.
I'll tell you.
But promise me you won't hurt me.
Okay.
After that night's party…
Pakorn picked only two close friends
to stay for the real highlight.
Prang, his favorite model,
was a surprise he'd prepared for them.
Pakorn wanted the two guests
to take part in his artistic creation.
He's the first one who died,
along with his entire family.
Your son's lighter is actually cool.
Tim!
Don't hurt me.
Tell me what you want!
I'll give you everything.
Just let me go.
Apologize to my mother.
Mom.
Mom, look at this.
Ruja.
Listen to me.
Prang…
and her son
are bad people.
They are a ghost-worshipping hill-tribe.
They hurt your dad.
They hurt me.
And they will hurt you.
Ruja.
Ruja!
Listen to me.
We must not let them hurt us.
If we pretend not to see them,
they cannot hurt us.
Repeat after me.
If we pretend not to see them,
they cannot hurt us.
You really didn't see it, Ruja?
Mom!
Dad, help mom!
Help her!
Dad, help her!
You'll be okay.
Somebody, help my mom.
Please, help my mom.
I still don't get it…
why dad didn't help mom that night.
But I knew
there's someone who could.
It's you, Ruja.
Help my mom, Ruja!
Help my mom!
If we pretend not to see them,
they cannot hurt us.
I told you to stay away when I'm working.
Is that hard to understand?
Idiot!
Ruja.
Help, please.
Help my mom, Ruja.
You fucking idiot!
Ruja.
What's wrong?
Help my mom, Ruja.
I know you saw everything.
But you and your mother
just ran away.
You know what they did to us after that?
I've been waiting
to paint your beautiful face.
But you're in pretty bad shape right now.
Rachel!
Help me, mommy.
I'm here, honey.
Rachel!
Mommy is right here.
Please don't hurt her.
Don't hurt her.
Hurt me instead!
Do it to me!
You never knew how it feels
seeing your loved one
being tortured and killed
and that you can't do anything about it.
You will know now.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry?
You're sorry?
Soon you'll be very sorry.
Don't touch her!
Let her go now!
Wichai's son is going to erase
the truth under the painting of yours.
I'm doing this for you, Prang.
Mommy.
Mommy!
Ruja.
We must not let them hurt us.
If we pretend not to see them,
they cannot hurt us.
Listen to mommy, Rachel.
We only have each other now.
I'll protect you with my own life.
No one can hurt you again.
I promise.
ONE MONTH BEFORE