All right, class. Today we're going
to talk about your dreams.
I want each of you
to tell me what you want to be
when you grow up.
Okay?
Let's start with Doc.
I want to be a doctor.
Very good.
Now, Boy, how about you?
I want to be like Toon Bodyslam.
Huh?
Anyone else with a serious answer?
I want to be pregnant.
I want to have kids.
That's awesome!
That's absolutely fine, dear.
But after you grow up, get married,
then think about it. Okay?
Understand?
PRINCIPAL
Well done, Kanlaya.
You're the top student of our province.
Your family must be proud.
HONORABLE CERTIFICATE
KANLAYA HEWSAKUL
Ho.
Dad.
Where's Mom and big sister?
I have something to tell you guys.
I have something to tell you, too.
Well, Dad, you go first.
Your mom and your sister
were in a car crash.
Ho.
Congratulations!
What gives?
CRAZY CRYING LADY
What's up?
Doc, I cried in my sleep again.
And are you okay?
Yeah, I guess.
If you're okay, then go back to bed.
Nothing to worry about.
But I was crying hard.
Then you're not okay.
-You want to tell me about it?
-Yeah.
Doc, why do I cry so often?
Every little thing can set me off.
I cry even when I'm asleep.
Can you help me?
You're a doctor!
What's that have to do with it?
Your problem isn't from some disease.
It comes from your feelings.
Your feelings are the problem.
Any problems in your life?
Of course.
You'll have a problem with me.
I can't take this.
Get out of my house!
You're getting too queer.
-In what way?
-In every way.
It's just the way things are, Dad.
Anything can happen these days.
Gays are the leaders of fashion.
The gay stuff is not normal.
Why is that?
What's wrong with being gay?
Nana is not wrong.
What did you just call yourself?
Nana.
I named you Nava,
and you changed it to Nana on your own!
Bastard!
What's going on, Dad?
Look at your brother.
Who raised him to be this way?
This is unacceptable.
Nava, please.
Please what? I don't care.
Why?
I am gay and so what?
I'm not hurting anybody.
It's me you're hurting.
Dad, calm down.
Just say what you want him to do.
-Here.
-What?
Three things.
One.
Don't bring that ugly
gay friend of yours here again.
I can't stand him.
I haven't introduced myself to you, Papa.
My name is Sabina.
Would slapping a child gay
be against a military rule?
Enough, Dad.
No! Two.
Don't dress like this again.
You don't like this?
Happy now?
Did you get a boob job?
Do I have to take it off?
No!
I'm almost barfing 'cause of this.
You criticize how I dress.
And look at you.
What about me?
You've been retired for a long time,
but you're still wearing
your full uniform.
Walking around
with your sweaty armpits all day.
It's pretty close to madness.
Really close.
Captain, don't forget the third one.
Three.
Don't do this again.
That's my phone!
What is it?
It is...
Still here.
Look at it yourself.
Hello.
Today I'm going to teach you
how to do a sweet makeup look.
EXPERT NANA
125 VIEWS
First of all, lip color.
Red is the color of attraction.
Next, we'll add some sweetness
with eyeshadow.
Pink is the only color to choose.
Apply.
And apply.
But if you have to be
up close to your guy,
try this, syrup or a sugar solution.
The same method.
Dip your finger in it,
then apply on the eyelids.
Apply.
In case your guy wants to taste it,
the sweetness on your eyelids
will linger on the tip of his tongue.
Next Monday,
I'll teach you how to play a ukulele.
On Wednesday,
I'll teach you how to dance the robot.
And on Friday,
I'll teach you how to open cockles
without hurting your hands.
And for now...
good-bye.
A high-ranking officer like me
has a son who teaches how to open cockles.
Why, Dad?
What's wrong with a gay on YouTube?
It's wrong in every way.
You don't have any art in your heart.
I neither have art nor heart.
My heart has been dead for a long time.
Shit.
Melodrama time.
Those tears are coming?
Not yet.
If your mom were still here,
it wouldn't have been like this.
There you go with those words.
I think we should split up for now.
Why do you want to be gay, Nava?
Nana!
Okay. Nana.
I'm begging you.
Try to change yourself.
Try to be a man.
Try to have manly friends.
It might turn out well.
You'll never know if you don't try.
No, I don't want to.
I'm not into it.
You don't understand me.
If our sister Lookpong were still here...
she wouldn't have said this to me.
There it is.
It looks like fun, Nana.
To do what we haven't done before.
It might be a good thing.
We'll never know if we don't try.
Try?
You think so?
Okay.
I'll try.
Yeah. We'll never know if we don't try.
I just said the exact same thing.
Come on. Let's plan this.
So exciting!
Wait.
There's one more person to deal with.
Dad.
Dad?
Dad!
Dad.
Dad. Come out and talk.
What's there to talk about?
I'd like to ask you to compromise.
Being strict is not always a good thing.
We need to learn
how and when to compromise.
You're a teacher.
Just teach at school, not at home.
I'm a soldier.
I follow rules strictly.
But this is our home, not a battlefield.
Could you please stop thinking about
the past and start thinking about future?
I have.
So, can you tell me
what you think about the future?
How about next year?
I want to get enlisted.
Oh, shit.
Being enlisted at the age of 60...
If you die on the battlefield,
they don't even count you as a casualty.
Damn, Doc.
You're a doctor, not a soldier.
You don't know shit.
When one sacrifices himself
on the battlefield
so someone else can survive,
the survivor...
must live on suffering dearly.
This is Major Choochai.
Why are you posing, Major?
Sit down now.
You all understand, right?
The one who picks the short stick
must carry the bomb and run in there.
Pick one now!
Long.
One down.
Pick one.
-Long.
Wow.
We're the last two, Major.
Don't be scared.
Why do you look so pale?
Remember, we are Thai,
we are born to fight.
No need to pick.
You have a family waiting for you.
I'll volunteer.
What's wrong with your voice?
It's trembling with fear?
I don't like it at all.
-Let me do it.
-Pick one.
-Short.
-Long.
Why did you let him do it?
I didn't.
I passed out.
The war has ended.
But you don't want to stop.
No, I don't.
You want to go risk your life?
Yes, I do.
Sacrifice myself for Thailand.
Or for someone.
Wow.
Dad.
To sacrifice,
we don't need to die for someone,
we can live for someone instead.
Wow.
Who do you want me to live for?
Dad.
Can't you think of anyone
that you should live for?
Why don't you understand anything?
You don't either.
In your life...
those who matter to you
have all died, haven't they?
Shut up!
Stop!
Go.
I don't want to hear you right now.
It's so hot.
Go.
Leave me alone with nature.
What are you doing?
Your face is all warm from anger.
Do this.
What is that?
It's to disperse some of the heat.
-Do it.
-No.
Come on, please.
Please, please. Once.
Why am I doing what you told me to?
I'm serious right now.
What for?
There are many elements in our lives.
When you're sad, find a friend.
Add something good.
Like what?
See?
The element of love.
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
I'm not smiling. This is my normal face.
Hello?
Hi, rocker.
Yeah. What's up?
I want to take you to the beach
for a couple of nights.
I want to take you to see the horizon.
Yeah? Is it a good idea?
What's good and what's bad?
I don't like beaches.
All right.
It's up to you.
How about hanging out in my room tonight?
I'll play guitar for you.
I don't want to get home late these days.
You can't get home late?
What the heck?
It's okay. That's it. Bye.
I am under pressure.
Boy asked me to go to the beach with him.
So?
You boyfriend asked you out.
What's wrong with that?
But I'm a girl.
We're not married yet.
And he hasn't met my family.
How sincere do you think he is?
Just the two of us? Staying overnight?
What do you think is on his mind?
Why are you mad at me?
I am mad.
In this day and age,
spending time alone with your guy
is absolutely normal.
So, I'm weird?
Sleeping with someone casually
is not weird?
Why? Virginity means nothing at all?
I didn't say that.
But people wouldn't expect
someone with your looks to think this way.
What does it have to do with looks?
People judge each other by their looks.
That's why they can't see
the real people inside.
You're pissing me off.
Blow it, don't spray it.
Does it look good, Buncha?
It's gonna get ugly
if you call me that again.
Sorry. Does it look good, Sabina?
Wow. It looks nice.
Do you think it would work?
Why not?
But I feel itchy on my breasts.
Look, it's very easy to pluck it.
Damn, Sabina.
I'm so sorry.
Stop it. I'll try this time.
To be a real man, we have to change a lot.
We might have to make some manly faces.
Is it okay now?
A bit more.
How about now?
To be honest,
your face looks like a male owl.
Damn you!
I'll slap you hard.
Or we should try to hang out with guys?
It might work out better.
You think so?
What?
He wants to show you the horizon?
It sounds a bit weird, doesn't it?
Not at all.
Guys like him sound like fun.
It was fun at first.
But as time passed... I don't know.
Don't take it too seriously.
Think of guys as toys.
Yeah. You slut.
-No need to give me a compliment.
-I'm not.
Ho, you don't need to worry about it
because you have some good news right now.
You got a two-year scholarship
to study in America, didn't you?
Hello?
I'm inside already.
Yeah. Come right in.
Nam Tarn. What the heck?
She's sad right now.
Why did you bring him here?
I asked him to come here
because I have something to tell you.
I'm getting married.
Please, come.
Isn't it too soon?
Not at all.
I'd like to cherish all my moments.
The biggest dream for a guy like me
is to marry the woman I love.
Let me take care of your heart, okay?
Oh, God.
Mang Gorn,
nobody says things like that these days.
Nam Tarn, I envy you so much.
I wish someone would
say something like that to me.
What are the sunglasses for?
I don't want you guys
to notice that I'm crying.
Wait. With the sunglasses,
we notice it even more.
-Really?
-Yeah.
She's a real crybaby just like you said.
Ho.
What?
No, I won't do it.
Come on.
Come on. One, two, three.
What are you guys laughing at?
You!
THE FACULTY CONGRATULATES MISS KANLAYA
HEWSAKUL FOR RECEIVING A GRANT
-Hi, Principal.
-Hello!
-Hi.
So, have you brought all the papers
and the letter from the medical exam?
I haven't had a medical exam.
Then, go get it done today.
Get your blood, heart, lungs,
and kidneys checked.
Inside and outside. Get them all checked.
Okay.
Is that all?
No. One more thing.
Before you can go,
you have to register and pay 30,000 baht.
Expensive, isn't it?
Did you also bring
your financial statements?
-Here.
-Yeah.
Let me see how much.
Thirty grand!
You'll have nothing left after you pay.
Yes.
You're so broke.
It's up to you.
If you want to pass it up,
you can tell me.
Let me think about it.
Go ahead, think about it.
I'll go now.
You're thinking about the money?
No.
Normally, I don't need much money.
I'm thinking about something else.
You're afraid that when you're gone,
your family won't survive, right?
I think they will.
They probably will
because I'm not an important person.
It won't affect them at all.
You should know an important person
is different from a necessary person.
What are you saying?
Sometimes we don't value someone
even though we need them.
And which one is better?
Actually, it should be the same person.
And if I'm a necessary person...
how come I'm not an important person?
Here we go.
-Why?
-Stop.
Why?
The field is ready. Bring the equipment
to the customers.
I'll tell them to get started.
-This uniform?
-Yes, sir.
Here's your gun.
Safety mask.
Look at me.
I don't need any safety equipment.
-Are you sure?
-You, give it back to him.
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls,
if the teams and players are ready,
please make your way to the firing zone.
Come on now, give it your all!
Push on through!
You can do it! Come on! Remember,
the most important thing
is not about winning or losing.
'Cause tomorrow will be a better day.
A brighter day.
Are you ready? I am ready!
Are you ready to rumble?
-What did he say?
-Dumbass!
You can't understand English,
you don't want safety equipment,
and then you laughed.
What's so damn funny?
SPORTS ARENA
SUPPORTED BY THAI INSURANCE
Can we play with you?
Hell no.
You should go jump rope.
Let them play.
I'm sorry.
Change serve.
Hit you again. I'm sorry.
Carry on.
I think you meant to do that.
You!
Given the situation,
I think they've got us.
Here's the plan.
I'll go out and distract them.
You guys retreat when you can.
Captain.
Do you realize
you're sacrificing yourself?
I have been living...
-for this.
-Captain.
All my brave soldiers,
today I'm very honored
to be fighting with all of you.
It will be written down in history.
Captain!
You fired away like New Year's fireworks.
I haven't even drawn my gun yet.
Damn it.
He's using a real gun!
-Help!
-Don't shoot!
GYNECOLOGY
-It's all done. Please wait a moment.
-Okay.
I'll bring you the results in two days.
Okay.
You can change your clothes now.
Here are your phones.
Are you using two phones?
Yeah. If you're smart,
you can save some money.
This one
has the Midnight Slider promotion,
free calls from 11:00 p.m. to 5:00 a.m.
And this one,
Free Day Hello-lo,
free calls from 5:00 a.m. to 11:00 p.m.
Hello?
It's the police.
Yeah.
What?
My dad shot someone?
Boy is calling.
Hello?
What? You were shot?
What the heck?
The same incident, for sure.
I'll be there right away.
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION
Are you really arresting me?
I'm a soldier, I defend this country.
And I'm a police officer.
I have to protect people.
If there are no soldiers,
how will people live?
In a condo, maybe?
-You're messing with me?
-You don't listen.
You don't want to mess with me.
Dad.
Boy.
Boy?
What? Boy?
Sounds familiar.
I see, Boy.
You looked Chinese when you were young.
Now, you look like a westerner.
Let's talk about you. Did your daughter
adopt you from somewhere?
People change over time.
-How so?
-When I was a young man,
I looked like Tom Cruise.
Is he your dad?
I can't recognize him.
See? We know each other.
Okay, I won't press charges against him.
No, no, no.
You shot him, even if it was just a graze.
He's the one who can decide.
Not the other way around.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Get inside, go.
-Sir, I'd like to file a report.
-What happened?
These two assaulted my son.
Nana!
What happened?
These two assaulted my son. See the blood?
Good. A soldier's seed
must stand up and fight.
Shit. You're a soldier,
but your son is a gay.
Shit. Right on my weak spot.
See?
I'm so embarrassed.
You can go home now.
I'll take care of this.
No. I came here to file a report.
My son was assaulted.
Yeah?
What now?
Sir, when can I go home?
You've lost your damn mind.
Sir, what do we have to do?
I'll let it go.
There. One problem solved.
No. It's a criminal charge.
The fine and the bail are
about 30,000 baht all together.
If you don't have the money,
then he'll be in jail. That's it.
Want me to help?
I can pay for it.
Are you mad?
POLICE TO SERVE PEOPLE
I wish I were. But I can't be.
Don't get angry at a crazy person, right?
Boy.
That crazy person is my dad.
I didn't say anything.
You don't need to say it.
If I had known he was your dad,
I wouldn't have come here.
You couldn't have known.
You never asked about my family.
-You're off topic.
-No.
It's about us.
It's about my gay brother.
It's about my crazy dad
who shot my boyfriend.
It's all about us.
Ho, I didn't mean to make you cry.
I'm sorry.
Tears can't win over everything, trust me.
I didn't want to cry.
The tears just come on their own.
Understand?
And I'm not trying to win over anything.
You know what?
On a dark starless night,
you're my shining light.
What?
It's wonderful.
I started off being shot by your dad
and ended up apologizing to you.
Never mind.
Let's go home.
I'm exhausted.
Let's go.
Cheer up.
Find some time and ask him out for dinner.
Talk to him and it'll get better.
For some women,
boyfriend problems are a very big deal.
You'll never understand.
Okay. Big deal.
How about this?
Take care of your smallest problem first.
Think about it.
What is your smallest problem?
Your brother, Nana.
You want him to be straight, right?
I agree with you.
If you can do it,
you'll solve two problems at once.
One, your brother becomes straight.
Two, you dad won't fight with him.
All good.
What should I do?
He'll fight with the guys
he hangs out with.
That's normal. Some guys who fight
become friends in the end.
Take him to see them.
They'll become close friends. Trust me.
Are you sure?
Better than doing nothing.
Yes.
And...
take your dad with them, too.
Your dad wants your brother
to be a macho man, right?
Maybe if you use one problem
to solve another, it might work.
Would my dad agree with me?
Go up and ask him now.
Go!
That hurt!
I should be the one to say that.
You stepped on my damn foot.
But I agree with you.
Told you he's the problem.
Parrot girl, you haven't stopped
running your mouth since you got here.
-I didn't know you were here.
-Still talking back!
-What did you say?
-Nothing. It was just a bird chirping.
Shut it!
Here comes this family again.
I'm sorry about the other day.
-I was wrong.
-Yes, you were.
Young man,
when a real man admits that he's wrong,
you should give him a second chance.
Yeah.
Friends are better than foes.
Today my son is going
to play sepak takraw.
-Anyone have a problem?
-Yes.
Today we're not playing sepak takraw.
We're practicing Thai boxing.
Anyone interested?
No way.
Today you'll meet the Beast from the East.
-Who is that?
-I'll tell you later.
Dad, won't he get hurt?
Yes.
Good. The more he gets hurt,
the tougher he'll be.
Don't give up.
Keep smiling.
Stop! Enough!
He's already down. This is outrageous.
This is nothing. I haven't gotten even
for what you did to me.
-Fight with me!
-No.
You have to fight
so you'll stop being mad at him.
Captain, aren't you going to stop them?
Mr. Son, a soldier's child,
even it's a girl,
will fight when the time comes.
Come on.
I'm ready.
Fight!
No! I don't fight with girls.
People would call me a bastard.
Don't worry. I challenged you.
Fight with me.
-Bastard! Bastard! Bastard!
I knew it.
It's all your fault.
Because of you, I got hurt.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't say you're sorry.
From now on, I'll stay being gay.
-I'll be gay. Got it?
-I don't.
Accept me the way I am or not,
I don't care.
I can't accept it.
Nana.
Dad.
Mom.
I wish you were here.
You would know what to do.
I have no idea what else to do.
Sis.
Will you switch places with me?
Come live my life.
Can I be the one who rests in peace?
I'm so tired.
Hello?
Okay.
SORRY!
Sorry?
Yes, sorry.
Why did you have to put it in a box?
I felt that on some occasions
"sorry" might be the best present.
Are you sure you want to do this?
I know it's risky, but I'll give it a try.
Like in Toon's song.
-I thought it was Big Ass' song.
-Yeah.
It's a joke.
I think what happened
wasn't your fault at all.
It was me that didn't come off well
with your dad.
-He's really at fault.
-But he's your dad, after all.
But I have a solution.
-What?
-We divide this world in two.
One has only two of us.
And I'll make it the happiest world.
I'll call this world...
Together
And the other one
I'll call the "Family" world.
There's only your family in it.
I won't get involved.
Do you think we can do it?
Can we?
Yes, we can.
Maybe.
I guess so.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Yeah.
This is my girlfriend, Ho.
Ho...
Look into my eyes. Look.
Look into my eyes!
Look into my eyes.
Do you know?
You are the one.
No more long-haired girls.
I would like to tell everyone.
I never feel like I'm wasting my time
when I'm with her.
I want to make her happy
with all my heart and soul.
I'll take her on a bike,
ride to see the horizon,
and hug her under the moonlight.
Please give us a big hand.
Clap your hands!
Yeah.
Clap your hands, everybody.
Come on, now.
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
I'm drunk, maybe. I cry when I'm drunk.
Why?
I don't know.
If you don't, then who knows.
You realize people are staring?
I do.
What do you want to do?
I don't know.
There should be a reason or something.
Explain to me why.
I don't know. Stop asking.
Why can't I ask you?
'Cause then I have to explain.
The more I say, the more I cry.
Even a short answer makes me cry,
a longer one would make it worse.
Ho, stop, please. I feel embarrassed.
Please.
Me, too.
How would we make our "together" world
happy if you always cry?
Remember, I told you I would do my best
to make it the happiest place.
But if one day I'm gone,
-please understand me.
-Yeah,
I do.
Now?
-I gotta pee.
-Right, okay.
Men always talk about themselves.
They care only about their happiness.
They only talk about what they want,
but never ask what I want.
It's not right! I'm pissed off.
There, there.
Did you console me or just hit my head?
Come on.
Did you cause any trouble?
I cry all the time.
I'm such a stupid, whiny person.
Who would tolerate me?
Would you?
So, why do you like to cry?
I don't like to.
But it comes from my feelings.
Then, fuck it.
You are who you are.
I can't fuck it.
You know that I want to have kids.
And if men can't tolerate me,
how can I have kids?
How could you say that?
Here. Here.
I shouldn't have said that.
Then, you shouldn't want to have kids.
-What?
-Come on.
I'm so different from you.
I don't want to have kids.
Why not?
That's my business.
But why do you really want to have kids?
I don't know.
I really can't answer that.
Yeah.
Why? Why do I want to have kids?
You know why? You answer it.
Answer me.
How would I know?
I think that's enough talking
about kids right now.
Let's talk about your boyfriend.
What is it he loves about you?
Or you've got nothing.
-Yes, I do.
-What?
I'm a cheap, pretty virgin.
Laughing at your own joke.
-Hello.
-Are you really getting married?
This is my dream.
During this wedding,
the bride and the bridesmaids
will surprise the groom.
Could the groom make his way to the stage?
You guys,
the reason I'm rushing into marriage
is that I'm pregnant.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I think it's great.
How?
I don't know how long he'll love me,
but now he has given me someone
who'll love me forever.
You're absolutely right!
Right?
Ho, are you all right?
Yes, I am. I'm touched.
What's next?
I believe my child will love me
the way my mom loves me.
This...
is the reason why I want to have kids.
Ho!
Your turn, go!
Thank you.
-Are you okay? Right?
-Okay.
Hungry.
WAI WAI
Let's eat together.
How about another cup?
Doctor.
Your friend's results are in.
280 DAYS FOR QUALITY PREGNANCY
Hey.
Is your baby kicking?
You crazy?
Only one month. No kicking yet.
It's probably just a clot of blood.
How do you prepare for it?
-You don't.
-No!
You have to.
If I were you, I would join a mom's club,
get some physical therapy for the baby.
When I have a big bump,
I would have a photo shoot in bikinis
and keep them for my kid to see.
Are you a movie star or something?
I really envy you.
You're the first one to get pregnant.
You make me more certain
that the only thing I want in life
is to have kids.
Because they would love me forever.
Yeah.
Hey, Doc.
Hello.
Talking about something serious?
No. Just talking about kids.
Listen carefully.
You might not be able to have kids.
You have an old uterus.
-What?
What? What the hell is that?
This is the first time I've seen it
in my life.
Everyone at the hospital is stunned.
Your lab results show
that you have a congenitally old uterus.
How come it's old?
It's like second-hand stuff.
It's aged.
It's like it was old since you were born.
The terms you're using, old or aged,
sound quite weird.
Is there such a thing?
It's a new disease.
How would it affect me?
It's like it's about to expire.
What?
A uterus has an expiration date?
And then?
Right now we're checking it out in detail.
It should last for a year or two.
But if we can't find a way to treat it,
we might have to dissect it.
Or it could become malignant.
That means you won't be able to have kids.
Wait...
There's a solution.
What is it?
Just use it before it expires.
You can get pregnant
and have a kid right away.
When the time comes,
it should be okay to dissect it.
And you get your kid.
How do I do it?
Do what makes people get pregnant.
Who would I do it with?
Boy, your boyfriend.
I think you'll have to propose to the guy.
No marriage. You have to hurry.
Just "do it" and talk later.
-"Do it"?
-Yes. Just do it.
But she said she wouldn't sleep
with anyone before getting married.
Ho, don't tell me you're still a virgin.
Shit.
I think it's time to take care
of the unimportant person.
Is there a way to treat her?
I don't know yet.
Shit. Dad.
Don't you want to do something?
Do what?
I don't know.
I've never been a father.
I don't know what to do.
You think I'm a good father?
But you're a soldier.
What does that have to do with it?
I don't know.
Help me think. Think like a soldier.
What?
Nana? What are you doing here?
-What? Dad?
-Hit my nose and mouth.
What are you guys doing here?
We...
Here.
I came to record a clip for Nana.
Action!
-Hello.
Meet me, Nana, again today.
I'll teach you how to...
-do free kicks.
-Smile.
Smile.
Thank you.
Dad.
Do you not hate gays anymore?
Ho.
Are you free tomorrow?
CHUMNAN CLINIC
Dad. How are they gonna treat me?
-With Botox.
-What?
Botox injection.
Botox is great.
Dad. Botox is used to tighten the face.
If it can tighten a face,
then it can tighten a uterus.
-I'm leaving.
-Don't piss me off.
Dad.
Stay, please, my dear child.
What? What did you call me?
My dear child.
That's so wrong.
I love you so much.
Dad. Tell me the truth. Is it hard to say?
A little.
You can talk to me the way you did before.
Your dear child is there.
Why don't you try? I'd love to try it.
-What, Dad?
-What do you need Botox for?
If it's dangerous, I'll take it...
for my beloved sister.
Beloved?
Yes.
If it's dangerous,
I'll sacrifice myself for you.
Sacrifice?
Then I'll take it, too.
I'll let you guess where I got Botox.
It's so obvious.
Does it hurt?
No.
But I'm sleepy.
Like I have strained my eyes.
I want to get some sleep.
You can sleep right here.
Dad hasn't come out yet.
Nana.
-Dad's here.
-Shit. What the fuck is that?
Are you guys mesmerized?
Do I disgust you or something?
I've had my mouth open for so long.
I'm so thirsty.
Hey.
What about the other one?
Where do you want it?
Dad. That's enough. It's not helping.
I said it is.
It's an innovation.
Trust me, it's good.
How could it be?
Your mouth can't hold water now.
Inject it into her uterus to tighten it.
Uterus?
That's impossible.
Botox is only for external use.
That is internal.
Doctor,
you said it can be done anywhere.
Now, what?
You're going back on your word?
-Dad, let's go.
-No.
What would you say?
One sec.
I am ready.
Are you ready?
Let's get ready to rumble!
I'll try.
EXAMINATION ROOM 1
Most people have a Chi problem.
-Right.
-If it doesn't flow,
then it causes us problems.
-I invented some herbal medicine.
-What is it?
It can really help with Chi.
It's very potent.
But I have never tried with a person.
It could be too strong.
I'll try it.
Nothing happened.
Dad.
Blood.
Okay now?
No.
It's just blood.
What about the flow, Doctor?
What the fuck just happened to me?
I don't think it's good.
You don't think so?
Do you have the antidote?
What are you looking at?
You don't look sad, why?
I am sad.
But what do you expect?
Crying?
I'm tired of crying.
Or it's because your dad and your brother
have come together.
Maybe.
But you still can't have a kid.
Or things between you and your beau
are better?
No.
He just says nothing.
So what will you do?
Are you gonna reconcile with him?
Maybe.
If he doesn't just take off.
I don't think he would.
I want to ask you out...
for fireflies.
I'm leaving now.
Actually, I didn't know if you would come,
but I've reserved a room.
Maybe during this trip
someone is going to propose, right?
Don't worry about it, Ho.
If you don't want to, it's all right.
Let's be frank.
At first, I thought...
the fact that I'm a crybaby
would have driven you away.
Why did you come back?
I miss you.
So, let's be frank.
Sure, I'd love that.
Since we are in a relationship,
do you think sex is important?
Of course.
That's why I want to save it for later.
That's not it.
I mean...
should we try it?
It depends on if we're married.
When we return, let's find the auspicious
time for a wedding, then.
You said we came to see fireflies...
I don't see any.
For those,
we have to go see in our room.
Am I going to have sex with him?
But he's going to find the auspicious time
for a wedding.
Are you sure?
It's just finding the time,
not the actual wedding.
Come on. So it won't be a waste of time.
Shouldn't I be worried
about wasting my virginity?
Try it, you might like it.
Have sex with him now
or after the wedding, it's all the same.
I'm talking to myself!
It's the end of the bed.
Boy.
It's ticklish there. Ticklish.
Oh, no. Don't.
Don't take it off.
Do you have to take my pants off?
They have to come off to have sex.
You can put them back on later.
I understand.
But you think it's a good idea?
When we do something for the one we love,
trust me, it'll turn out well.
Not toward the left, no.
Not to the left.
If not to the left,
it won't get to the middle.
Really?
I'm sorry.
You're not ready for this, are you?
Maybe not.
So why did you come with me?
At first I thought I'd try.
-And?
-And...
Wait a sec.
We can't try something like this.
I understand.
Boy,
I'm sorry.
I know that you took me here
because you wanted to help me.
But I screwed it all up.
Did I also screw up your life?
Don't worry about it.
It's not all your fault.
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger.
Are you all right, though?
I have to live with it.
Boy.
I'm so sorry.
You can scold me any way you want.
No, I can't.
Never.
What if you could, what would it be?
Cockteaser!
Why are you fucking dating me?
I don't care that people think I'm a fool,
I still want a girl whose body and heart
want the same thing.
You're giving me
neither your heart nor your body,
you helmet-top!
Are you just faking it or something?
Shit, want to save it for later.
If I had a new girlfriend,
she would be up for it,
a real looker who likes to have
fun and stay up all night.
Let me ask you this.
Why are you fucking wasting my time?
Go stay with the one that you love,
you mushroom-head!
If I could say something,
it would be that,
but I wasn't scolding you.
I mean, if I could.
EMERGENCY
What's wrong? You look so sad.
What are you doing here?
Same problem.
We want to talk about how to help Ho.
Someone helped her already, right?
She just called and told us
that it didn't work out.
She ruined the plan.
Really?
If he's not the one,
why bother seeing him?
Jump right in it.
Has it ever happened to you?
You're with someone
and you know that he's not the one,
but you still try your best.
-Can't let go.
-Sounds complicated.
Never mind. If it's so complicated,
then let it go.
-Emotional.
-Let what go?
Your boyfriend...
-or your desire to have kids?
-Right on.
If they're both problems,
then let both of them go.
Seriously.
Actually,
what he said about you is spot-on.
If you love someone, then go tell him.
-An instigator.
-Helmet-top...
That hurts.
Why are you smiling?
Or do you like Ho?
No.
Would he like me?
I don't know. You've got to find out.
Would he like a whiny woman like me?
Probably not, just give up.
"No" means you like her, right?
-No.
-Right?
No!
Dad.
What do we do to say that we love someone.
What did you say to Mom?
That day, I decided to stare at your mom,
and I said...
"Hey, my love is on your face."
It sounds difficult. Right, Dad?
-Somebody likes it. Yeah.
-What did Mom say?
Your mom jumped right up.
But if I say that,
I would sound like an unreasonable person.
If you don't have a reason, then don't.
It's what you do.
Doctor,
the research center sent out
your friend's results again.
They said they found out something new.
What did they find?
The abnormality
is increasing exponentially.
The uterus might expire
faster than we expected.
She would have an acute stomachache.
Ho!
I have something to tell you.
Wait.
Me first.
I think...
I like you.
When I see your face,
my heart starts whining.
It probably wants you to console me.
It probably wants your attention.
I think...
I see my love on your face.
I think I have been in love with you,
but I had a boyfriend.
But I broke up with him already.
And if you need more reasons...
What's happening?
What are you feeling?
Positive or negative?
Positive.
So, why are you crying?
I don't know. It's coming from inside.
I've just learned that kisses are yummy.
They are sweet.
Did you add some syrup?
-Stomachache?
-Yeah.
Just now?
Yes.
Looks like we're too late.
Given your symptoms,
I'll have to dissect the uterus.
That means...
you won't be able to have kids.
Tell me.
What?
Tell me why you don't want kids.
Are you sure?
It's pretty cheesy.
I want to hear it. Say it.
You might not like it.
It's okay. Tell me.
I believe...
I can love only one person.
See? That's it.
Tell me more.
Come on.
If I find the one I love,
I can love just one at a time.
If I have a kid one day,
if I have to love two people
at the same time,
I don't think I know how.
Are you crazy?
It's cheesy, huh?
I like it.
You're so sweet.
If men really think
like what you've just said,
some women might not want to have kids.
And some women are around here?
I don't know.
You can love only one person, right?
Yes.
Do as you said!
How is she?
Don't tell me...
Tell me now.
Sis!
She's dead!
Damn it, Doc!
You killed my daughter.
You know what,
my daughter...
is very important to our family.
Without her, how would my family survive?
Sis.
You have to come back.
Come back, sis!
I know that you really want to have kids.
If you want a kid...
I'll be your kid.
If you want a son...
I'll be your son.
If you want a daughter,
I'm good at that!
Ho.
Come back, dear.
I'm sorry.
I love you, kiddo.
I really love you.
Enough, probably.
What the hell?
She's not dead?
I'm not dead.
Doc said if I wanted to know
how much you love me,
I should do this.
I told you I loved you
at the Botox clinic.
That felt so prepared,
but this looks very real.
I love you, Dad.
Me, too.
I love you, too.
Too much hugging.
Wait. Don't cry yet.
Let's do your operation.
-Good luck, sis.
-You can do it.
ONE YEAR LATER
Ho, if one day you're not pretty
or a virgin,
would I want to be with you?
Don't worry about that.
Even if I'm not pretty and not a virgin,
I know what to do.
And what if I'm still whining
and crying all the time?
I have a very easy way to console you?
-How?
-Give you hugs and kisses.
What? Are you crazy?
That's no way to console someone.
Do you want to try to cry?
I'm saying goodbye.
Dad, are you really going to war?
I volunteered to be a soldier.
Dad--
Don't stop me.
Let me redeem myself.
Why? Why do you want to do this?
Everyone wants to be somebody.
If so, you can't say goodbye to just me.
Ho!
You had your dress enlarged
for your brother?
Nana!
What did you just call me?
Nana.
Whether you're Nana or Nava,
I still love you.
-Dad--
-Stop!
Remember this.
I'll give you a lesson.
If you're a girl,
you have to save it for later.
It might be too late.
Dad. Don't give up.
Sis...
you know...
you're my idol.
Are you okay?
Okay.
My life is drifting.
Yeah, I've been wanting to ask you.
Why did you call Ho "mushroom-head."
I don't know.
What if you needed to call me names,
what would they be?
-No.
-Come on. I won't be mad.
You're a fake! Acting like
you're sweet and innocent.
Got knocked up before marriage,
you whore!
If I were to call you names,
that would be it.
You're a very cool guy.
Where did you get all that from?
Probably from my feelings.
I love it.
You love something like this? Really?
So...
Would you mind
if your friend's ex-boyfriend wanted to...
ask you out?
You mind?
I feel very honored.
Today I'm here to teach you
how to do the robot dance.
If you're ready,
let's get started.
The robot dance is all about
using each part of your body individually.
Look at this. Roll your neck.
See? Now, reverse. It made a noise.
And your hands. Look at this.
It's longer. Clap your hands.
How is the robot dance?
Some people might say it is fucking hard.
To be honest, it is hard, but not fucking.
We are in the hornet's nest right now.
If we attack, we're sure to lose.
Let's do this.
I, Burapha,
will carry the bomb into their camp.
Please give this bag of letters
to my daughter.
This is the remote.
When I say "I love Thailand,"
then you press it.
Captain.
Can you let us praise you?
Off you go. My tongue hurts now.
I love Thailand!
Fuck!
I gave them the wrong one.
THANK YOU
HO