Come on. Hurry up.
Come on.
We all know that
we need eight to ten hours of sleep,
but what we really don't know is
how long a person can go without sleep.
Insomnia is a physical disorder
that is deeply rooted
in a person's mental health.
The mind can be highly affected
by stress and anxieties
which then in turn may prevent us
from falling asleep.
But in most recorded cases,
it doesn't last for more than a few days.
Now that's for the majority.
There are exception with serious cases
of clinical insomnia.
Extreme insomniacs can lose sleep
that lasts for months or even years.
This is triggered
by something more complicated
than just your average stress,
trauma, strain of a heavy ordeal
or anything tragic one may suffer from.
So what happens to you if you stay awake
for months or perhaps even years?
Can you imagine the side effects
it will bring?
Just one or two sleepless nights
are enough to throw your mental capacity
into complete disarray.
That's how easily it happens.
You may call it
a state of emotional deviation.
You increase that and go
more than three nights without sleep,
then you're looking at acute confusion.
Not just that, it also causes
an onset of derangement and delirium.
So now this becomes a problem.
Your immediate perception of reality
is distorted.
And if the condition persists
longer than that,
the symptoms intensify
into auditory and visual hallucinations.
You won't be able to separate imagination
from what's real.
When I was in med school like you,
oftentimes, I would go
on consecutive nights without sleep
while working on projects.
I remember once,
a lab rabbit started talking.
Spoke to me, just wouldn't stop prattling.
Good rabbit kept me company.
All night long.
Made me happy.
Three nights is the longest
I've gone without sleep.
I remember I was in the ninth grade
back then
when June and I moved to live
with our grandmother.
Ever since moving there,
I've been obsessively concerned
with the security of the house.
Every night,
I compulsively check all of the locks.
I know I've already locked all the doors,
but I can't stop myself from rechecking.
It gives me peace of mind.
Lately, June has started coming home late.
I'm worried about her.
I have to call her a dozen times
before she answers.
Please try again later.
I can't sleep.
In the past few weeks,
I'd consciously stay awake,
studying past midnight until two a.m.
Then at three a.m., I have to go
to the market to buy ingredients.
But I look at the bright side.
Twenty-four hours used.
I don't waste a second.
NOTICE OF LATE HOME LOAN PAYMENT
AMOUNT DUE 782,155 BAHT
June.
So you're finally home, huh.
I'm gonna get changed
and go back to school.
Well, hurry up
and come down for breakfast.
June, you hear me?
So you're thinking of
dropping out of med school?
I know you have financial problems
at home, Jane.
But that doesn't mean it's over.
We can always try and find a way.
There's a lab assistant job
that's available.
Would you like to give it a shot?
I've already asked.
It's a complete waste of time.
Not even worth what they're going to pay.
Well, it would be a waste, too,
if you suddenly abandon everything.
Hmm.
What about June?
Maybe she could help out after school.
Think about it. You know what they say.
Two heads are always better than one.
Oh, I have an idea.
Jane?
Jane.
Yes?
Sorry. I just remembered that
a German pharmaceutical company
has been in touch.
They need volunteers
for a new drug research.
I hear they pay good money
for anyone willing to join.
I figured that
judging from your interview on insomnia,
you should easily qualify
for that research.
How soon do you think I can start?
Qratonin is a substance
that comes from a part of the brain
called the thalamus.
Qratonin can be used to treat
brain-dead patients,
and the substance only releases
when we're awake.
So we started the experiment called Deep.
The Deep process consists of three levels.
The higher the level,
the more concentrated Qratonin becomes.
And the duration of each level
may vary from person to person.
This experiment must only be conducted
by Weimar personnel.
Hello.
My name is Hans Miller.
And I am the Director of Research
of this facility.
Firstly, I would like to say
thank you so much for coming today.
-Uh, what is your name?
-It's Jane.
Jane, have you heard of Alexander Fleming?
Is he the one who discovered penicillin?
Correct.
When Alexander Fleming
discovered penicillin,
he revolutionized
the pharmaceutical business.
Now, Qratonin will do exactly the same.
One question.
Why does this Qratonin only release
when we're awake?
Now, have you heard
of the substance melatonin?
Ah, yes. Isn't that the substance
that helps with our sleep?
Excellent.
Melatonin helps us sleep.
And Qratonin will do the absolute opposite
and keep us awake.
Last question.
How much money will I get?
For Level 1,
you will get
100,000 baht.
Okay.
By participating in the Deep process,
you will need a microchip implant
in your occipital area.
This microchip will only extract
Qratonin from the brain.
Now, as long as
you have the microchip in your neck,
you must wear this watch.
It will measure your heartbeat
and the amount of Qratonin
that we have harvested in percentage.
When it reaches 100 percent,
you must come back here immediately.
And then we can remove the microchip
from your neck.
I have to remind you,
that you have signed an agreement.
This experiment is secret,
and we don't want you talking to anybody.
Because we do not want our rivals
to hear what we're doing.
Okay.
All right, that's all set.
The Level 1 process has started.
Oh, there is one thing
you should know first.
You must not fall asleep, ever.
If you fall asleep
for more than 60 seconds,
the microchip may short-circuit,
and it may stop your heart.
Don't worry if you fall asleep.
This watch will warn you
before reaching 60 seconds.
I guarantee you, it's safe.
Grandma!
I'm all right.
I just dropped my dentures.
Gran, next time if you need help, tell me.
Can you sit still?
You shouldn't strain yourself so much.
Ah. All right, enough.
See? You know, you're way too active
for someone your age.
How come you never listen to me?
I need to move every now and then.
Or else my joints
would get all tired and stiff.
Oh, Jane. Have you seen the notice yet?
We're a few months behind the mortgage.
Grandma, it's all right.
I'll take care of it. Okay?
I don't want you losing sleep over it.
Don't tire yourself.
You've worked so hard.
Just relax.
Huh?
What did you say just now?
Come on. I'm not falling for it.
And who was that?
June.
What?
Who just drove you here?
I booked online.
Then why were you sitting in the front?
If I didn't,
then regular cabs would have harrassed us.
And also why didn't you text me back?
Hey, you better answer me.
What the hell, Jane.
I ran out of data. So chill, okay?
-Then why won't you answer my calls?
-Well, you know I had band practice.
Really? You had practice all night?
I see.
So you think I'm sleeping around?
What else should I think?
Okay.
Then that's what I'll do.
Hey, give me an abortion if ever.
Since you're a doctor.
Hey!
So you're on Deep, aren't you?
Deep? What is it?
That's Win,
our top-class party animal.
He actually spends more time in nightclubs
than he does in the classroom.
I'm on it, too.
I don't think
you're supposed to tell anyone that.
It's just between us.
How did you get in?
Was it Professor Nichcha?
Mm-hmm.
I guess
I just met all of their qualifications.
I guess you're good at staying awake, too.
But you know there are others…
who are professional insomniacs.
Just like you and me.
Check it out.
That's Cin,
the famous beauty blogger
and the local school's celebrity.
And whatever she does,
her thousands of followers
go crazy about it.
Let me show you this Korean essence water.
It is super awesome.
Can't recommend it enough.
Chip, chip, chip, chip. Ooh.
Brilliant in high school.
Her family forced her to study Medicine.
But what she really wanted
was to study Communications.
School stresses her out so much.
She barely sleeps.
Has to rely on sleeping pills.
What's with you, Win?
Shouting my name around like a maniac.
Oh, so Jane is on Deep, too?
And you know what else?
Wherever you find Cin,
you're always gonna find this guy.
Hey, Peach!
Peach, the gaming nerd.
When he's not studying, he's living
inside one of his online games.
Games, games, and more games.
Has a thousand friends
in the virtual world.
In the real world, however,
it's the complete opposite of that.
Hi there.
You too, Peach?
So when was it you signed up?
Yesterday.
That's like the same day I did.
Not fair. How come you're still looking
so dang radiant?
Look at my panda eyes.
I would have never done it
if it weren't for the 100 grand.
So everyone gets the same deal.
Of course. It's easy money, you know.
I mean,
I can keep doing it forever.
Well, that's no surprise.
You're a movie marathon monster after all.
And you, Peach?
How you holding up?
-Good.
-And you, Cin?
It's easy-peasy, Win.
That 100,000 baht is definitely
keeping my eyes wide open.
Keep your voice down, Cin.
Sorry.
Aren't any of you afraid of this thing?
We sleep,
and we're dead.
I'm not.
We stay up,
and we stay alive.
Hell yeah. Right on.
Look, check it. Mine's almost full.
How about you? Let me see yours.
And you, Cin?
Whoa, 77 percent. Way ahead of us.
Come on, Peach. You're lagging.
Oh. I don't have any of you on my LINE.
What do you say?
Let's add each other online.
We can watch each other's backs.
Mm. Oh.
Instagram accounts, too.
Follow and like me on that.
Hey, guys, what is going on?
It's kinda still a bit too early
to hit the sack.
So why don't we all play
a fun little game tonight.
Look.
I love you.
So help me name this show
and if your entry has the most likes,
you'll get this cutie doll.
ALL-NIGHTER LIVESTREAM WITH CUTIE CIN
WHY USE FINN MOBILE?
OUTSTANDING DEBT 658,901 BAHT
-Whoo!
-Whatever. Not impressed.
-You know what, I think I should turn pro.
-Yuck.
Hey, you guys.
I feel like I have a stalker.
Since I've been on Deep,
someone has been stalking me for sure.
Just the other day,
I heard a strange sound.
I looked around and checked,
but there was no one around.
It's probably a serial killer.
Not funny, I'm being dead serious here.
Not being crazy.
If the Deep lab asks you
to do another round,
would you still do it?
Whoo!
And why not? Easy money, right?
-We got through Level 1 in one piece.
-Right.
They'll pay even more for Level 2.
You do know we'd have to stay awake
for a whole lot longer.
But if we stay awake…
we stay alive, right?
Yeah, I'm all in.
With the money,
I can get a boob job in South Korea.
Gonna get them all nice and gigantic.
Big, huge boobs.
Oh, that's right.
Let's start a group chat.
And if they get in touch,
then we can just go together.
-All right?
-Sounds good.
Pick a group name.
The "Deep Process Group Research"
kind of sounds appropriate.
Sounds kinda like a term paper,
doesn't it?
How about this?
We are the Great Sleepless Gang
and mind you,
the gang that shocked the world
for being paid an enormous amount
by just staying awake.
-Good, right? Right?
-You're an idiot.
What a buzzkill. So then what?
Uh…
-How about "Non Non"?
-What? "Non Non"?
"Non Non"?
-What's that supposed to mean?
-Right.
-Well, the N-O-N.
-What's Non mean?
-Non is French for no.
-Uh-huh.
The Thai word for sleep is "non".
Put together, it means "no sleep."
"Non Non." No sleep.
-Oh.
-Oh. Non Non.
Oh, that's wicked and cool.
We're going with that.
It's a cool name. Non Non.
-Are you sure about it?
-I'm already doing it.
Too late, it's done.
-Non Non.
-You're in?
-I am. Joining up. Non Non.
-Right.
Ladies and gents,
that's it. We are Non Non.
Get ready.
Watch us conquer the Deep levels.
Uh-huh.
We won't be going to bed,
-we'll be getting rich instead!
-Whoo!
-Cheers, everyone.
-Mm. Mm.
-Ah.
Awesome. Come on, guys, it's bowling time.
-Mm.
-Cin, Peach, it's the two of you.
-You're on the same team.
-Sorry, I'm gonna have to go.
-What's the rush, Jane?
-Yeah.
-There's plenty of time left.
-Need to go home to do something.
I guess I'll see you.
See you then.
Goodbye.
Guess I'll see you later.
Bye-bye.
Cin!
-Huh?
-Peach needs a cab, too.
-Would do better if you let him tag along.
-Come on then.
Go on.
I'll see you, okay?
Bye-bye.
Come on.
Go.
Hurry.
Hey, dude, what's wrong with you?
I don't have COVID-19. I swear.
I think…
I think it's a side effect
of the Deep implant.
I think I might have…
butterflies in my stomach.
Which title?
ALL-NIGHTER LIVESTREAM WITH CUTIE CIN
CINDERELLA AFTER MIDNIGHT
Pick.
Huh?
This title.
The All-Nighter Buddy,
A Livestream Marathon with the…
…one and only Cutie Cin.
Hmm. Okay.
But you know I guess that
whoever came up
with such a weird name like that
could either be a… a huge idiot
or a really crazy psycho lunatic.
Makes sense?
Uh…
I…
You… you really have to watch out.
Lots of psy… psychos running around.
It makes me worry a lot about you. A lot.
You worry about me?
Hey. You have a crush on me.
-I don't, I don't, I don't.
-What then?
I… what I mean is
we… we're friends
and so we have to watch out for each…
other.
Peach!
Don't forget to subscribe to my channel.
Bye. Bye. Blehh.
For you to know that I like you ♪
Here.
What is this?
Well, I did break your old one.
And what about the sim card?
You always ran out of data.
So I got you unlimited.
The best data plan.
Now you no longer have an excuse
for not replying to me.
But where did you get the money for this?
From a part-time job.
A job doing?
It seems a bit early for you.
Hello, Mom, what's up?
Cin,
you didn't answer your dad's calls.
Because he just kept calling me
all day long.
Well, he's really upset
after seeing your grades.
But, Ma, it's not like
I'm not doing the best that I can.
You know I never even wanted
to study Medicine.
Well then, you're just going to have
to try a little harder.
Your dad's family are all doctors.
So just do it for him.
-You know--
-It's not exactly genetic, is it?
Studying Communications
won't kill his good genes.
That's just great.
So no allowance for you this month then.
You're on your own, Cin.
Oh, well, that's fine then.
'Cause I can support myself. No problem.
Level 2 will take longer than Level 1.
So that we will get more
concentrated Qratonin.
How many days will it take?
Each person is different.
But based on your past performance,
I would guess…
about five days.
Hey. Five days. Can we do that?
Go ahead and tell him if you can't.
How much?
Five hundred thousand baht.
DEBT 165,784 BAHT
Win!
Oh, yeah.
Let's go.
Win!
Do a backdoor cut.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Let's go.
Win.
Do it!
What's wrong, Win?
Are you all right, buddy?
Just take the kids.
Sucker got schooled.
No wonder his mom killed herself.
Oh, oh.
-Let go.
-Oh. Hey.
-Come on.
-Stop it.
You all hear what he just said.
What the heck's going on?
Take it easy, man.
Have you gone nuts?
He didn't even say anything.
You all right, Win?
What's gotten into you?
Looks like he's gone mad.
Are you trying to drill a hole
into the lock?
June.
How about you clean it
the next time you use it?
It's gross.
Stop!
What? I'm trying to practice at home.
You told me that, didn't you?
Well, you had all day to practice that.
And you had all day to study.
Don't make me kick you out.
Hey.
What's with this mood swing,
all of a sudden?
Honestly, what you've been up to?
You're obsessively fussing
over the locks and the stove.
You've been checking on Gran
like a thousand times.
And if you couldn't tell,
it's getting worse.
Come on. Tell me.
What is it you do really?
I'm tutoring.
You really gonna expect me
to believe that?
Tutoring won't never bring in that much,
even if you did it 24 hours a day.
What I do is none of your damn business.
Like that, you're always getting grumpy
and yelling at me.
-I deserve to know what's going on.
-What the hell do you know?
I go to work,
so I can pay the goddamn bills.
Do you have any idea, any idea at all
how much sleep I've lost over this?
Quit changing the subject.
-I'm asking what you've been up to?
-Just leave me alone.
-Go check it. Make sure that it's correct.
-Okay.
Jane, come over here
and help me clean this up.
Are you okay, Jane?
I've had enough of this!
-The percentage is totally stuck up low.
-Shh.
And apart from us,
there are other people in on this.
-I've seen many other people on Deep.
-Huh?
How did you know that?
Their wristwatches.
But we're the only ones
who are on Level 2 now.
What a complete and total rip-off.
We look like zombies.
Ah, shit.
Last time I check,
the number kept going up.
Is thing broken or something?
Come on. Wake up, buddy.
Hey, Win, do you work out regularly?
Mm. Yeah, why?
We started Level 2 all at the same time,
right?
Our readings shouldn't have been
that much different.
And it should have all dropped
at the same rate.
But yours is clearly higher than ours.
I think it's got something to do
with our bodies.
Or more specifically,
how our body movements can affect it.
Keep moving and the number goes up.
I have an idea. I know what we can do.
Come on, not now.
My connection sucks.
So why don't you make the switch
to Finn Mobile?
Top Internet service. You can all use
my code to avail a discount.
And both you and I will be able to get
really big savings all the way.
I need you to go home and stay with Gran.
I'm not coming home tonight.
Huh? Say what?
I said you need to go home tonight
and be the one to take care of Grandma.
Uh, oh. Oh, all right. Yeah, I will.
Hey, no sleeping.
Can you believe that weirdo?
I had no idea he was rich.
Say cheese.
-Mm.
-Wake up.
And I never knew that
he was such a dope, too.
And look at you right now.
You're kinda crazy.
I've just been so stressed out lately.
So what do… what do you usually do?
Well, I study.
Oh, you study.
And then what?
And then I study.
Mm, So that's why
you're always top of the class.
But when you're not studying,
what do you do?
I also help out at home.
You help out with what exactly?
Well,
cooking, setting the tables,
selling the food.
Mm.
What about your parents?
Breaking news report.
-We've just received report of the murder.
-Jane?
The incident occurred
in a townhouse in Bangna District.
Authorities who went inside to investigate
-discovering the bodies of the husband…
-Jane?
Jane.
…there were no signs of forced entry.
Jane?
What about you?
What do you do when you're not drinking?
Mm, drink some more.
Then drink.
And drink.
And drink again.
And your parents don't have a problem
with that?
My parents?
Well, my mom is dead.
Hey. It's all right.
It was a long time ago.
I'm okay.
Hey, Jane, don't worry about us tonight.
You won't be falling asleep.
I've got a plan.
Oh, look at that. He's awake now.
You awake, you awake, you awake.
-Yeah.
-Great.
-Oh. One more?
-Yeah.
-You sure?
-I'm sure.
Okay. Just for now.
So Win comes up with a plan
to help us sail through the fourth night
without falling asleep.
He gets stimulant pills
and starts mixing them
into these sweet-looking mocktails.
Where did you get these?
It's courtesy of our Faculty of Pharmacy.
You know that Crenyl has known
to cause strokes, right?
Are we gonna die tonight?
Ooh.
Have you actually gone crazy?
Jane.
We need to make it through the night.
If we fall asleep,
then we're all dead.
There's nothing else that can help keep
our eyes wide open.
Fine. I'll just throw them away.
Jane.
What are you doing sitting here alone?
Don't you wanna go for a dance?
What? You can't dance.
Oh, it's all right, darling.
I'll teach you. Come on, get up.
Get up.
I don't really remember anything
other than that.
I had a really, really great time.
Hi, everyone, how you doing?
Today, I'm going to give you a peek in
to what my everyday life looks like.
Let's go.
Hi, everyone.
Today, I'm going to give you a peek in
to what my everyday life looks like.
Hi, everyone.
Today, I'm going to give you a peek in
to what my everyday life looks like.
Hi, everyone.
Today, I'm going to give you a peek in
to what my everyday life looks like.
Hi, everyone.
Today, I'm going to give you a peek in
to what my everyday life looks like.
Hi, everyone.
Today, I'm going to give you a peek in
to what my everyday life looks like.
Hi, everyone.
Today, I'm going to give you a peek in
to what my everyday life looks like.
Hi, everyone.
Today, I'm going to give you a peek in
to what my everyday life looks like.
Hi, everyone. Hi, everyone. Hi, everyone.
Hi, everyone. Hi, everyone.
Hi, everyone.
I love you. I love you. I love you.
You have to watch out.
Lots of psychos running around.
Cin.
Cin. Cin.
-Cin!
-Hey, Peach.
what the fuck is this?
Well, answer me!
-I can't feel her pulse, guys.
-Oh, shit.
Cin.
Cin, just wake up.
Is Cin gonna die?
Will she be okay?
-She has to be okay.
-It's because of you!
Not the time, guys. Win!
-Win.
-Let me try.
Cin, please wake up.
Cin.
Please don't die.
Please don't die. Can you hear me, Cin?
-Don't die. Please.
-Peach.
How many seconds?
-Peach, how much time?
-Peach!
-Twenty seconds.
-Cin, please wake up.
Cin.
-Cin, please. Please.
-Cin.
How much time left?
There's only…
ten seconds.
Win, move.
We will not do it anymore.
Why?
Nobody's done it better than you guys.
Don't you see how bad it is?
I almost died.
But Deep Level 3
will bring you one million baht…
each.
Sorry.
After Cin's near-death experience,
we all decided
not to go back on Deep again.
I'm going, Grandma.
Cin.
Cin!
I…
I did what I did…
because I like you.
Cin.
I'm…
I… I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
Can you please stop following me
before I'll call security on you.
I…
I can explain everything.
I just…
boosted your likes
watched your clips again and again.
I did it to support you.
I only meant to help.
So that's why you went psycho?
I didn't mean…
Can we still be friends, please?
I don't think so.
Your scores
have dropped drastically, Jane.
I was under the impression
this was your favorite subject.
I just haven't had time to study lately.
Don't tell me
it's because of that research job
which I recommended to you earlier.
Yeah.
Come on, Jane,
if that's what's preventing you
from being able to study
and costing you your grade,
then why don't you quit?
I'm very concerned about your performance.
Actually, it's a lot more complicated.
But never mind that.
It doesn't matter because I already quit.
Med schools may demand a whole lot
from their students.
That a lot of people would die
to get the opportunity you've been given.
You're still young.
You can make money later on.
Jane.
I can't believe
I slept like a rock last night.
How did you wake up before a class?
I barely made it myself.
What are you up to later?
I have two tickets
for the Ed Sheeran concert.
You wanna come with me?
I don't think I can.
Come on, it'll only be a couple of hours.
I promise you.
Why don't you go and ask Peach and Cin?
No way. Those two have a lot to sort out.
You're trying to hit on me?
Mm-hmm.
Well, I don't think of you that way, Win.
So don't waste your time on me.
I study and take care of June and Grandma.
That's all.
I don't have time for anything else.
I'm sorry.
Make way please.
-Clear the way.
-Let us through. Let us through.
Move aside, please.
-Out of the way, people.
-Clear the way, please.
-Clear the way.
-Move aside.
-Make way, people. Come on.
-Move aside, please.
-Steady.
-Clear out. Please let us work.
Gran?
Gran!
Jane.
Where's Gran? How was she?
She suffered a stroke
so we need to move her
to a different hospital.
Why is that?
We can't afford it here, June.
I'll go and talk to the doctor
about the transfer.
I… Is this gonna cover it?
Where did you get this?
Turn around, June.
Yeah, so what?
How did you know about it?
You should have told me before you did it.
It's very dangerous.
Well, you did it too, right?
Which is why you shouldn't have.
People died in that experiment,
did you know that?
I only have to stay awake.
You're not the only one who can save her.
June, please don't be so arrogant.
That's bullshit, Jane.
I'm just trying to help Gran.
So you can do it but I can't, is that it?
She's not just your grandma.
Keep your voice down. We're in a hospital.
Oh, fuck it. I don't care.
June.
Mrs. Duangjai's family?
Can you please come in?
Where did you put Mom's stuff?
Tell me!
There's no reason to hang on to them.
She's gone.
Her things have to stay.
You can't just throw them away.
Why should it matter that she's gone?
What were you thinking?
I just don't want us
to be lingering around
stuck forever with her memory.
If it's out of sight, it's out of mind.
Without her things around,
we'll forget what happened and moved on.
Are you serious right now?
Then how come we didn't just do that
three years ago?
I would never forget her.
You can forget her on your own.
Don't expect me to forget her.
Or maybe it's…
because you couldn't save her, so…
you'd rather forget why she died.
I did everything I could, Win.
If you were in my shoes,
then you'd understand.
I tried everything.
But there was just no way your mother was.
She was just far beyond anyone's help
by that point.
Do you even hear yourself?
No wonder Mom killed herself.
Win!
What kind of person are you?
Just like that. You gave up.
If I had just been given the same chance…
she'd still be around.
The number you dialed
cannot be reached right now.
I only have to stay awake.
I'm just trying to help Gran.
-Sorry, Miss, you can't come in.
-Where is Dr. Hans?
You can't come inside.
No, wait.
Miss, wait.
Miss, you have to leave right now.
Please stop.
Why did you do this to me?
I didn't do anything.
This is your sister's decision.
Just like I said, I can help.
We need the money.
-So you can stop--
-Shut your mouth, June.
Take the chip off now
or I'll call the police.
You didn't read it carefully, did you?
That's unfortunate, and…
I'm sorry.
Let me tell you something.
Instead of trying to sue me,
why don't you bring your friends
back here?
Even if you give us a million,
no one will do it.
If you don't bring your friends back
for Deep Level 3,
I'm not going to remove the chip
from your sister.
And that means
she's going to die.
June, let's go.
Be hurry, Jane!
Your sister's Deep 3 treatment
has started.
Tick-tock.
Now you know what happened.
I'm pretty much at my wits' end here.
We all know that, Jane.
It's tough but you gotta remember,
we barely got pass Level 2.
Imagine Level 3,
we might as well just commit suicide.
But if we're careful every step,
there's still a chance we can beat it.
Without your help,
my sister will surely die.
Jane.
I… can't take the risk.
I don't… want to die myself either.
Sorry to be blunt but…
we're talking about risking everyone.
Four lives just to save one.
Sounds like a bad bet.
The only reason that
you're still breathing…
is because of Jane.
She saved your life and that's a fact.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be sitting here.
It is risky…
but I will help her.
I can't. I'm sorry, Jane.
Cin, come on, I'm begging you.
I don't know what else I can do now.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, Peach.
Hey, Peach!
Jane.
Don't you worry.
I'm not gonna leave you behind.
I just wasn't thinking straight.
And now, I've put everyone in trouble.
I understand, June.
We needed the money
for Grandma's treatment anyway.
All right?
I'm sorry, Jane.
I'm with you,
no matter what happens.
Yeah, the texture of this cream
is totally different.
If we were to compare it
to the other ones,
well, I'd say it's pretty light overall.
Safety is on the face.
Sounds like a term paper.
Hey, Peach.
I knew you'd come around.
Well, I'm your friend.
Jane.
There are three of us now.
I think we can negotiate with Dr. Hans.
Then let's go see him already.
You better not start without me.
I don't like being indebted to anyone.
Don't smile.
Want to go Deep?
Quick before I change my mind.
Are you ready?
You have a plan, right? No turning back.
It's now or never.
Of course I do.
The plan is to get help
from someone we can trust.
I'll give you a dose Exerall every day.
It'll keep you alert.
I really appreciate you helping us.
Actually, I owe you an apology.
If only I didn't send you
to that research program.
It's okay, professor.
None of this was your fault. Trust me.
We made our own decisions,
and we'll own up to it.
Besides, we really should thank you
for allowing us to stay here.
Everyone,
feel free to make yourself at home.
This is old ward belonged to my father.
It's safe.
All the equipment is in good condition
and are working fine.
The intercom is over there.
Simply buzz for me
if you ever need any help.
Well, I have a class to teach now.
So make yourself at home.
Call me immediately
as soon as anything goes wrong.
Jane, you have my number, right?
Yeah, I do.
Really?
You really gonna do your online thing?
Yeah. I mean,
what else am I supposed to do here?
All right. Whatever.
Now let me tell you
why Finn Mobile is so special.
It comes with a great
and complete package.
You pay less and get more.
With the maximum speed
of ten megabits per second.
You can enjoy movies, series,
and games with unlimited data,
plus all the other online services.
It's so easy and convenient. All right?
In the brutal murder case,
both husband and wife
were the house owners
were found stabbed by a knife
and died at the scene.
Win.
June. June.
June. Please, June, wake up right now.
-June.
-Win.
Win.
June!
Jane!
Jane, what's the matter?
Oh, shit.
You okay, Cin?
What happened?
Cin.
Don't touch me, you psychopath!
Cin, please calm yourself.
Let me look at your wound.
My face looks like shit
because of your sister.
I've become a walking corpse
just because of you.
I'm in this fucking mess
over a mistake by this little shit.
Cin. Take it easy, okay?
Take it easy, my ass.
Take a good look
at what happened to my face!
Cin, you have to listen to me.
You need to pull yourself together.
What? You think this is the key?
You'll win her heart because of this?
Let me break it to you.
It really doesn't matter how hard you try,
she's never going to look at you twice.
Come on.
So you think being a nice guy,
trying to save her precious sister
and all that shit
will make you so fucking cool in her eyes?
-It's none of your business, okay?
-Win. Win. Win.
Win. Win. Win.
Win, we have to stay calm.
We're all friends here, right?
We're friends, my ass!
What kind of a friend would mouth off
and attack Jane and her sister like that?
Let's just calmly sort this out.
You've never had any friends.
-So how would you know anything?
-Win.
No one wants to be friends
with a sick loser like you.
Win.
Don't do it, Win. Win.
Win. Stay calm, okay?
Are you out of your mind?
You want a piece of me, you prick. Huh?
Huh?
Win. Win, stop it, Win.
-Get back!
-Win. Win.
You think you're tough, huh?
Huh? Huh?
What's the matter? Take this shot.
Professor, we're in trouble.
Professor, help us!
Professor!
Professor Nichcha, please! Professor!
Professor Nichcha?
Jane, if you're feeling up,
you can give them a call at this number.
Hello.
My name is Hans Miller.
Jane.
You're not supposed to be here.
Cin, call the police!
What?
Professor Nichcha is behind everything.
What was that?
Professor Nichcha is behind Deep.
Call the police now.
Shit, there's no signal.
Children…
you won't be getting any signal in there.
Signal's gone. There's nothing.
Move it.
Shit.
It's locked tight.
Professor, please let us out of here.
Don't do this, please.
Stop this. Professor, please!
I will let you out, don't worry.
Once I extract the chips from all of you.
Then come and get it now, bitch.
I'll only remove all your chips
once you have reached full percentage.
Fuck!
-Or when you're…
-Hey, Peach, help us.
…dead.
I know that you're watching us.
So you want the chips?
You're never getting them
'cause I'm gonna kill you.
Fuck you!
Bitch!
Win. Win. Win.
Win.
Win?
Win. Win.
-Win. Win. Win.
-Ma?
But how…
Imagine how lucky we were
to find some CCL.
Which can cause temporary cardiac arrest.
We're not going anywhere.
We certainly can't max out the chip,
but we can still fake our death.
So why the hell are you doing this to us?
This is Jed.
The love of my life from 24 years ago.
Back then, he had used himself
as a subject for his own research
on sleep deprivation.
Extended sleeplessness drove him
into a fit of hallucination.
Eventually,
he fell from a building.
He survived but went into coma.
Years after that,
I found a practical way
to extract Qratonin
from the brain of sleep-deprived humans.
Jed responded positively
to the Qratonin treatment.
But a Qratonin from a single person
was just not enough to awaken him
from his coma.
You're risking people's lives
for your own benefit.
You call yourself human?
I never intended for anyone to die
from this, Cin.
But then someone did actually die.
What do you have to say about that?
Jane,
that was a momentary anomaly.
It was a glitch.
If she had followed the instruction,
she would've been fine.
I have done everything I can for everyone,
and you know it.
You know how important my students are.
To me, I care about them.
I have always looked after the four of you
from the start.
If I had really wanted you to die,
then I wouldn't have brought you here,
right?
You don't think
I've tried everything on myself too?
Here. Why don't you take a look?
All I ever wanted to achieve from this
was to bring back the man I love.
So you really don't get it?
You can't see how
what you're doing is wrong.
Jane, you know what it's like.
How extremely painful it is
to lose somebody you love.
I know that you know, Jane.
And if you were in my position,
then you wouldn't have done
anything different!
Let's hurry up and call the police.
ANESTHETIC DRUG
-Hey!
-Jane!
Jane!
-Somebody please help us.
-Hey, Peach, a little help.
-Jane!
-Let me.
Jane. Jane!
Jane.
Jane!
June, hand me that AED.
-Jane!
-June, you take the pads out.
Put one right over her left rib
and press firmly.
The other one on her right collarbone.
Okay. Now move.
How's Jane doing?
Still unconscious.
We need some room.
You did it.
Jane!
Wake up, Jane.
I'm with you,
no matter what happens.
Jane!
You said you're with me
no matter what happens.
Jane!
After that,
Professor Nichcha was arrested.
All the students who'd taken part in Deep
had their chip implants removed.
No one had gotten paid
for joining Level 3.
All of your mother's stuff
that I had given away earlier,
I promise you I'm gonna get it all back.
I love you, son.
Now what?
Come on.
What are you waiting for?
It's heavy.
What?
Gran, you see that?
She's so hard to please.
You're a snitch.
I'll tell on you.
You got nothing.
So, guys, I would like to tell all of you,
my loyal followers
to see my life as a case study.
Follow your heart no matter what.
Life is very short, so what's the harm?
Regardless of the outcome really,
it's all right.
At least you chose it, now that's freedom.
Cin finally decided
to quit med school
to study Communications.
So no more sleeping pills for her.
NITE NITE, GUYS.
Go to sleep.
Come on.
Sleep.
And Peach…
he realized that
living with friends in the real world
makes him just as happy
as in the virtual world.
Hey!
-Win…
-Hey.
Hey!
You're in it, Win!
Win!
Hey!
Take this.
And finally,
everyone had chosen to sleep like a rock
rather than to sleep like the dead
never to wake up and see the sun again.