Wave here!
Pose for the camera!
Yes! Just like that.
-Wave!
-What are you doing?
What's this?
Stop recording!
What foolishness is this, Patrick?
Why are you in a dress?
Barbs, make the lower lip bigger.
Jolie's upper lip is bigger.
Wait. Who is this?
Angelina Jolie.
I thought you said Jolina.
Angelina Jolie?
But both of them have big lips.
Would you both stop?
Don't they have an AC unit?
She might melt from the heat.
They only turn it on at night.
Have you heard from little miss orphan?
How frustrating.
That child was born with bad luck.
Both of her mothers are now dead.
Go ahead inside.
I'll pay for this.
Thank you.
Cover this chair.
Shirley Mae.
Where have you been?
Sorry!
Was your phone stolen?
We've been trying to call you.
I didn't know. I turned off my phone.
Why?
I didn't want Mama to find me.
I was shocked when I turned it on
and saw the messages...
Please take a rest.
Even chemo couldn't save her.
Did she refuse it?
With her salary?
What worries me...
is that one.
If I could, I'd adopt her myself.
Baby Adora is close to my heart.
I took care of her when Ella got sick.
But look at me.
This is my sixth.
And the father?
Never showed up.
Not even a shadow.
After Ella's burial,
her mother, Vangie,
will go home to Bulusan.
And she said...
that she plans to leave Adora behind.
She's never recognized her
as her granddaughter.
So you think raising that child
makes you a real woman?
God gave her to me.
How can I refuse?
Wow.
God also gave you a dick.
-But you still want to be a woman.
-Be quiet, she's sleeping.
Don't take God's name in vain.
You decided that on your own.
-Really now?
-Yes, really.
How about you praying to God
to get Gregory?
-That's nothing?
-Don't jinx it.
-I've prayed to God for a BF for so long.
-You started it.
Well...
Consider it an investment.
As they say,
us gays,
we should adopt a child
to take care of us in our old age.
I'm not like that.
What about the legalities of adoption?
She doesn't have a birth certificate.
She wasn't even born in a hospital.
It's your call.
I don't like her name though.
-What is it?
-Adora.
Sounds like a brand of rat poison.
-Let's change it.
-To what?
I believe in the saying,
"Having a flat tire
is better than having a flat nose."
My niece is brilliant!
You bitch, what was that?
But it's cute.
Flat nose?
She was cute.
She can afford wings!
The things you teach her.
It's cute!
You could have taught her a better saying.
Good kids go to heaven.
Naughty kids go to hell.
Blame it on the judges.
They favored the grandest costume.
Of course!
Her costume occupied the entire stage.
She even had minions.
Next year, Shirley,
I'll make your gown myself.
And we're going to put a long train on it.
It will cover the entire city.
-Yes, right up to the toll gate.
-For sure you'll win.
My mother is in Singapore.
She takes care of the sick.
She said I can visit her someday.
ABOUT MY PARENTS
Up next is Erica!
My father is a teacher
while my mother is a housewife.
She cooks our food and takes care of us.
Sometimes, my father helps me
with my homework.
The next one is Shirley Mae.
Let's pick on this girl.
Are you going home?
Yes...
Is your mama here?
What's your mama's profession again?
The real question is:
What is your mom?
Faggot.
Her mom's a faggot,
and she's just like her.
She's ugly, too.
She thinks she's so pretty?
Ouch!
You're ugly, just like your mother!
Yeah, you faggot!
My classmate said being a beauty queen
isn't a real job.
I told her, "Of course it is."
Ouch!
And then?
Then they started laughing
because they said you're a faggot.
And so you pulled her hair?
Then Miss Parco shut them up.
Aren't you a real mother?
I am.
I love you, right?
I'm just not a real woman yet.
But I am your mother.
Ouch!
So you don't have a vagina?
Hey, don't be nasty.
No, not yet.
But look, I have boobs.
Even bigger than yours.
Did you breastfeed me?
No, your first mother did.
My boobs don't have milk.
I don't get pregnant.
Another mother gave birth to you.
But,
I am your mother because
I take care of you.
There are women out there
who make lots of babies,
but it doesn't mean they are mothers.
That's exactly what Miss Parco said.
That's right.
When you see that girl again,
bring her to me, OK?
Why?
I'm going to tweeze her pubies!
She's such a bitch.
Being a beauty queen is hard work.
That hurts, Ma...
I turned on my phone.
I just wanted to know if she would call,
and then...
I wasn't able to tell her...
that I'm pregnant.
-What?
-Don't hit her!
Now, you won't be able to join pageants.
Why not?
Some were able to join
even though they had kids.
Just avoid getting stretch marks.
Why Angelina Jolie?
Was it her request?
There are seven looks.
Tomorrow will be a new one.
Awesome.
That guy...
Is he your boyfriend?
Fuck him!
He thought he could squeeze money
from me. Asshole!
Hey.
Language.
He wasn't even that handsome.
He's got nothing on Jesse. He's a jerk.
Jesse, again?
Can't you move on?
Just focus on your pageant.
It's only days before the finals.
Shirley Mae,
talk some sense into your mother.
She doesn't listen to me.
Don't think I didn't hear you last night.
You were fighting with someone
over the phone.
It was a guy, wasn't it?
Shirley Mae, don't be like me.
You're already menstruating.
Don't lose your future over a boy.
It's just a dick.
Girl, that's too much.
Let her experience it.
Make sure you don't get pregnant.
You can touch it, lick it,
or even suck it,
but no penetration.
Remember, you will be a beauty queen.
Is it a requirement to be a virgin
in pageants?
What if she gets pregnant?
I don't want to join pageants anymore, Ma.
How can you say that?
After Little Miss Barangay,
and Miss Girl of the 21st Century,
and Miss Young and the Restless?
-How dare you!
-Stop it.
I've invested so much in you,
I even gave you beauty supplements.
Damn you.
I don't want to be a beauty queen!
It's not what I want.
Where are you going?
Let her be.
Foolish girl!
Your manicure isn't even done yet!
Bitch, guess who?
Let me see.
A Lego person?
What Lego person?
Guess who? Look at the mole.
A Lego person with a mole?
Bitch, you're so annoying.
-Tell me who already.
-Fine, here.
So annoying.
Here.
-Yes, there's a resemblance.
-Right?
Show off!
Can you guess who I'm impersonating?
Wow, yes!
-You look just like her!
-Really?
Yes! Regine?
-Yes!
-Regine Tolentino!
No!
It's Velasquez.
-You're crazy!
-Reg...
You think if Migs saw me
looking like this,
he would like me?
For horny boys, a hole is a hole.
Especially your hole, my friend.
They like it...
tight.
Does it really hurt?
Only at first.
But...
once it really hits the spot, and
you start to relax,
that's when you really enjoy it.
What was that?
You look a lot like Regine.
What spot?
Instead of explaining it,
I'll just let you experience it yourself.
I'll get you a rent boy.
They're everywhere outside.
I don't want that.
Your Migs is not going to happen.
Fashion show, like that.
Sway your hips more.
-Like that?
-Like that!
Sashay.
Sashay away.
Butterfly walk.
What have we here?
We're not friends with her.
What's the matter with you?
You're such a flirt.
There's the teacher.
-Where is he?
-Let's go that way.
Girl, let's go.
I don't like it here, it stinks.
Come on, let's watch some basketball.
Migs is playing.
The guy who will pop my cherry.
How scandalous.
Have some fun, will you?
There are lots of cute guys here.
They're not my type.
They look too wholesome.
Why are they stripping?
I told you so, let's stay here and watch.
-OK, fine.
-Look at this pervert.
I hope Migs misses.
What do you want him to remove?
Shirt or shorts?
-That gave me an erection.
-You horny bitch.
Look, there he goes.
Pray that he misses.
He's taking off his shirt.
What's with that armpit?
-That's his girlfriend.
-I hate her.
-She's so stuck up.
-She's got a water jug for him.
Girl, where's your water?
You're not prepared.
I don't care.
Her legs are just three inches long.
She's so small.
So stuck up.
Here he comes.
-Is he coming here?
-Behave yourself!
Is he going to hurt us?
Fuck him! He can try!
How do I look?
Move over.
He wiped it on himself.
Now it's dirty. Wash it.
This year's Miss Gay Philippines is...
Wow, your mom looks great!
Are you going to text her?
Tell her congratulations.
Why did you turn it off?
She'll still be excited.
She won't think of me until next week.
How long can we stay here?
Don't worry about Uncle James.
It's fine with him.
He's cool.
How about you?
How long will you hold a grudge
against your mama?
Just let us be.
Thank you.
Miss Iza Calzado, can we take a picture
of you with the winner?
Of course. Why not!
I feel dizzy.
Do you want water?
Oh my God! What happened?
A doctor, an ambulance, a medic!
-Move back! She needs some air!
-Water please!
Look girls, Pia Wurtzbach.
I like this one better.
Megan Young.
Pia is Miss Universe,
Megan is just Miss World.
But Megan is the first Filipino
to win the Miss World crown.
Right, Barbs?
I prefer Pia.
-No, Megan all the way.
-Miss Universe, Miss World, whatever.
Will you two stop?
Here.
Since she's the one who crowned Trisha.
Oh, Trisha.
My Trisha.
-Mother.
-Dear, how are you?
How are you?
Good.
Oh, Mother.
We're so glad you could come.
Girl.
Paula.
How fabulous.
Who's that?
It's Iza Calzado, Mother.
You're right.
I just saw her.
Really, Mother?
Does she have a new TV show?
No. She has a new movie.
And also a concert.
No.
Mother, trust me.
-I saw the trailer, she has a movie.
-No, really,
-I just saw her.
-Really now.
She's here.
Fuck.
It is her.
I sent her manager a message,
but I didn't think she would come...
Thank you so much for coming.
My condolences, I also feel so sad.
We thought so too, madam.
Thank you again for coming, madam,
We really appreciate it.
I feel really sad...
Of course, madam, this way.
Girls, behave yourselves.
You're the one she chose, ma'am.
Just for tonight.
To be her look-alike.
You're embarrassing.
Come here everyone, let's get our picture
taken with Iza Calzado!
Come here!
Shirley Mae, come here!
Come here.
Let's take a selfie.
Didn't I tell you to get that fixed?
I'll call maintenance, sir.
I need to meet my classmates.
We need to finish our thesis.
Bullshit.
You think I'm an idiot?
You were just hospitalized.
You think you can fool me?
But it's true.
We have a deadline.
And...
because I was hospitalized,
we're running late.
Patrick...
perhaps you...
should take it easy.
-But, Pa--
-Damn you.
Everything that comes out of it
is garbage.
I am this close...
to kicking you out of the house.
Shame on you for not only dishonoring me,
your father,
but the entire family.
Be thankful I'm still letting you
eat in my house
even though you disgust me!
Where are you going?
Where else?
What if Papa wakes up?
You don't need to scare me.
You're still going?
Didn't Papa say you weren't allowed?
I'll be back before he knows it.
Patrick... don't do this.
Papa might not forgive you this time.
I'm ready.
Try not to breathe!
Mother Celing, it hurts.
You want to be a beauty queen, right?
Since you don't have real breasts yet,
endure it.
Mother, she's ready for shipping.
Put her inside the box.
They're just joking.
I know, Mother.
Tonight, the third runner-up
gets 500 pesos.
Second runner up
gets 1,000.
First runner up
gets 2,000.
And the winner
gets 5,000 pesos.
-Five thousand?
-Wow, 5,000.
-What country will you represent?
-Bahamas.
Make your eyes bigger.
If you get Miss Friendship,
that's 200 pesos.
Two hundred? Barbs, 200!
But if you want to win a crown...
impress them with your beauty.
In life, there are many mysteries.
Questions that remain unanswered,
such as:
Why do we fart?
Why are some people poor?
Why...
are others poorer?
Tonight,
I will solve a mystery.
Which came first?
The egg...
or the chicken?
-Chicken!
-Egg!
Let me answer it for you.
It's the egg!
As you can see, the egg came first.
Thank you.
Patrick.
Come here.
How dare you?
You have no respect.
Get out.
Leave this house at once.
-I'll just get my things.
-You won't get anything.
Nothing in this house is yours.
Now leave.
-I need my things.
-No!
But they're mine!
You own nothing here!
You want to be a different person?
Then buy your own clothes,
get a new ID
and change your surname,
because I won't let you use my name
anymore.
-Pa.
-Papa, please.
-Don't you dare...!
-Papa!
Don't ever come back.
Stick that in your head, Patrick!
I am Trisha.
It was bound to happen.
I wish I had left earlier.
If only I'd had the money.
Aren't you going to eat?
I'm OK, Mama Ruby.
Who knows?
He might change his mind.
I am not going back.
What about your studies?
I think...
-Mama, I'm leaving.
-Where are you going?
I might as well stop.
I can't afford it anymore.
Barbs will have to stop too.
He failed all his subjects.
Ma...
I just need to find a job, and then...
I will look for a room to rent.
You just moved in
and you're already thinking of leaving?
It's going to be difficult finding work.
Barbs had to do odd jobs.
I do makeup at weddings, graduations...
You know those whores at casinos
and at Makati Avenue?
They don't know how to apply makeup.
Fucking is their only skill.
I still have 1,000 pesos. Please take it.
-What's the matter with you?
-No, you should keep it.
Sorry to trouble you.
Girl.
Are you ready?
Yes, I am.
Wherever this leads us?
Even if that's hell.
This is so exciting.
Reserve your energy, girls.
Don't push your limits.
We have more pageants to go to.
But, tell you what, the councilor here,
if a candidate pleases him,
he will give her a bonus.
So, do your best.
Is that clear?
Oh God, all this mud...
-Barbs, look.
-Girl, what the hell?
Look!
What?
-I have an idea.
-Girl, the things you come up with...
-A great idea in mind.
-What is it?
I'm going to buy these birds
and hide them in my costume
so that when I introduce myself,
I'll open my cape and let the birds fly!
Fabulous, right?
The birds could bite you!
-Plus, you'll be wasting cash.
-Right?
But these birds aren't that expensive.
If it pleases the councilor,
I might just win.
Fine, do what you want.
Great changes are happening in our town.
We have fixed the power outage,
we repaired Maristela Bridge,
and we built additional schools
in Syjuco and Capas.
Will he ever stop talking?
The birds are clawing at my nipples.
Remember, you wanted this.
Hug them tightly so they won't move.
From the country of Israel!
It's so itchy, we have so many... Russia!
Spain!
Good evening, everyone!
Who believes in this saying:
I catch balls under the bridge.
Stop with the gimmicks.
Work on your Q&amp;A skills.
Didn't I give you a sample Q&amp;A?
Memorize that.
Or you can crack a joke
if you can't think of an answer.
Or ask for an interpreter.
Or just blabber anything in English.
Say something like:
Something like that!
What does that mean, Mother?
Nothing.
Dumbass, just say it with confidence.
Take it from Barbs.
Her English is hopeless,
yet she took home Miss Friendship.
Our next stop is Concepcion,
Tarlac, girls.
-Let's team up! One more!
-My bikini area is burning already.
The bones in my feet
will show up any time.
It's my mom.
Let's go home.
Ma!
Hello, child!
Did you win, Ma?
Same as always.
You should join
Miss Gay Philippines instead.
So I can watch you on TV.
Dear, I've been telling her that.
She refuses.
She's too insecure.
You two are too ambitious.
Even in small-time pageants,
I only get First Runner-up.
What more in Miss Gay Philippines?
That's because
your beauty isn't for small-time pageants.
You really know how to
make Mama feel good.
Go inside now.
You have school tomorrow.
Here, take this.
-Good night.
-Brush your teeth!
-Yes, Ma!
I'll go ahead.
I'll pick you up tomorrow at six.
Wait, really? At six?
Isn't that too early?
We're doing make up for the entourage.
We need to be early.
Stop complaining.
Be thankful that we have a job.
Why, it feels like...
I'm so tired of joining beauty contests.
These boobs have taken us nowhere.
Idiot.
All you think about are pageants.
Personally, I've given up.
I'm only still joining them
because of you.
Really, now?
Looking at you, I wouldn't have guessed.
Pageants are a nice way to earn money.
Yes, I know.
But we're getting old.
Your boobs are wasted on nothing.
You should use them to
breastfeed some boys.
I'm leaving.
Good night. See you tomorrow.
I'm getting sleepy.
Hurry, please.
What happened to her? Put her here.
-Trisha?
-Ma'am sorry, you can't be here.
Where's Trisha?
-See, you're Miley Cyrus today.
-Good morning!
Good morning, Madam!
You caught me by surprise.
-My sympathies.
-Thank you very much.
I'm Flora,
the owner of this funeral parlor.
Yes, I know you, Madam.
I've been to a number of wakes
here before.
This funeral home wasn't called
Happy Ending back then.
It was called "Living Things" then,
back when I was still a
Born Again Christian.
What a nice lamp.
Oh, it's not a lamp.
It's a wrecking ball.
Are you going to wreck something here?
Where is her family?
That's a tragedy.
She was disowned?
Growing old is already tough.
Look at me.
All my family died before me.
That's why I take care of my boy toys.
So someone will be there for me
when it's time for me to die.
Look.
-That's my boyfriend.
-Oh, really, Madam?
We've been together a long time.
He's never left me.
Perhaps he really does love me.
Babe!
Motel later?
That one is Bruce Walis.
We've only been together two years.
Really, madam?
I noticed them yesterday.
Bruce, mop the floors next.
He's my embalmer.
When I die,
I want him to embalm my body.
I know my organs
will be handled with care.
I feel like vomiting.
Joke.
The other one is 19 years old.
Although, he's leaving soon.
But oh my, he's always hard.
Oh, really?
Your funeral parlor is like a gay bar,
too.
That's why it's called Happy Ending.
That's right, Happy Ending.
Oh, every night it's different.
That was her last request.
Why?
Did she know that she was going to die?
Did she die of cancer?
No.
We once talked about her last wishes.
She's very young.
What a waste.
Was she flirty with boys?
Even at two years old.
Good. She's very beautiful, after all.
She looks like she's just asleep.
Can I take a selfie?
Sure.
Thanks.
You can do it here, for a better view.
Can you take the picture?
Here, just press it here.
-Here?
-Yes, that's right.
Your phone's so lit.
-Now, let's do a candid shot.
-OK, candid--
Such a beautiful girl.
A town in Spain?
my mother loves Spanish bread.
-So, where does Echevarria come from?
-Jan-jan!
Nowhere really, it just sounded nice.
I invented that name when I was a kid.
Oh, I see.
How does that feel?
I'm excited. And nervous.
It says here, makeup is your hobby.
And you can transform into any celebrity.
Yes, me and my best friend, Barbs,
when we have nothing to do,
-we study and copy the faces of stars.
-I'll feed my grandchild.
Jan-jan.
Can you copy her face?
Me?
How about next time?
Girl, look at that lump.
Did you spot anyone?
I want him!
Him? Or him?
That one is cute.
-There.
-Where?
We start with that one.
Looks like a biggie.
You're totally gay.
But his nose looks a bit big.
Look down!
That's also big.
My ovaries can't handle the excitement.
It makes me want to just open my mouth.
You like him, too.
Guess what?
My plaster is falling off instantly.
He's mine.
Stop it.
I'll just take a look at it.
The doctor said leave it for a week.
-Promise, just a peak.
-Michael Angelo.
That nose of yours
might get infected because of your antics.
I don't have money to have it fixed again.
You're so irritable.
I'll stop, Mommy.
But thank you, really.
I've always wanted a nose job.
That's my Valentine's, Birthday, Christmas
and Three Kings gift to you.
Didn't the doctor give you a discount?
I'm saving up to get a vagina.
But I spent it on your nose first.
That's why I love you so much.
Shirley Mae! What are you doing there?
We're now a family.
What, I'm a mother to both of you?
I'm the father.
I may be young,
but I know how to be a father.
Shirley, starting today, call me "Daddy".
If you say so.
And you...
you're now my wife.
And I am your husband.
Wow.
Just because I paid for your nose,
we're married now?
And one day,
I'll get you your vagina.
Your vulgar mouth.
When it comes to that,
do you plan to quit stripping?
Why?
Are you ashamed of me?
It's not as easy as it looks.
And even though I show it to everyone,
my dick is yours alone.
Keep your voice down.
Sorry, what should I call you now?
Are you about to cry?
Or just suppressing a yawn?
You're so beautiful.
I'm so happy to see you again.
Your boobs are bigger than mine.
Thank you.
Are those real?
I've been saving money.
I've been thinking--
I want to be a complete woman.
Is that a wig?
No, this is real.
How have you been?
I'm pregnant.
I thought I was going to die an old maid.
You finally got a man.
Papa... he's doing well.
He still talks about you.
That's history.
I don't regret anything.
It's the best decision I made in my life.
He's still your father.
And I'm still your sister.
Not anymore.
That's all in the past, Beth.
It's better if...
we just treat each other as friends.
I have a new family now.
It's so hot!
Hurry! We're going to be late.
Calm your tits!
You sure we didn't forget anything?
Put on your wig.
Later. Just hold it for now.
OK, let's go!
She's still not answering.
I can't believe she's doing this to me
on the day of the finals.
Just call her later. We're late.
You think she turned off her phone?
-Stop it!
-Maybe her phone was stolen?
She'll come back. This is getting tiring.
What if she doesn't?
I didn't come back home.
Nobody asked you to come back.
Excuse me! I didn't want to come back.
Whatever. After the grand finals,
we'll look for her, OK?
We'll call the police.
We're here. Let's go.
Remember the makeup kits.
And don't forget the costumes.
Hurry up, hurry.
The prizes here are huge.
You'll get 5,000 pesos
for placing third runner-up.
Come on.
Just a tiny bit of contour here.
And some highlight on the cheeks.
And the dark eyeshadow.
Dark or black?
What's that? That's a lot of makeup.
I have a gimmick in mind, Mother.
-Another gimmick?
-This will be fun.
Barbs will help me.
We're going to copy the face
of Britney Spears.
What you need to prepare for
is the Q&amp;A portion.
Did you study the sample Q&amp;A I gave you?
I've only been able to memorize one.
Which one?
There are too many.
This one:
You waste your time on gimmicks.
Look at what you've done to your face.
You must be cursed.
Of all the questions,
you were asked that one.
Mother Celing,
they just won't let me win.
Who knows if that was the question
written on the paper?
Correct! No one else won, aside from you.
Look at your competition.
You shouldn't have expected to win.
Why is that, Mother?
They are post-operated women.
They went to Japan.
Especially that Tonette...
Look at her boobs,
so firm as if she's always horny.
Trisha, please don't make a scene.
Hey!
Fuck you, where are you going?
I already saw you. Don't hide from me!
What are you doing here?
Trisha, why?
You're asking me why? You bitch.
You seduced my husband!
That's not true. I only asked Miko
to help paint the parlor.
-Right, Miko?
-Why? Is my husband a painter?
Since when did he become
Leonardo da Vinci?
He can't even color a coloring book.
You've had your eyes on him
ever since I took him here for a haircut.
Girl, you're being paranoid.
I only have one question for you.
Tell me the truth.
Are you having an affair with my husband?
-Affair?
-Affair.
Are you his concubine,
kept woman, mistress?
-Trisha...
-Don't call me Trisha!
Answer my question!
Wait...
Isn't that a line from a movie?
-Enough of this.
-That's right.
Don't play innocent with me.
You've been found out.
And you're still playing coy!
Damn it, girl.
Are you going to use
all of Maricel Soriano's dialogues?
Teach her a lesson already!
You don't want to do it?
OK then, I'll do it myself!
Bitch!
You idiot.
We were almost arrested
for starting a fight!
It hurts!
-Thanks, Shirley.
-Ouch!
Thank God, your face is unscathed.
We still have a pageant tonight.
You did nothing but talk
and bitch at her like crazy.
What was that about?
That's all you've got?
That's the best you could do?
-You're a war freak!
-I admit it!
You really attacked her?
I made her boobs a punching bag!
You should have also taken back
Miko's nose.
How much did you spend on it, Ma?
Let's not talk about it.
How dare he?
I really believed that he loved me.
He promised he would marry me.
But Ma...
you don't really love him.
You only liked him because
you thought no one was going to love you.
Listen to your daughter.
I hope you learn from her.
You talk too much for your age.
What do you know about love?
Not much.
All I know is how you love me.
I hope you find the same kind of love
from your boyfriends.
By the way, Ma...
I found this in the cabinet.
Here.
This is Mother Celing's...
-I wasn't able to return it to her.
-I remember this.
Look at this.
She wrote down all the possible
pageant questions.
You still have time to memorize them.
At my age?
I don't know.
For the longest time,
I've only managed to memorize
one answer here.
Bravo! You're amazing!
Do you want to work here?
Probably when I run out of
other career options.
Bitchy!
-Where did you see this?
-Facebook.
Do you know them?
Aren't they friends of Trisha?
But how did they know?
Barbs, we have a problem.
What?
Let me see.
I'm the one who posted it.
In case you didn't know,
my funeral parlor has a fan page.
That's why her corpse is trending.
Look at this, Barbs.
It has 20,000 likes.
There will be more people coming
to verify if it's a hoax.
Shit... that's bad.
Isn't that good?
She'll have many visitors.
We stole her body.
What?
Her father might find her.
We won't complete the seven days.
I don't understand.
It's supposed to be a secret.
Let's keep it a secret.
Can we take a photo with her?
Go ahead, but this is a secret.
-Why did you let them?
-It's for their eyes only!
Thank you.
I know you're gossipers.
Call me once you get home.
-Hey, look at that.
-Where?
It's Migs.
You got sharp eyes.
He's with his girlfriend again.
That girl's annoying!
Now's your chance.
Right now?
Yes, right now. It's up to you.
-Did she confess already?
-Yes.
-Hi.
-Your fan.
Have you washed this?
Nice.
You should come with us.
Let's eat out.
Are you game?
Yes, c'mon.
I'm shy.
Come on.
Let's go!
That bitch left me.
She didn't even look back.
She hasn't showed up for two days.
Did you try calling her?
She's not answering.
What's up with her?
Look, she's here.
Trish!
Hey!
What happened to you?
What's up with you?
Trisha!
Will you please wait for me?
What really happened?
Hey, girl!
Trisha?
Wait.
Are you crying?
I feel sick to my stomach.
Are you pregnant?
You're crazy.
Then what is it?
Hey!
Maybe it's something I ate.
Don't change the topic.
What happened to you?
I'm no longer a virgin.
Now I know...
what you're talking about.
You know,
the feeling when something's inside you.
At first, I agreed.
I told Migs,
OK, but he has to be the first one.
I thought of it as a challenge...
and a game.
Maybe it could lead to something.
But...
by the fourth guy,
I started thinking,
am I getting raped?
I don't know.
I was so confused.
You said it would hurt,
but I would get used to it.
They didn't force me.
I didn't even object.
I felt so helpless.
Sis...
You're bleeding, Trish.
Let's go to the hospital.
Come on, get your things.
So who's bigger, girl?
-Is it Migs or Josh?
-It's Migs.
You said you were only hurt
after Migs left.
What happened to you?
Papa, it's gastroenteritis, they said.
I think I ate something bad.
Patrick Villar?
And, well,
he got bruised and it got infected.
What trauma?
Perhaps you should ask him.
But there are...
Excuse me, sir.
I'll leave you alone for now.
You shameless faggot.
You're not going to stop, are you?
Papa, not here.
You're disgusting. You son of a bitch.
Patrick, I'm trying to understand you,
but why did you do this?
If I were in his situation,
I wouldn't mind.
Wow! Look at you and your red lipstick!
It will heal with the help of antibiotics.
You're sure?
It also happened to Sonia.
-She was also gangbanged?
-Moron.
I don't want to see you all.
You don't want to mess with me.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Just leave it there! Barbs!
Barbs!
What are you doing?
Have you saved enough money?
I'm 20,000 pesos short.
Maybe there's a bulk discount
since it's for the two of us?
A total of four boobs.
Breasts...
Trish,
I'm scared.
Does it hurt?
-Or you can use a stapler.
-Why don't you try it first.
Idiot, of course it will hurt,
it's a wound.
But no pain, no gain, right?
This is a career move.
-A career move?
-So?
I liked the way you did that.
You love it?
I'm OK.
-I think it's time.
-Yes, sir.
You can go inside now.
Can we skip my boob job?
Give me a vagina first
so we can have a child.
I'm just like you, Trisha.
You have a vagina?
Just take a nap.
Let's start.
We'll just put an IV line.
Ma'am, we're closing.
What time is it?
It's already late, ma'am.
Ouch!
Does it hurt?
I think so.
We're already closing.
Ouch!
It's a wound, that's why it hurts.
But it will heal.
Just take what the doctor prescribed.
Don't carry anything heavy for six weeks.
And don't remove the surgical tape.
That's what the doctor said.
Girl, it really hurts.
Girl, endure it.
It's for our future.
We should finally win
because of these boobs.
Wait, I think this is wrong grammar.
One year already...
He's been beating you up...
-What's the reason?
-Yes, what is it?
You just get tired one day.
Just a moment.
Barbs!
It's Maumau Zaldriaga.
-Who?
-The famous couturier.
My condolences.
Thank you.
What's her name?
Madame, she's Trisha.
And you are?
I'm Barbs.
You're the one who does
the makeup creation?
Yes, madam.
Thank you, madam.
Who is Trisha tonight?
Julia Roberts from Runaway Bride.
And this is her gown?
Yes, madam.
Is it OK?
Wow!
How will you dress the corpse?
What do you mean?
We can't make the corpse stand.
What do we need to do?
Cut it at the back.
Madame, it's OK.
We can use the other gown.
Badong.
Scissors.
Don't cover the coffin.
Excuse me.
What a beautiful transwoman.
Madam, she's a real woman.
You're together now.
You're really meant for each other.
This is the men's room.
Why?
Do I look like a man to you?
Sir, just use that other toilet.
You're joining me?
Sir.
Show the lady some respect.
It's OK, I got this.
OK, sir.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
I'll stand guard while you're inside.
Why would you do that?
To protect you.
Are you looking for something?
Are you an angel fallen from heaven?
Let's talk again...
after you've split up.
With whom?
The reason why your eyes are sad.
I've been watching you with your friend.
Stop right there.
Are you drunk? Maybe on drugs?
You need to know that I have testicles.
Maybe bigger than yours.
I'm just good at hiding it.
Don't guys tell you you're beautiful?
They do.
But guys who think I'm pretty are animals.
If you're one of them, go away.
I'm only an animal in bed.
-I'm only an animal in bed.
-Trish?
Is he doing something to you?
He hasn't done anything to me yet.
Get lost.
What are you doing?
Just wait a little more.
How much longer?
You're too excited.
-Wait, I'm coming.
-OK.
-Now, open your eyes.
-Now?
That's amazing.
Angelina Jolie was my teenage crush.
I know.
That's why I copied her face.
So who do you love more...
Julia Roberts or Angelina Jolie?
The one I truly love the most is...
Really?
Your friend might come back.
We should leave.
We can stay here all day.
Why bother your friends?
We could have gone to a motel.
I'm not hiding you in a sleazy motel.
I'm serious about you.
Cut the crap.
The truth is, you're just being cheap.
I gave all of my salary to my wife.
I have money.
No, I don't want you to spend.
You might think I'm using you.
I know...
I know my place.
I wanted a straight man for a boyfriend.
That's why I'm willing to share you.
It's unfair to your wife.
Imagine if she learns that her rival
is a transwoman.
I don't even have a vagina.
I know.
But I fell in love.
Straight right here.
-Really? There?
-Yes.
What can a guy do?
Hide this gift before Jesse comes.
Is it his birthday, Ma?
It's our sixth monthsary next week.
Help me cook for him, OK?
Giddy as a schoolgirl?
Don't tease me.
When you fall in love, you'll understand.
Why is he picking us up?
No reason. He's free today.
I hope you give him a chance.
He's not going to hurt me.
What?
You're happy with him. What can I do?
Did you wait too long?
Sorry, traffic's bad.
It's OK.
Get in.
Let's see a movie after we eat?
Sure.
You can sleep in the room now.
He's not coming.
What time is it?
OK, go to sleep. I'll just clean up.
I'll just clean up.
My feet hurt already.
Why do you have to wear
high heels every time?
It's been almost a month, Barbs.
What if something bad happened to Jesse?
-He's not like that--
-That's false hope again!
He used to answer all my calls.
Should I go to his house?
Do you know where that is?
Somewhere in Better Living, Paraaque.
Better Living, Paraaque, that's it?
So your plan is
to knock on all the houses there?
Good luck.
And if you see his wife...
you'll act out another
Maricel Soriano film?
"You are the intelligent one!
The pretty one!
Bitch!
Cunt! You took everything from me!
Everything!"
Like that?
That's overacting.
-Then what?
-Be subtle.
-Okay, show me how.
-Like Jaclyn Jose.
"You are the wife.
I'm just a mistress.
Fuck you!"
Like that!
Bitch, always overacting.
Hey, smile.
He's going to call.
You should be used to waiting by now.
Just relax.
-Thank you, what time will she arrive?
-Shirley!
You have a visitor?
Shirley, why did you let a stranger
come into our house?
I'm Diana.
I'm Jesse's wife.
He's been in remission from leukemia
for a year.
But his sickness came back.
It's more aggressive this time.
He wants to talk to you.
Just wait for him to wake up.
I'll be at the lobby.
Nothing.
Where's Diana?
She went outside.
I thought I wouldn't be able to
convince her to bring you here.
She knows about us?
I told her.
I don't understand what's happening.
Why didn't you tell me you were sick?
I really thought I was cured.
My sins from the past still haunt me.
I still have a lot to atone for.
I've done you so much wrong.
What are you talking about?
Don't you remember anything?
You really don't recognize me?
I'm a friend of Migs.
I was there the night it happened.
Your turn.
Be quick. So we can all go home.
Meeting you at the bar wasn't an accident.
I have been following you.
Watching you.
My guilt is killing me
for what we did to you.
So that's why you're so nice to me.
I thought I hit the jackpot.
You're just an asshole like the others.
Please forgive me.
I don't know what's worse.
You raping me before,
or you deceiving me now?
Is this why you made me fall in love?
Because of your guilt?
I love you.
Are you sure?
I used up all my concealer
on your eye bags.
You look like you're going to
your funeral.
Can you relax?
I know how this ends.
Always the favorite at the start,
then comes the Q&amp;A, and I'll fail again.
You will really lose
with that negative attitude.
I want to win. You know that.
Yes.
That's my only dream.
To be crowned a beauty queen.
Then, I'll be ready.
Ready for what?
I'll be ready to die.
Idiot.
You haven't met the love of your life
and you want to die?
I'm done with heartbreaks.
Promise me this.
What?
When I die, I want different makeup looks
during my wake.
Before you bury me. Promise me, OK?
Trisha, that's nonsense.
Promise me.
Or I'll come back to haunt you.
And I promise that when you die,
I'll give you a beautiful make-over.
I'll dress you fabulously...
in gowns with those high slits.
I don't want to wear a gown.
I want to wear a Barong Tagalog.
Tomboy?
Seriously?
I thought about it.
As they say...
-Kidding!
-C'mon!
So if he's taking it back,
I want to return it to its original form.
I played with it all my life.
At the end, I want to honor it.
When I die, I will tell God, "Take a look.
I made your gift even more beautiful.
More fabulous."
He will be pleased...
-Girls, come to the studio now.
-OK.
Hurry up.
Remember, confidence.
Give me that, I'll do it.
For the first night of my wake...
-How ambitious!
-Really?
Go, they need you now.
Do your best, girl! Good luck!
We won't allow it.
Why not? We're the family.
-But you disowned him!
-Can you just stop it?
Why do we have to fight over this?
I reached out to you
because you have the right to know,
being her sister.
But, I repeat,
you cannot take her away from us.
I have plans for her wake.
So do we.
I've already spoken with our father.
He wants Trisha to be brought home.
Patrick.
I won't forbid you to visit him.
But I'll warn you now,
if you decide to visit him,
-you can't be...
-We can't be what?
You can't be that way.
For your information,
Trisha wanted to be buried...
looking this way.
Your sister, Trisha.
I told you to supervise this.
Why are those still there?
What, Pa?
Those!
People won't notice.
Perhaps we should leave those there
for now.
I'm not going to let people see him
unless those are removed.
I'll talk to the embalmer.
Can't we just respect
Patrick's last wishes?
After all, we don't know half of his life.
But he's back with us.
I want his old self back.
That's only right.
Yes?
We're here at the funeral parlor.
Maybe tomorrow morning.
I'll leave you to it.
You can let them know,
but don't invite everyone, OK!
What did you do to Trisha?
If you really knew your sister,
you would know that she wouldn't
want to be seen looking like that.
I know.
That's why I'm returning her to you.
What about your father?
Won't he get mad at you?
I'll handle him.
Just give my sister
the funeral she wished for.
Beth?
Thank you.
I should be the one thanking you.
Papa might come back.
Leave now before he sees you.
Thank you, Beth.
I'll make you beautiful again.
This is the last night of Trisha's wake.
I know you're all curious
to see her look for tonight.
I've thought about this long and hard.
As her best friend,
this is how I want you to remember her.
In her short life,
she's worn many faces.
As a daughter,
as a mother,
a friend,
a girlfriend,
a wife,
and most of all,
a beauty queen.
Tonight,
I want you to see her simply as Trisha.
Trisha Echevarria.
The most beautiful woman I know.
FOR JOSHUA