I still remember
the first time
I had to be far away from home.
It was a Sunday afternoon.
It felt both hectic and lonely.
It was the last day
of school break for the seventh graders,
like me and my friends.
It was like the last day of being free.
The freedom that we enjoyed
during our vacation.
Stop crying!
You didn't get any work done
during your vacation.
The one thing
we could never come to terms with
is...
How do you want it cut?
Crew cut.
The last day of school break.
However,
some of us can't wait to go to school.
Because it means
being reunited with our friends.
Except for me.
Hey! Stop pressing the buttons!
KITROONGRUANG
Jaew, Pen, take good care of the house.
Yes, ma'am.
We could have let Ton
finish seventh grade
before transferring him to another school.
Moving suddenly
is a shock for me as well.
Can you stop talking about this subject?
Dad, is Ton's new school
in another province?
Yes, it's in Chonburi.
Where will he stay after school?
In the school dormitory.
They have everything there.
Remember, son,
a man must be able to live anywhere.
Are we almost there?
No, we have to cross
the Bangpakong River first.
Let's make a wish, Tor.
If you hold your breath
as we cross the bridge,
whatever you wish for will come true.
Really?
But don't cheat. Hold your breath
until we have passed the bridge.
Ton, hold your breath too.
What did you wish for?
For Dad to send me
to boarding school with Ton.
What about you, Ton?
SAICHON WITTAYA SCHOOL
Tor, don't go too far.
STUDENT DORMITORY
Hello, ma'am.
My name is Pranee.
I'm the dorm supervisor
for junior high boys.
This must be Chatree.
Yes, ma'am.
Parents, please wait here.
Chatree, follow me.
Don't dawdle.
Hey, it's a new kid.
Where's he from?
He seems like a troublemaker.
This is your bed.
Go and get your blanket.
Make sure
to make your bed every morning.
Every boy must take care of himself here.
No one will serve you or pamper you
like when you were at home.
Dad has written your name on everything.
CHATREE
Study hard and don't get into trouble.
Please keep an eye on him.
I will.
Don't be so noisy!
Chatree, follow me.
Dinner is served at 6 p.m.
Everyone must eat on time.
This is your seat.
Sit down.
I'm sending Ton
to a boarding school next semester.
Why is it so sudden?
Darling,
this new school has high standards
and a good reputation
unlike his current school.
The kids don't study hard enough.
Playing around and watching TV are
all they do before having exams.
But they still get good grades.
That means the school has low standards.
This is Chatree.
Your new classmate.
Chatree will board here and study with you
starting from this term.
Go take your seat.
CHATREE
Chatree, Master Peng is calling you.
My name's Peng.
That's Dr. Nui.
This idiot is Sarote.
That ass is Pok.
I'm Toei.
What's your name?
His name is Chatree.
Okay, Chatree.
Are you scared of ghosts?
Of course, why wouldn't he be?
I'm not asking you, idiot.
Are you scared of ghosts?
Good. As we've been here longer
we're going to tell you
the history of our school.
I just found out about this story.
I'm sure you guys haven't heard it.
A senior told me that
one of the cooks had a beautiful daughter.
She was the crush of every boy in school.
But one day,
she hung herself
from a Bodhi tree.
No one knew
why she suddenly killed herself.
When the police conducted an autopsy,
they discovered that she was
four months pregnant.
A pregnant ghost
is the nastiest kind around.
A group of senior boys
wanted to find out the truth.
-One, two, three!
What did they see?
No need to go to the Bodhi tree.
There are ghosts in the dorm.
Someone once saw an old man
walking around the dorms at night.
At first, no one knew who he was.
But when they looked into old yearbooks,
they found out that
he used to be the dorm supervisor.
You've got goosebumps, Master Peng.
Hey, bugger off.
Have you ever experienced
feeling like you're not alone
when you go to the toilet
in our dorm at night?
Keep this in mind.
Any night the dogs howl in unison,
you better stay away from the toilet.
Do you guys know
why our school had to build
a new swimming pool?
SCHOOL POOL RULES
Because a student drowned himself
in the old pool behind the school.
More importantly,
he was in seventh grade just like us.
Most importantly,
he used to board in this dorm.
They shut down the pool years ago.
A senior told me that
Ms. Pranee almost lost her mind.
Yes, that's when she became weird.
And she still hasn't recovered.
Do you know how weird she is?
Have you seen
the old record player in her office?
She likes to listen to
this creepy love song.
It gives me the creeps.
One day,
someone saw her
staring and crying at an open drawer.
To this day nobody knows
what the hell is in that drawer.
Maybe Doraemon's there.
Doraemon, my ass.
After a while,
you'll see for yourself, Chatree.
Maybe
Ms. Pranee had something to do with
the boy's death.
And that boy's ghost is a vicious one.
Anyone who slept in his bed
was kicked out of it every night.
Finally, they had to put
the bed in storage.
But...
I saw the janitor bring his bed out
from the storage room today.
Boys!
Bedtime is for sleeping.
Anyone who can't wake up tomorrow
will get whacked.
Hey, the new kid wet his bed!
The new kid wet his bed!
-Gosh.
-He wet his bed.
Look at him.
-The new kid wet his bed!
-Will it be washed?
If you hang it that way
it'll just fall to the ground.
The clothesline is a battle zone.
If you're going to make space
you have to be tricky.
And you only need one pair of
bathing shorts.
Or else every pair will get moldy.
VICHIEN CHAMCHONG
Do you guys smell something?
Not this.
Not this, too.
I know. It reeks of his piss.
All the ghost stories
made you wet your pants.
Make fun of the new boy, everyone.
Pok, why are you laughing?
Your mouth stinks pretty bad as well.
Is it broken?
I don't know. Maybe I can fix it.
You know how to fix it?
I'm not sure, but I'll try.
Can I play with it
after you fix it?
Sure.
Chatree, you have a phone call.
It's your dad.
Chatree Ananpitisook,
your father is on the dormitory phone.
I bought some snacks for you.
Don't you dare do this again.
If you get bad grades this semester,
I'll really punish you.
Chatree isn't here right now.
Would you like to leave a message?
No, that's okay.
I'll call back another day.
Thank you.
Hey, who's there?
Open the door!
Asshole, just wait until I get out!
That was awesome.
Just a few ghost tales,
and he peed his pants.
What a sucker!
Open the door!
Hey!
You woke up late?
Yes.
You're really curious about
Ms. Pranee, aren't you?
You better watch out.
I know.
Do you know why Ms. Pranee is so weird?
There are lots of theories.
Worst of all are the ghost stories.
They're not true.
You've been here for a long time?
Why did you ask?
It's just that
you seem to know everything.
Of course, I do!
Don't you know I'm Vichien
"Know-it-all" Chamchong?
Take a bath quickly.
Ms. Pranee is coming down.
Before we go down for breakfast,
I have something to say.
This is a school, not a graveyard.
I want you to stop telling ghost stories
to scare each other.
If I catch anyone
engaging in such nonsense,
that person will be punished.
Hey, Chatree!
Wait up!
What are you daydreaming about?
Have you ever snuck out of school?
Where to?
Home.
Why would I do that?
School is more fun than at home.
No parents to tell you what to do.
Like hell, it is!
It's hard at first,
but you'll get used to it.
No, I won't.
Do you see what I see?
Geese?
Look again.
Those are goose eggs!
Hold it.
Geese are really protective of their eggs.
There's only one way
to get their eggs.
Hurry up, man.
Hurry up!
I got them!
Chatree.
Your father's on the phone.
Hold on, please.
Okay.
-I'll see you later.
-Okay.
Chatree, grab a seat for us
in the courtyard after dinner.
There's an outdoor cinema tonight.
Have you watched Hungry Ghost 1, 2, and 3?
-I have.
-Me, too.
I've watched them all.
Part two is the best.
HUNGRY GHOST 4
Part one had the female ghost.
Part two had the child ghost, right?
You've got it wrong.
Part three had the female ghost.
Part one had the child ghost.
No, part two was the girl,
and part three was the kid.
-Wrong.
-I told you part three was the girl.
Part one had the female ghost.
Part two had the child ghost.
Part three had the female ghost.
Part one had the child ghost.
Baby, you're so beautiful today.
-Hey!
-Yes, sir?
Where have you been?
Here, swallow this pubic hair.
What?
And chant the eight points of this prayer
to exact revenge on your enemy.
It's so frizzy.
-Can I eat your two buns?
-What?
May the force be with me.
It might work.
Go insane.
-Wait.
-You...
Why did I slap my face?
What? Here comes
the important part, master.
-Sir...
-My hands...
They're moving on their own.
Baby!
-That's right.
-Hey, hold it!
-I didn't mean to--
-You pervert!
Hey, let's go sit
with Tay and his friends.
How did I get here?
The mantra has been loose.
The ghost is free!
He's following me.
Help me.
Help me!
Hey! He's grabbing my leg!
Don't trust me, you idiot!
I'm coming for you.
I'm leaving now.
How about this?
Open the freaking door!
He's still here.
-Let's move.
-He's coming.
-Stop.
-It's his treasure.
I only have one!
No, don't bite it!
Stop! Help me!
-Help me!
-I'll help you.
Don't pass out. How can you do this?
You can't do this to me.
Master.
-Master, wake up.
-He's coming.
-Don't!
-We're not going to make it.
Everyone, hold your breath.
Hey.
Where have you been?
Are you also scared of me?
Like I told you,
I saw a ghost.
I swear.
It looked...
He looked like us.
Sure.
Now you have ghost stories to share.
Don't forget Ms. Pranee's warning
that telling ghost stories
will get you punished.
Do you want to be punished?
Can you still see the ghost right now?
I haven't seen him
since I moved to a different seat.
Do you guys think
it's the kid who drowned in the pool?
Maybe
he's looking for a friend.
Dr. Nui, how can you believe him?
Are you delirious?
You should get some rest
until your fever subsides.
I bet he will wet his bed again tonight.
Chatree.
Daydreaming again?
Have you finished your homework?
Yes, sir.
Then study your textbook.
Chatree Ananpitisook,
your father is on the phone.
Chatree.
Your father called to say that
he can't pick you up this weekend.
-Shoot!
-Yes!
Watch out!
It has been fixed. Do you want it?
You know, we have something in common.
We are invisible to others.
Go ahead.
I don't know how to play.
You don't know how to play?
I'll show you how.
You need to avoid this guy.
Turn right. Go down.
Turn left.
Master Peng.
What?
What's up?
Who is Chatree talking to?
Here, you need to avoid these guys.
Understood?
Shit! He has lost his mind.
What's strange about that?
I talk to myself all the time.
Isn't your dad picking you up?
No, I'm not going home this weekend.
When will your dad come to pick you up?
He stopped to make a delivery first.
He is on his way.
Well...
Can you still see the ghost?
Why did you ask?
I want to see it too.
Let me know if you see it again.
I like this stuff.
My dad's here.
UTAIN COFFIN
See you later.
Hey, what's this button for?
-This one.
-What a noob.
I'll show you how it's done.
Walk. Jump.
Jump.
You lost.
Remember the night you wet your bed?
Are you making fun of me?
No. I have something to confess.
Are you ready?
You were the one who spooked me, Vichien!
What the heck?
I didn't mean to.
You went to the toilet by yourself.
May I have more dessert, please?
Is something wrong with the food?
-May I have more dessert, please?
May I have more dessert, please?
-No, it's good.
-I have finished my dessert.
Pretty lady,
may I have more dessert, please?
Eat more, so you can grow up fast.
All gone.
Are you tired?
Mom, I have to go
and rehearse for Sports Day at school.
All right.
-I'm off then.
-Okay.
Hey.
She's mine, okay?
Why did you bring me here?
You said you wanted
to grow up quickly, right?
This is my treasure trove.
The illustrated guide
to becoming a manly man.
Why was he called in?
PLAYBOY FOR STUDENTS 2
Do you have anything to say for yourself?
I bet she's going to lash him
black and blue.
I think a stickler like Ms. Pranee
put him on her blacklist
and called his parents.
This happens every year.
Don't do this again, understood?
You can leave now.
Guys, he's out.
-Hey, what happened?
-Are you all right?
She didn't punish me or anything.
-What?
How come?
How long has Ms. Pranee
been teaching here?
A long time.
Even before I attended this school.
Why did you ask?
Nothing.
Wait.
Are you sure there's a way out
around here?
Just follow me, all right?
Hey, are you sure about this?
Hey.
How did you get here?
-Namtarn, can I take a picture with you?
-Sure.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
Do you want to take a picture?
Can you hold my baton?
Okay, I'm ready.
Big smile, okay?
Your cheeks look like
they're going to burst.
Okay, one, two, three.
-Can I ask you something?
-Sure.
How did you die?
I died of old age.
I'm serious, you idiot.
Wait a minute. I have to pee.
Do you want to know
why I have been sent here
during the second semester?
Shit. It's already 6 p.m.
Let's hurry back.
Vichien, wait up!
Chatree Ananpitisook,
your father's waiting at the dormitory.
Pen, follow me downstairs.
Don't worry. Everyone's asleep
Where have you been?
What have you been up to?
Why did you do this?
Why didn't you tell me anything.
Don't do this again.
Did you hear me? Don't do this ever again!
Be a good boy.
Chatree,
Ms. Pranee asked me to bring this to you!
Here, your father left this for you.
Where did you go? Your dad was here.
What about you?
Where the heck have you been?
You said you're invisible to other people.
What about you?
Do you care about
anyone else but yourself?
Hey.
If you've got something good,
you should share it with us.
Why would I do that?
Come on.
We're friends.
Friends always
share things with friends, right?
Let's make up, all right?
MEN'S DESIRE
VICHAI
I bet the new boy's a faggot.
What?
I don't know. He seems like a fairy.
Maybe
that porn magazine
has many naked men photos.
That's why he won't share it with us.
No wonder
Ms. Pranee let him off so easily.
And kept the magazine for herself.
Pok, lend me your sima lotion.
I'm getting a rash again.
Here.
Damn! Do you have big balls
like a dinosaur?
How come it's all gone?
Nui, do you have any?
No, but I have formalin. Do you want some?
Save it for your dad!
Do you want it?
Yes, thanks.
Hold on.
Do you have any sima lotion?
POL. CAPT. VICHAI CHAMCHONG
SENTENCED TO PRISON FOR CORRUPTION
FAMILY PLEADS FOR MERCY FROM THE JUDGE
POL. CAPT. VICHAI CHAMCHONG SHOCKED
KNOWING HE'S GOING TO JAIL FOR 25 YEARS
RESULTING TO BAD HEALTH
Chatree, your mom's on the phone.
Mom?
Ton, it's me, Dad.
Ton.
Pen no longer stays at our house.
Why didn't you pick up the phone
when I called?
If you think that I sent you away
because of Pen
then you misunderstood.
Well...
Do you like your new school?
STUDENT DORMITORY
VICHIEN
You have to stay here every night
because I'm sleeping in your bed, right?
Hurry up, but don't take a picture.
-Hurry up.
-That's enough.
-What's wrong with him?
-Did he faint?
No, I think he sniffed the ether
used to knock out the rabbits.
-Hey.
-What should we do?
-He is unconscious.
-What's happening?
Don't crowd him. Back off, boys.
Chalermphol, how many times
have I told you not to sniff ether?
-He's regaining consciousness.
-He's still alive.
-He woke up.
It's like I died and came back to life.
Don't exaggerate.
You were only out for a few seconds.
But I really felt like I died.
And I had trouble breathing.
And everything was dark.
And I saw...
That's so insane.
If anyone wants to know
what lies beyond death,
feel free to consult me.
Stop it, you fatty.
I don't give any shit about your stuff.
Gosh, I'm starving now.
Let's go. I'm starving.
Shit!
Vichien, Don't jump!
Now you know
how I died.
Why did you drown yourself?
Who said I drowned myself?
It's stupider than that.
That day,
we didn't want to stop swimming.
It was getting dark.
Help...
Help me!
Guys, Jira is drowning.
-Where is he?
-Idiots! I fooled you!
You were faking it?
Gosh!
Have you done your homework already?
I forgot. It's due first period too.
-Help me.
-Which subject?
Get up.
-Vichien is drowning.
-Help me!
Help me!
Hey.
-Go ahead and save him.
-Help me!
But he could be faking it.
Help me!
We all know the trick.
No one is going to believe you.
Hey, it's 6 p.m.
Let's go back to our dorm.
-Let's go.
-All right.
I'm leaving now.
How come
they say that
Ms. Pranee was related to your death?
You read that newspaper, right?
POL. CAPT. VICHAI CHAMCHONG
SENTENCED TO PRISON
It's about my father.
Ms. Pranee didn't want me to find out.
Vichien!
What are you doing?
Who gave you permission to enter here?
Come here. Why did you do this?
I'll hit you until I break my hand.
You can't do this!
I just wanted to read the news
about my father.
Unfortunately,
Ms. Pranee caught me.
Ms. Pranee,
Vichien hasn't returned to the dorm yet.
Before my accident,
I managed to sneak back in
to steal the newspaper.
What?
Ever since then,
Ms. Pranee has thought that
my death
was her fault.
Why do you have to drown yourself
over and over again like this?
I don't know.
How much longer
will you be stuck like this?
I don't know that either.
But it's really cold
at the bottom of the pool.
See? I told you.
It must be the boy
who drowned in the pool.
I've seen ghosts like this before.
At my old house...
UTAIN COFFIN
a motorcycle crashed
rounding the corner one night.
The driver died instantly.
After that,
I would hear the same motorbike
skid around the corner almost every night.
As if
the spirit hadn't been reborn yet,
so it had to re-enact its death
over and over.
What then?
We moved the heck out of there.
No. How do we help the spirits get reborn
so they stop re-enacting their own deaths?
Ghosts and humans
live in separate worlds.
To help a ghost, you must be a ghost.
To be a ghost, you have to die first.
Unless you can split your spirit
from your body.
Do you want to try?
Are you crazy?
Why would you want to die?
Ton,
promise me that you won't do it.
Can you promise me that?
Dr. Nui, what the hell are you looking at?
Something's wrong with Chatree.
He seems strange.
What the heck?
The other day, you said he wasn't strange.
I know.
But today, he seems strange.
Maybe he's going to jump off the building.
How the hell
can he jump through the grille?
Can you see that water tank?
I had climbed to the top before.
The view is even better from up there.
I'll take you there someday.
Chatree
has disappeared.
Playing during dinner again?
I'll teach you a lesson with this stick.
-Chatree.
Chatree, what's wrong?
-What's wrong with him?
-Chatree.
-Are you okay?
TOO MUCH INHALATION IS DANGEROUS
He killed himself, right?
-No.
-Don't die, Chatree.
I think he split his spirit from his body.
What are you talking about?
Splitting spirits from what?
He told me
he wanted to help his friend
that drowned in the pool.
I cluelessly suggested he could do that
if he splits his spirit from his body.
Trust me.
We have to take him to the old pool.
Ms. Pranee, Chatree killed himself.
What?
-Vichien is drowning.
-Help me!
Help me.
Here.
What's that for?
Why are you so stupid?
What do we do now?
You said you're invisible to other people.
What about you?
Do you care about
anyone else but yourself?
Hey, let me out!
Are you still mad at your friends
for not saving you from drowning?
No, I'm not mad anymore.
What about you?
Do you still want to run away from school?
No, not anymore.
If I did,
I would run straight to Namtarn's embrace.
I know what you're thinking.
Don't get me started!
I saw the way you looked at her, too.
I've had my heart set on her for years.
When will we visit her again?
Ton.
I've got to leave now.
Hey, Chatree woke up!
Chatree woke up!
-Chatree.
-How are you, Chatree?
-Are you okay?
Are you okay?
-You're fine now.
-Hey.
He woke up.
Ms. Pranee, Chatree is fine now.
CHATREE
I never knew our school was this big.
Why are you so amazed
by the size of our school?
I know from experience. Ms. Pranee
made me run around the school before.
That's awesome.
I'm even having goosebumps!
Do you want to fall down there?
Take it easy.
I won't tease you again.
Ton.
Why didn't you tell Ms. Pranee
the truth about Vichien?
Right. You made us all get punished.
I don't think she would believe me.
But
we all really believe you.
If you happen to see another ghost,
feel free to consult me, okay?
But don't consult me, okay?
Let me be the first one
to consult you then, Dr, Nui.
Why the heck do you speak with a lisp?
Chatree Ananpitisook,
please meet your parents in the dorm.
I'm leaving now!
See you guys next year.
-Damn.
Good luck, man.
-See you.
-Good luck.
Ton, I want to see the swimming pool.
Be patient, Tor.
Let him pack his things first.
-Okay, but then can we see it?
-Yes.
Have you been eating enough food?
You've gotten darker.
You lost weight as well.
You've been playing outside
too much, haven't you?
Mom, you're embarrassing me.
Why?
When you're older,
I won't get to hug you anymore.
Tor, stay around here.
Let's get your bags, dear.
Dad.
I like this school.
Ms. Pranee.
Vichien didn't kill himself.
His drowning
was really an accident.
Vichien asked me to apologize
for breaking your record player that day.
He knows that
you were concerned about him.
Thank you, Ms. Pranee,
for always taking care of us.
Goodbye.
I still remember the first day
my father took me home.
It was a Friday afternoon,
and everything seemed normal.
But one thing that had changed was me.
I was two centimeters taller.
It will take a while
before I become a teenager.
Being friends with Vichien
has taught me many things.
I couldn't tell
if there would be other fun things
happening in the next semester or not.
But I could tell that
I wanted to see my friends again
because I learned that
if we have one good friend
who sticks by our side,
the hard times in our lives
would get better
and that takes only some breath.
FOR MY BELOVED FRIENDS AND TEACHERS
FROM ASSUMPTION COLLEGE SRIRACHA
Subtitle translation by Lee Chatametikool