What happened, Kade?
Tae has gone to Korea on a business trip.
He was supposed to be back yesterday.
But he disappeared
and I can't contact him.
Has he ever disappeared like this before?
Never.
He's never turned off his phone like this.
How do you want me to help you?
I don't know.
Tum, you're a police officer.
Can you tell me what to do?
Can you send me his flight details?
I'll check with the airline first.
Give me his hotel address in Korea, too.
I'll check if there
was an accident or anything.
Does his mom know about this?
I already called her this morning.
I didn't want her to be the last to know.
Tae won't be gone for too long.
He'll be back.
Don't worry.
Tum will take care of it.
Okay.
Mac, did you drive Tae to the airport?
The day he flew to Korea.
Yes, I did.
Did he tell you to pick him up
when he gets back?
No, he didn't.
He didn't tell me anything.
Did you see anything unusual, Mac?
How unusual?
You really don't know...
or are you hiding something for your boss?
I'm a driver.
My job is to drive.
Men.
When they're not with us,
they're not our husbands.
We can't control them all the time.
What am I supposed to do?
Just let them be.
There's no such thing as trust.
See what you like to see, Kade.
And you don't need to know everything.
I'm trying.
I've never pried into his business.
We both give each other privacy.
Are you sure?
What about the maid you just fired?
You don't need
a young and beautiful housemaid.
Get the old one with kids...
to avoid trouble.
If you don't,
you've to wash your dishes yourself.
Not on the lips.
If not on the lips...
then can I kiss somewhere else?
Excuse me.
Don't you have to drive mom?
Tum is taking care of her now.
Do you want me to do anything else?
There's no work at the office.
Boss hasn't come back yet anyway.
Oh...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to worry you.
It's okay.
Can you take me to Tae's office?
Sure.
Let me get changed first.
Excuse me.
-Miss Kade is here.
-Oh!
-Hello.
-Hi.
Can I take a look at Tae's office?
Of course.
Boss didn't come home, did he?
That's why she's here.
Have you seen him here today?
No, I haven't.
I haven't seen him since the day
you dropped him at the airport.
Same here.
Our boss's wife looks so intimidating.
When she looked at me,
I was afraid to look back.
It has to be a woman like her
to win boss's heart.
Beautiful, smart...
and big tits.
It's an electricity bill.
But the address is a house in Chonburi.
I never knew about a house there.
Have you ever driven him there, Mac?
Never.
Can you take me there, please?
Sure.
Do you know exactly where this house is?
Do you want to take a look
at the bill again?
It's okay.
I know how to get there.
Do you drive to Chonburi often?
Just passed by.
Boss came for work often.
Aren't you going to tell Tum about this?
About what?
About where we're going to.
We don't even know whose house it is.
If he knows, he's going to tell Tae's mom.
Let's not make her worried.
Perhaps I've troubled you
too much already.
Not at all. It's my job.
Thank you.
Do you want me to turn on the radio?
Please don't.
Just talk to me like this...
it helps clear my mind.
Let me help you.
Here.
Okay.
-Here you are.
-Thank you.
Do you think there's someone in there?
I hope so.
Tae!
Kade...
I found a nice house design.
Look.
The beach house
with big glass windows.
You're going to love it.
-Which one?
-Here. See?
Listen,
if I finish this project,
I might have the money
to build this house for you.
We can wait until I get pregnant.
Let's try again now.
Right here?
What are you doing?
We've already broken into someone's house.
Stealing some food
shouldn't be much of a problem.
I forgot.
We didn't stop by anywhere to eat.
Let's have some cereal.
Is it the boss's house?
I think so.
Here are his phone and credit card bills.
Maybe he rented it...
because he wouldn't have any money
to buy this house.
You'd better eat something.
It will make you feel better.
You are a very polite driver,
you know that?
No wonder Tae hired you.
I can't do anything better than driving.
Is this blazer a uniform?
It looks good on you.
I've never seen other drivers
wearing a blazer like that.
If I'm not wearing this,
they'll cut my salary.
Does a driver like you...
get lost sometimes?
If I get lost too often,
they'll cut my salary, too.
I mean getting lost on purpose.
Like getting lost...
in a place you can't tell
anybody about...
or in some secret places.
If I found Tae here in this house...
with his significant other...
what do you think I should do?
There's something
at the bottom of the pool.
Do you want to get it out?
I'm going to get wet
if I get into the pool.
I don't have a spare set of clothes.
Alright.
Can you go and get it for me?
I'm going to get wet
if I get into the pool.
I don't have a spare set of clothes.
Get in without any clothes, then.
Are you kidding me?
I'll get you a towel.
A key?
Why was it in the pool?
Can I have the towel?
I found a VIP card for his spa membership.
There's a phone number here.
Can you call to ask if Tae's there?
Do you think it's a good idea?
Jasmine Spa and Massage.
Can I have your membership number?
What's that?
Your membership number on the card.
JASMINE SPA &amp; MASSAGE
Three, eight, zero, six.
Hello, Tae.
Would you like to confirm the booking
at 4 p.m. today?
Yes.
Jacuzzi room, right?
With the same staff?
Yes.
Alrighty!
He might be there at 4 p.m.
Where have you been?
I went out for a cigarette.
Smoking?
Don't you know that
you can't smoke during work hours?
Mind your own business.
How many staff does Tae want today?
Today...
it's just you,
no one else is in this early.
After this, I'm out.
How come? You'd better stay on call.
I can't.
I already came four times yesterday.
I need to go back to the gym.
My muscles are shrinking.
Never mind muscles.
Don't let your dick shrink.
Or else you will lose your job.
Come on.
My dick doesn't shrink easily.
Do you want to check it out?
Stop it, before I puke.
Wait in bed.
Let me get back to the reception.
-Hey!
-Wait!
Wait. Let me ask you something.
Ask me what?
Where is Tae?
I don't know. I'm waiting for him, too.
Does he come here often?
Why don't you answer her?
Why are you asking? Are you a cop?
No...
but Tae is my husband.
Do you know what this place is?
A spa?
A spa or a brothel?
You've come here often, haven't you?
-Watch your mouth, asshole!
-Wait.
Why did Tae pick a male masseuse?
I'm telling you nothing.
We can't share clients' information.
Give me a minute.
-I'll take care of it.
-Hey!
What is this? Why are you bullying me?
Can you talk now?
Shame on you.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
And there is a price for everything.
Tell me everything.
We've got a new boy in town, sir.
Tae made a house call once
to his old apartment in Pattanakarn.
Maybe it turned him on.
Do you still have the address?
This way.
I think that's enough for today.
Tae wouldn't be here anyway.
Did you lose something?
You were born into a good family...
and a wealthy life.
But your palm tells...
that you will lose...
something important.
What should I do?
What was it that you lost?
What's the matter?
How come we can't talk on the phone?
Well...
I must show you some photos.
I can't send them to you
because I don't want them to leak.
What photos?
May I go to the restroom?
A client of mine hired me
to follow her husband.
I took a lot of photos of him, everywhere.
Until I remembered...
he is your friend.
Who is he?
Why do you carry a gun in your bag?
What is wrong with you?
Nothing's fucking wrong with me.
I'm legally his wife...
and you're...
just a driver...
that he happened to have sex with.
You can say anything you want.
But the truth is still the truth.
Do you know about the truth?
Well...
tell me the truth, Mac.
Your husband...
stayed with you...
because of your money.
He doesn't love you.
He loves me.
Do you understand?
He never loved you. He loves me.
If he loves you that much...
why did he put you in a place like this?
Why?
I want you to hear it from Tae...
which one he will choose.
And who he built...
that beach house for?
Do you really believe...
that he would...
leave me...
for a driver like you?
TUM
Tum.
Maybe he found Tae.
Do you want to talk to him?
Hello, Tum.
Where are you, Kade?
I'm out running an errand.
Do you have any updates?
Kade, I happen to know
that you hired someone to follow Tae.
That person used to work for me.
He recognized Tae from the photos he took.
Have you seen the photos?
I've seen them.
Tae has been seeing a lot of people.
But it's a surprise
he's seeing this person.
It looks serious.
Who are you talking about?
I mean his driver.
You knew all about it.
I was with you everywhere.
I was with you all day.
And you knew all about it.
What do you want?
You forgot this at the shop.
Thank you.
How come you look so pale and sweaty?
Um...
Oh...
that pretty lady, right?
I'm not going to bother you then.
You know where Tae is, right?
Do you want some, bitch?
I don't take leftovers, bitch!
Try my fucking leftovers then.
Where is Tae?
Mac.
Don't do this. I want to rest.
Why are you avoiding me?
I'm not avoiding you. I'm taking a nap.
I was away for so many days.
Didn't you miss me?
Tell me.
-No.
-Did you miss me?
But I missed you, Mac.
I missed you every day.
Let me kiss you.
What is all this? Come on, let's talk.
No need to talk,
it won't make any difference.
I don't want to talk anymore.
Maybe you don't want a gift from Korea.
What a shame. No one wants my gift.
-What is it?
-Guess!
I don't want to guess. Give it to me.
I thought you were taking a nap,
weren't you?
Give it to me.
Tae!
Don't do this again.
Let's move in together.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
Move in with you to be what?
If I have to live like a mistress...
these keys mean nothing at all.
I'll take care of everything.
You always say this.
I don't believe you anymore.
Give me more time.
I'll tell Kade everything
when I get back to her.
I had to let you marry her...
even though we were seeing
each other long before.
I had to see you with her every day.
I had to put up with that...
because you needed it for business.
But now I can't do it anymore.
You have to let me go.
No.
I'm not letting you go anywhere.
We're going to live here together.
I can't pretend to be her husband anymore.
Is Tae here?
Follow me if you want to find out.
Hello, can I take your order?
Whiskey on the rocks.
And for the gentleman?
Same, please.
Stop playing games. Where is he?
You've lost your husband...
let's have a drink to relax.
Where is Tae?
Go and look around.
Do you want to drink with me?
No, thanks.
Excuse me.
Do you know
where the woman who was with me is?
Maybe she went to the restroom.
Aren't you having your drink, sir?
No, I'm not.
Try this one,
it tastes better than whiskey.
No, thanks.
I don't drink. I don't want to get drunk.
Where is the restroom?
You look so cute.
You don't drink. What about a smoke?
I don't smoke.
No alcohol, no cigarettes.
What else do you want?
We got it all here.
No, thanks.
You don't want anything.
Why did you come here?
I'm looking for someone.
Can I be someone for you?
No, you can't.
You can't keep saying "no" to hurt people,
you know that?
Where is the restroom?
Have some of these
and I'll take you to the restroom.
Don't tell me you don't like sweets.
What is all this?
You don't like women, do you?
Can I have some water?
Where is the restroom?
I can't pretend to be her husband anymore.
I'm only yours.
Do you really mean it?
I mean it.
Hey!
Do you really have to go?
I can't cancel on my mom.
I don't want you to go.
I'll come back soon.
I need to get my stuff from the apartment.
Hey!
You want to kill me now?
Don't you want to see your husband?
Where is Tae?
Did you hear me? Where is Tae?
He's been waiting for you
down at the beach.
Tae!
-Let go.
-Why did you kill him?
Kade...
how did you get here?
Nice house.
It's the house I built for you, baby.
I was planning to surprise you
on our anniversary.
This must be...
the key you were planning to give me,
right?
Oh, yes.
You knew everything,
so it's not a surprise anymore.
I caught you like this...
but you're still lying to me.
I'm not lying.
Do you want him to be your driver...
or your wife?
What are you talking about?
I saw you fuck him on that couch.
Just fucking.
I don't even love him.
It's just sex, Kade.
I hope you understand.
I don't want to understand
a liar like you.
Hello, Tum. What's the matter?
Tum...
what are you trying to tell me?
You don't need to tell me that.
I know how Tae is.
I even know what happened
between you and him.
I just didn't want to talk about it.
If he chooses to live like this...
I'm not going to warn him anymore.
If he hadn't married Kade...
he wouldn't have come this far.
Did you find him?
Subtitle translation by
Somborworn Saksopit