Just tell me honestly,
What do you really feel about me?
I'm just a bodyguard.
No right to be something else.
What's just happened?
I don't know.
I'll tell dad I want another guy.
-Young master...
-I don't want you...
to be my bodyguard anymore.
Was it your doing?
I've warned you, Sakkhee.
Don't mess with my son.
Dad said when everything's done.
He'll send another guy.
Young master.
What is it?
Hey.
How did you get it?
What were you thinking?
They were gifts from you.
They mean a lot to me.
I'll help.
Don't take it off.
How is everything?
I've contacted and gathered
all our guys, sir.
Good.
Since I have nothing left to lose,
you'll lose everything too, Phu.
Are you free today, Toktaeng, Juno?
Absolutely, why?
I want to ask you out for a date.
Really?
Cool.
So, we'll all go together,
as a double date, alright?
A double date? Yes.
Do you have a problem with that?
Do you know where the restroom is, Juno?
A restroom, over there.
Excuse me for a bit.
Juno, can you take me there?
You guys wait here.
Then we'll go in together.
Okay.
Why are you doing this, young master?
What? I'm going out for a date.
In fact,
I want to be alone with Toktaeng.
But I knew that
you have to butt in anyway.
So I invited Juno to come along.
It's obvious that she has a crush on you.
You've never had a lover.
Isn't it great though?
If you order, I'll do it.
If I order you to go to hell,
will you do it?
You can try that, young master.
Sorry to make you wait.
It's alright.
I think we should part here.
There are a lot of cute backgrounds
to take photos with.
Toktaeng, do you want to take a look,
or order some snacks first?
Sounds good, I want to take a photo.
Sun, can you take a photo for me?
Let's go.
It looks nice here.
Can we sit down and take a selfie?
Then we'll catch up with them later.
-Sit here.
-Alright.
Let's take a selfie.
Sky, look at the camera.
One, two, three.
Again.
Here, Sky, look here.
One, two, three.
Hey, it's cute.
Sky...
Sky?
What?
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I'll take a photo for a sec.
Alright.
Sun...
Sun?
You're sweating a lot.
I'll give you a tissue.
Toktaeng, I'm feeling unwell.
I'll go back first.
Wait, Sky!
Sky!
Please stop doing this, young master.
It's dangerous.
You'll always find me anyway.
Young master,
you can do whatever you like,
but don't put yourself in danger.
Alright, I'll go back to Toktaeng.
Let go.
No, sir.
We should go home.
I don't want to.
Tok...
Young master.
What do you want from me?
I have to protect you.
I didn't mean why you dragged me here.
I ask you, what do you want
to do with my heart?
The reason you took care of me...
Was it just because you're my bodyguard?
Tell me,
you protected me,
did everything for me,
you don't have any feelings for me.
I...
You what?
You tell me.
Tell me,
that you also have feelings for me,
that you love me.
Say it!
Say it, say you love me.
You say it now.
♪There is no one else,♪
♪who would trade their heart,♪
♪to get hurt instead for
not loving enough.♪
♪I’d do it without having to ask,♪
♪even losing everything.♪
♪I'd do it for the rest of my life♪
♪I’d trade my heart
to protect you from getting hurt.♪
♪I’m willing to do all things
just to make you smile,♪
♪and get to rise up again.♪
♪Trade your sorrows with me...♪
I'm sorry.
♪for you to be yourself again
I’m willing to trade my happiness.♪
Was that your answer?
♪I cannot tolerate seeing
your tears again.♪
♪Please have my heart
if this could save you.♪
Stop!
Hey, stop it, be still.
Let go of me.
Young master!
Sun!
-Go.
-Sun...
Young master.
Sun, wake up.
Sun.
Mr. Bank, Mr. Pitch?
How did you get here?
I've seen Juno posted on her FB
that you guys are dating.
So, I followed you here.
What happened? Who did that to you?
Sky...
Sky was kidnapped.
What?
I've downloaded a tracking application
on his mobile.
I'll follow them.
Hey, hang on, I'll go with you.
Sky is also my friend.
Then, we'll go help too.
But, I think you two should go back first.
It's dangerous. We'll handle this.
-My car is this way.
-Go.
Asshole!
Be polite to your elders.
Didn't your dad teach you that?
You think my dad will let you get away,
doing this to me.
Actually, I want him to know.
He should realise what he would get
from burning off my factory.
Sakkhee?
Yeah, it's me.
You know what?
Your father was a pain in the ass.
This time, I'll make him buried alive.
Have you gone nuts? What will you do?
How's it going, Sakkhee?
Where have you been hidden?
It's not important where I am, it's all...
Who I'm with.
-Dad!
-Sky.
Dad, help me, dad!
Sakkhee, what did you do to him?
Dad, help me.
Sakkhee!
If you hurt him, I'll kill you.
Before I die,
your son's already a cold body, Phu.
Don't worry.
I'll leave his body for you.
If you still remember his face though.
Sakkhee!
Boss, Sun just called me.
He's heading to help young master.
Good, tell him to send his location.
You gather all our guys.
I'll end all of this.
Yes, sir.
Boss, boss.
The nearby factory is on fire.
Why the heck is it on fire?
You two, guard here, the rest follow me.
Hey, it was really his plan.
He dares come to get beaten.
Aren't you too bold for your size?
Hey, where you think you going?
The exit is this way.
Thanks, bro.
You can't escape now.
Are you really going to do this?
Alright.
His moves look scary.
Loser!
I'll teach you
how we do in a real fight.
Ouch, it hurts, bro.
You alright?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Young master.
Why aren't they back yet?
Yeah, bro.
So, you're so low to the point
you use a weapon.
Don't you know, this knife...
also stabbed through that loser's heart.
You and your master should be happy,
to die by this very same knife.
You three, go look around there.
Yes, boss!
You think luring me out
by the fire will work, huh?
I double-cross you.
Your bodyguard, huh.
My underling will beat him
to the ground.
You wait just a bit,
I'll let him cut off his head for you.
Dad!
Bastard!
Hey.
Young master!
There are gunshots, bro.
Why isn't Sky's dad here yet?
What should we do, bro?
You wait here, I'll go.
Hold on, bro.
It's dangerous.
I'll go too.
Where you think you're running off to?
Hey, you bastard.
You can't get away from me.
I'm not afraid.
Retard, what a mouth you have.
Earlier, I planned to kill you
in front of your dad.
But you little wench, should die here.
I'll picture how your dad's
gone nuts later.
Young master.
Young master!
Young master...
Young master, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Let's get out of here.
Hurry up, find them.
Go!
Hey, that way.
Hey!
Stop. Stop...
Stop there!
I said stop!
Where do you think you're running off to?
Hey, over there.
Come on, try me.
Come on.
Go.
Hey!
Where are you going?
Hey, Pitch, what do we do?
Come here.
Watch out!
Get out of the way!
Get him!
Young master!
Hey, stay back.
Stay back.
Young master, watch out!
Stay down.
Sun.
Sun...
Stay with me.
Sun.
Go, Shain!
Stay with me.
Young master.
You've got to be okay, Sun,
stay with me.
You'll be alright.
Don't leave me, Sun.
Sky!
Sun, Sun!
You've got to be alright.
Sun!
Sun, wake up, Sun!
I don't want this, Sun.
How can I live without you, Sun.
Doctor!
How is he?
The bullet didn't injure any main organs.
But the patient has lost a lot of blood.
The hospital is trying to find
more blood for him.
Take my blood,
I used to donate my blood.
Me, too.
You can't.
Patient has a very special blood-type,
called "RH-null" or Golden Blood.
What is it, doc?
Normally, our blood-type...
are O, B, AB,
either positive or negative.
But golden blood is AB Rh-negative.
There are only 20,000
out of 70 million people.
How do you know all that?
That doesn't matter.
The thing is...
How can we find the rare blood for Sun?
Right, bro, where do we find that?
Doctor.
I have golden blood.
I'm afraid that's not enough.
Because the patient needs a lot of blood.
I'll take my leave.
Sky.
How are you?
Dad.
Sun.
There's not enough blood to help Sun.
Even if I donated my blood,
it will be hard to save him.
You don't need to give him your blood.
How can I not?
Sun also has a rare blood-type.
And he's dying because he saved me.
Calm down, Sky.
Listen to me, Sky.
Sun will be alright.
I've already contacted the staff
to bring the blood Sun's been donated.
He's on his way here.
Sun will be alright.
Has Sun been donating blood?
It's the reason I adopted him
in the first place.
Reason?
You adopted Sun
to keep his blood for me?
Since the day we lost your mother.
I swear...
they won't happen ever again.
Are you ready?
Where are you going, Sky?
Come here.
Mom.
Mom, wake up!
Mom...
Doctor.
I'm sorry for your loss.
We've done our best for her.
Due to too much blood loss...
Moreover, her blood-type is very rare.
We've performed our best.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Yes.
Thank you.
Your mother's blood-type
is also golden blood.
I swear it won't happen to you.
I tried to find someone
who had the same blood-type as you.
Then, I found Sun.
Have you ever considered his feelings?
Sky, everything that I did is for you.
Sun is also a human being.
He's alive and has feelings too.
What you did to him
is like a cave animal.
I just wanted to protect you, Sky.
I ordered him to learn self-defense.
You know what for?
To protect you.
I don't need that, dad.
It's all because of you.
Sun doesn't get to live like others.
If I didn't do that, would you have
spare blood to use, Sky.
Why don't you understand?
Your blood is very rare.
How precious is it?
More importantly,
Sun is willing to do that too.
He agreed to donate his blood
every three months.
You've got to understand me.
Do I have to be happy
knowing that how Sun...
think of his life as nothing,
nothing but only his blood.
Sky!
Everything has been taken care of.
Good.
Boss, do you want me to escort
young master back first?
Even if you drag him, he wouldn't go.
I've never seen young master
acting like that.
Me, too.
How's Sun?
Still unconscious.
But over all,
he's over the critical stage.
We couldn't believe it
when Bank told us.
Did the doctor say anything
about when he'll be awake?
Hey, guys, a man like Sun
will definitely get better soon.
Right, Pitch?
He won't die that easily.
How are you, Sky?
Have you gotten enough sleep?
Right now, I'm alright.
I want Sun to regain consciousness soon.
Sky.
You've been watching him for many days.
You should go home and have some rest.
I don't want to.
Young master, you should take some rest
before you get sick too.
I said I won't go, you hear me?
Alright, son.
Alright.
I'll bring you some clothes.
Sun.
I love you.
Can you open your eyes?
Please, I beg you.
Please, wake up.
I'll go to the hospital, bye.
Wait, Sky.
Sakkhee's already been caught.
I think you don't need
a bodyguard anymore.
When he gets better,
I'll bring him back to work with me.
No, dad, Sun should stay here with me.
Sky.
You didn't want a bodyguard at first,
did you?
You said you want your freedom.
But now,
I want to finish the school with him, dad.
I know, now you feel attached to Sun.
Because he saved your life.
But don't forget that it's also his job.
I don't want you to cross the boundary.
You have no right to decide
for me or Sun.
I didn't decide for anyone. It's a fact.
He's brought up for that reason.
Do you only see him as your pet?
Both Sun and I will make a decision
for ourselves.
Bro, I took notes
from the classes for you.
Here.
Hey.
Are you listening to me?
What did you say?
I said I took notes
from today's lectures.
Are you alright? You look absent-minded.
I think you should have some rest.
You look like shit.
I'm alright.
I want to watch him
until he's conscious.
I know you're worried about him.
But if he knows you are like this,
he'd be sad.
You know how much he cares for you.
He cares about me
only because it's his job.
Not like how I care about him.
Thanks for the notes.
Yeah.
It's been so long.
Why isn't he waking up?
He's been severely injured.
It's not fair.
Why did he have to take the shot?
Though, he's a distant relative
and also his bodyguard.
What if...
Sun never regains consciousness?
Hey, it's not like you to say that.
The Juno I know...
always has hope.
Thanks.
Sun.
Sun, you've got to come back.
Or else I'll give you a kiss
to wake you up like a sleeping beauty.
If my dad won't approve,
will you die for the sake of true love?
Well, you can try dying first.
When you get discharged,
can we go on a date?
Sun and I, we're in love.
You might feel bad,
and responsible for his life.
Because he took the bullet for you.
Sun also has a heart, dad.
He's not a thing nor a pet.
You boldly dare to mess
with my only son, huh?
Get rid of him!
♪Trade your sorrows with me
if it could save you,♪
♪for you to be yourself again
I’m willing to trade my happiness.♪
♪Trade it with me your miserable heart.♪
♪I cannot tolerate seeing
your tears again.♪
♪Please have my heart
if this could save you.♪