Say it, that you also love me.
Young master!
Young master.
Watch out! Young master!
I don't want things
to be any more out of control.
Do you only think of him as your pet?
Both Sun and I will decide
what is best for ourselves.
Young master...
I'm checking in to see if you're alright.
Truth is, Sun being like this...
is actually all my fault.
Sun is willing to do everything
for you, young master.
He's just doing his job.
After all that,
don't you understand, young master?
What he actually feels about you.
I'm just his boss.
He did what dad ordered him to do.
Including the blood donation.
Even if boss didn't order him,
he's still willing to donate his blood
for you, young master.
Don't get my hopes up.
I just want you to know that.
He dared putting his life at risk.
Because for him,
Young master is the center
of his universe.
Without you, he wouldn't want to live.
You don't have to believe me though,
but I want you to take a look
at this notebook.
Whether it was just his duty
like you think or not.
I'll take my leave now.
♪Tremble, you make me feel tremble♪
♪just realize what it is♪
♪It's the love that blooming
and coming to me♪
♪it begins with you and our times♪
♪just you and me until now♪
♪it's coming, dearest love♪
♪the love that doesn't hurt anyone♪
♪love comes to me, enormously♪
♪Overflowing my heart♪
What are you doing?
Come on.
Wet hair in front of the AC,
do you want to get sick?
Well, what a blessing to have
such a kind boyfriend.
Who said I'm kind?
I don't want you to get sick,
because I'm sick of taking care of you.
What's the matter?
You look troubled.
It's about Sky.
Since that incident,
he's been watching Sun all the time.
He looks very worn-out.
What should I do?
You just have to be a good friend.
Listen to him.
Maybe that's the only thing he needs.
Wow, I didn't think you were so capable.
Was that a compliment?
Of course, my boyfriend is very cute,
how can I not praise him?
Come here, I'll give you a reward.
One more time.
What to reward?
I don't want it.
Come here,
come get your reward.
What are you doing?
You want to play hard to get? Alright.
So you have all those feelings for me,
why don't you just confess it to me.
Can you wake up and tell me now?
Wake up and confess
your true feelings to me, Sun.
Say that you also love me.
Like how I love you.
Can I have yours?
And you can keep mine.
Why?
That represents my heart.
This represents yours.
That represents my heart,
and this represents yours.
If you're not here,
what's the meaning
of this other half, Sun.
Can you wake up Sun?
I'm not ready to lose you now.
Young master.
Sun!
Don't disappear on me again.
I don't know what to do, Bank.
When Sun gets better,
Dad would want to take him back.
What's the reason
you don't want to let him go?
Because I love him.
I thought so.
Hold on.
You knew?
Well, Sky. I eat rice, not grass.
I'm not the only one who knows.
Hey, do you know about me and Pitch?
What?
Don't tell me.
Hey, when did you guys get together?
Anyway, that's not the main point here.
It's about you and Sun.
What are you going to do?
It's not that easy to find someone
who can risk his life for you.
I know.
I've been worried.
Don't think too much.
Let's go.
How is it?
Do you feel better breathing fresh air?
Yes, I'm feeling much better.
Although, you don't have
to bother taking care of me.
Don't say that.
I'm willing to do this.
Futhurmore,
I have something to talk to you.
I love you, Sun.
I want you to honestly tell me.
Do you feel the same way?
Young master.
There, I order you, don't lie.
I love you, Young master.
If possible, I want to be with you,
Not only as a bodyguard
or a made-up relation.
I also want to be with you.
Not as your young master.
But as your lover.
If you don't mind,
I want to be with you...
as long as you want.
What if I want you
for the rest of my life?
I'm...
more than... please.
From now on, call me Sky.
I will be your Sky forever.
Yes,
You are my Sky.
Dad.
Hey, Sky.
Why don't you call me?
Coming all the way here,
what's the matter?
I have something to beg of you.
Can you let Sun live with me?
Sky, you're not listening to me.
We're done with that.
I don't want to talk anymore.
I want Sun to continue living with me.
I love him.
And he also loves me.
You see, he's willing
to risk his life for me.
Also I'm willing to risk
my life for him too.
Isn't this enough?
How many times
do you want me to say this?
Sun was just doing his job.
He wasn't just doing his job.
He was following his heart.
Stop fooling yourself.
You just feel guilty
and responsible for his life.
Because he took the bullet for you.
Can you stop thinking for me?
Listen to what I have to say,
Sun and I, we love each other.
Whether you approve of this or not.
Sun is the one for me.
Anyhow, he has to come back
and work with me.
Immediately, when he gets better.
And you, your only duty is to study hard.
You can't do this.
Go back to your house.
Go back!
I've never thought you'd be this mean.
You raised him up
just because you want his blood?
You also look down on him.
Then, why did you have
to make him call you father?
If you just want to use him?
Sun also has a heart.
He's not a thing nor a pet.
Bank!
This way.
Hey girls, you come so early.
What about you?
You are with Pitch all the time.
Is something going on?
We're lover.
Hey, you.
Are you for real?
Why? You don't believe me?
Alright.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Why? When we're at home
you didn't even tell me to stop.
If he's home,
he wouldn't tell me to stop.
Is this a revenge?
No more.
Oh, are you surprised?
Don't be surprised, don't be.
Other than us, there's one more.
Is it good?
It's an apple from Korea.
Yummy.
She's very happy to know
that you're awake.
Did the doctor tell you
when you can get discharged?
Have to get checked one more time,
then I'm good to go.
Great. I've been missing you.
When you get discharged,
let's go on a date.
I can't.
Why?
I already have someone I love.
You mean...
Yeah, I love Sky.
I'm sorry.
Good for you.
Then, I'll leave Sun to Sky.
If he's hurt again,
I won't forgive you.
Then, I'll leave Sky to you, Sun.
There, we should get going.
When you get better,
can you run away with me?
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere, far away.
So, dad couldn't find us.
Sky, don't joke around.
I'm not joking.
Dad said he wants you to go back with him.
He won't let you stay with me anymore.
No matter how I beg him.
I don't know what else to do.
But running away won't solve anything.
Eventually, father will find us.
He's not that great.
I don't want you to be reckless
and do things hastily.
But if you really want to run away,
I'm willing to follow you.
Thanks for the heads up.
Anyway,
I'm not giving you up to dad.
Ew, too much love in the air.
What's wrong?
It's my dad.
He won't accept Sun.
He said I was just being moody.
Give him some time.
Think about it,
If your dad doesn't love you,
or care about you.
He wouldn't send Sun to protect you.
Moreover, if he didn't send Sun over
in the first place,
you wouldn't get to see him
and fall in love.
Don't think too much.
Thanks, bro.
This is today's ledger, boss.
Thanks.
-Shin.
-Yes, sir.
Do you think
I'm doing anything wrong?
About young master?
At first, I wanted Sun to protect him.
How does everything
and it turn out like this?
Maybe, it's destiny.
For those two kids who have
the same rare blood-type.
To meet each other.
A destiny?
I'm the one who brought them together.
I found Sun, so everything
is the way it is now.
It's love, no one can control that, boss.
You're right.
You can't control love.
Then, from now on,
I'll control everything.
Get rid of Sun!
Going to buy some food for you.
Riders are not picking up my order.
Allow yourself to miss me while waiting.
Yes, Shin?
I'm back.
I'm sorry.
I went to the supermarket
while I was out.
Come down and help me arrange things.
Sun.
Sun?
Where is he?
Eh? When did he send this?
Sky, Shin called me to meet up.
I know it was father's order.
I think it's time.
Don't be mad at father.
He did this because he loves you.
A guy like me is not worth it for you.
Sky, you have a bright future ahead,
not like me.
Even without me,
you have to take good care of yourself.
I love you, Sky.
More than my life.
Sun?
Hey, how is it?
Can you contact him?
Not at all.
I couldn't reach him.
Oh, I remember something.
Sun downloaded the tracking app
on your phone.
If his phone is still on,
we'll be able to reach him.
Yeah, right. I forgot about it.
Let's hurry now. Get in my car.
You search the map.
You know that you can't win.
Why don't you give up?
You knew why.
I won't hesitate, I'm serious.
Run while you still have the chance.
That's the only thing I can help.
No.
A life without young master
is like living dead.
My life belongs to father.
If father wants me dead,
then I'll accept it.
Then, be prepared for your death.
GPS said it's here.
Let's split up to look for him.
Okay.
Then, I'll go inside.
-Bank, you go that way.
-Alright, bro
I'll go this way.
Do you think you can make
my only son happy?
I'm not quite sure.
But I'm sure that I love him,
and I will protect him with my own life.
Just love is not enough.
Not worth it for Sky.
You were adopted,
don't be so arrogant.
You dare to touch my only son.
I'm just a bodyguard.
My only duty is to protect you,
no right to be otherwise.
Sun?
Let it all end here.
Sun!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Dad, don't you think
you went a bit too far?
Do you know how much
I'm worried about him?
I just want to test him.
If he's worth it for you.
But...
For the test result,
I'll say pass.
Are you happy?
So, you mean
you approve of our relationship?
Nope.
Today is just the first test.
I'll send you to study abroad.
-I won't go.
-You have to go.
You can't separate us like that.
Sun and I love each other.
Do you hear me?
We love each other.
I won't go anywhere.
I said you have to go.
If you believe that it's the actual love.
You've got to prove it.
If you both
are in a long distant relationship,
then you forget about each other.
That means it's just a teen-love,
not real love.
Father.
Please send young master aboard.
During that time, we'll break our contact.
We'll prove our love for you.
Our feelings are not just
a spark because we're close.
I'll wait until Sky finishes school
and comes back.
Till that day,
if we are still the same.
I beg you,
can you approve of our love then?
Alright,
I accept the deal.
Why don't you fight for us?
Why you want us to be apart?
It's our fight.
We'll fight together.
We'll get father's approval.
I'm sure that time won't change me.
What about you?
For me, you define forever.
Hey, can I play with another rubik's cube?
I only have one.
What about the one poking my back?
That's a gun.
Can I check out your gun?
Didn't you say you want to check the gun?
Didn't dad tell you?
Before you check someone's gun,
you have to search him first.
What are you thinking?
I miss you.
I'm right here.
Why do you still miss me?
But soon, I have to go.
Let's leave the worries to the future.
Today, we're still together.
When I come back,
what if dad still doesn't approve?
Then, I'll wait until he does.
What if it's been five years,
ten years,
but dad still doesn't.
For me, I can wait for you my whole life.
You won't forget me right?
How can I forget?
My heart is with you, Sky.
My heart is with you too.
This is BYSENSTER's butterfly Pea
natural formula with Thai flower flavor!
You'll have a floral breath
when you talk.
Does it smell good?
What is it?
A face mask.
Here you go.
I miss the sea of stars back then.
I can't see any stars in Bangkok,
even though we are under the same sky.
When you come back,
we'll go there together.
Promise?
I promise.
Why are you looking at me?
Aren't you getting used to it?
Do you remember the last time
when we were watching the stars?
Suppose you are not my bodyguard.
Will you help me like what you did?
Definitely, I'll help you.
-Because I...
-You what?
You know what I was going to say?
Do you?
You didn't say it.
How would I know?
You really don't?
Alright, I do,
but I want to hear it from you.
I love you.
It doesn't matter what we are.
I'll protect you with my life.
Sun?
We won't say goodbye, Sky.
Take good care of yourself.
Let's trade the hat once we meet again.
Ps. Finish this too.
(Six years later)
(Japan)
-I'll apply ointment.
-I already did.
Can you actually reach your back?
Take off your shirt.
Are you hurt?
Hi, dad.
Welcome back home, son.
Really miss you, son.
How are you? Feels like home?
I miss Thailand, and also miss you too.
How's it going? What's your plans
after coming back?
I want to help your business.
You've been hard working.
It's time for retirement.
I'm glad to hear you say that.
So I can retire from all this.
When do you want to start?
I want to have a break
and meet up with my friends first.
Hey.
Where is Sun?
Why didn't he come to pick me up?
He won't get to see you till I allow him.
I keep my promise.
I hope you do too.
It's been six years.
How can you be so sure...
that he'll still have feelings for you?
I believe in him.
-Shin.
-Yes, sir.
Where is Sky?
Young master went out to donate his blood.
He said later he'll meet up
with his friends.
Boss.
They both proved themselves,
what are you going to do?
Just kidding.
Hey, Sky.
Come sit next to me.
It's been so long.
How long have you been here?
For ages.
Oh, it's just you, Pitch.
How did you get here?
It's our class reunion.
Why can't I be here?
Your class reunion includes my lover.
He's here.
Then, I have to watch over him.
Oh, so sweet of you two.
Too sweet, everyone's envious.
Toktaeng, Juno, how are you?
I'm good.
What about Sun?
Didn't he come with you?
Don't tell me you
haven't seen him yet?
Yeah.
You knew about my dad.
What are you going to do then?
For now, I just keep donating
my blood every three months.
So I can have my own spare.
I don't have to bother him.
You both are like, born for each other.
The golden blood, so romantic, man.
Well, you said you're going
to work with your dad.
When will you start?
I have something I want to do first.
When you come back,
we'll go there together.
Promise?
Don't go out by yourself.
It's dangerous.
You promised, we'll go together.
Why did you sneak here alone?
How did you know I'm here?
Father told me to come here.
Dad?
Father said you're here.
And he allows me to protect you.
I'm here now.
I miss you.
Very very much.
From now on, I'll be by your side,
young master.
I'm not going anywhere.
Forever?
For the rest of my life.
Hey!
Did you forget something?
I'm not your young master anymore.
Yes.
You're my Sky.
(The End)
Subtitle translation by:
Chanapa, Sorawit and Monchaya