=Nitiman The Series=
♪What's outside and what's in front
remain a mystery to us♪
♪But the heart is longing
to see the world outside♪
♪How far is the horizon anyway?
Just approach it♪
♪Just start marching forward♪
♪No time to worry or be afraid♪
♪Open your heart♪
♪Can't stop♪
♪Don't have to wait♪
♪Meet each other at the destination♪
♪Even though I'm all weary
and exhausted♪
♪Meeting and creating memories with you
make the challenge harder♪
♪I'll give my all. If I fall,
I'll just get back up and move forward♪
♪To the finishing line♪
♪No matter how high or steep it is,
I'm not afraid♪
=Nitiman The Series=
(Previously)
What's wrong?
You can tell me about it.
Do you feel embarrassed because
you're dating me?
I don't know.
I don't like the way they stare at us.
I'm at a loss.
Jin, do you want to join us?
We lack one team member.
No, Jin is joining my team.
Jin, you need to join my team.
We belong to the same faculty, you know?
Cut! Why are you being so shy?
Did you memorise the script or not?
If you aren't ready for this,
you should tell us earlier.
That way, we don't need to
waste our time on you.
We can have a one-on-one practice later.
Maybe you'll get better.
(Jin)
Hello?
Jin, what do you mean by the
profile picture that you've just posted?
Hey, calm down.
What's with the two of you?
There's nothing between us.
That's just a picture
to promote our drama.
Do you need to have body contact
with him in order to do so?
Yeah, but I didn't have
any body contact with Mark.
You shouldn't overthink it.
How could I not overthink it?
Look at the picture you just posted.
Hey, Bbomb, don't overthink it.
I'll talk to you
when I get back to the dorm.
The drama will end by tomorrow.
But I want it to end by now.
Jin! Yin is calling for us.
Let's go.
I'll hang up now.
(Non-Stop)
(Penn: I've reached my dorm.)
Each of us has three chances.
The loser will
treat the winner to a meal.
Fine.
Come.
Jay.
What is it? Out with it.
I think we should change this part
to this. What do you think?
That's fine.
We'll follow your suggestion.
I think it's pretty good.
But, I think
this part should be like this.
Let me try it.
I think we play a F chord here.
A G minor chord.
And A minor chord.
Oh, sorry.
Help me put the strap on.
You're so troublesome.
You won't be able to live without me.
Come, let's continue.
You're the best.
What are you doing?
Do it again? This part.
G minor.
A minor.
And C.
Do that for this part.
Only then, it can become
the highlight of our song.
Yeah.
This part will be the most unique part
of the song.
Som Som,
can I sit beside you?
Sure.
Here you go.
Oh, I forgot about it.
It's part of my treasured collection.
Yeah.
What do you want?
- You must order something.
- I...
I'll have the same one as hers.
Alright.
Wait a moment.
Do you like her?
Do you want me to
get her number for you?
I can smell your sourness.
Keam, do you want to
swap your rice with mine?
What rice did you receive?
Oh, Bbomb, I can't take
spicy food either.
- What's wrong?
- Senior, I can't take spicy food.
Do you have other food available?
We've already given all of them away.
Can you eat this for now?
But, I really can't take any spicy food.
Juniors, is there anyone who's willing
to swap your rice with him?
He can't take spicy food.
Senior, I'm okay with it.
Thank you.
I want my spoon.
Here you go.
Thank you so much.
You did great. Hurry and
look for your girlfriend.
Yes, sir!
Sawedee! Where are you?
- Tanapoong!
- Sawedee!
I'm over here!
How do you feel?
I'm fine!
I missed you!
I missed you as well!
Over there.
Jin!
My child, you did great.
You were so cool.
I'm not a child anymore.
Do you have a crush on the female lead?
It's just a show.
Is that so?
Yeah.
You looked like you've changed a lot.
Mum, is that true?
Are you hiding any secret from me?
No.
Not even one secret?
Nothing at all.
You can tell me in private.
Okay?
Come, let's take a group photo.
Hurry, Bbomb. Help us take a picture.
Come, let's take the photo together.
It's fine. I'll take the picture
for you guys.
Really?
Thank you for that.
You're welcome.
Are you tired? You're the best!
You were super cool!
Come, let's take a picture.
One, two, three.
Let's take another shot.
You guys should be closer this time.
One, two, three.
Alright.
Yeah!
- How was it?
- Thank you.
Wen!
It's our turn to perform!
Alright, I'll be there immediately.
Aunty, sisters, I'll make a move first.
- Goodbye.
Ji, Jin, let's leave as well.
We don't want to be late for our flight.
Mum, you're right.
We'll make our move now. Goodbye.
My child, you did great.
See you next time.
- Do your best, okay?
- See you next time, Mum.
Goodbye.
Give us a hug.
- I'll miss you.
- Do your best, okay?
I will.
Go now. Goodbye.
Did you sleep in your dorm last night?
Yeah.
I had an exam this morning.
What did you and my mother talk about?
Nothing much.
I saw you chatting with her just now.
She said I was handsome. She wants me
to be her son-in-law.
After that, I asked her about the dowry.
With this IQ of yours, I'm afraid
you couldn't afford it.
She said I don't need to
give her any dowry.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Song. This is my best friend, Jay.
I believe everyone here
knows who we are.
Yes, but today is a special occasion
because we're going to perform
the ending song for the drama.
Now, Tong will take over the stage.
Here you go.
Is this for me?
Yeah.
You're giving me a toy cow.
Are you trying to insult me?
What about your comments for me then?
♪There's no need for reasons♪
♪There's no need for forms♪
♪We all know that
ceremonies are unnecessary♪
♪This is the love we need♪
♪Words cannot describe our love♪
♪When I'm with you,
every second is meaningful♪
Let's go.
♪You made my life better
and more fulfilling♪
Hey, Bbomb.
♪It's obvious that
you're the only one in my heart♪
Thank you.
♪You're the best gift of my life♪
♪Thank you, the sky, the rain,
the people in my life♪
♪Thank you for allowing me
to encounter you♪
♪Even though there are
no stars in the dark sky♪
♪When I turn around,
you were always by my side♪
♪I feel lucky to be together with you♪
♪I will love you with
all of my heart forever♪
♪Please never let go of my hands♪
♪Let me follow you♪
♪Until the end of time♪
Bbomb.
About Mark...
Yeah, I got it.
I was just afraid you might be shaken.
Don't you trust me at all?
Lend me your phone.
What's your password?
220620.
Is that your birthday?
It's the first day I met you.
(Set it as wallpaper)
Why did you like me in the first place?
To me, there's no
particular reason.
Maybe you've already forgotten about
that day.
But I've never forgotten about that day.
Juniors, is there anyone who's willing
to swap your rice with him?
He can't take spicy food.
Excuse me.
Hey, Jin.
How are you doing?
I'm doing pretty good.
By the way, Jin, do you know
how to get to the concert hall?
Go straight and turn left.
Oh, thanks. Let's have a chat
when both of us are free.
Goodbye.
Is he your friend?
Yeah, we got to know each other
during a football match.
Bbomb, aren't you worried that you might
be making a wrong decision?
I mean, your decision in courting me.
I don't know about the future,
and I don't care about it as well.
What about you? Why are you
willing to date me?
Maybe it's because you're rich.
It's like I'm dating a sponsor.
Excuse me, senior.
Can I take a picture with you?
Sure.
Are you here to watch my performance?
Yes. I wanted to take a picture
with you as well.
One, two, three.
Senior, are you two a couple?
I'm sorry and thank you.
What time is it?
(21:11)
Although I don't remember that day,
I still remember the Pad Kra Pao.
I will keep the packet of rice
in a display case.
♪You're the best gift of my life♪
♪Thank you, the sky, the rain,
the people in my life♪
♪Thank you for allowing me
to encounter you♪
♪Even though there are
no stars in the dark sky♪
♪When I turn around,
you were always by my side♪
♪I feel lucky to be together with you♪
♪I will love you with
all of my heart forever♪
♪Please never let go of my hands♪
♪Let me follow you♪
♪Until the end of time♪
♪Stay with me like this forever♪
♪Please accept my heart♪
♪To repay you♪
♪For never letting go♪
♪Of my hands♪
♪You're the best gift of my life♪
♪Thank you, the sky, the rain,
the people in my life♪
♪Thank you for allowing me
to encounter you♪
♪Even though there are
no stars in the dark sky♪
♪When I turn around,
you were always by my side♪
♪I feel lucky to be together with you♪
♪Thank you, the sky, the rain,
the people in my life♪
♪Thank you for allowing me
to encounter you♪
♪Even though there are
no stars in the dark sky♪
♪When I turn around,
you were always by my side♪
♪I feel lucky to be together with you♪
♪I will love you with
all of my heart forever♪
♪Please never let go of my hands♪
♪Let me follow you♪
♪Until the end of time♪
How is it? Do you have new information?
Yes, sister.
Look.
I think they're dating each other.
They just didn't want to tell anyone.
Here you go.
Thank you.
(Do we still continue with
our revision later?)
(Library Zone 24.)
(Alright. Keam and I will have lunch
together. Do you want to join us?)
(Do you want to join us?)
(I'm joining you guys.)
(I'll answer on behalf of Jin.)
(#$%@)
(He won't join you guys.)
(Dummy)
U, you always take my food.
(Butter BBQ)
I did refill your plate for you.
You should stop eating.
(Butter BBQ)
This isn't fully cooked yet.
No, you should stop eating.
Hey!
What are you guys doing? Give it to me.
I'll put this on the grill now.
U, give me some of it.
I'm going to go home.
Eating is the only thing you're good at.
Everyone, let's have a toast.
Come on.
Cheers.
What's wrong?
Bring me out for lunch.
Alright, I'll pick you up later.
Very good.
Hey, Bbomb. Where are you going?
I'm going to look for Jin.
We became single dogs all of a sudden.
Sorry about that. I'll make a move now.
Show me your paw.
Don't you Bbomb is treating Jin
too nicely?
I'm sure they're dating each other.
Hey, stop pretending.
Cook it for me.
I haven't had one piece of meat yet
even though I've been cooking them.
U, you shouldn't overthink it.
He will tell us about it in due time.
Let's dig in.
What do you want to eat?
Stir-fried dishes, soup, rice bowls,
porridge, or beef steak?
I want to have something with soup.
How about some rotating hotpot?
Are you footing the bill?
Yeah.
It's fine. It's not that far away.
Come here.
Get on.
Are you that hungry?
Yeah.
I need to use the washroom.
Okay.
(Song: BBQ or rotating hotpot
with your loved one?)
(U: He abandoned his friends straight
away when his partner is calling him.)
(Jay: The exam is nearing. I guess he
needs encouragement from his friend.)
(Jay: Are you together with them?)
(Song: See you guys in the library.
#someonewhoclingstoyourpartner)
(Library)
Did someone send you here?
Oh, I guess you had a comfortable ride.
Hey, don't forget about me.
I'm afraid I won't understand them.
(Ways to measure unequal values)
(Raw construction materials)
Okay.
That's about it.
That was difficult.
Yeah, I don't understand them at all.
There are too many of them.
Do you guys believe this? I'll forget
about it once I leave the library.
You guys didn't focus
during our classes.
And now, you want me to teach you.
I'm the one who's exhausted, you know?
It's all because of you.
It's because of you.
I'll leave first. Keep my stuff for me.
I'm sure he has a new flirting target.
I think it's still the same girl.
Keam and I will return first.
Alright, see you.
See you.
Bbomb, I'm done. Come and pick me up.
♪What's outside and what's in front
remain a mystery to us♪
♪But the heart is longing
to see the world outside♪
♪How far is the horizon anyway?
Just approach it♪
♪Just start marching forward♪
♪No time to worry or be afraid♪
♪Open your heart♪
♪Can't stop♪
♪Don't have to wait♪
♪Meet each other at the destination♪
♪Even though I'm all weary
and exhausted♪
♪Meeting and creating memories with you
make the challenge harder♪
♪I'll give my all. If I fall,
I'll just get back up and move forward♪
♪To the finishing line♪
♪No matter how high or steep it is,
I'm not afraid♪
(Done with my exams! Good luck to those
who need to burn the midnight oil.)
(How much?)
(You mean the drink?)
(No, I mean how much for Jin.)
(You need to ask this person. @Bbomb)
(Bye.)
(Haha.)
Hello?
Let's have a drink since
we're done with our exams.
Sure.
See you at the liquor stall.
Alright.
Hey, you guys didn't wait for me.
Blame it on Keam.
I just took a small sip.
Are you sure it was a small sip?
Thank you, boss.
No problem.
What's wrong with Keam?
I don't know either.
I'm over here, you fool.
I don't know.
Keam, are you okay?
Bottoms up.
You came all the way here just to drink
some fruit juice with your buddies?
Bottoms up.
Our papers were really easy, huh?
Easy? My foot. You were
biting your pen during the exam.
Jack, I'll wait for your exam result.
We should change a topic. I don't want
to mention my marks.
Boss, give us another plate of this.
Give us some fried intestines as well.
Boss, get us another round of drinks.
You do know me well.
I'll beat you up if you continue this.
Thank you, boss.
Keam, are you sure you can continue?
Come, let us give a toast to our gang.
Give cake and ale to perfect soul. Hey!
Jin, what's wrong?
Nothing. I just feel like it's been a
long time since I've seen you guys.
You only realised that by now?
Where did your boyfriend go?
Jack!
Jack, you only know how to tease him.
Jin, I understand you.
Being with your friends is different
from being with your partner.
Singh, seems like you do know him well.
Of course, you fool.
Singh.
What's the matter?
Pour me another cup.
Here. Why does he look so fierce
when he's drinking?
My goodness.
Here, cheers.
We'll never get drunk when we
drink with our friends. Cheers.
The liquor here is really strong.
Here you go.
Hey, Keam!
Go.
I think he's out.
Let's drink until we drop.
Hey, what about me?
Hey, of course we remember you.
Here you go.
The fried intestines here are amazing.
They're so chewy.
Is this the intestine or skin?
Look who's here.
Oh.
My goodness!
Jin, we should go. You're drunk.
Can't you just let him spend some time
with his buddies?
Jin, you should go.
Goodbye, my dear little brother.
Goodbye, Jack. Goodbye, Singh.
You're saying the opposite.
♪We'll cry when our husbands are here♪
Jin!
What?
Singh, Jin forgot to pay for his drinks.
Go and search Keam to see if
he has any money.
Keam, did you bring money with you?
That's it.
Boss!
Are you okay?
I'll leave with my bike then.
Alright.
Bbomb.
Can you bring me some food?
Don't you want to wait for me?
No thanks.
Fine then.
Which page?
Page 2.1.
How is it?
Where are Song and Jay?
I think Song just woke up.
I'm here.
Wen.
What?
Were you badmouthing me just now?
Nope.
I heard everything.
Bbomb,
I need to ask you something.
What is it?
Do you still remember the day
when we went to the pub together?
Hey, he's here!
Guys, I need to make a move first.
What?
Jin is drunk. I need to pick him up.
Wait.
Finish your last drink
before you leave.
Yeah.
Cheers.
- Bottoms up.
Yeah, what about that?
After you went back to
the dorm with Jin,
did you feel...
I mean, did you feel
a special sensation?
I don't know. I felt ordinary.
Is that so?
Didn't you feel a tingling sensation?
No.
What are you doing?
Don't do this.
Jin,
don't move.
You'll touch it.
Are you guys hiding anything from me?
No.
I was just asking.
You were drunk back then. I thought
you tried to make Jin yours.
That's not true.
Aren't you guys being too much?
Will we be okay?
Will you be okay?
I guess so.
What about you?
No problem.
Guys, I'll go and look for Jin.
Alright.
(Jin)
So, did our plan fail?
I think so.
I'm sure Aim will tell me off.
It's scary when I think about it.
Don't overthink it.
I'm sure she won't do so.
Do you want her to tell you off then?
No thanks.
How's the progress?
Aim! I'm sorry!
I didn't mean it!
I've already done my best!
But Bbomb did nothing at all!
- I'm sorry! I didn't know anything!
- Song!
I'm starving.
Do you want to join us for lunch?
I'll treat you to lunch. Come on.
No thanks, I'm going to look for Jin.
That's great! You should leave first.
Good luck.
Yeah, good luck.
- Go now.
Goodbye!
Stupid Song! It's your fault again.
You rat us out every time.
I'm sorry!
Beg me.
Kneel down.
Beg me!
Kneel down immediately!
I'm kneeling!
Let's go! You need to
treat me to a meal.
Oh, I thought it was someone else.
Come to the middle lane.
I'll go to another lane.
Jin, Jack, come and help me out
in the middle lane!
I'm dead!
Bbomb, look. It's because you poked me.
I'm dead because of you.
Why are you blaming him
when you're lousy at the game?
Jack!
I quit.
Top!
They're gone.
Singh, what are you doing?
Come and help us out!
I'll farm the jungle creeps for now.
I'm dead.
I'm dead as well.
I quit.
Let's have lunch.
I'm starving.
How about the mall beside our school?
We should get something simple.
Yeah, let's go.
Can you ride your bike?
Fine, I'll ride my bike.
Why don't you drive my car then?
Sure.
Let's go.
(This is an emergency meeting! See you
in the activity room this afternoon.)
Keam,
will you go home for the holiday?
No, since no one's home anyway.
By the way, Bbomb,
you should return to your dorm
after lunch.
But why?
Our drama club has
a drinking session later.
For what reason?
To celebrate the end of our drama.
Jin, I'll leave first.
See you later.
Only my friends and
some of the drama casts
will attend the session.
Fine then.
I'll pick you up later.
Suit yourself.
Remember to pick up my call.
Alright.
(1:00)
(You have reached the voicemail of...)
Here's your change, 40 baht.
Please check your change.
Do you need a straw?
No thanks.
Thank you.
Hey, Bbomb. Are you here
to buy something?
Yeah.
Tonight will be a long night. That's why
I'm buying some food.
What about you? Is the gathering over?
The gathering has been over
for a while now.
What's wrong?
Jin hasn't returned to his dorm yet?
Yeah.
I don't know what's the situation
between both of you,
but brother, listen to my advice.
Never trust Jin entirely.
Understood?
Do you understand?
Yeah, I'll make a move now.
I need to study.
Goodbye.
Hello, what do you need?
The usual.
The usual? What do you mean?
One sausage.
One sausage?
Yes.
Choi!
One sausage.
Yes, brother.
(Jin)
Bbomb, pick me up later.
Hey, you...
Goodbye, Senior.
Goodbye.
Why didn't you pick up my call?
My battery was flat.
Don't your friends have any
batteries to spare?
I told you my battery was flat.
What else do you want me to do?
Why didn't you return with
your friends then?
Because Mark told me to accompany him.
You knew I can't reject him.
You can't reject him, huh?
So, you'll say yes
even if he wants to date you, right?
You always try to correct my mistakes.
You never trusted me.
Have you ever trusted me then?
You aren't willing to tell anyone
about our relationship at all!
Because of what?
It's because you can continue to
flirt with other people!
♪Sometimes, I feel alone
even when you're standing beside me♪
♪As if I was a forgotten person♪
♪Am I overthinking?
When you care for someone else♪
♪I can only take a peek,
trying my best not to overthink♪
♪I'm upset, but I can understand why♪
♪Forget it, I'll get over it soon♪
(Next Episode)
Let me join you.
♪But, I just want you to know♪
How many times do I have to repeat this?
There's nothing between Mark and me.
Can you stop it? I feel shy.
Jin, did you see Aim's post?
Do you need anything?
Thank you.
Aim, I couldn't reach Bbomb.
I'm going back to Chiang Mai.
Not eating? I'll keep them away then.
Have you seen Bbomb's significant other?
Aunty, I'm his significant other.
♪I'm ready to stay by your side♪
♪I will offer all of my love to you♪
♪Until the end of time♪
♪From now on, I hope
you can stay with me, okay?♪
♪I'm willing to move forward
with you no matter what happens♪
♪I'm fearless as long as
you're by my side♪
♪Maybe we'll reach the finish line soon♪
♪I won't make things
difficult for you. Believe me♪
♪But I still want to let you understand♪
♪No matter what happens,
I'm here for you♪
♪I will wait for you unconditionally♪