(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(THUNDER CONTINUES RUMBLING)
(FLY BUZZING)
(CREATURE TRILLING)
You'll be glad
to be rid of him, I expect.
We'd be more than happy
to keep him here in custody.
Six months are enough.
It's time for him to answer
for his crimes in Europe.
MR. ABERNATHY: President Picquery.
Mr. Spielman, sir.
Prisoner is secured and ready to travel.
SPIELMAN: You've thrown
everything at him, I see.
SERAPHINA: It was necessary.
He's extremely powerful.
We've had to change his guard
three times. He's very persuasive.
So we removed his tongue.
PRISONERS: (YELLING) Grindelwald!
Grindelwald! Grindelwald!
(YELLING)
PRISONERS: Grindelwald! Grindelwald!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
SPIELMAN: The wizarding
community worldwide
owes you a great debt, Madam President.
Do not underestimate him.
Mr. Spielman,
we found his wand hidden away.
Abernathy.
And we found this.
(SERAPHINA SIGHS)
- (B0TH WHINNYING)
- Hiyah!
(WIND HOWLING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
No more silver tongue. Hmm?
(GROANING)
(BOTH HISSING)
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
(ALL GROAN)
(GASPS)
- (SNARLS)
- (GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(YELLING)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(SPIELMAN SCREAMS)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(SCREAMS)
(BOTH SCREAM)
GRINDELWALD: You have joined
a noble cause, my friend.
(MR. ABERNATHY COUGHING)
(CREATURE TRILLING)
(GROANING)
I know. I know. I know, Antonio.
(PURRING)
So needy.
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING IN RELIEF)
(COUGHING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(PICKETT STRUGGLING)
They're ready for you, Newt.
Leta.
What are you doing here?
Theseus thought it would be good
if I became part of the Ministry family.
Did he actually say the words
"Ministry family"?
- (LAUGHS)
- That sounds like my brother.
(CLEANER APPROACHING)
Theseus was disappointed
you couldn't come to dinner.
Any of the nights we've asked you.
NEWT: Well, I've been busy.
LETA: He's your brother, Newt.
He likes spending time with you.
And so do I.
(PICKETT CHITTERS)
Oi, you! Hop in, Pick.
Why do strange creatures
love you so much?
Well, there are no strange creatures.
Only blinkered people.
How long did you get in detention
for saying that to Prendergast?
I think it was a month that time.
And I set off a Dungbomb under his desk
so I could join you. Do you remember?
NEWT: Um...
No, I actually don't remember that.
THESEUS: Hello.
Theseus. We were just talking
about Newt coming for dinner.
Really? Well...
Look, before we go in there, I...
It's my fifth attempt, Theseus.
I know the form.
This isn't gonna
be like the other times. This is...
Just try and keep an open mind.
Will you?
And maybe a little less...
Like me.
Well, it can't hurt.
Come on, let's go.
TRAVERS: Hearing commences.
You want an end to the ban
on you traveling internationally.
Why?
Because I'd like
to travel internationally.
Subject uncooperative and evasive
on reasons for last international trip.
It was a field trip, sir.
I was just collecting material
for my book on magical beasts.
You destroyed half of New York.
No, that's actually factually incorrect
on two counts.
THESEUS: Newt.
Mr. Scamander, it's clear
you're frustrated,
and, frankly, so are we.
In the spirit of compromise,
we'd like to make a proposition.
What kind of proposition?
The committee will agree to lift
your travel ban under one condition.
SPIELMAN: You join the Ministry.
Specifically, your brother's department.
No.
(STAMMERS) I think that...
Theseus is the Auror.
I think my talents lie elsewhere.
GUZMAN: Mr. Scamander,
the wizarding and non-wizarding worlds
have been at peace for over a century.
Grindelwald wants to see
that peace destroyed.
And for certain members
of our community,
his message is very seductive.
Many pure-bloods believe
it is their birthright to rule.
Not only our world
but the non-magic world as well.
They see Grindelwald as their hero,
and Grindelwald sees this boy
as a means to make this all come true.
I'm sorry. You're talking about Credence
as if he were still here.
He survived, Newt.
He's still alive.
He left New York months ago.
He's somewhere in Europe.
Where exactly, we don't know, but...
NEWT: You want me to
hunt Credence down?
To kill him?
Same old Scamander.
What is he doing here?
I'm taking on the job
that you're too soft to do.
Is that it?
- Travel documentation denied.
- (DOOR OPENS)
Newt!
You think I like the idea of Grimmson
any more than you do?
Listen, I don't want to hear how
the ends justify the means, Theseus.
I think you're gonna have to pull
your head out the sand!
Okay, right, here we go.
What a selfish, irresponsible...
The time is coming when everyone
is gonna have to pick a side.
Even you.
I don't do sides.
(THESEUS SIGHS)
Newt. Newt.
Come here.
They're watching you.
GRIMMSON: Well, gentlemen...
I assume this means I have the job.
(DOOR OPENING)
(MAN SPEAKING FRENCH)
(WOMAN SPEAKS FRENCH)
(BOTH SCREAM)
This will be suitable
after a thorough cleanse.
I want you to go to the circus now.
Give my note to Credence.
Begin his journey.
When we've won,
they'll flee cities in the millions.
They've had their time.
We don't say such things out loud.
We want only freedom.
Freedom to be ourselves.
To annihilate non-wizards.
Not all of them. Not all.
We're not merciless.
The beast of burden
will always be necessary.
(BOY SPEAKING FRENCH IN THE DISTANCE)
(BOY BABBLES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(CAR HORN HONKING)
Ventus.
- (WIND WHOOSHING)
- (GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
(SIGHS)
NEWT: Dumbledore.
Were the less conspicuous
rooftops full, then?
Hmm.
I do enjoy a view.
Nebulus.
How was it?
NEWT: They're still convinced
that you sent me to New York.
DUMBLEDORE: You told them I didn't?
Yes.
MAN: Evening.
Even though you did.
You told me where to find that
trafficked Thunderbird, Dumbledore.
You knew that I would take him home,
and you knew I'd have to
take him through a Muggle port.
DUMBLEDORE: I've always felt an
affinity with the great magical birds.
There's a story in my family
that a phoenix will come
to any Dumbledore in desperate need.
They say my great-grandfather had one.
And that it took flight when he died,
never to return.
With all due respect, Professor,
I don't believe for a minute
that's why you told me
about the Thunderbird.
So why did you send me to New York?
Because I knew Grindelwald
would try to catch Credence.
He had a vision, you see,
many years ago.
In which an Obscurial killed
the man he fears above all others.
You.
I thought you might deprive Grindelwald
of his weapon,
not by killing Credence,
but by saving him.
Credence is in Paris, Newt.
Trying to trace his real family.
I take it you've heard the rumors
about who he really is.
No.
The pure-bloods think he's the last
of an important French line.
A baby whom everyone thought lost.
Not Leta's brother?
That's what they're whispering.
And pure-blood or not, I know this.
An Obscurus grows in the absence of love
as a dark twin, an only friend.
If Credence has a real brother or sister
out there that can take its place,
he might yet be saved.
Wherever Credence is in Paris,
he's either in danger,
or a danger to others.
We may not know who he is yet,
but he needs to be found.
And I rather hope
you might be the one to find him.
What's that?
An address of a very old
acquaintance of mine.
A safe house in Paris
reinforced with enchantments.
Safe house?
Why would I need a safe house in Paris?
One hopes you won't, but should things
at some point go terribly wrong,
it's good to have a place to go.
You know, for a cup of tea.
No. No, no, no.
- (ENGINE STARTING)
- Absolutely not.
No, 'cause I'm banned from
international travel, Dumbledore.
If I leave the country,
they will put me in Azkaban,
and they will throw away the key.
- Do you know why I admire you, Newt?
- What?
More, perhaps, than any man I know.
You do not seek power.
Or popularity.
You simply ask,
is a thing right in itself?
If it is, you do it no matter the cost.
That's all very well, Dumbledore,
but forgive me for asking.
Why can't you go?
I cannot move against Grindelwald.
It has to be you.
Well, I can't blame you.
In your shoes, I'd probably refuse too.
- What?
- It's late. Good evening, Newt.
Wait, no.
Oh, come on.
- (AIR WHOOSHES)
- (NEWT SCOFFS)
(PICKETT SQUEAKING)
(SIGHS) Dumbledore.
(DOOR CREAKING)
(SQUEAKING)
(SQUEALS)
(POT CLATTERS)
(SQUEAKING)
(BABY NIFFLER GRUNTING)
Bunty!
Bunty, the baby Nifflers
are loose again.
(CREATURE BRAYING)
NEWT: Well done.
I'm so sorry, Newt.
They must've picked the lock
- while I was cleaning out the Augureys.
- Not to worry.
BUNTY: Hmm.
I fed nearly everyone.
Pinky's had his nose drops and...
And Elsie?
Elsie's droppings
are nearly normal again.
Wonderful.
You can, um... You can clock off now.
- I told you to leave the Kelpie to me.
- That wound needs more ointment.
I don't want you losing fingers over it.
Seriously, you go home now, Bunty.
You must be exhausted.
You know the Kelpie's easier with two.
(KELPIE CALLING)
Perhaps you should take off your shirt.
Don't worry.
I'll dry off quick enough.
(BUNTY INHALES SHARPLY)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPING)
(NEWT WHOOPING)
(GRUNTING)
Someone needed to let off some steam.
Ointment, Bunty.
(KELPIE GROWLS)
You bite Bunty again,
and there'll be trouble, mister.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
What was that?
I don't know.
But I want you to go home now, Bunty.
- Shall I call the Ministry?
- No.
I want you to go home. Please.
(WAND TINKLING)
- WOMAN: Just give me the pieces.
- MAN: I got it.
WOMAN: Honey, if you could
just give it to me...
MAN: He doesn't care.
If you could just give this
to me, sweetheart.
- (VASE SMASHES)
- Hey!
Newt! Get over here, you maniac.
- (JACOB LAUGHING)
- We hope you don't mind, Newt.
We let ourselves in.
It's rainin' out there, cats and dogs.
London's cold.
You were supposed
to have been obliviated.
(LAUGHING) I know.
It didn't work, pal.
I mean, you said it.
The potion only erases bad memories.
I didn't have any.
I mean, uh, don't get me wrong.
I had some weird ones,
and I had some scary ones.
But this angel...
This angel over here,
she filled me in on all the bad parts,
and, uh, here we are, I guess, huh?
- (ALL LAUGH)
- This is wonderful.
- (JACOB MOANS)
- NEWT: Wait. Is...
Tina? Tina?
(JACOB SIGHS)
Oh, it's just us, honey.
Me and Jacob.
Oh.
QUEENIE: Why don't I
make us some dinner, huh?
JACOB: Yes!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey, honey.
Tina and I aren't talking.
- NEWT: Why?
- Oh, well, you know...
She found out about
Jacob and I seeing each other,
and she didn't like it,
'cause of the law.
Not allowed to... Oop!
Not allowed to date No-Majs,
not allowed to marry them.
Blah, blah, blah.
Well, she was all in a tizzy anyway
'cause of you.
- Me?
- Yeah, you, Newt.
It was in Spellbound.
Here. I brought it for you.
"Newt Scamander with fiancée
Leta Lestrange,"
"brother Theseus and unknown woman."
No. So Theseus is marrying Leta, not me.
Oh!
Oh... Oh, dear.
Well...
See, Tina read that,
and she started dating someone else.
He's an Auror.
His name's Achilles Tolliver.
JACOB: Tolliver. (LAUGHING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
QUEENIE: Anyway...
We are real excited to be here, Newt.
This is a...
Well, it's a special trip for us.
You see, Jacob and I,
we're getting married.
- (LAUGHING)
- I'm marrying Jacob.
Ah! (LAUGHING)
JACOB: Oh. (SIGHS)
NEWT: You've enchanted him,
haven't you?
What? (LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
- I have not.
- Will you stop reading my mind?
Queenie, you've brought him here
against his will.
Oh, that is an outrageous accusation.
Look at him.
He's just happy. He's so happy.
Then you won't mind if I, um...
Please don't.
NEWT: Queenie, you've got nothing
to fear if he wants to get married.
We can just lift the enchantment,
and he can tell us himself.
JACOB: What do you got there?
What are you gonna do?
What are you gonna do with that,
Mr. Scamander?
Surgito.
(GROANING)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Congratulations
on your engagement, Jacob.
Wait, what?
Oh, no. You didn't.
Queenie!
One second.
- (DOOR OPENS)
- It's very nice to see you.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- Where the hell am I right now?
Uh, London.
Oh!
I always wanted to go here!
Queenie!
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
JACOB: Oh, Queenie, honey.
Well, I'm curious
when you were gonna wake me up.
After we had five kids?
Why is it wrong to wanna marry you?
- Okay.
- To wanna have a family?
I just want what everyone else has,
that's all.
Wait, wait.
We've talked about this
like a million times.
If we get married and they find out,
they're gonna
throw you in jail, sweetheart.
- I can't have that.
- (SIGHS HEAVILY)
They don't like people like me
marrying people like you.
I ain't a wizard. I'm just me.
They're really progressive here,
and they'll let us get married properly.
Sweetheart, you don't need
to enchant me.
I'm already enchanted.
I love you so much.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
But I can't have you
risking everything like this, you know?
You're not giving us
a choice, sweetheart.
You're not giving me a choice.
One of us had to be brave,
and you were being a coward.
I was being a coward?
If I'm a coward, you're... (MUTTERS)
Crazy.
I didn't say it.
- You didn't have to.
- No, I didn't mean it, sweetheart.
Yeah, you did.
- No.
- I'm gonna go see my sister.
Fine. See your sister.
- Fine.
- No, wait! Wait!
No! Queenie!
I didn't mean it.
I didn't say nothin'.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Papyrus Reparo.
(TINA'S VOICE)
"My dear Queenie, what a beautiful city.
I'm thinking of you, Tina."
(CREATURE BRAYING)
Hey, Newt!
NEWT: Down here, Jacob.
So I'll be with you in a second.
(SQUAWKS)
I got my own problems.
Queenie left a postcard.
Tina's in Paris looking for Credence.
Genius.
Queenie's gonna go straight for Tina.
Okay, we're going to France, pal.
- Oh, hold on. I'll get my jacket.
- I've got it.
Oh.
Beautiful.
Come on.
I don't think it's reasonable to ask
Bunty to cope with everyone in here
and a bunch of newborns, so...
- Are you insane?
- (SQUEAKING)
You've got a pack of Nifflers now?
- NEWT: In you hop.
- Remember what happened last time?
I fixed the lock.
So nothing gets out without my say-so.
- (WHISTLES)
- (SNIFFING)
Come on.
Get a move on.
(SIGHS)
All right then, Accio necklace.
(SNIFFING)
Now you set a good example.
(LOCKS CASE)
- (LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING)
- (PEOPLE CHEERING)
(BARKER SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(ROARING)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
- (CREATURE GROWLING)
(PEOPLE GASP)
Nagini.
(GASPS)
Credence.
I think I know where she is.
We escape tonight.
Hey-
I've told you
to stay away from her, boy.
Did I say you could take a break?
Clean out the Kappa.
And you, get ready.
(CREATURES HISSING)
Next, in our little show
of freaks and oddities,
I present to you a Maledictus.
(AUDIENCE GASPING)
Once trapped
in the jungles of Indonesia,
she is the carrier of a blood curse.
AUDIENCE: Ohh!
SKENDER: Such Underbeings are destined
through the course of their lives
to turn permanently into beasts.
AUDIENCE: Ohh!
SKENDER: But look at her.
So beautiful. Yes.
So desirable.
But soon, she will be trapped forever
in a very different body.
Every night when she sleeps,
mesdames et messieurs,
she is forced to become...
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
- She is forced to become...
- (AUDIENCE CHATTERING)
She is forced to become...
(CHATTER STOPS)
(AUDIENCE GASPING)
Over time, she will not be able
to transform back.
(HISSING)
She will be forever trapped
in the body of a snake.
(CREDENCE GRUNTS)
(CREATURES SCREECHING)
- (GROANS)
- (AUDIENCE GASPS)
(SCREECHING CONTINUES)
(PANICKED SCREAMING)
- (CREATURE ROARING)
- (SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(MAN SCREAMING)
Credence!
(ROARS)
(GROANS)
Pack it up.
Paris is done for us now.
(BLOWING)
The boy with the Maledictus,
what do you know about him?
He's looking for his mother.
All my freaks think they can go home.
Okay, let's go.
Look, I think you and I
were at the circus
for the same reason, Monsieur...
Kama. Yusuf Kama.
And you think right.
- What do you want with Credence?
- The same as you.
Which is?
To prove who the boy really is.
If the rumors of his identity
are correct,
he and I are, distantly, related.
I am the last male
of my pure-blooded line,
and so,
if the rumors are correct, is he.
Have you read
The Predictions of Tycho Dodonus?
Yeah. But that's poetry, not proof.
YUSUF: Hmm.
If I could show you something better,
more concrete,
something that proves who he is,
would the Ministries of Europe
and America let him live?
They might.
Then come.
LETA: Oh, no, Yaxley.
I hate the way he makes a beeline for me
every time.
Well, if you insist on being
the most beautiful woman in the room.
It's not that and you know it.
It's all blood with Yaxley.
Let me go and congratulate him
and we can dance
and I promise I won't say a word
to anyone for the rest of the night.
- Promise?
- Promise.
Sorry.
(CHUCKLES)
- How have you been? (LAUGHS)
- You sly dog.
WOMAN: Is it her?
It is, look.
(WHISPERING) Her brother's alive.
MAN: The prediction is true.
Her brother will lead us
from the shadows.
(WHISPERS) Return, great avenger,
with wings from the water.
Congratulations, Leta.
Your brother lives.
We all truly believe it.
(BLOWING)
GRINDELWALD: So...
Credence Barebone.
Nearly destroyed
by the woman who raised him.
Yet now he seeks
the mother who bore him.
He's desperate for family.
He's desperate for love.
He's the key to our victory.
We know where the boy is, don't we?
- Why don't we grab him and leave?
- He must come to me freely,
and he will.
The path has been laid,
and he is following it.
The trail that will lead him to me
and the strange and glorious truth
of who he is.
KRALL: Why is he so important?
Who represents the greatest threat
to our cause?
Albus Dumbledore.
If I asked you now
to go to the school where he is hiding
and kill him for me,
would you do it for me, Krall?
Credence is the only entity alive
who can kill him.
You really think
he can kill the Great...
Can kill Albus Dumbledore?
I know he can.
But will you be with us
when that happens, Krall?
Will you?
(WINGS FLAPPING)
CREDENCE: What if she doesn't want me?
NAGINI: Make it happen.
What?
Because we're free.
NEWT: Jacob, that man
Tina's been seeing...
JACOB: Don't worry.
She's gonna see you,
and she'll see the four of us together,
it'll be just like New York
all over again. Don't worry about it.
NEWT: Yes, but he's an Auror,
Queenie said.
JACOB: Yeah, he's an Auror. So what?
Don't worry about him.
What do you think
I should say to her if I see her?
Oh, well, it's best
not to plan these things.
You know, you just say
whatever comes to you in the moment.
She has eyes just like a salamander.
Don't say that.
Look, (CLEARS THROAT)
you just tell her that you missed her.
- Right.
- Right, and then,
you came all the way to Paris
just to find her.
She'll love that. And then,
tell her you're losing sleep at night
for thinking of her and...
Just don't say nothing about
no salamanders, all right?
- Okay.
Hey. Hey, hey...
It's gonna be all right.
We're in this together, pal.
Okay, I'm gonna help you out.
I'm gonna help you find Tina,
find Queenie,
and we'll all be happy again,
just like old times.
Who is this guy?
NEWT: Oh, he's the only way I can
leave the country without documentation.
Now, you don't suffer from
motion sickness, do you?
I don't do well on boats, Newt.
You'll be fine.
PORTKEY TOUT: Stir your stumps.
Leaves in one minute.
50 Galleons.
No, we said 30.
Uh-huh. 30 to go to France.
20 not to tell anyone
I seen Newt Scamander
leaving the country illegally.
Price of fame, pal.
Mmm. Ten seconds.
- Eight.
- Jacob.
Seven.
Six.
Mmm...
Four.
Three. Two.
One.
(JACOB SCREAMING)
(GROANS) I didn't like
that Portkey, Newt.
So you keep saying.
Follow me.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
Confundus.
(HICCUPING DRUNKENLY)
- (GIGGLING)
- (JACOB LAUGHS)
(SHUSHES)
NEWT: Come on.
It'll wear off in a few minutes.
(HICCUPS)
(GIGGLING)
Appare Vestigium.
Accio Nfifler.
Get looking.
Oi! Get looking!
That's a Kappa.
It's a Japanese water demon.
Tina?
Tina!
What have you found?
JACOB: And we're licking the dirt now.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Revelio.
Newt, what made those?
That is a Zouwu.
It's a Chinese creature.
They are incredibly fast
and incredibly powerful.
They can travel 1,000 miles in a day,
and this one could take you
from one part of Paris to the next
in a single leap.
(NIFFLER CHITTERING)
NEWT: Oh, good boy.
Jacob, she was here.
Tina stood here.
She has incredibly narrow feet.
Have you noticed?
Can't say that I have.
Then someone came towards her.
(SNIFFING)
Avensegium.
- Right. Follow that feather.
- What?
- Jacob, follow the feather.
- Follow the feather.
Where is he?
Accio Nfifler.
Drop the bucket.
(GREETING IN FRENCH)
I'm sorry,
I don't know what you just said at all.
Welcome to the French Ministry of Magic.
What is your business, please?
(SLOWLY) I need to
speak to Tina Goldstein.
She's an American Auror
working on a case here.
We have no Tina Goldstein here.
No, I'm sorry.
There must be some sort of mistake.
See, I know she's in Paris.
She sent me a postcard.
I brought it.
I can show it to you. Here.
Maybe you can help me find it here.
It's just in here. Oh!
Rabbits! If you can
just wait one moment!
I know it's in here somewhere.
I definitely packed it.
Where is it?
One second.
What did I do with you?
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(ELEVATOR DOORS CLOSING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
JACOB: Could we at least
stop for coffee or...
NEWT: Not now, Jacob.
JACOB: Chocolat chaud or...
Just for a second?
- I don't know.
- NEWT: This way. Come on.
JACOB: Pain au chocolat?
Half a croissant and a bonbon?
NEWT: This way.
Jacob!
(ECHOING CHATTER)
Jacob?
- (ECHOING CHATTER CONTINUES)
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
(ECHOING CHATTER CONTINUES)
(CHATTER STOPS)
(WOMAN SPEAKING FRENCH)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CREDENCE SNIFFLES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
She's home.
(DOOR CREAKING)
(BOTH SPEAKING FRENCH)
CREDENCE: (IN ENGLISH) Are you Irma?
Are you Irma Dugard?
I'm sorry.
Your name is on my adoption paper.
Does this make sense?
You gave me
to Mrs. Barebone in New York.
I am not your mother.
I was only a servant.
You were so beautiful a baby.
And you are a beautiful man.
I did not want to leave you there.
CREDENCE: Why didn't they want me?
Why is your name on my adoption paper?
I took you to Mrs. Barebone
because she was supposed
to look after you.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(NAGINI GASPS)
(YELPS)
(ROARING)
(CREDENCE YELLING)
(GASPS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
She's dead.
How did the boy take it?
He's sensitive.
The Ministry won't be happy
when I tell them I missed.
I know my reputation.
Listen to me. The disapproval of cowards
is praise to the brave.
Your name will be written in glory
when wizards rule the world.
And the clock is ticking faster.
You watch over Credence. Keep him safe.
For the greater good.
(COUPLE SPEAKING FRENCH)
JACOB: You know what
I miss about Queenie?
Everything.
I even miss the stuff
that drove me nuts.
Like the mind reading.
(JACOB CHUCKLING)
(JACOB SIGHS)
I was lucky to have someone like her
even interested in anything I thought.
You know what I mean?
Sorry?
I was saying, you're sure
the guy is here that we're looking for?
Yeah, definitely. The feather says so.
(FEATHER TAPPING GLASS)
(EXHALES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(TAPPING GLASS)
JACOB: Is that the guy
we're looking for?
NEWT: Yes.
Ooh...
Sorry.
Bonjour. Bonjour, monsieur.
(IN ENGLISH) Oh, wait, no.
Sorry. So we actually...
We were just wondering
if you'd come across a friend of ours.
JACOB: Tina Goldstein.
Monsieur, Paris is a large city.
NEWT: She's an Auror.
And when Aurors go missing,
the Ministry tend to come looking, so...
No, I suppose it would probably
be better if we just report her absence.
Is she tall?
Dark? Rather...
- intense.
- Beautiful. She's...
JACOB: Yeah, what I meant to say was...
- No, she's very pretty.
- She's intense too.
I think I saw
someone like this last night.
Perhaps if I showed you where...
If you wouldn't mind. That would be...
- That would be lovely.
- Sure.
(JACOB CLEARING THROAT)
(GASPS)
Tina.
Newt.
- YUSUF: Expelliarmus.
- Oh!
(ALL YELPING)
My apologies, Mr. Scamander.
I shall return and release you
once Credence is dead.
Kama, wait.
You see, either he dies or I do.
No, no, no.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
(GROANING)
(THUDDING)
Well, that's not the best start
to a rescue attempt.
Oh, this was a rescue attempt?
You just lost me my only lead.
Well, how was the interrogation going
before we turned up?
(PICKETT SQUEAKS)
(JACOB LAUGHS)
JACOB: Newt!
Well done, Pick.
So you need this man, you said?
Yeah.
I think he knows
where Credence is, Mr. Scamander.
(ZOUWU ROARING)
Well, that'll be that Zouwu.
- (ROARING)
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Come on, Newt. Get outta there.
(ROARING)
(TOY TINKLING)
(PURRING)
(TINKLING)
(GASPS)
(ROARS)
(CROWD MURMURING)
Come on!
What were the three biggest mistakes
that you made last time?
(STUDENTS MURMURING)
- Caught by surprise, sir.
- DUMBLEDORE: Mmm.
What else?
Didn't parry before counter-curse, sir.
Very good. The last one?
The most important one?
(STUDENTS GASP)
Not learning from the first two.
- (ALL LAUGHING)
- (DOOR OPENS)
This is a school. You've no right.
I'm the Head of Magical Law Enforcement.
I have the right
to go wherever I please.
Out of here.
Go with Professor McGonagall, please.
(STUDENTS MURMURING)
He's the best teacher we've got.
- Thanks, McClaggan.
- TRAVERS: Get out.
Come, McClaggan.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Newt Scamander is in Paris.
Really?
Cut the pretense.
I know he's there on your orders.
Oh, if you'd ever had the pleasure
to teach him,
you'd know Newt is not
a great follower of orders.
You've read
The Predictions of Tycho Dodonus?
Mmm. Many years ago.
"A son cruelly banished."
"Despair of the daughter."
- "Return..."
- Yes, I know it.
There's a rumor this prediction
refers to the Obscurial.
They say that Grindelwald wants...
As a highborn henchman.
I've heard the rumor.
And yet, Scamander appears
wherever the Obscurial goes,
to protect him.
Meanwhile, you've built up
quite the little network
of international contacts.
However long you keep me
and my friends under surveillance,
you're not going to discover
plots against you, Travers,
because we want the same thing.
The defeat of Grindelwald.
(DUMBLEDORE SIGHS)
But I warn you, your policies
of suppression and violence
are pushing supporters into his arms.
I'm not interested in your warnings.
Now... (SIGHS)
It pains me to say it
because I don't like you...
(BOTH LAUGH)
But...
You are the only wizard
who is his equal.
I need you to fight him.
I can't.
Because of this?
You and Grindelwald
were as close as brothers.
Oh, we were closer than brothers.
Will you fight him?
I can't.
Well, then you have chosen your side.
From now on,
I shall know every spell you cast.
I'm doubling the watch on you,
and you will no longer teach
Defense Against the Dark Arts.
Where's Leta? We need to go to Paris.
DUMBLEDORE: Theseus.
Theseus, if Grindelwald calls a rally,
don't try and break it up.
Don't let Travers send you in there.
If you ever trusted me...
TRAVERS: Theseus.
Theseus!
(BELL RINGING)
GIRL #1: Even the name Lestrange
makes me feel sick.
You know she stays here every vacation.
Her family don't actually want her home.
GIRL #1: I don't blame them.
She's so annoying.
Did you see her last week?
Oscausi!
GIRL #2: Professor McGonagall!
Lestrange has done it again!
MCGONAGALL: Lestrange, stop running!
- Lestrange! Disobedient children.
- GIRL #3: Leta, come back!
Stop! Shame on the House of Slytherin.
A hundred points! Two hundred!
Get back here, right now!
Children, stop it! You, stop! Come back!
- BOY #1: Out of my way!
- BOY #2: Where has she gone?
BOY #3 I think she went that way!
Miss, it was Lestrange. She's horrible.
YOUNG LETA: Scamander,
why aren't you packing?
I'm not going home.
Why not?
- He needs me.
- (BABY BIRD CHIRPING)
He was hurt.
What is that?
A raven chick.
Isn't the raven your family emblem?
- YOUNG LETA: Yes, it is.
- (CHIRPING CONTINUES)
DUMBLEDORE: All right, Newt.
Be brave.
That's an unusual one.
So Mr. Scamander fears what
more than anything else in the world?
Having to work in an office, sir.
- (STUDENTS LAUGHING)
- Go ahead, Newt.
Riddikulus.
DUMBLEDORE: Well done.
- (STUDENTS APPLAUDING)
- Good job. Leta.
It's only a Boggart.
It can't hurt you.
Everyone is scared of something.
I've been looking forward to this.
(GASPS)
I don't want to talk about it.
YOUNG NEWT: They know me,
- or they'd hide.
- (SQUEAKING)
They only nest in trees
with wand-quality wood.
Did you know that?
And they have very complex social lives.
If you watch them for long enough,
you realize...
Hello, Leta. This is a surprise.
- Finding me in a classroom?
- (CHUCKLES)
Was I such a bad student?
On the contrary,
you were one of my cleverest.
I said "bad," not "stupid."
Don't bother answering.
I know you never liked me.
You're wrong.
I never thought you bad.
You were alone, then.
Everybody else did.
And they were right.
I was wicked.
Leta, I know how painful
the rumors about your brother Corvus
must be for you.
No, you don't.
Not unless
you had a brother who died, too.
In my case, it was my sister.
Did you love her?
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Not as well as I should have done.
Never too late to free yourself.
Confession is a relief, I'm told.
A great weight lifted.
Regret is my constant companion.
Do not let it become yours.
Oh! No, thank you.
Well...
You've been really kind,
but my sister Tina's probably
worried sick about me.
You know,
banging on all the doors and things,
so I think I'd better be going.
But you haven't met your host.
Oh, are you married?
Let's say,
deeply committed.
You see, I can't tell if you're
making a joke or if you're just...
(SIGHS) French.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh.
Hey, knock it off.
You stay right there.
I know what you are.
Queenie.
We are not here to hurt you.
We only want to help you.
You're so very, very far away from home.
Far away from everything you love,
everything that is comfortable.
I would never see you harmed.
Ever.
It is not your fault
that your sister is an Auror.
I wish you were working with me now
towards a world where
we wizards were free to live openly.
To love freely.
You are an innocent.
So go now.
Leave this place.
There you are.
What did Travers want?
Absolutely outrageous behavior.
Marching into a school like that.
It was all very mundane,
I'm fine, sorry, Minerva,
lot of marking.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
(ZOUWU GROWLING)
(NEWT GRUNTING)
JACOB: Hey, uh, Newt, buddy. Uh...
Tina's up here.
She's all by her lonesome,
and, uh, maybe you want to come up
and keep her company?
Uh, I've been looking for food,
and I ain't found any,
(ZOUWU SNIFFING)
So I guess I'm gonna go upstairs
and try my luck
in, oh, I don't know, the attic.
NEWT: You're all right.
Relashio.
Okay.
She's responded well to the Dittany.
She was born to run, you see.
But I think she's...
She's just lacking in confidence.
Mr. Scamander,
have you got anything in your case
that might help revive this man?
I need to question him.
I think he knows who Credence really is.
And the scars on his hand
- suggest an Unbreakable Vow.
- An Unbreakable Vow.
Yeah, I noticed that, too.
Lumos.
(GASPS)
What was that?
There must be
a Water Dragon in that sewer.
They carry these parasites,
you see. They, um...
- Jacob.
- Yeah?
In my case, in the pocket there,
you'll find a pair of tweezers.
Tweezers?
- They're thin, pointy...
- Little pointy things.
JACOB: Yes, I know what tweezers are.
All right.
You might not want to watch this.
I can handle it.
NEWT: Come out.
- (PARASITE SQUEALING)
- Come on. You're all right.
- Ew.
- Come on. I got you.
Jacob, will you take that for me?
Huh. Ugh!
Calamari.
Must kill him.
Who?
Credence?
NEWT: It may take him
a few hours to recover.
That parasite's poison is quite strong.
I have to go back to the Ministry
with what I've got.
It's nice to see you again,
Mr. Scamander.
JACOB: Hey. Hey.
Hold on a second, will ya?
Hold on. Hold on.
Wait! Tina.
You didn't mention salamanders, did you?
(STAMMERING) No, I didn't.
She just ran. I don't know...
So you chase after her.
Tina. Please, just listen to me.
Mr. Scamander, I need to go talk
to the Ministry.
I know how you feel about Aurors.
I may have been a little strong
in the way that I expressed myself
in that letter.
What was the exact phrase?
"A bunch of careerist hypocrites"?
I'm sorry, but I can't admire people
whose answer to everything that
they fear or misunderstand is "kill it."
I'm an Auror and I don't.
Yes, I know.
That's because you've gone middle head.
Excuse me?
It's an expression derived from
the three heads of the Runespoor.
So the middle one is the visionary.
Now, every Auror in Europe
wants Credence dead, except you.
You've gone middle head.
Who else uses that expression,
Mr. Scamander?
I think it might just be me.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
TINA: It's Grindelwald.
He's calling his followers.
It's too late.
Grindelwald has come for Credence.
- He might already have him.
- It's not too late.
We can still get to him first.
Where are you going?
The French Ministry of Magic.
That's the last place Credence would go.
There's a box
hidden in the Ministry, Tina.
It's a box that can tell us
who Credence really is.
A box? What are you talking about?
Trust me.
CREDENCE: You wanna come out,
just for a little while?
You can be free.
(BABY BIRD CHIRPING)
NAGINI: Credence.
(SHUSHING)
What do you want?
GRINDELWALD: From you?
Nothing.
For you?
Everything I never had.
But what is it you want, my boy?
I want to know who I am.
This is where you will find proof
of your true identity.
Come to Pére Lachaise tonight,
and you will discover the truth.
(GRINDELWALD DISAPPEARING)
Father, why did you make me...
JACOB: Wait...
(GASPS) Wait.
(CLEARING THROAT)
(STOMACH RUMBLING)
I'm afraid we keep no food in the house.
(STAMMERS) Are you a ghost?
No.
No. I'm alive.
But I'm an alchemist
and therefore immortal.
You don't look a day over 375.
(ALCHEMIST CHUCKLES)
I'm sorry that we didn't knock.
No. No matter.
Albus told me some friends
might be dropping in.
Nicolas Flamel.
Oh.
Jacob Kowalski.
- (BONE CRACKS)
- Oh!
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
- I didn't...
- Oh... on!
(PANTING)
At last, we see some development.
Yeah. I've seen one of these before.
(CLEARS THROAT) It was at the fair.
There was this dame there,
and she had a veil,
and I gave her a nickel,
and she told me about my future.
And she missed out
on quite a bit, actually.
Oh. Hey, hey.
Wait a minute, I know him.
That's the kid. That's Credence.
Jeez.
Hey... Hey!
That's Queenie. There she is. Hi, baby.
Where is this? Is this here?
Yes. This is the Lestrange tomb.
It lies in the cemetery
of Pere Lachaise.
I'm coming, baby. Stay right there.
Thank you, Mr. Flamel.
- Ouch.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay.
Oh, look after Mr. Tentacles for me.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry. I gotta go.
FLAMEL: Please,
you mustn't go to the cemetery.
(EXCLAIMS IN FRENCH)
(GASPS)
What's happening?
FLAMEL: Exactly what he said
would happen.
Grindelwald rallies
at the cemetery tonight,
and there will be death.
Then you gotta go.
What? I haven't seen action
in 200 years.
Flamel, you can do this.
We believe in you.
The box is in
the Ancestral Records room, Tina.
So it's three floors down.
Is that Polyjuice?
It's just enough to get me inside.
(NEWT GROANING)
- Who...
- It's my brother, Theseus.
He's an Auror and a hugger.
What's happening?
Grindelwald's rallying.
We don't know where,
but we think it's tonight.
- Be careful.
- Of course.
- Promise me you'll be careful.
- Of course. I'm gonna be careful.
Listen, I want you to hear this from me.
They think that Credence boy
might be your missing brother.
- My brother is dead.
- I know.
- He died.
- How many times, Theseus?
- And the records will prove that.
- Okay? They can't lie.
- Theseus.
I want every person at that rally
arrested. If they resist...
Sir, forgive me, but if we go in
too heavy,
- don't we run the risk of adding to...
- Just do it.
I don't suppose you can Disapparate
on Ministry premises in France, can you?
Nope.
(GRUNTING) Pity.
- Newt!
- Yes, I know. I know it's...
(ANNOUNCEMENT IN FRENCH ON PA)
THESEUS: Newt!
Newt!
- Oh!
- That's your brother?
So I think I may have mentioned
in my letters
that we have quite
a complicated relationship.
Newt, stop!
- Does he wanna kill you?
- Frequently.
Enough!
He needs to control his temper.
(GRUNTING)
I think that might have been
the best moment of my life.
Queenie.
Queenie, honey.
Don't. Don't move.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Yes, this is Leta Lestrange.
And, uh, I'm her...
Fiancé.
(TINA CLEARS THROAT)
Thank you.
(SWITCH CLICKS)
Tina, about that fiancée business...
Oh, sorry. Yeah, I should have
congratulated you.
- No, that's-
- Lu mos.
Lestrange.
Tina, about Leta...
Yes, I've just said I am happy for you.
No, I don't... Please, don't be happy.
No. Sorry. I don't...
- Obviously, I...
- (CLATTERS)
Obviously, I want you to be...
And I hear that you are now.
Which is wonderful.
Sorry, what I'm trying to say is,
I want you to be happy,
but I don't want you to be happy
that I'm happy, because I'm not...
- ..."happy".
- (SCOFFS)
Or engaged.
- What?
- It was a mistake in a stupid magazine.
My brother's marrying Leta,
June the 6th.
I'm supposed to be best man,
which is sort of mildly hilarious.
Does he think you're here
to win her back?
Are you here to win her back?
No, I'm here...
You know, your eyes really are...
Are what?
I'm not supposed to say.
- I cut a picture of you...
- Newt, I read your book and...
- Wait, did you read...
- Did you?
I cut this, um...
It's just a picture of you
from the paper,
but it's interesting
'cause your eyes in newsprint...
See, in reality they have
this effect in them, Tina. It's like...
It's like fire in water, in dark water.
And I've only ever seen that...
I've only ever seen that in...
(STAMMERING)
Salamanders.
(DOOR OPENS)
(GASPS)
Come.
LETA: Lestrange.
Whoa!
(LETA READING)
(PICKETT CHITTERS)
Circumrota.
Hello, Newt.
Hello, Leta.
Hi.
(CREATURES GROWLING)
NEWT: Oh, no.
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
TINA: What kind of cats are those?
NEWT: Uh, these aren't cats.
They're Matagots.
They're spirit familiars.
- They guard the Ministry.
- (GROWLING)
But they won't hurt you unless you...
Stupefy!
Unless you attack them.
Oops.
- Leta.
- LETA: Reverte.
(SNARLING)
(BOTH HISS)
(ROARING)
Accio!
(GRUNTING)
Ascendio!
(ALL SNARLING)
(MEOWING)
- (PURRING)
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Okay. Wait. Hold it there, please.
Come on. (GRUNTS)
Oh! (LAUGHING)
All right.
- (TINKLING)
- NEWT: Okay, wait.
- (PURRING)
- (TINKLING)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
YUSUF: You, go back.
Move! Out of the way!
If I must kill you as well as Corvus,
I shall.
Stop!
Yusuf.
Is that really you?
My little sister?
CREDENCE: So he's your brother.
Who am I?
I don't know.
I'm tired of living with no name
and no history.
Just tell me my story,
then you can end it.
Your story is our story.
- Our story.
- No, Yusuf.
YUSUF: My father was Mustafa Kama.
Pure-blood of Senegalese descent
and most accomplished.
My mother, Laurena,
was equally highbred, a noted beauty.
They were deeply in love.
They knew a man of great influence
from a famous French pure-blood family.
He desired her.
Maman. Maman!
Lestrange used the lmperius Curse
to seduce and abduct her.
I tried to prevent it,
but he attacked me.
That was the last time I ever saw her.
- She died giving birth to a little girl.
- (BABY COOING)
You.
The news of her death
drove my father insane.
With his dying breath,
my father charged me to seek revenge.
Kill the person Lestrange loves
best in the world.
I thought at first it'd be easy.
He had only one close relative.
You.
But he... (SIGHS)
Say it.
YUSUF: He never loved you.
He remarried,
and not three months after her death.
He loved her no more
than he had loved you.
But then his son, Corvus,
was born at last.
And that man who had never known love
was filled with it.
All he cared about
was little Corvus.
So this is the truth?
I am Corvus Lestrange?
- Yes. Yes.
- No. No.
YUSUF: Realizing that Mustafa Kama's
son had sworn revenge,
your father sought to hide you
where I couldn't find you.
So he confided you to his servant,
who boarded a ship for America.
- He did send Corvus to America, but...
- YUSUF: His servant, Irma Dugard,
was a half-elf.
Her magic was weak,
and therefore left no trace
I could follow.
I had only just discovered
how you had escaped
when I received news I never expected.
The ship had gone down at sea.
But you survived, didn't you?
Somehow, someone had pulled you
from the water.
"A son cruelly banished,
Despair of the daughter."
"Return, great avenger,
With wings from the water."
There stands the despairing daughter.
You are the winged raven,
returned from the sea,
but I'm the avenger of my family's ruin.
I pity you, Corvus.
But you must die.
Corvus Lestrange is already dead!
I killed him!
Accio!
My father owned
a very strange family tree.
It only recorded the men.
The women in my family
were recorded as flowers.
Beautiful.
Separate.
My father sent me to America
with Corvus.
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (WIND HOWLING)
Irma was to pose as a grandmother
with two grandchildren.
(CORVUS CRYING)
Corvus never stopped crying.
WOMAN: Do you have any news?
SAILOR: All hands to station!
- Run to station!
- (CRYING CONTINUES)
- LETA: I never wanted to hurt him.
I only wanted to be free of him.
Just for a moment.
- Just a single moment.
- (CRYING CONTINUES)
Give him to me.
SAILOR: Everyone, to the lifeboats!
WOMAN: They want us
to put on life jackets.
(CORVUS CRYING)
(BLOWING)
(SNIFFLES)
NEWT: You didn't mean to do it, Leta.
So it wasn't your fault.
Oh, Newt.
You never met a monster
you couldn't love.
TINA: Leta...
Do you know who Credence really is?
Did you know when you swapped them?
No.
(RUMBLING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
JACOB: Queenie?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
They're pure-bloods.
They kill the likes of us for sport.
Queenie?
Jacob! (GASPS)
Honey, you're here! Hi!
Hi, hon. Hi.
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
I never should have done it.
I love you so much.
And you know that I love you, right?
- Yeah.
- Good. Let's get the hell outta here.
Oh, no, wait a second.
I just thought maybe we could
hear him first.
Just listen. That's all.
What are you talking about?
It's a trap.
Yeah.
Queenie, the family tree.
It's all been bait.
We have to find a way out of here
right now.
You go find the others.
What are you gonna do?
I'll think of something.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
My brothers, my sisters,
my friends,
the great gift of your applause
is not for me. No.
It is for yourselves.
You came today because of a craving
and a knowledge
that the old ways serve us no longer.
You came today because you crave
something new.
Something different.
It is said
that I hate les non-Magiques.
The Muggles.
- MAN: Vermin!
- GRINDELWALD: The No-Maj.
The Can't-Spells.
I do not hate them.
I do not.
For I do not fight out of hatred.
I say the Muggles are not lesser,
but other.
Not worthless,
but of other value.
Not disposable,
but of a different disposition.
Magic blooms
only in rare souls.
It is granted to those
who live for higher things.
Oh, and what a world we would make
for all of humanity.
We who live for freedom,
for truth,
and for love.
It isn't illegal to listen to him.
Use minimum force on the crowd.
We mustn't be what he says we are.
The moment has come
to share my vision of the future
that awaits if we do not rise up
and take our rightful place
in the world.
(GRINDELWALD INHALING DEEPLY)
(GASPING)
(GUNFIRE)
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING IN FEAR)
Not another war.
That is what we are fighting.
That is the enemy.
Their arrogance.
Their power lust.
Their barbarity.
How long will it take
before they turn their weapons on us?
Do nothing when I speak of this.
You must remain calm
and contain your emotions.
There are Aurors here among us.
(PANICKED MURMURING)
Come closer, brother wizards. Join us.
Do nothing.
And no force.
GRINDELWALD: They have killed
many of my followers.
It is true.
They confined me
and tortured me in New York.
They had struck down
their fellow witches and wizards.
For the simple crime
of seeking the truth.
For wanting freedom.
Your anger, your desire for revenge
is natural.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
GRINDELWALD: No!
Take this young warrior
back to her family.
Disapparate.
Leave.
Go forth from this place
and spread the word.
It is not we who are violent.
Let's take him.
(SCREAMING)
Aurors, join me in this circle.
Pledge to me
your eternal allegiance,
or die.
Only here shall you know freedom.
Only here shall you know yourself.
AUROR: Move! Run! Run!
Play by the rules!
- No cheating, children.
- (AURORS SCREAMING)
He knows who I am.
He knows what you were born,
not who you are!
NEWT: Credence!
Queenie, honey. Queenie.
You gotta wake up.
Jacob.
He's the answer.
He wants what we want.
- No.
- Yeah.
This has all been for you, Credence.
Walk with me.
Hon. No!
Walk with me!
You're crazy.
Queenie.
No!
Queenie, don't do it!
Queenie.
TINA: Queenie!
GRINDELWALD: Mr. Scamander.
Do you think Dumbledore
will mourn for you?
LETA: Grindelwald! Stop!
Leta...
(GRUNTING)
GRINDELWALD:
This one I believe I know.
Leta Lestrange.
Despised entirely amongst wizards,
unloved, mistreated,
yet brave, so very brave.
Time to come home.
I love you.
Go!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(STRUGGLING)
I hate Paris.
(YELPS)
(ROARING)
(NEWT SHOUTS)
(WIZARDS YELLING)
Together, in a circle.
Your wand into the earth.
Or all Paris will be destroyed.
(ROARING)
BOTH: Finite!
Finite!
(ROARING)
(SCREECHING)
(YELLING)
(ALL PANTING)
(JACOB CRYING)
(SNIFFLES)
(THESEUS CRYING)
I've chosen my side.
(NIFFLER CHITTERS)
Oh.
Come here.
I've got you. I've got you.
(NIFFLER SNIFFING)
I think it's best
if he speaks to him alone.
GRINDELWALD:
Is he frightened of me still?
You need to be careful.
He's not sure he made the right choice.
Be very gentle with him.
I have a gift for you, my boy.
DUMBLEDORE: Is it true?
About Leta?
Yes.
I'm so sorry.
It's a blood pact, isn't it?
You swore not to fight each other.
How in the name of Merlin
did you manage to get...
(CHUCKLES)
Grindelwald doesn't seem to understand
the nature of the things
he considers simple.
Can you destroy it?
Maybe.
Would he like a cup of tea?
He'll have some milk.
Hide the teaspoons.
(GRUNTING)
GRINDELWALD: You have suffered
the most heinous of betrayals,
most purposely bestowed upon you
by your own blood.
Your own flesh and blood.
And just as
he has celebrated your torment,
your brother seeks to destroy you.
(CHIRPING)
There is a legend in your family
that a phoenix will come to any member
who is in dire need.
(SCREECHING)
It is your birthright, my boy.
As is
the name I now restore to you.
Aurelius.
Aurelius Dumbledore.
We will go down in history together
as we remake this world.