Despite being a quarter mile apart,
Paul hasn't gone anywhere.
He's with us forever.
We are family.
You watch too many movies?
I think you're cuckoo.
Playing too many games?
You guys.
Are you just talk or do you wanna race?
You really watch too many movies.
Hey, Pon.
Wake up.
It's late.
-Your night races are ruining your sleep.
-I'm awake.
You have trouble getting up every morning.
Hurry.
One moment.
Hey.
-Pon, wake up.
-One more minute.
Pon, get up!
Get up! Get up!
One minute!
I told you to get up!
Fuck! With your lazy ass, when are you
going to be well off like others?
When will you be rich?
Wife, listen to me.
We are family.
Family, my ass!
I hate your face enough.
Don't make me hate your voice, too.
We humans...
do not have equal chances to be rich.
But we all do have equal chances
to do good deeds.
Yeah?
How about my foot there?
Want some more?
You can't be rich with your lazy ass.
The rich get richer.
The poor get poorer.
Don't think too much about it.
Be like a plastic bag.
How?
Fly here, fly there.
But live for a hundred years, dear.
"Dear"?
Philosopher!
You're nonsense.
I'm going to work now.
Hang in there, okay, Dad?
Okay? Hang in there.
Dilly-dallying?
Finish feeding him, then go to work!
And hurry back.
Look.
Nothing gets done
as a result of taking care of your dad
being paralyzed for many years.
Go to work and come home.
Don't stop anywhere, okay, Vin?
Mom! Stop complaining.
Cheer me up.
So I can go to work.
-Cheer you up? Amen.
-So we'll be rich.
Let that wish come true.
-Come on.
-You've been saying that for years.
Let me kiss you.
No. Hurry up and go.
Come on.
No!
Hugs, hugs.
-Hurry up and go.
-Are you shy?
-Go!
-Okay, Mom. Bye.
-Buy some food on the way home.
-Bye, Dad.
-Okay.
-I don't want to cook.
Bye, Mom.
Bye. Take care of him.
Pon!
It's late. Coming?
-Hey, bro.
-What?
What happened to your face?
I told you. You deserve this.
-Whose blood is it?
-My wife's.
You slapped her so hard,
her blood splashed on your face?
My action scene is this awesome.
Hey. How many times have I told you
not to call me Pon?
-So what do I call you?
-Paul.
-No.
Paul.
-Paul.
Enough! Fuck!
You didn't shit this morning?
Your brain is full of shit.
Not true.
Close the door.
Hey.
Ingrain this in your brain.
-Don't have a wife.
-Because?
When you start dating, she's still a Thai.
After a while, she'll be check...
Czechoslovakian?
Check you morning, noon, and night.
You can't go anywhere.
What? So why do you have a wife?
It's better than a hand.
Don't you know "Sperm Murder"?
That's it.
Paul!
Wait for me!
Hey, hurry, Davika.
I am. This skirt is tight.
-Let's go.
-Pon?
Still here?
Well, well, well, Davika.
Let go of my husband.
If I find out you two have something...
Move away from him.
Mia.
I won't get involved when you're looking.
I always do.
He's so handsome. I can't look away.
-We're going now.
-Wait.
Forget something?
Bye, my ass!
Good!
You have to wai your wife?
Yes, sir.
-No arguing?
-Yes.
So cute.
I'm going to wash the clothes now.
It serves you right!
Not only is my wife beautiful...
she's also a klutz.
Falls down everyday.
Her womb must have moved.
Let's go.
The bus for hire
Runs on the road parallel to the highway
Sit, sit.
Sit down, sit.
It's so hot.
Why sit so close to me?
It's got to be you.
Every day.
Hey, Vin.
Is your dad better now?
What? My dad is not that bad.
What the heck? I meant your dad's health.
I see. He's better now.
The day that you and your mom
were not at home,
it was lucky I went in there.
Or your dad would have been...
Vin!
Vin.
It's not locked?
What? Papa?
Mom! Mom!
Vin!
Shit. Who dropped him here? Papa?
Mom? Vin?
Easy. Easy, Papa.
What, Papa? We're not at the hospital yet.
Almost there.
Pon.
If it hadn't been for you that day,
my dad would have died.
I love you.
No need to love me so much.
Let me ask you this.
If you saw your dad drowning,
would you help him?
Of course. My dad.
Good.
Well, let me ask you this.
If you were on a boat
and saw your parents drowning,
and you could only help one of them,
who would that be?
-Mom, of course.
-Fuck your dad?
What about you?
Here. We're here.
Come.
Asshole.
What's going on there?
Come on.
Hey, show him!
What's going on?
They're hitting a handicapped person.
Nobody is helping?
Who's gonna help? He's a cop's son.
But a cop's son shouldn't be
hitting a handicapped person.
You. Help him!
What?
Hurry.
He has a knife.
Yeah, yeah.
Beat him to death!
Stop!
-Beat him to death!
-Stop!
Beat him to death!
I told you guys to stop!
Watch out.
Hey!
-What did you do to my wife?
-Your wife?
-Yeah.
-All right.
Kill him, my love.
Kill him?
Shut up.
I'm a cop's son.
I'm a security guard's son.
-Here.
-Gun!
What?
I'll call the cops.
You're hooligans.
My dad is a cop.
My dad is a cop, too.
My dad is also a cop.
Tell them your dad has cancer.
-My dad has cancer. What's wrong with you?
-Your dad really has cancer.
Still standing around?
-What?
-Want some?
Let's go!
-This bitch ran her mouth.
-This side.
Get her.
What are you doing to my wife?
If you don't want her
to be stomped to death,
give me the knife.
You want it? Here.
I think it is a knife for anchovies.
-How do you know?
-So stinky!
I know your dad is a cop.
But think,
being a cop's son
means you can't hurt people.
You can't hurt a handicapped person.
Don't disgrace your dad's police uniform.
Your dad is a cop, I am...
a bus driver.
Here. Bus conductor.
-Here. Bus conductress.
-Yeah!
I never brag to anyone. Dumbass!
Yeah.
-Don't come around here again. Go away!
-Go!
I'll tell my dad.
Dum, let's go home. Start the engine.
Go away!
Awesome!
He's looking at me.
What?
We'll see.
There.
Paul!
I'll go with you.
Are you crazy?
You're on a different bus and round
from me. You can't come with me.
My bus has left.
I missed it.
Was busy with the cop's son.
I'll catch up with my bus.
Okay, come on.
Hurry.
And where are you going?
Go on with making a living.
You're badly hurt.
Why don't you report it to the cops?
There's no point reporting it.
Yeah, you're right.
We all know...
who's big in this country.
I don't know who's big.
But I know mine is long.
-Are we talking about the same thing?
-You haven't seen mine.
What are you doing?
Come here, Vin!
What?
When did you get on the bus?
Same time as you.
I was here and didn't see you.
I got on through the front door.
And you didn't tell me.
I was waiting for you.
All over my eye.
Well, well, well.
Hello, sir. I like your work.
I'm a big fan of yours.
-Calm down.
-Don't come close.
I'm going to commit suicide.
Wait. Listen to me.
Listen to me. Calm down.
Focus and talk to me.
Please. Tell me what's on your mind.
What's going on?
I...
told my girlfriend
to meet on a bus.
We'd meet every day.
But it's been eight days!
She never came to see me.
Shit. Eight days?
I can't take it anymore. I'm so depressed.
I want to die.
Please, please. Chill.
Chill. Listen to me.
We have only one chance to be born,
only once. And you don't know
if you'll be born again.
Think about your mom and dad
who raised you.
They want to see your future.
If you do something, how would they feel?
If you die,
how will they live their lives?
Who would they be with?
Girls are like a washing machine.
If you don't have one,
then you hand-wash your clothes.
-That's right.
-Hand-wash?
I'd rather die.
Stop!
Even though you have a face
like a dog's elbow
and your mouth
is like skin under the foot,
I believe, really believe, that one day
no one would ever love you.
Shit!
If you're gonna talk shit about me,
let's fight.
What?
You're so mean.
No more. I'm going to jump.
Calm down.
Don't jump.
Thank you very much
for letting me help you.
You are incredible!
You helped him.
Yeah, yeah.
Aren't you jumping off a bridge today?
I want to die!
Can't take it anymore. Ma'am.
Help me.
My life is so tough.
My girlfriend left me.
I'm all alone.
My love isn't coming back.
Stop me. I'm going to jump.
Stop me now.
Stop me, pull me back.
Good, pull me back...
You!
You remember me, right?
I'm about to commit suicide.
Stop me, stop me now.
Jump! Go ahead!
-You're not worried about my parents?
-Fuck them.
-Jump!
-Go ahead.
Kick me! Kick me now.
I'm about to jump, so kick me.
Nah. You're not worth kicking.
I would like to suggest something.
On my bus,
don't jump off the bus.
Or I'll really kick your ass.
No. Who would do such a thing?
If my girlfriend comes and doesn't see me,
she'll be sad.
I really want to see how beautiful
your girlfriend is.
Very.
Yeah.
All right, let's go.
Leaving.
What?
He'll hear it.
There.
Hurry. The bus is leaving.
Sit down, sit down.
Sit, sit.
Are you okay?
I'm all right.
Hanging around for so long
and getting on at the last moment.
Life is too precious
to mess with bus number 888.
RAMA VIII - HAPPYLAND
Pon! Stop fooling around. The next bus
will catch up and take the passengers.
Okay.
Sorry.
Hey.
I told you to cut the brake line.
How is he still able to stop the bus?
You told me to put a phone there.
You have to call the number
-to activate the cutting.
-Really?
Give me the phone.
I didn't bring it with me.
Me, neither.
What? How can we cut the brake line, then?
It's all right. I'll borrow his phone.
I don't have one.
-I do.
-Why're you going to give it to him?
Come on. We have the same enemy.
-I won't let you borrow it.
-Stingy.
-I won't.
-It's only a phone.
Hey!
No fighting on my bus!
Get off if you're going to fight.
-Bus fares.
-Here.
Do I have to?
Here.
Bus fare.
For two.
Two?
Okay.
All done, Pon. Now!
Okay!
We need to reach the target.
Our income has been down
these past few days.
The boss is bitching us.
Hey, isn't it fast enough?
I've already floored it,
my foot is almost out to the headlight.
You're exaggerating!
Passengers are weird these days.
If we drive too fast,
they think we have taken speed.
Too slow, they think we are losers.
Do they know that I drive this fast
to earn a living for my family?
How about we get 1,000 people today?
I'll make it 2,500.
Okay.
Vin!
Tell Paul to stop if he sees my bus.
I need to get off.
Tell Paul!
Vin!
Did you hear me?
-Fuck! I heard you.
-Pon, the bus!
What's all the fuss?
I don't want to hear your voice anymore.
I can't drive!
What?
Go drive the bus! We'll all fucking die!
Don't you want to die?
I don't want to die with you. Go!
Go!
Just give me the phone and end it.
You said you'd let me borrow it.
No, I didn't.
Fuck!
Hey, Pon!
Hey!
What the hell?
Stop!
Hey, stop.
-Stop.
-No.
I said, "stop."
I told you to stop!
Come back and drive!
Pon!
And you!
What about me?
I told you to stop!
What is with all the talking?
Why talk so much?
-Pon!
-I want to say...
I don't want to hear you anymore.
We're gonna hit something.
Fucking Pon!
No one is driving!
My balls.
-Move.
-What the hell?
Shouldn't have left the seat.
No more fighting!
Don't blame me.
And why do you have to fight all the time?
Stop to pick up the Magic Monkey.
Must be going to Southern Asia.
-Should have stayed home with that makeup.
-Bus fare.
What color is your foundation?
Probably a wrong one.
Oh, you look shy.
More passengers at the next stop.
Right here.
Open the doors.
The day you let go of my hand,
I went crazy
Been calling you until my tears dried up
Could you not leave me like this?
Please, please
Let's sit over there.
Bus fares.
You can take a bus now?
Of course, when we travel
with someone we love.
I can go with him anywhere.
Pon!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Pon.
In the past, she wouldn't get on a bus.
She said it's for the poor and it's hot.
But now, she said
she can do it to please her lover.
Damn, you puppy.
Stop sobbing, you little puppy.
I'll tell you something.
As long as your face
is not even half as handsome as mine,
your heart will always be broken.
You're making it worse!
It's not my intention,
but it's the way I am.
You can be sad, but don't kill yourself.
There is no bridge around here.
Fuck you! Want to get your ass kicked?
Men are taught to be tough
Men cannot whine
No matter how hard the situation is
Men have to bear with it
With broken hearts, or disappointment
Men cannot be sad
Must keep their chin up
You can take it, right, real man?
Your Holiness.
What are you doing?
It's heavy, isn't it?
Did you really need to say that?
It's almost 10:00 a.m.
Nobody's in the market.
A little bit longer, to get the cart full.
-Your Holiness...
-Police! Run!
Police! Let's go!
Your Holiness.
Your Holiness!
-Your Holiness.
-Hurry. Go straight.
Your Holiness.
Police. Let's go.
No talk, just run.
-Run.
-Your Holiness.
Leave anything that falls. Hurry up.
Run, run.
Your Holiness.
Hurry, hurry.
Stop, stop!
What the heck?
Are you okay?
Let us in.
You surprised me! Get on!
Get on. Hurry.
Are you okay?
No.
What's happening?
-Sit.
-Your Holiness.
Drive carefully.
What a hellish driver.
Your Holiness.
Hi. I'd like to make merit.
He just wanted to make merit,
and chased us this far to do it?
You, hold this.
Give me.
Stopped a bus just to make merit.
Next time, you'll probably
hold a charity, Sergeant.
Are you done?
Please bless me.
Okay.
Age, Skin,
Happiness, Para... cetamol.
Para... cetamol.
-Are you done yet?
-Yes, yes.
Damn. Stopped the bus to make merit.
The next bus is coming.
-Come on.
-Kid.
For two.
Monks go free.
Government employees and monks go free.
Here. Kid.
No fares?
Yeah. How long have you been a monk?
Long time.
-You forgot or you have Alzheimer's?
-I don't take a bus often.
Let me ask you something.
What were you thinking running after me?
I don't know.
I saw you shouting something.
I panicked, so I ran.
I see.
Yes, panic.
How long have you been a monk?
Nine terms.
Nine terms?
-Are you sure you're a real monk?
-You said it, not me.
So you're not a real monk?
Are you crazy? Are you trying to frame me?
Do you know Monk Jazz?
Yeah, that son of a bitch.
He's really famous now.
Five hundred million.
Five hundred million, of course.
He is really handsome.
No. Monk Jazz at Wat Saket.
Not the one in the movie.
Different Jazz, then.
I know the one at Wat Sakae.
I see.
It's so hot, sister!
Hang in there.
Our van broke down.
I'm taking you to catch a bus.
Why not a taxi?
You crazy? What are you thinking?
No money for taxis.
Our clients haven't paid us.
It's so hot that we're melting.
Stop!
If you complain, I'll take back
all the money for boobs.
Do you know Monk Thepmahayan?
That's every monk.
Monks don't wear an underwear.
Bus 888.
Please stop.
Step up here, girls.
Come on up.
Stop!
-Don't sit! Your dress will wrinkle.
-Yes, ma'am.
Stand.
All wrinkled.
Do I need to tell you every time?
Cover your boobs.
I'm a monk, not a ghost.
I'm so sorry. We're booth girls.
Our dresses are quite revealing.
There's nothing there.
Well, I haven't got them done.
Take care of yourself. Cover your boobs.
All right, just sit.
Forget about the dresses. Just sit.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Pervert! Sister!
Are you harassing her?
-Well...
-You're harassing her?
No.
-Yes?
-No. Stop!
You're framing me.
Do you have proof?
Is there a CCTV? Play it.
No need.
That's very clear.
It's hard here but not anywhere else.
Follow my hand.
Sit down. Sit. And...
Don't be a pervert anymore, okay?
Yikes! Your smell.
Sit and cover your boobs.
They are too stimulating.
Go sit!
-What are you doing?
-What is that?
Hey. Look at how you dress.
Disrespecting the bus.
Not nice.
Sit still.
Lord.
-Lord.
-Buddha.
What?
Hey!
Where are they?
Where are all the big boobs?
-They got off.
-When?
They all got off.
Why didn't you wake me up?
Well, I saw you asleep
and didn't want to bother you.
No one woke me up.
-Why didn't you get off with them?
-Be quiet!
What?
Hey!
-What are you guys talking about?
-What?
Done? The bus is coming.
One moment.
Lad Phrao, The Mall Bang Kapi...
-Hurry. The bus is here.
-Okay, okay.
Here. Hundred each.
The bus is here. Let's go.
Get on, hurry.
Let's go.
Hey.
No adults are giving up seats for kids?
What? There are empty seats. Sit.
-Do I have to use my hand here?
-Relax.
Why are you angry with me?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Who are you talking to?
I don't know.
My bad.
What are you doing?
Touching up.
You don't need any more.
It's as white as a temple wall.
I'm cute, aren't I?
Cute like a monkey!
And you're pretty like a buffalo!
A buffalo.
You, too.
Passengers next stop.
Wait.
How do you know?
-How does he know?
-Look.
Wait.
That's a dead body!
Come on up.
Through the window is easier.
-Okay.
-Yeah, through the window.
-Go help them.
-Damn!
No one's gonna help?
Come on up.
Lift.
Catch.
Hurry.
What the heck?
Come on, come on.
Don't pull his head.
Take the gurney, too.
Come on, come on.
Take me in.
Turn, turn, turn.
-Turn it.
-Put him on the floor.
You two didn't even think
to help us at all?
It's against the rules.
Your Holiness.
-Anything I can help with?
-It's done.
See? Even the crazy person wanted to help.
I'm not crazy.
I came here to apply for...
The Voyyy Singing Contest.
What's your name?
Theppitak Aesala.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Where are you going?
Go ahead and sing.
Prepare to handle all the flirts
From now on we'll be choo-be-dub-be-doo
'Cause something like that
Happened to me before, so I never forget
Enough! Stop!
Go ahead.
Go ahead towards the exit.
Are you sure you're not the Magic Monkey?
I'm gonna go drive now. Move.
Get out of my way.
Everyone, sit down.
We're leaving.
Kid.
What is this bus? You take on everything?
Don't complain, please.
We are all equally worth something.
What the fuck? You startled me.
What's wrong with you?
Taking "hem" to hospital?
"Hem" who?
Hemorrhoids.
What's up?
He's sick with many illnesses.
Cancer, diabetes, heart disease,
high blood pressure.
No. What's up with your face?
I had it tattooed.
-Where?
-In prison.
Okay. Never mind.
RAMA VIII - HAPPYLAND
Hey, bro.
You left long before me.
How come I caught you?
What are you saying?
Louder, my eyesight is bad.
Your listening is bad.
Why? What's up?
Up for a race?
Who are you challenging, four-eyes?
You!
I've been driving since before
your mom and dad met each other.
Don't let him win, bro.
-I'm not scared.
-Show him.
I've been the bus champion
since I was a sperm.
Get your binoculars ready to see
the rear end of my bus, fuckface!
Fowl mouth, camel-balls head!
-I'll tell you this...
-What?
Lollygaggers like you
never become winners.
Stop running your mouth and just race.
Donkey-feet face!
Pon. I'm getting off here.
Go, go. Hurry.
I miss you.
Miss me for what?
See you in the evening.
I miss you already.
Evening? You've seen my wife?
Yikes. Don't make me throw up. Go!
Open the door.
Hey, wait!
-What?
-Tell your driver. Life means something.
Don't risk it with Paul Walker.
My head!
Sorry. You're in my way.
Hey, you know what? After the race,
you'll know I'm Vin S.H.
Paul!
Bye, bye, Paul!
Get on the bus.
Is that hair or a scourer?
Let's go. My robe is all wet.
My dear passengers,
it's time to hold on to your seats.
Let's go!
Paul!
Pon, they're behind us. Hurry.
Hurry, bro.
Hurry.
Go!
Hey, don't let him win.
Let's go.
Don't let them win!
Sit in your seat!
They're coming.
Skunk, skunk!
Paul is winning, he's winning!
Bitch!
Come after me.
Pon, show him.
Try to beat me.
Don't let him win, okay?
RAMA VIII - HAPPYLAND
Hurry, hurry.
Hey, someone is sick.
Brother, I'm scared.
Don't be scared. I'm right here.
Are you what I think you are?
How could that be?
What about you?
Yes.
So I guess one of them.
Go back to cheering. Let's go!
-What the hell?
-Gear stick.
Put it back.
Awesome!
-Paul is winning!
-Here.
What's happening?
Right.
Hey.
Where are you going?
Is there a snake?
Can't hold it anymore.
It got me!
Help! Somebody help!
There's a snake biting my balls.
You!
It's even worse now.
Somebody help me.
Hurry up. Hurry.
Hurry.
Help me!
Pon!
Aren't you getting off?
I don't know.
What do you know?
Why are you playing with a snake?
I'm not playing. It's biting my balls.
Help him.
-I'm scared of snakes.
-What?
Scared of a snake?
-Where's the snake?
-I'm not scared of snakes.
Look. Right here.
If you're not scared, then help me.
-Okay.
-Don't worry about me. Mind the snake.
Hurry. Come help.
Hurry.
Stop!
This isn't helping.
I used to be a nurse. I'll help you.
It must be hungry
and must have mistaken that for a rat
and swallowed it.
Don't pull,
rather let it swallow the whole thing.
Then pull it hard.
Hey, the snake's head is still there.
No. It's my penis.
Don't worry. I can suck up the venom.
Live sucking. Never seen it before.
You're all right. There's no more venom.
Girl, a python doesn't have venom.
What? So what did I just suck out?
My venom.
Serves you right. Sucking without asking.
Some must have gone down your throat.
-Pon, are you all right?
-Bring the gurney.
I can take the snake bite.
But when she sucked me...
What?
I'm exhausted.
Bring the gurney.
Hurry up, bro!
Hurry up.
Lay down.
Bro, let's retrieve what we hid.
Let's go.
Lift him up. Come on.
Hey, what are you doing?
Let's go.
Easy.
Go, go.
Up there, help him.
Get on the bus.
Help! Help! The snake is squeezing me.
Help. The snake is squeezing me.
Don't bite me, okay?
Who can drive a bus?
No.
Can anyone drive a bus?
Me. I can drive.
Go ahead then. Take him to hospital.
-Okay, okay.
-Hurry.
You can do everything? Are you crazy?
Yes, I am.
We're all right now.
You're okay, right?
I'm sorry. Before going to the hospital,
let's dress the wound.
-Go ahead.
-Wait.
-Okay.
-Girl.
After him, could you help me, too?
-What's wrong with you?
-Hemorrhoids.
Easy. Use a rubber band.
Open it.
Are you crazy? Show my penis
to all these people?
It's swollen to the size of a cat's head.
It's not appealing.
I'm sorry. I need eyewitnesses.
No need.
Easy, bro.
Let me sterilize it.
Put a lot on.
Why scream?
It's to kill germs.
Kill germs, or me?
You sprayed the whole thing, bitch?
Okay, okay. Let's get started.
Let me put on gloves. So it's clean.
Other side.
Sorry, sorry.
-Bitch!
-Easy, girl.
Carefully put them on.
Great. You hit yourself.
We'll sterilize it and then suture.
-Do you have anesthetic?
-One moment. Sorry. Can I borrow it?
-What are you doing?
-One moment.
-Numbing it.
Numb, my ass. It hurts!
Not there yet.
He's injured. Please help him.
Hang in there.
We'll take you to the hospital.
Enough.
My head!
Calm down. You'll soon be at the hospital.
You're so capable.
Thank you.
-Nurse.
-Yeah.
Wash it sometimes.
I always wash it. It's a sweaty day.
It's so smelly, you pole dancer.
-Hush! Or I'll cut your suture.
-Stuck in my nose.
What'd you bandage my face for?
My penis hurts, not my face.
Take it off.
Right now?
Yes.
Don't just look at it.
What are you doing? Grooming?
-Let's go!
-Okay, okay.
He's almost dead.
Hey...
Be calm and collected.
I don't care.
Ready?
I've been ready.
Let's go to the hospital.
So painful!
Calm down, Grandpa.
Wait... Well... teacher...
Soon you'll be dead.
You'll soon be at the hospital.
Drive faster! He's almost dead.
You two are not helping,
just cursing me to death.
Move. We're in a rush to the hospital.
Hang on tight.
Don't get too excited.
Get out of the way!
Help him sit.
Be careful, your Holiness.
So, how is he? Dead?
Looks dead.
Not yet.
-Pull over! I want to get off.
-Why?
Pull over!
You guys. He's dead.
Dead?
What the hell?
Not breathing anymore!
Somebody's dead?
What the hell?
Everything is wrong here.
Shit.
Move! We need to go to the hospital.
Why'd you bring me on this crappy bus?
All this commotion.
I didn't know it'd be like this.
By now, I should have been home.
Yeah.
What would my mom say?
Somebody take a look at him.
Dead or alive? Fuck.
Yikes!
Bro, it's your phone.
-You stole my phone?
-Yes.
No! You dropped it over there.
Can I borrow it to make a call?
-You need it?
-Yes.
What's the number?
-0-8-8...
-8-8-8...
-8-8-8-8.
-Here.
-I think I'll die before I get home.
-Want to get off at the next stop?
-Okay, okay. Ring the bell.
Thank you very much.
It rang, but nobody answered.
Quick. Ring it.
This stop, please!
It rang, but nobody answered.
-What number did you call?
-0-8-8-8-8-8-8-8-8-8.
Whose number is that?
The number to cut the brake line.
-Cut the brake line?
-Fuck!
The brakes aren't working!
What? The brakes aren't working.
-I didn't mean to.
-You didn't mean to?
It wasn't me.
The brakes are just not working.
Red light!
Station One to Station Two.
A bus ran a red light.
Code 40. Tien Ruammit intersection.
There are some injured.
Please send an ambulance, stat.
Calm down. Focus.
The bus could crash and kill us all.
Shut the fuck up.
Don't worry.
I'm used to handling responsibilities.
-I'm scared, I'm scared.
-What are you mumbling?
Are you drunk?
Move.
He's cutting us off.
Everybody, stop!
Find a way to stop the bus. Or...
I'll kill myself.
Okay.
Go ahead, shoot yourself.
Come on.
Stop. If you don't stop me,
I'll shoot at my heart.
Go ahead.
Hey!
Are you gonna shut up now?
Sit down. Sit!
Are you crazy? Carrying a gun on the bus.
It's dangerous, you know?
Or you're a criminal
who has just robbed a bank?
Or you're a kidnapper. Who are you?
Why do you have a gun?
Why? Want to be the first to die?
Dumbass! That's all you got?
-Are you gonna sit down? Go.
-Okay.
Calm down, okay?
-Shut the hell up!
-He's just sick.
The blonde head.
Hey!
Why are you jumpy? Call the police.
Tell them the brakes aren't working.
Hurry.
I called a meeting today...
because I really need help.
I have been chasing them all over.
But I still can't catch them.
To tell you the truth...
many people are also chasing them.
That's why I called you guys here.
All hands on deck.
Understand?
If we can catch them,
it will be your success.
Do you have something to report?
I want to tell you that this morning...
I caught one of them.
-Slowball.
-You're good.
Amazing.
Why didn't you tell me?
I secretly did it.
I heard that one of them
is in our station.
I was gonna tell you
that it's in your office.
-Really?
-Yes.
Yes. Wait.
Hey! Wait.
Stay still. I found it.
-Right in front of your face.
-Really?
Here it is. Stay still.
Dodging?
Wait. You stay still.
Stay still. This way.
Don't dodge. Damn. No more balls.
-Boss. Here, I found it.
-What?
It's yellow, isn't it?
-Hey. It's with me?
-Same one. Boss, stay still.
-Fuck. Get this!
-Hey...
-That's our boss.
-Sorry.
-Boss.
-What's up?
We got a 191 call. The brakes of bus
number 888 aren't working.
It's now on Ratchada Road,
which is in our jurisdiction.
Tell everyone on the bus
to get a grip and calm down.
I'll go there immediately.
Let me catch a Pokémon.
-Where is it now?
-Boss? I think we should go now.
-Why?
-In our area,
there should be a lot of them
because there are courts.
I've found so many of them. All beautiful.
Here. 1,500-1,600 XP. High points.
All beautiful.
Where?
-Poseidon, sir.
-That's a Pokémon?
A masseuse.
Yeah. Yes, sir.
Okay, sir.
Everybody, relax.
Calm down.
Right now the police are chasing Pokémons.
No. They are finding a way to help us.
Wait, guys. Calm down.
The police are coming.
Thai police can do a lot of things.
Catch criminals, drugs, set up checkpoints
by electric poles to surprise the bikers.
And this is a serious case,
catching Pokémons.
They are not easy to find.
When are you gonna stop being delusional?
The bus can't stop. What should we do?
-Stop!
-Move. I want them to see us.
Did you hear something?
What?
Clock.
Correct. It's a clock.
That's because I put a time bomb
on this bus.
Bomb! Bomb!
It will all go off at once.
Boom.
-Done.
-Very good.
-Nobody saw us.
-Great. Let's go home.
No. I didn't plot any bomb.
And I didn't cut any brake line.
Then let's go.
Remember us?
Think.
Think. Think.
That fucker is looking at me.
He might be one of your friends.
I don't have a friend like this.
Bro, he's choking me.
-What are you looking at me for?
-And you're looking at me.
What? Are you messing with me?
Shit. Are you sleeping now?
He's not sleeping.
My friend knocked him out.
Fucker!
We are here, motherfuckers.
Where?
Police station.
What did I do?
-Let's go for a re-education.
-You the driver, nerd,
remember my face. I'll get you back later.
Now I know.
You're the ones
that were fighting on my bus.
Yeah.
I wished you would become good guys.
But you are fucking worse.
Are you calling me names?
We are Youths of the Year,
seven years in a row...
Youths? Your faces are super old.
Should have been sent for re-education.
Bastards.
Should have sent you to...
Eat this!
Will you shut up now?
Now... when I put my finger
and press it
like this...
the bomb will be activated.
You'll all be dead.
But we'll go home and sleep happily.
But you've pressed it.
-Have I?
-Shit. You pressed it so many times.
Can you hear it?
-Yes, your Holiness.
-What noise?
-Engine noise.
-Listen for a bomb.
-Yes, I heard.
-What is it?
A time bomb.
What should we do now?
It'll go off in less than an hour.
Good. Then I have time to kick your ass.
There's a bomb?
Yes, sir. We need to do something
before it goes off.
I agree with him.
Then we should get this bus
out of our jurisdiction asap.
We should take it to an open area.
And help the passengers out
by asking for military help,
for safety.
How about at Don Mueang
or Suvarnabhumi Airport?
That's good.
Because neither
are in our jurisdiction.
See? All because of your dumbness.
Speaking before thinking.
Why are you yelling at me?
We're in this together. We're all hurt.
Yeah?
What's up with your face?
I've was wondering.
Since we've got on the bus,
you haven't spoken to anybody. Why?
I got my ass kicked by a cop's son
and his boys.
Got your ass kicked?
Why are you so dumb to let them do that?
Yeah, why are you so dumb
to let them do that?
Don't you see lots of feet here?
Bro, it's all right.
If we survive this,
my boys and I
will go help you to get back at them.
Still want to fight?
Breaking news. Bus no. 888,
full of passengers, can't stop
because the brake isn't working.
Right now, the bus is on Ratchada Road
near Thailand Culture Center Intersection.
We are informed that the bus driver is
Ponsak Chuanchuen.
Pon! Fuck!
Don't die yet, please.
To all gods and angels,
if I survive this,
I'll become a real monk.
-What? You're not a monk?
-No.
Why are you wearing a monk robe?
I bought it.
You know it's wrong?
-Yes, I do.
-Then why did you do it?
Your Holiness, all the alms I got,
I never sell them,
I donate them to the poor in slums.
Where are all the kids?
I'm here.
Here. Eat it.
Remember, work hard at school.
Your stomach is full now.
Study hard, not just play.
Your parents are tired.
Tomorrow I'll bring some more.
You're so bad.
Pretending to be a monk.
-Sinner! I wish you go to hell.
-Yeah.
You tarnish the religion. I might not
survive today, but let me yell at you.
-Yeah.
-I did respect you.
Wait.
Did I kill your parents or something?
Why are you yelling at me?
Not the least bit of shame?
This is not nice.
Hey!
Let me take care of him.
Yeah. Give him some.
Fake monk.
Fuck. You're just putting
your hands on your hips.
When you do something good
and somebody says you're doing it
for an image,
let them think so.
They can only criticize other people,
but do nothing good.
Well...
let's think of him as a Robin Hood monk.
Taking from the rich
to give to the poor.
Uniform or good clothes...
are not proof of good people.
But a good mind is.
Amen.
That was unexpected.
You should become a monk.
-I was once, don't want to be again.
-Why?
Too tiring to climb a mountain.
Come here.
I'm so sorry.
That's all right.
While we are alive...
do something good to each other.
When you die,
you can't take anything with you.
Hey, lift the corpse up.
Be careful.
What? Give him some respect.
You, too?
-Ob!
-What's up?
Ob...
Have you heard about my boyfriend?
Yeah.
Please. Please help him, Ob.
Okay. My boss is giving the orders.
Please help him. I love him very much.
Don't worry. My sister's boyfriend
is like my brother. I love you the same.
Thank you so much.
You love him, but what about Dad?
I don't know if he's still mad at me
for leaving him for Pon.
Nah. He's been asking about you every day.
What did he say?
He's worried about whether
you can afford your living.
It's all about love.
I can't help it. Pon is good,
handsome, and capable.
You're sure?
-Anyway, please help him.
-Okay.
By the way, have you got
your tattoo removed?
He had his replaced with another tattoo.
Hurry.
-This way.
-What?
Fuck.
The bus with no brakes
is the same one that I forgot my gun on.
Don't panic.
We'll find a way to get it together.
We? Get it together?
Get your gun back together.
Well, I have to get back
-before our boss finds out this, too.
-I'm glad. I'm so glad to see my gun.
-See you.
-To see my gun.
What do we do to get my gun back?
What's up with you?
Nothing.
You're frowning.
It's nothing.
If you want to ask me something, you can.
Remember that night?
Which night?
That night?
Salin just kept me company.
Nothing happened between us.
How about me?
You, I love.
Neither airport is giving us permission
to use their space.
Well, then, contact the airport
nearest to Bangkok.
Yes, sir.
You go tell the passengers on the bus
to be calm and collected.
Don't panic.
We'll lead them to the nearest airport.
Yes, sir.
Let me say it here.
I want this to be confidential.
Do not let the press know.
Yes, sir.
Hello, Mom.
I'll do my homework at my friend's.
I might be late. Yeah.
Yeah.
Don't worry about me. Yeah.
Love you, Mom.
Why did you lie to her?
A little white lie.
-Where's the bus going?
-I don't know.
Get up!
I told you to get up.
Hey, back off.
Calm down. What are you doing?
I want my stuff.
-What is it?
-Something valuable to me,
and can make me rich.
I knew it! He's a criminal.
Criminal?
Then that child is not his brother?
He's my brother.
He doesn't look like you at all.
You're black as coal,
he's white as cotton.
I'll shoot anyone who comes closer.
Lift your butt.
He'll hurt the hostage.
Taking a child as a hostage?
Let's kick his ass.
I'll kick your ass instead!
Fucking yelling out.
Move back.
You!
Don't be scared. It's a fake gun.
How do you know?
The noise when it fell.
That's right. The real one is here.
Here, look if you don't believe me.
Why are you doing this?
Brother.
Yes.
Today, my friends told me
that they went to a theme park.
I want to go there sometime.
Can you take me there? I want to go there.
Maud, the entry fees are expensive.
Shouldn't we spend all this money on food?
Okay?
Okay.
If Mom and Dad were still alive,
they could have taken us there.
I should go to bed now.
Maud.
What's going on?
Why are you crying?
I'm missing Mom and Dad.
Maud.
Don't cry.
We're poor.
That's not the point.
You're not the only one.
We can't choose how we were born.
Look at me.
A face like this should be a CEO,
but I'm a bus driver.
Kid, you look like a blobfish.
Give it back to me!
-Shoot me if you dare.
-Fuck!
The bullet would hit me first.
-Here. Open it.
-Defy me?
You defy me?
You want to see my wrath? Give it back.
Give it back to me.
Here, bro.
You'll be in jail for a long time.
Because you sell... sausage.
This alone will fill you up.
Hey, stop!
Kid, hold this.
Where did you get this?
Somebody told me to hold it.
Stop!
Let's go.
Sergeant! Somebody saw them outside
-Let's go.
-Yes, sir.
Maud, don't tell anybody
where I hid it, okay?
We'll be rich
and can go to the theme park.
Hey, you know what?
It's bad enough to be poor,
don't be a criminal.
Many poor people with legal jobs
have become rich.
Stop doing this.
Don't let the rich look down upon us.
Be poor but proud with a legal job.
Two sausages can't make you rich.
Pon, the police are calling.
Hello.
Yes.
The police said
they would lead us to the nearest airport.
Okay, sir. Bye.
Think about it.
About what I told you.
Stop crying.
I'll take you to the theme park.
Guys, we're here.
We're okay now.
Hey! The driver!
Why don't you follow the police?
Why did you turn this way?
Over there!
What's up with you?
-What?
-Hey! An airplane!
Everyone, don't panic.
We have less than eight minutes left
until this bus explodes.
Hey, hey.
Guys, there's a military truck.
They came to help us.
We'll be okay.
Let the injured go first. Open the door.
-Where are you going?
-What?
Let the injured go first.
I don't care. I'll go first.
Hey, your Holiness.
You're a fake.
You deserve to die on the bus.
I should go first, my girl is waiting.
Stop. Your girl means nothing.
I have to go do my boobs.
Can we cut in front of you?
-Where are you going?
-Home to play games.
Fuck! Still thinking of games? Move back.
You all move away.
I'll go first. I come with a child.
Why did you bring him here?
You go.
Hey. No need to fight.
-There's another door.
-The back door is broken. It won't open.
-Hey!
-The front door can open. Let's take it.
Hey!
-So take the back door, not the front.
-Hey!
What is that for?
Let me go first.
Do your boobs? Do a repair first.
Here.
Point it at me.
-You're not becoming a monk?
-If I survive, I'll come back.
Go!
Good!
-Go on.
-Open the door.
Help me, please.
Go on.
Hurry.
Almost there, Pon. Hurry.
Step right here.
Hey! Hey!
The airplane!
Fuck!
The driver! You drive!
I'm the conductor.
I'm not the driver. You are.
I love you.
I love you, too, Pon.
-If we must die, you die first, okay?
-What?
-You die first.
-Shit. We die together.
Sir, the bus is going into the forest.
-What the fuck?
-What do we do?
It's the meaning of love
No matter how far apart we are
It's the meaning of friendship
It will never fade
Sir, the passengers on the bus
are all safe.
And the bus fell off the cliff
into the sea, and exploded.
Luckily, it didn't explode in our area.
Yippee!
It's just hatched. Look.
Awesome.
-Look!
-It's hatched.
LATER... ON
I know that deep down
you're a good person.
So, I'd like you to work hard
on practicing the dharma
and help maintain the religion
to stay strong.
I'd like to congratulate you
with this merit
and bless you.
Brother, are you ready?
I don't want to miss the theme park.
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Let's go. You ready?
-Yes.
-Okay. Let's go.
Before I go home,
can I get your line ID?
What line?
The end of the line.
Love you till the end of the line.
Nurse. I'd like to take you
to see America.
Which state?
-The state of love.
-Love you very much.
How about you? Got something?
Nurse. Don't sit like that for long.
You might be hungry.
-Hungry for food?
-Hungry for me.
Really?
You can't beat me.
Let me see your hand.
Your skin is so smooth.
If you come live with me,
I'll give it a good cleaning.
The sea has sand.
My heart has you. I'm fantasizing...
My fucking foot in your mouth.
You're good. But...
we've just met, you shouldn't use
that kind of language.
In response,
I'll slap you with my nose.
Slap here! Slap with your nose.
Want to try my foot? Fragrant.
There's nothing here, my dear wife.
I was complimenting you, your beauty,
and your kindness to the nurse.
Really? Then it's okay.
Let's go home, my dear.
You look beautiful today.
I'm still single.
-Hey!
-You begging for an ass kicking?
Let's go home, my dear.
I brought a car today.
What a beautiful car. Whose car is it?
My dad's car.
You two talk to each other now.
Well, we are not mad at each other.
I just chose to be with my dear husband.
Are you just talk or do you wanna race?
Stay or leave?
Let's go.
-It's in the movie.
-Pon!
Ready?
-Let's go!
-Go!
It's the meaning of love
No matter how far we are apart
It's the meaning of friendship
It will never fade
Have you found your girl?
No. But I'll keep looking.
Good luck to you.
I hope you find her soon.
Thank you.
You know what?
I waited for you
at the bus stop every day.
Days become months.
Months became forever.
No one can replace you.
Today, could you do me the honor?
Go on a date with me,
dinner with me, will you?
I can't today.
I'm in a hurry.
I have to take her to Hong Kong.
It's okay.
Please remember,
no matter how long,
I'll be waiting for you right here.
Ten years?
Are you moving to Hong Kong?
I'll be in jail. Let's go.
Or I'll sue your mom for stealing.
No.
-No!
-Hey.
-What's wrong?
Do you remember him?
Yeah, the handicapped guy.
And I thought you'd learned.
How can you say that?
Guys, hold them up.
Here.
I'm a cop's son, you know.
My dad holds a high rank.
I don't care.
Switch to another person.
Okay. No problem.
Nut. Do it.
-No, I can't.
-Why?
Because I have premeditated it.
How about you?
No? Then go ahead.
I didn't mean to do this.
Why are you slapping me?
I'm a drag queen.
I don't care.
Mia.
I don't think we can go on like this.
-What would you say if I sold drugs?
-Are you crazy?
The fellow at the end of the alley does it
and he's become rich.
So you want to do it too?
It's illegal, you know.
Think about me.
If you got caught,
how long would you be in jail?
What are you talking about?
I mean, gluta beauty drug.
Fuck.
I thought you meant amphetamine
or something.
Are you crazy? Look at me.
The police always search me.
Test my pee and even my poop.
If I were a drug dealer,
I'd be in jail for sure.
Well, you look like one.
I do?
You don't know?
You really look like one.
-Goddess...
-No need to say it.
I know it all. Ask me.
-Well...
-No need to say it.
I know it all.
Ask me.
Well, I've been broke for a long time.
When will I become rich?
When you have a lot of money.
What would you say
if I got up and kicked her?
Why are you all here?
Fake and bull... shit!
What are you saying?
I have no idea what happened.
Have no idea...
No idea at all...
Swear on your dad's life...
Yeah.
Be careful. It'll spill on my bike.
I'm so lucky to see
a hard-to-find creature.
Your face looks so funny.
You were so brave to be born like that.
You!
Before you criticize someone,
look at your own face.
Why do people like to insult someone else?
Don't judge people by the outside,
but the inside.
-You, in the red shirt...
-Yeah.
You have a boyfriend?
No.
-Want to be my girlfriend?
-Are you sure?
Yeah. Hop on.
Bye-bye.
There.
Sister, I'll let you kiss me.
Great.
Why didn't he pick a pretty face like me?
-Are you okay?
-Enough. That's enough.
Why are you driving so fast?
The bus is full of people.
He needs to bring the injured to hospital.
I'm afraid to be us as well.
-Where is your temple?
-Koh Lak.
-Where is it?
-Phuttake.
-What temple again?
-Are you messing with me?
Now?
-I'm filing my nails, waiting for you.
-Yeah, yeah.
That makes me horny.
-Damn it. I'm right here.
-Where?
What the hell?
Don't smile.
I'm sorry.
It's too tight. He can't breathe.
Do you know Monk Thammachaiya?
Forget it. I won't play this joke.
The one who plays Likay?
Okay, okay.
-Can we redo the suture?
-Why?
-My ring is gone.
-You lost it in my balls?
-Get it back when I'm better.
-My engagement ring.
Shit.
Take a photo.
What? What?
What?
-What's next, pal?
-I'm not your pal.
Sorry, sorry.
Subtitle translation by Sudaporn