Butr,
wanna dive into the TV?
Yes. Well done.
Come on, Butr!
You wanna fight?
-You wanna fight?
Splash!
Draw a circle first.
Slowly…
Good job.
This one doesn't look good.
Try again.
Yuke, don't plug in the cell phone here.
Its radiation can affect
your brain while sleeping.
We haven't slept yet.
Don't forget to put it away
before you sleep. It's harmful.
Yes, Mr. Daddy.
Papi is Daddy's son.
You smart-mouth.
Why don't we drive a car like others?
It's fine.
Your dad's car is so cool. Can I try?
Quick! Get on!
Are you guys sure?
Let's go!
I heard this morning that the same-sex
marriage bill is about to be passed.
Really?
Great. Everything will be easier.
Except me. I'm not easy.
You always come back to yourself.
Shall we register our marriage?
Sure!
I'm so glad, you know?
Butr will finally become
my adopted son as well.
I'm so excited.
Me too.
So glad and excited.
It's like we're getting married again.
Do you think about having a child?
He lost a tooth.
You've just lost the first baby tooth?
You've become a big boy now!
Did it hurt?
It's all right.
Yuke,
the school sent us an invitation to join
the Mother's Day event this Monday.
They send this kind of letter
to students' houses these days?
But I have no mother.
Well, I'll go for you.
They invited 'Mother', not 'Father'.
That's true.
But you have two fathers.
You have Papi and Daddy.
You love Papi.
Papi also loves you.
You love Daddy. Daddy loves you too.
And that's even more special than others.
Not many people have two fathers, right?
-Yes, Mom?
-Is that Grandma?
I wanna see her.
They didn't register their marriage.
When the girl's family
didn't let Tul register as father,
it turns out
that he has no right to his son.
As Dad said,
if the DNA profiling
proves his fatherhood,
it may help in some way.
How about consulting a lawyer?
I'll ask Phoon to help.
Okay, If the bill is passed,
you'd better get it done
to prevent problems.
I am concerned.
How about Butr? Is he fine?
Yes, Mom.
If it's passed, everything will be okay.
I'll take Butr to visit you then.
And don't think too much. Tell Dad, too.
Okay, I'll try.
Take care of yourself.
I will.
A mother possesses great kindness
She takes care of us
Since we're babies
She stays around
Singing lullabies until we fall asleep
From little to grown-up
She has nurtured us
She works tirelessly to show us
Her pure and true love
We have become who we are
Because of none other
Than the mother's milk
WE LOVE MOM
You came on behalf of your wife,
didn't you?
So did I.
My wife just gave birth
to a new child yesterday.
That's why she isn't here.
I see.
His mom must be busy, huh?
Well, his mother left when he was a baby.
Oh... I'm sorry to hear that.
It's all right.
Did you finish your lunch, my handsome?
I'll come to pick you up
after the afternoon class.
What is this stain?
Butr, why don't you put
your mother on the card?
But you put two fathers.
It's a card for the Mother's Day.
Because I'm more special than anyone.
How? I don’t talk to boys who brag.
I'm not bragging.
Everyone, stand up.
Thank you, teacher.
Hey, Butr. Let's play soccer this evening.
He can't play soccer.
The other day he missed every kick.
So funny.
Really?
Well, Butr! I heard you have
two fathers. Is that true?
Really? Without a mother,
how were you born?
Or your dad is a fag.
Let me go.
No way.
Does he know he was adopted
from an orphanage?
Not really.
We haven't seriously talked
about this with him.
We try to be both father
and mother to him.
I understand.
But I'd like both of you to be careful
about what you tell your kid.
And please tell him to be calmer.
And for those kids,
we will discipline them.
I hope you don't mind.
But I do.
You know physical abuse is a crime.
That boy physically abused my son.
Mr. Sakchai, please calm down.
All of them are still kids.
I must apologize for my son.
Do you think your apology is enough?
Your son bullied my kid. That's terrible.
We have apologized!
Your son is also wrong.
And do you think
about apologizing in any way?
You must punish that boy anyway.
I wonder how that kid was raised.
As they say, gays are easily aggressive.
They want to have a child,
but don't know how to raise him properly.
Hey!
Mind your words.
Yuke!
Yuke…
You see?
I didn't even finish my sentence,
and he got aggressive.
It's solely their child's fault.
If that child has
to grow up with these gays,
what kind of person will he become?
And what kind of person are you?
You have a child, but please
learn how to be a good father.
Your son made fun of my kid first.
He was just kidding like any other child.
Who knows your son is…
abnormal?
Actually, you have to blame yourselves
for being abnormal
and adopting an abnormal kid.
That's why everything
is even more abnormal.
I think that the abnormal ones
are those who think others are abnormal.
Hey!
You're a teacher! How could you say that?
You should be neutral.
And how did you say that?
You should be a role model for your kid.
Watch your mouth,
or I'll take action on you too.
Being a father is easy.
Anyone could say he's a good father.
I hope you succeed in raising your kid.
Butr,
What's the matter?
You can tell Papi and Daddy.
What does my mom look like?
I want to have a mother.
Butr, listen to me.
It's not only you in the world
who doesn't have a mother.
I don't either.
My mother passed away.
And there are so many
who lost their mother since birth.
But they know
what their mother looks like,
unlike me.
I have no mother,
and I even have two fathers.
Don't you want to have Papi and Daddy?
Do you want to live with someone else
who has never taken care of you?
No, I love Papi and Daddy.
I don't wanna go anywhere.
Daddy and Papi love you so much, too.
Can you play soccer?
Well, quite a bit.
Can you teach me tomorrow?
Fine, but maybe on Saturday.
Come get it. Here it is.
Hello.
This is Ms. Rattiya, the director of the
Children's Rights Protection Organization.
To save time, let's get to the point.
I was informed by Mr. Sakchai
that an adopted child in this house has
been raised in an environment that's...
So I am concerned,
and afraid that the kid
will feel different.
He may feel unhappy,
and become aggressive or even depressed.
Well, Ms. Rattiya.
I think Mr. Sakchai is too prejudiced.
Some children are born from love,
others from just sexual desire.
But, that's not so important
as long as they grow up in a warm family.
How could you indicate
which family is warm?
Because we didn't adopt him from desire.
My boyfriend and I adopted him
because of our love.
I'm confident that our love is no less
than that of any male-female couple.
Yes,
and the same-sex marriage bill
is about to be passed.
I believe that this bill will make
society more open to our relationship,
and have a better understanding
of our son and family.
I understand.
But even if you are accepted by the law,
the society may not be that open.
Children are brought up
by their society, not by the law.
Many people, including myself,
appreciate your love.
But when we talk about family,
we can't speak just for the sake
of an individual.
Whether they're adopted or not,
they should have the right to grow up in
the same environment as ordinary people.
And what about his real mother?
We have no idea.
We just know that
he was abandoned at the orphanage
when he was just a few days old.
And the orphanage hasn't heard
from his mother since then.
Fortunately, I applied
for an adoption at the time.
I brought him after my qualifications
were approved.
Considering your house,
I don't doubt your qualifications.
But you probably don't want your son
to have a shortcoming
and feel isolated, do you?
Do you mind if I talk with your son?
And do you mind if I do?
How can we trust you?
What's your son's name?
Your house is cozy, Butr.
Who do you live with?
Just Papi, Daddy, and me.
I see. And what do Papi and Daddy mean?
Father.
And what's the difference
between Papi and Daddy?
Papi is Daddy's son,
because Daddy often reprimands Papi.
Do you have a mother?
No… I don't.
So we are the same.
And do you have Papi and Daddy?
I don't have a Papi and Daddy either.
I don't have a father.
Poor you!
What's the difference
between a mother and a father?
A father and mother are what
we have had since we were born.
How were we born?
I have two fathers.
And how are they related?
My friends say my fathers are queers.
There is no right or wrong
way to raise a child.
But there is absolutely no easy way.
I understand.
I kind of hate her.
Butr will have school holidays next week.
How about taking a trip?
-Where do you wanna go?
-I wanna go to a beach.
Let's go…
to a beach
What is this?
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Yes, thank you.
Butr!
What are you doing?
Let's go boating.
Papi, stop here.
Why?
I'm a big boy now.
I'm afraid my friends
will call me a little baby.
What's the matter with him?
If I'd driven more carefully,
we wouldn't have lost our son.
It was just an accident, Tiw.
No one ever wanted it to happen.
I just wish it was just a dream
and I would wake up soon.
It's been more than a year, Nan.
Hello.
Nan, someone's calling you.
Just a moment, please.
Hello.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to say sorry to me.
You didn't leave me at the orphanage.
I was in the final year at university.
And because I got pregnant,
I had to drop out.
That man didn't even care.
He didn't take any responsibility.
I didn't even dare to tell my parents.
I was so scared and not ready then.
And how is he now?
Now he has good fathers,
but every kid needs a mother.
I'm sorry. It could be my karma.
I had a new baby boy,
but he's gone.
Would you like to see him?
Rattiya is really meddlesome.
So much.
Just ignore her.
He is your son by law anyway.
But that woman might be his birth mother.
But we've raised him.
If she takes legal action against us,
we will win by all means
because she abandoned him.
By law, yes.
But law cannot be applied to everything,
especially when it comes to feelings.
Then don't let her see our son.
That might be the way.
Anyway, we should go tomorrow
and see what they have to say.
I'm sorry.
I know I was a bad mother.
Actually, just knowing that he is happy,
I'm already glad.
But now that I know he wants
to have a mother, I feel so guilty.
Knowing he wants to see me,
I feel even worse.
I just want to see him and make up
for what I did.
Without a mother, Butr is already pitiful.
Do you want him to know
that his own mother abandoned him?
You left him,
and now you wanna see him
when you want.
Don't you think
you're a little too selfish?
I must apologize
for my wife's selfishness.
But I believe your beloved son
somehow wants to see his own mother.
Mr. Phoon, Mr. Yuke,
though Butr is Mr. Phoon's
adopted son by law,
or even if the same-sex marriage
bill is passed;
a same-sex couple
can't have a baby by nature.
It is obvious that your son
is having a problem.
If you really love your son,
you should give him a chance.
Perhaps the boy
doesn't want something special,
just the same things as his friends.
What's next?
Phoon…
Just let him spend time with his mom,
a week or two,
then come back to stay with you.
I believe it will help fulfill
what he longs for.
This is clearly selfish.
You'd better be more generous.
And this is your son we're talking about.
He just wants to have a mother.
Not every orphan is lucky
enough to find his birth mother.
And how could I be sure you
won't abandon him again?
Losing my little kid
is more than enough already.
I just want to see him
to make up for what I had done.
How would you explain how he was born?
He will learn from school when it's time.
And he'll understand.
And how would you describe
your relationship?
Being homosexual is not wrong.
But if there are choices,
I believe no one
would want a kid to be gay.
I think, deep inside,
you are also afraid, aren't you?
Yes?
Yes, yes. I'll be there.
You don't need to come.
I'm all right.
Your friend told me you fell down.
I was just dancing as usual.
Falling down when dancing is normal.
You have to be more careful.
No wonder why Mom left.
Yes,
I was too late.
Unlike both of you.
He is just worried about you.
Take good care of yourself, though.
It's like you're not accustomed to me.
I raised you.
Sometimes, being accustomed is harmful.
It makes us unprepared.
Just use protection.
You're over 30 now.
I'm not talking about that.
I know, you're talking about Butr.
I'm sorry for what I am.
I feel guilty about you and also your mom.
I'm sorry for being the main reason
that you became like me.
But what can I do?
I've tried not to chitchat with Butr,
because I know you're afraid. So am I.
Go… I'm going to sleep.
Just go.
Goodnight, Dad.
Turn off the light.
Thank you.
I did it for my son.
He's easygoing, isn't he?
Of course. He wants to have a mother.
I meant to make you feel okay
that our son is friendly
and can understand things easily.
I hope so,
because I'm not sure
if I'm right or wrong.
At first, I didn't agree
with you letting them in.
But when I see him smile,
my prejudice is gone.
Because we are his fathers.
Butr,
let's take a shower together.
No, I'm grown now!
What's the matter?
Butr might come in.
He's sleeping.
Don't you notice
that he's acting strangely?
Is that because of that family?
He's been strange
since we came back from the beach.
He doesn't let us go into the school
or have a shower with him.
Are you too worried?
Kids at this age normally think
they are grown up.
Exactly. The more he grows,
the more careful we have to be.
We'll be in trouble if he comes in.
Last time, he found the lube in the bag.
I'm worried.
He just gets naughtier as he grows up.
But I'm certainly naughtier.
Shall we try to behave
like we are friends?
He probably understands
we are his fathers.
But he doesn't understand
our relationship.
What do you mean?
Like…
if we behave like friends or brothers,
it might be easier
for him to understand us.
What about the registration?
I'm also worried about this.
If we register our marriage,
society will know.
Butr's official documents will
be visible for the rest of his life.
I think we'd better postpone it.
It's not too late to do it
after we consider it carefully.
Also,
same-sex love is not all about
marriage registration.
It's more important
to understand each other.
There are a lot of normal couples
who don't register their marriage.
Like Tul and his girlfriend?
The girl's family took the kid away
and doesn't even allow Tul
to register himself as father.
Now Tul has no right to his son
and wastes time suing his girlfriend,
even though they're a normal couple.
Right now only you have the right to Butr.
If something unexpected happened,
I would become someone
without a legal relationship to Butr.
I understand,
but… Yuke!
Yuke!
What are you doing?
Don't you have your own?
Butr touched mine first.
Butr touched mine, too.
Mine too.
Can I stay here?
You said you wanted
to have a mother, didn't you?
I wanna have a mother,
but I don't want to leave Papi and Daddy.
If I did something wrong, I'm sorry.
Phoon…
Papi, help me.
Phoon... No.
You become stubborn again.
Why is it so hard to please you?
We've tried to be both father
and mother for you,
but you still wanna have a mother.
You found you own mother,
but you don't wanna go with her.
What should I do to please you?
I'm sorry.
I'm guilty.
I don't want anything.
I don't wanna go.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
You're hurting our family.
All of us will only regret it.
I don't want to confuse him.
I know it hurts to heal the wound,
but it's better than waiting
until it's too late.
Well said!
-Don't you love him?
-I do.
I don't want him to be a problem child.
A problem child, or your problem?
What do you mean?
I'm acting for our son
and trying to sustain our family.
For him or for yourself?
And most importantly,
this is our family.
Aren't you afraid
that he’ll become gay like us?
Don't put your weakness on him.
I won't let him go anywhere.
But he is my son.
That's right.
Butr is a son only to you.
What about my love for Butr?
Is it nothing to you?
Daddy doesn't love me now?
He does.
But probably too much.
What do you mean?
Too much? I don't understand.
Let's sleep.
You have to get up early tomorrow.
I don't want to sleep
if I have to wake up and leave.
I've never slept anywhere else
without Papi and Daddy.
I'm scared. I know I'll miss you.
So am I.
Shall we run away and live with grandma?
How were we born?
We were born from the love
of a man and a woman.
And when they have a baby,
they become father and mother.
So, you have two fathers, don't you?
Or your dad is a fag?
What do you like to eat, Butr?
I like fried chicken.
Good. I'm good at frying chicken.
Your Papi and Daddy told me
you wanted to play soccer.
How about getting some soccer uniforms?
And how about learning soccer
with Uncle Tiw?
He was a soccer player at school.
Really?
Yes.
But today, let's go
to the countryside first.
Okay.
What?
Are you pregnant?
How did you come in?
Why didn't you ask for permission?
You put your nose in our business
without asking for permission, too.
That's because I felt sympathetic.
You didn't have to.
Just don't see us as abnormal ones.
That's enough.
I just tried to solve the problem instead.
I insist that I truly understand him.
You don't have to understand everything,
especially others' business.
You try to be a looking glass
reflecting others' sufferings,
but never look at your meddling self.
Daddy is busy.
I love you, too.
Sweet dreams.
Is that Butr?
How is he?
You said he is your son.
Call him if you want to know.
-You missed!
-Tag him!
Help me.
Help.
Here's your backpack.
Good boy. Let's go.
Butr, don't your Papi and Daddy
bring you here these days?
My mom brought me!
Her boyfriend drove for me.
Haven't you taken a shower yet, Tiw?
Neither have you.
Are you okay?
I miss our son.
I miss him too.
But we're still lucky that we have Butr.
Hello.
What? It's due in two days, isn't it?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought it's Wednesday.
I'll send it to you this evening.
Mr. Phoon,
Did you sign it in the wrong place?
This is for the other board member.
Oh, I'm really sorry.
Can you get me a new one?
Yes.
Thank you.
Hello.
Yes, Mr. Phoon.
How is Butr doing?
He's fine.
He is well-adjusted.
He's at school now.
Do you want to talk with him?
I'll tell him
to call you back this evening.
That's fine.
Thank you.
THE BIBLE OF X
Hey class,
do you know what next Monday is?
It's Father's Day.
That's correct.
So today, let's make a card
for Father's day.
Here you are.
Yours.
Good.
And yours.
That's right.
This is yours.
Here you go.
Go ahead.
Yes.
The number you have dialed
cannot be connected.
Butr,
I'll be right back.
What's wrong, Nan?
Nothing.
I just want to use the toilet.
Hey! Who was it?
I told you. A child is not like a puppy
that can be replaced.
But he's my son.
He's just curious like other boys.
If we teach and give him some time,
he might be better.
I have no idea
how that gay couple raised him.
So, do you still want
to register our marriage?
Nothing would change.
It will neither make me
become a true father
nor make you a good father.
Wait.
What do you mean?
Everything I've done has been for our son.
If you're so scared,
you shouldn't have adopted him
in the first place.
And what about this?
The invitation letter for Father's Day.
Why is it in the trash?
I was afraid that when you see it,
you would miss him
and wanna join the activity.
I just realized
that you're such a coward.
Missing him means
that we love him so much.
Letting him go with his mother
doesn't mean we're no longer his fathers.
Phoon! Phoon!
Phoon!
Phoon! Please don't.
Phoon! Stop! Don't act like this!
Phoon! Stop!
Phoon!
Phoon…
It was my fault.
I made everything worse.
I never wanted to let him go.
But… I was scared.
It's the parents' responsibility
to raise their child,
not to choose.
Why didn't you bring me to my senses?
Do I have the right to?
I'm afraid you will say
he is your son again.
You know, I didn't dare to talk
about him again since then.
I'm sorry.
I am a coward.
I'm selfish.
I don't care about
marriage registration now.
I realized that possession
is less important than
having a chance to take care of him.
I miss him.
So do I.
You know?
He was so sad that night.
He thought we didn't love him.
He even asked me to run away with him.
I feel like I ruined everything.
I'm sorry.
I'm ashamed.
I don't even dare to see him.
We're still fine.
You are still his father by law.
Perhaps,
let's just be who we are
and let him be who he is.
That's enough.
I don't believe it's impossible for us to
take care of him on our own.
Butr…
It's been more than a week.
Are you happy to have me?
It's good.
Do you love me?
I don't know.
No love can replace another.
None.
I have two fathers.
How are Papi and Daddy
related to each other?
My friends said my fathers are queers.
It's nonsense.
Both of them are the ones
who love you the most.
How much do you love them?
The most in the world.
Why is that?
I don't know, but it's so much.
Good.
I believe you can't imagine
how much you'll love your mom.
But for Papi and Daddy,
you don't need to imagine at all.
You can see and feel it every second.
You're luckier than I am, you know.
I grew up in an orphanage.
What does orphan mean?
It means a child without a mom and dad.
Ever since I could remember,
I had to admit that I have neither.
And what did you do?
It might be too difficult
for a kid like you.
But if you love what you have,
you'll have what you love.
Who… always see you through
When you are sad?
Who... always comfort you?
Who… love you
More than anything?
Their love is bigger than
The earth and sky
If the world was a pen
And the sky was paper
And the ocean was ink
Those wouldn't be
Enough to declare their love
Who… love you
As much as their lives?
Who… are always kind to you?
Who… love you unconditionally
With no ill intent?
An everlasting love
Who…?