-Dad, are you driving to Chonburi?
-Yes.
I'm going straight there.
Buy me some crabs too.
Give me the money.
So stingy.
Don’t eat until tomorrow.
When I get back,
we'll eat a lot.
Okay.
Thank you, my dear daughter.
Sure.
Good morning.
I’m so damn nervous!
Will anyone see us?
Don't worry.
I've been here for a while.
I haven't seen anyone pass by.
-Shit!
-What?
You scared me!
What the heck?
There might be cameras.
Palm.
Palm!
There he is. Go.
Can't you get any closer?
Your dad won't disappear.
Chonburi is straight ahead.
Sit back. You're blocking my view.
Palm.
If I catch him, what should I say?
Don't tell people off just yet.
It might really be about work.
"Shameless!
You already know he has a family,
and yet you still mess with him."
Or should I tell her off coldly?
"Slut."
Let's go ask him.
Hold it, Palm.
Hold on, I was joking!
-Sir, Gink has a question for you!
-Palm! Damn you!
-Sir!
-Palm!
Gink has a question.
Sir!
Hey...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I've got an iron dick.
Disgusting.
Why is he turning left?
-Follow him!
-Okay.
-Palm!
-Sorry!
You...
Is he flying to Chonburi?
How will we know where he's flying to?
I've checked the flight schedule.
Morning flights are only to Chiangmai.
His factory doesn't have a branch there.
He might have some business there.
Let it go.
Palm.
Lend me some money.
Here. I'll pay you later.
Isn't that too much?
Are you taking first class?
I’m buying you a ticket too.
What?
Gink!
I'm going in.
Not yet! Calm down.
He's probably here for business.
Who knows who's in there?
Let's go downstairs.
Okay?
Gink.
Gink, don't go there.
It's too high.
I can't hear a thing.
The walls are too thick.
They say you can hear better
through an outlet.
Do you hear anything?
It's really thick.
Let's go.
We'll be in trouble if someone comes in.
Let me try.
I said you can't hear anything.
Why are you insisting?
If there's really nothing, then move.
Is it really that bad?
Let's go.
Gink. Where are you going?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're arriving at Suvarnabhumi Airport.
I think I'll tell my mom.
Okay.
And they'll probably get a divorce.
When my parents got divorced,
I cried for a week.
But believe me,
it will get better.
It might even be better
than them being together.
You know...
my dad's really busy with work.
But he still finds time
to drive me to school every morning.
Because he doesn't want Mom to get tired.
I've always thought he loved
me and Mom so much.
Now, I'm not sure
if he really does love us.
I don't know who does or doesn't love you.
But I love you, Gink.
It's okay.
I'll stay with you for now.
Palm.
Can I ask you something?
I won't ask it again.
When you said you love me,
what kind of love is it?
Answer me first.
I really love you, Gink.
You're my only friend
who I can truly talk to.
Being friends means
not worrying about each other.
Not being possessive.
Not fighting. Not indulging every whim.
Yes.
And the best part is...
friends don't break up.
Fine.
Don't cheer me up with quotes
from Facebook.
-Gink.
-Let me gather my thoughts.
Excuse me, please sit down.
Hey! Watch out!
I'm sorry.
Good job! Try again.
"Good job! Try again."
Hey!
"Hey!"
-Why are you copying me?
-"Why are you copying me?"
How much wood would a woodchuck chuck?
"How much wood would a woodchuck chuck?"
-Sally sold seashells at the seashore.
-"Sally sold seashells at the seashore."
There.
Jerk. Who the hell can repeat that?
Damn you.
You're so mean.
You're the mean one.
You don't even talk to me
and still have Piyachart sit next to me.
His feet stink.
I don't get what he's saying.
I miss your nagging.
Fine.
I'll move back tomorrow.
Wait. Are you going to use me
to do something?
I'm seeing Louis.
Damn.
What did he do to get you to give in?
It's a secret.
Whatever.
You have a boy now,
so you're keeping secrets from me.
Whatever.
Being friends is good enough, right?
All right.
I have to go.
Yes. Bye.
Let's go.
-I got new chords.
-Really?
Louis!
"Being friends is good enough."
When I heard this sentence,
I don't know why it hurt.
That was a tell-tale sign
that I was jealous.
But I was the one
who told her to be just friends.
Which one?
The one over there.
The one singing on stage.
What now?
Overall you're so charming
Don't be shy, I'm telling the truth
She's really charming.
Can you get any cuter?
I want to be next to you
I know how you feel.
Mine is also here.
And she's dancing
with her boyfriend right now.
We've been best friends for ages.
But...
she's clueless.
Like the movie Dear Dakanda?
Not really!
The guy,
when Dakanda turned him down,
he manned up,
went to the sea,
and got a new girlfriend.
But I don't have the balls!
When I was turned down,
I didn't even dare to leave.
-I understand.
-I know how you feel.
Mine's also the same.
She can't forget her ex.
So she told me to wait as her friend.
Just like a dog
who can only love one owner.
-I understand.
-Thanks a lot.
My friend...
is not ready for a relationship.
She wanted to graduate first.
Has she graduated yet?
She just applied for a second masters.
She's planning to get a Ph.D. too.
I've found my friends!
-We've fallen hard for them.
-Yes!
-But they just want to be friends.
-Damn!
And we give in!
-Yes!
To the friend zone!
One year.
Three years already.
Mine's five years.
Ten years!
Wait a second.
That's a decade?
You've been waiting for ten years?
I wasn't really waiting.
Pang.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
Never mind. Let's just say I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
If you're going to disappear like that,
then just get lost!
Hold on, Pang.
Palm!
Is this how you talk to a freshman?
Just go be with her!
Wait!
Let's finally be over and done with.
Well, I'm...
I'm going to tell you something.
Someone like you
will never find true love.
Damn you!
Don't all those years mean anything?
-Of course.
-What, then?
Good memories in Savanna Park.
Our picture was here.
And they did it right here!
This is not mine.
Are you really my friend?
I'm not sleeping with you.
How am I supposed to know?
Go sit down.
I'll get them myself.
And Gink will get through it
She'll have a change of heart
And Louis will fade away
Even if that table's still there
Even if it hasn't gone anywhere
I'll throw it out for you
Gink, you know,
men are nice to us in the beginning.
They'll be by our side, taking care of us.
But in the end, they will be unfaithful.
You can't trust men!
Trust me.
I've seen a lot.
I've been through it all.
Don't bother with love.
Parn.
My friend is just your manager.
Does she have to join
your Spinster Club too?
Damn you, Palm.
You're the one who sang the lyrics,
"Loneliness are opposite poles.
Young people should find love," right?
I didn't sing that line.
I was just in the chorus then.
Gink, turn the song on.
I'm ready. I'm feeling it.
I agree with you.
I don't want to be in love again.
I'm done.
What?
Are you really done with love?
I was just trying to side with Parn.
Actually, I still believe
there is a good guy out there for me.
Sneaky bastard.
Hey.
If she's flirting like that,
-then it's time to seal the deal.
-Right.
She didn't mean me.
-What?
Sorry!
It's all over.
If you still love me, care about me
And don't want to hurt me
Please don't leave me hanging
If I'm not good enough for your love
Give me a chance to show it
Please don't hurt me
Ted!
He's cool, isn't he?
Too cool.
Let me have my moment!
I moved in with him.
Really?
Because you’re his manager
and it'll make the commute easier, right?
No. I want to hook up
whenever I want, okay?
Good. Don't bring too much stuff.
Goong-Gink.
No, I'm not going to sing.
-I don't know any of your friends here.
-Just one duet.
No. Take Palm, then.
Isn't the host his friend?
But it's a New and Jiew song.
-Which song?
-Come on.
Just go. I'll film you.
Stop it. You just want to film the singer.
She's my friend. Do you want her number?
Don't give it to him.
He can't even remember
all his girls' names.
But I can remember their faces.
You're my idol.
-Ted.
-What?
-Hey.
-Listen.
Don't be like him, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
Don't even try.
Roger that, Goong-Gink.
I won't.
Goong-Gink, just one duet
with my friend. She's waiting.
No.
Stop it with the "Goong-Gink"!
Palm. Fill this up.
I'll be back.
Just one duet.
I'll fill it to the rim.
A refill again?
I've seen you here twice.
Are these two mugs for you?
No.
The other one is for my friend.
I see.
Same here.
I wonder why they don't do it themselves?
That's a good question.
My friend is dancing with her boyfriend.
You're a good friend.
Maybe too good?
Being nice is painful.
You're really hurt. Look at your face.
I...
Don't tell me
you're also a good friend.
We've got a lot to talk about.
Excuse me.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Are those for a friend?
They're both mine.
Such a heavy drinker.
I suppose.
I was first. Sorry.
If you don't love me
Then don't be nice to me
Then don't care for me
If there isn't any love
Then don't do anything
Because my heart is weak
If you don't love me
Then don't call to check up on me
Because the sound of your voice is painful
-Can you please stop?
-If there isn't any love, just let me go
-Shit!
-Gink!
-Goong-Gink!
Don't move. Stay still.
Don't move yet.
Are you hurt?
Shit!
Does it hurt a lot?
I'm okay.
You'll be dancing again in no time.
Only one person is allowed.
Palm.
Go enjoy your beer.
Don't worry about me.
Ted?
I'll keep you posted.
I know there's a thin line
between friend and boyfriend.
It's very uncomfortable,
being in this friend zone.
It's like we're close,
but in reality,
we're freaking far.
I understand you.
They talk to us on the phone for hours.
But they only talk about other guys.
Yes.
They say they feel comfortable around us.
But when they go on trips,
they go with their boyfriends.
-Exactly!
Tell us they love us every day.
Say they miss us every night.
But they never choose us!
-Right!
The friend zone is
just another kind of prison!
How can you tolerate it for ten years?
Right. I shouldn't!
I've crossed the damn line!
-Cross the damn line!
-Yes!
We don’t want to be just friends.
We want to be hubbies!
Wait, hold on.
You've already crossed the line?
Love never changes
When the opportunity is there,
you have to take the risk.
-Are you making that up?
-It's up to you if you don't believe me.
What did you wish for? I heard my name.
What?
What did you wish for?
Wait a second.
Hello, klutz.
Have you taken off your cast?
Palm.
I've been puking.
And my period hasn't come yet.
-I might be pregnant.
-What?
Where are you?
I'm in Malaysia.
What?
Oh, sorry.
What are you doing there?
Where are you?
Myanmar.
Where's Ted?
I came alone.
Can you come see me?
I'm not just down the road.
I don't know what to do next.
Calm down.
I'll call you back.
Palm, can you tell me now?
What did you wish for?
I wish to leave.
Gink.
You really came!
I think it's just a food baby,
you're not pregnant.
What food baby?
I couldn't eat anything.
I bought a pregnancy test.
But I haven't used it yet.
I've been waiting for you.
Where is it?
Where did it go?
Gink.
Get it together.
It's in your hand.
I'm...
going to do it now.
Have you told Ted yet?
I've only told you.
I can't pee.
Try to force it out.
Man, it won't come out.
I'll help you.
Why are you holding it in?
I'm not. I'm forcing it out!
What does it mean?
I'm not pregnant!
I told you it's a food baby.
Why did you puke?
I must be...
stressed out.
Did you have a fight with Ted?
Well,
we're working on a jingle for King Power.
It's Palmy's song.
It has to be sung in different languages.
We've got to record singers
from different countries.
I hurt my leg, so I couldn't go with him.
He had to fly alone to Laos.
Can you please tell me?
Is this real or am I overthinking?
I'm starting to get anxious
With an unanswered question
Tell me what's in your heart
I want to know what you're thinking
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
Let's go eat.
I see. Okay.
Do you want to see my tears?
And he went to Vietnam.
I want to tell you
How anxious I am
Before you say anything
I want you to promise me
That you won't let me down
Then the Philippines.
Is our love still as good as before?
Are we still together in our dreams?
Your heart hasn't changed
And our love is still the same
And then to Malaysia.
All I want is for you to say it
Tell me that you think about it
Tell me, so I can be sure
That our love is still the same
Am I right?
The singers
are all young and pretty too.
Ted is such a good guy
and I trust him.
I'm not being a baby.
Stop bragging. Get to the point.
Get up. Come closer.
When he was done in Malaysia,
he flew to Indonesia.
I met up with him there.
Why did you go this time?
Well, I missed him.
Stop interrupting me.
When I went to Indonesia,
guess what happened.
These headphones aren't good.
Gink.
Could you please get my new ones?
They're in my bag.
He bought new ones again?
How many ears does he have?
It's in the navy blue box.
-This one?
-Yes.
What is this for?
For love.
I was totally surprised.
He bought us the same watches.
Even though it wasn't my birthday,
our anniversary,
or any other important day.
I couldn't stop thinking about it.
It's like he's guilty of something,
and he's covering up.
So...
I checked on a little something.
Before saying anything else
I want you to promise me
That you won't let me down
You should go inside to talk to them.
So, it's clearer.
Okay.
Good idea.
So smart.
I peeked at his phone.
But there wasn't anything strange.
I went through his wallet.
Do you want to know what I found?
A restaurant receipt from Malaysia.
I thought you found a bra.
You flew here because of a receipt?
Are you a millionaire?
My money, my business.
Read what he ordered!
"Hamburger. Beer."
So?
Those were what he ate.
Keep reading.
Who do you think Ted came with?
The singer, I think.
She's cuter than me too.
Check this out.
Let me see. Who's cuter than you?
You're right.
Because I'll see her come.
Now, I'm confused about who came or not.
I think she came, but they can't remember.
They might have come for dinner
and parted after that.
Just trust him.
Then why does Ted have to feel guilty?
Hey.
These dim lights.
These ballads.
With a girl staring into his eyes,
wouldn't sparks start flying?
I don't know.
I'm not Ted.
Sorry. Let me get this.
Hello, Goong-Gink?
I'm going back now.
Don't go to sleep just yet.
I'll get home and talk
with my honey Goong-Gink all night.
Wait for me.
Okay. Yes. I see.
I'm sorry, Joyce.
My girlfriend is waiting for me.
I have to go.
Really?
But I'm still having a good time.
Can't you stay a bit longer?
Please?
Pretty please?
Let's not do that.
I already have a girlfriend.
Although she's got a flat rack,
they're natural.
I like them.
Ted.
Is your beard too thin?
Let me fill it in.
Hey, don't play with food.
And you can?
Palm.
It's messy.
It's the last step.
Very good.
Do you want a piggyback?
No. I'll break your back.
Leave me here.
What's your plan?
Actually, I told Ted that
I have a checkup in Bangkok.
I'll meet up with him later.
Where are you flying to?
Ted's in Cambodia.
Don't get ballsy.
Look at yourself.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
I don't know where I'd get
another best friend like you.
I'm glad you know it.
Gink?
What are you doing?
I'm afraid it'll be a long wait.
I'm keeping you company.
Hey! Hold on. Don't go just yet.
Stay.
You're really something.
This was pointless.
So...
let me know if you get back safe.
Are we still together in our dreams?
Your heart hasn't changed
And our love is still the same
Am I right?
Gink.
Is the backing track ready?
One moment.
Tell me, so I am sure
That our love is still the same
Am I right?
It's beautiful!
Shit!
Oh, my god!
Goong-Gink.
You don't have to cancel.
Give me 15 minutes.
I want to tell you
How anxious I am
Before you say anything
I want you to promise me
That you won't let me down
Is our love still as good as before?
Are we still together in our dreams?
Your heart hasn't changed
You can yell at me.
My heart can't.
Do you have any extra pajamas?
I forgot mine.
THREE PIECES
Thank you. Have a good day.
Choose the next trip for us.
Can it wait?
I don't want to go anywhere for a while.
Okay.
Aui.
I'm sorry.
I've been flying a lot.
I want to rest at home.
You really like staying at home?
When we were in Myanmar, you left early.
You used to fly six times
and we still went out afterward.
Fine.
Let's go.
When will you be free?
If you don't want to go, then don't.
Do you want me to drop you off?
Let me know the next time
you want to come.
Yes?
Where are you?
I'm home. What's up?
Look down here.
I'm in front of your house!
Think about it.
Ted's alone in Cambodia,
why would he buy condoms?
Just in case.
But he used one!
Have you asked him yet?
He'll come up with excuses.
I think it's probably
one of those singers.
I'm going to see for myself.
What?
Gink.
Have you lost your mind?
Are you trying to be Detective Conan?
There's only one truth.
You can go now.
Bye.
Don't worry about me.
May I assist you?
Thank you so much.
Without you, I'd be so helpless.
My pleasure.
You're so manly.
Excuse me.
You know whenever I fly,
I always think of you.
I've always wanted to see you at work.
-Palm.
-What?
You have an employee discount
for flights, right?
Yes.
Is there any discount for your friends?
Only tickets for moms.
Maternal mom?
The mom of my child.
Interested?
It's good to be you.
There's nothing to be stressed about.
Says who?
When you didn't repay me
for the Chiang Mai tickets,
I was stressed.
I couldn't go out on any dates.
Why didn't you ask me for it?
You weren't even talking to me.
My date had to treat me.
So damn embarrassing.
Give me your hand.
The other one.
Hong Kong's an hour early.
Who asked?
Palm.
The manager is outside.
They're almost finished.
Shit!
Ted's video calling!
What should I do?
Don't answer it.
I can't.
I want to see who he is with.
Hello.
Hello, Goong-Gink.
Where are you?
Well...
Hold on, Ted.
Damn.
Where am I?
Where they sell
dumplings and steamed buns.
Gold shops.
I'm in Chinatown.
I just got my cast off
and stopped by to eat.
I see.
Dumplings and steamed buns.
Dim sum.
Har gow and beef balls.
Do you want anything else?
Do you have fried taro?
This is a steamed dish cart,
not a fried dish cart.
The fried dish cart just passed by,
why didn't you order?
What about gyoza? It's the best.
Bring whatever you have.
Shithead.
Hey!
-Oh, hey!
-That hungry? Don't bite him, okay?
Sorry, Ted.
I'm starving.
So...
how's the recording session? Are you done?
I'm done.
The singer is fabulous.
Are you still with her?
Do you want to talk to her?
Are you going home after dinner?
Yes. How about you?
Are you going anywhere else?
I'm going straight to the hotel and sleep.
I'm so exhausted.
Okay. I won't bother you.
Enjoy your dinner.
See you.
I miss you.
Satisfied?
Gink.
The singer's here.
Who is he talking to?
Gink. She's looking at us.
Palm.
Gink.
There's a girl in the car.
Wait for me!
Gink.
Calm down.
Do you know where to find him?
I'll wait for him at the hotel.
Intercon.
People have generic faces.
She said that Ted isn't back yet.
Okay.
Why did you order a lot?
This is yours. This is mine.
The rest are for throwing at him
if he brings her here.
Damn! Are you going to stab him?
It's for cutting off my cast.
I told Ted I took it off.
It won't look real.
But you told him you're in Chinatown.
Well, I wanted to surprise him.
Hurry up and cut it.
What?
You've lost it.
Can't you see?
Why are you so obsessed with him?
You know I don't want to get married.
Yes, I know.
But I want to marry him
as soon as possible.
You know...
every song I listen to
makes me think of him.
I was never like this with Louis.
You're infatuated.
Palm.
I'm obsessed!
When I heard him talk about our future,
I just want to time travel to that moment.
He said he wants to have three kids.
So he can form a band.
The firstborn will play the piano.
The second will play the violin.
You're daydreaming.
That's what everyone says before marriage.
But who knows if it'll turn out like that?
Actually, marriage is a good thing.
Mom told me,
if he strays,
I can sue both him and the mistress.
You say it as if money
can get rid of your sorrow.
Fine. You just go on
being the player you are.
Who said I don't want to get married?
In your case,
marriage will make you go broke!
Yes.
Stop being nosy
if you want to get married.
You'll get divorced.
What do you mean?
I'm not supposed to know what he has done?
I'm sick of this.
You didn't do anything wrong.
What are you sick of?
Your foot!
It's so damn stinky.
That's enough.
Don't start with me.
We're not getting married.
Go wait for your groom.
Where is Ted?
Why isn't he answering?
He said he's coming back to the hotel.
Has it been too long?
Should I report it to the police?
He's been with the girl
for a couple of hours.
The police won't take the report.
Go hide.
Palm, I can’t look.
They're getting out.
It's Ted, right? Is it Ted?
I think he must be
in some kind of accident.
Should I call the police?
At least we'll know what happened.
You should try calling
with a different number.
Hello.
Can you hear me?
Let's go.
Maybe...
the woman in the taxi is Ted's friend.
They might have dinner plans.
Then they will go their separate ways.
Ted might...
be drunk and couldn't get to the hotel.
So, he...
went to a hostel nearby
to spend the night.
That's why he didn't answer your calls.
And...
Ted...
Well...
he had to take a piss.
So, he got up to take a piss,
which was the same time
you used my number to call him.
What am I doing here?
What?
Shit!
What am I doing here?
Gink!
You're being noisy!
Stop!
My friend's in danger.
She jumped on the sign.
Look outside.
Move back.
Please back up.
Go back.
Gink!
Gink.
Hold on.
Hold on tight.
Gink. I'm coming.
Gink!
I'm here to help you.
I shouldn't have come!
I shouldn't have found out!
Look at me, Gink.
I'm right here.
I'm here for you.
Good girl.
You're my good girl.
I'm not your friend, fatso!
Gink.
Don't ever do that again.
If you fall, you could die.
Come on.
Let's go home.
I don't want to go home yet.
Are you working tomorrow?
Of course.
I'll fly back in the morning.
I can't take a leave either.
I don't want to be alone.
For your safety,
please keep your seat belt secure
until the airplane has come to a full stop
and the seat belt sign has turned off.
When opening the overhead bins,
please be mindful of any items
that may fall on you or other passengers.
You can pick up your baggage at belt one.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you. Have a fun trip.
Can't you go with me now?
I have another flight
and I'll rush back to see you.
Thanks a lot.
Thank you.
Palm!
Why didn't you tell us
your friend was flying?
Well...
This is Gink.
-Is this your first time in Krabi?
-Oh, we're just friends.
Gink!
Don't forget to eat.
Excuse me.
Just like the ad.
-Hello.
Gink, I'm here.
Damn!
Have you been here all this time?
Palm.
Go buy me more beer and freeze it.
I want some beer slushie.
That's enough.
What the hell are you eating?
Come on. Let's go out.
No.
I'm going to sleep right here.
I'm going to eat, sleep, and repeat.
Go get some fresh air.
It'll help.
Believe me.
I'm always breaking up with girls.
Take a look at me.
This is what all the girls
you've dumped look like.
I'm a mortician.
You're such a burden.
I’m here to avenge your exes.
Bring it on.
I've never been this worried
about anyone else.
Enough.
I'm already pretty.
Where are you taking me?
You know how to speak Chinese?
What did you wish for?
I heard my name.
For us to stay together forever.
Come on.
You only know one sentence.
It's your cheesy pickup line, right?
How about you?
Don't you know?
If you tell others, it won't come true.
How is that?
Together forever?
Has it come true for anyone?
Why did you look at me earlier?
Did you curse me?
I was wishing for you
to stop being a player.
See, I told you.
It won't come true.
Why do you want me to stop?
I feel sorry for all your victims.
Let's go.
Have you ever wondered...
What if we were an item?
We'd probably be like today.
What?
Well, what do you think?
I'd probably go crazy.
I'd probably check your phone all day.
Other girls probably text you all day.
Who would dare to cheat?
You hanging off that sign
is stuck in my head.
How can a player stop playing?
How many girls are you talking to?
"How many"?
I'm talking to no one right now.
Let me see.
Palm reading?
Passcode?
Are you my girlfriend?
You're checking my phone.
Don't!
I'm kidding.
Stop for a second.
-What?
-Stop the bike first.
Ted's calling.
Palm! Look ahead!
Damn it. Sorry. Are you hurt?
Gink!
Gink, come on now!
Hold on tight.
Palm!
Monkey!
That hurts!
You thought I was the monkey?
There are similarities.
I nearly pissed myself!
Take me to the toilet right now!
Can't you hold it?
We're almost in the city.
I can't!
Go away, dumbass monkey!
One day, Gink took a piss in the woods
Gink met a little monkey
-Palm.
-What?
It's poop.
Gosh.
What's wrong with your butthole?
Do you have any tissues?
Nasty.
I'll use my panties to wipe it.
What the hell!
Are you crazy?
I'll use the leaves.
Wait. Stop!
Gosh.
Here.
Man, your shirt?
Yes.
What are you going to wear?
Just wipe it, will you?
Mom, look. A naked dude!
-One hundred baht.
-Here.
-Here you are.
-Thank you.
Hello, Ted.
I'm not going back to work yet.
The doctor told me not to walk so much.
Are you done mixing the song?
All right.
Send it over, I'll listen to it.
I miss you too.
When are you going to
give your "Ted" talk?
Not right now.
Then when?
Are you going to keep flying around
with me?
-Are you?
-Here.
Listen.
The Chinese version.
You like to speak Chinese, right?
Are you listening to me at all?
I used to like this song a lot.
It's fun.
But now I really hate it.
Do you like shitting in the woods?
Right?
And jumping onto signs like Jackie Chan
When you fall down, you're a klutz again
I don't want to see you
Going crazy like this
Like this
Can't you just find a good guy for once?
But if you can't, then stay with me
For the time being, can you?
This is a new version.
The lyrics are really good.
You like it now?
Hold this.
What a feeling!
Let's go drink in my room.
That'll be 100.
That'll be 190.
That'll be 190!
Take it or leave it.
I'll take it.
Make up your mind.
I'll take it. I'm sorry.
I bought some snacks.
Okay.
Come in.
I've always wanted to do this.
Beer spa.
Why don't you...
come and chill with me?
Come on.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
My jeans are stuck.
I thought we were going to drink beer.
Am I supposed to drink it from the tub?
Did you know?
Beer nourishes our hair.
It gets rid of the chemicals.
You're always styling your hair.
Turn around.
I'll wash it.
Okay.
Lay back.
Rest on my legs.
Is this okay?
Do you like it?
Are you drunk?
I'm not drunk.
I can't do this.
It's okay.
I understand.
We've always been friends.
Stuff like this takes time.
Let's take it one step at a time.
Why could he do it, but I can't?
Clear things up with him first.
Don't use me to get back at him!
It's too fucked up!
How about when you flirt with me?
You think I don't know?
I want you to feel better.
Is that all?
What about that thing in your pocket?
I'm not sure if you see me
as a friend anymore.
I really want to get up.
But you know why I can't?
-Why?
-I have a hard-on!
Damn you.
If we weren't friends,
I'd have my way with you right now.
Stop it.
If I let you,
there is no way you'd resist.
Let's stop being friends then!
Is this how you want it?
Come back in!
Come in here!
Don't taunt me!
You're so brainless.
If I were Ted, I'd cheat on you too.
Is this how you want it?
Then go for it.
Come on.
Do it!
You know I love you...
Is that why you're doing
whatever you want?
Palm.
Hey.
I'm sorry for taking it out on you.
Before you do anything,
think about it first.
If you don't really feel it,
don't act on it, okay?
Who said I don’t feel it?
I'll break up with Ted.
If you don't break up, I'll kiss you.
Sure.
If I do, you have to take me to Europe.
What?
To see the Northern Lights.
Eat caviar. Go to five-star hotels.
Deal?
What a long list.
It can be anywhere
as long as I'm with you.
Okay.
Deal.
Gink.
Yes?
After you're done with Ted,
I'll see you at Shwedagon Pagoda.
Sure.
Before you say anything
I want you to promise me
That you won't let me down
Is our love still as good as before?
Are we still together in our dreams?
Your heart hasn't changed
And our love is still the same
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Really.
You forgot your watch?
Yes.
Sorry.
I didn't forget it.
I threw it away!
Threw what?
The gift you bought me out of guilt!
-I don't understand.
-Who is it?
Who? What?
In Hong Kong, I spied on you.
Who did you get in the taxi with?
Tell me!
A singer?
A manager?
An interpreter?
Someone from Tinder?
Who?
Calm down, Gink.
I went with Poupe.
Which Poupe?
The girl you sang the duet with.
She flew over for a trip.
So, we went out for dinner.
And...
You told me you'd go back
to the hotel, but you didn't.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
Poupe and I used to like each other
when we were in college.
After we played music together
at the wedding,
we kept in touch.
And...
when you didn't come with me to record,
Poupe flew out to see me.
At first, we were...
just going to hang out.
But things got out of hand.
Why didn't you just tell me that,
after dinner, you went your separate ways?
And...
you were so drunk
that you stayed at a hostel instead.
You didn't answer my calls
because you fell asleep.
Or that someone else called you
when you woke up to pee.
Can't you make up excuses?
I don't want to make things worse for you.
I've told you before.
I don't like this kind of person.
I won't accept it.
I know.
I don't want to let you go.
What's up, Maung Palm?
Maung Gink.
Do they also call girls "Maung"?
Here.
Light the candle.
Make a wish.
Then light the other end and put it down.
Ted didn't cheat on you?
I want to give him another chance.
Damn you.
Being friends is good enough, right?
Gink.
We like each other,
but we stay as friends.
Friends, my ass.
Are we really just friends?
You came here to see me.
What did you tell Ted?
Did you tell him
that you're here to see me?
Did you even mention my name?
Did you?
See?
Palm.
You're very important to me.
Think about what would happen
if we broke up.
Who knows if we would break up or not?
Can you foresee the future?
I don't want to risk you.
I shouldn't have asked you
to be just friends.
Would we have lasted this long
if you didn't?
I really can't stay any longer.
When you have a girlfriend...
We can still be friends
again someday, right?
Right?
If you take one more step, I'll kiss you!
FIVE MISSED CALLS
Beware. End of the walkway.
It was the worst breakup I've ever had,
even though we weren't even a couple.
You guys don't have to get carried away.
Are you saying that...
no matter how long we wait,
there's no happy ending for us?
If you cross the line...
there's no going back.
How did you handle it?
When the text has been read,
but there's no reply...
I can't sleep.
I can't imagine my life without her.
How did you do it?
I had to start over
with new people.
Hey.
Are you making a wish or cursing me?
Palm.
-Hey.
-What?
Buy three and get one for free.
Don't you have high cholesterol?
It's okay. One strip makes my day.
One strip or one pack?
This pack is for our beef stroganoff.
It's a Russian must-have.
This pack...
-I'm going to make spaghetti
-No, that's fine.
and bacon with dried chilies.
Made with Thai flavors.
The ad came out early?
Are you Jackie Chan or what?
Why are you so mean?
You know I overthink things
It makes my heart jittery
Who will take responsibility?
I want to tell you
How anxious I am
Before you say anything
I want you to promise me
That you won't make me cry
Do you like shitting in the woods?
Are we still together in our dreams?
Your heart hasn’t changed
And our love is still the same
All I want is for you to say it
Tell me that you think about it
Tell me, so I am sure
That our love is still the same
Am I right?
Goong-Gink.
Why are you smiling?
What?
What are you smiling about?
What are you thinking?
Tell me now.
You won't tell me?
I admit it.
Even when I'm dating someone new,
I can't help but compare them to her.
So, I stopped talking to them all.
If I had to be friends with her,
that's also unacceptable.
Palm.
Trust me.
-Don't turn around.
-Gink?
Don't!
Gink, right?
That's enough.
I think you should go your own way.
I know it's not my place.
But...
you should stop bothering him,
or pretending you're still
friends with him.
You need to understand
that he can't be friends with you.
He can't be friends with you.
I don't want to be his friend either.
What do you want?
I broke up with Ted!
Why? Did he cheat again?
No, he didn't.
I want to see
the Northern Lights with you.
I need to ask you one question.
I won't ask it again.
What?
You and I,
if we can't be friends anymore...
let's just get married, okay?
What?
Will you marry me?
What? I didn't hear you!
I said...
Palm. You...
Are you okay?
I told her, "no marriage license."
In the end, she made me sign it.
Damn!
Shit.
Man.
I'm so happy for you!
Your one decade didn't go to waste.
You know,
we have always thought that...
the longer we wait, the less hope we have.
The longer we're together,
the harder it gets to cut ties.
My friend has been waiting.
I need to give this to her.
See you around.
Nice talking to you.
Same here.
What did you brag about?
Beer slushie, right?
I had to chill it first.
It's already a slushie. Shut up.
I was just giving them a pep talk.
Thanks.
Yes.
-Cheers.
Get your friend to bring it.
Yes.
Where have you been?
Getting your beer.
Thanks.
What?
-Gink.
-What?
Your ring?
It must have fallen off
when I was dancing.
-Shit!
-Christ!
Calm down, Gink.
It's me, Ju. What are you looking for?
The wedding ring.
You lost my wedding ring?
Look at your finger first.
Oh, it's here!
I'll help you look.
Honey, help us.
Help us look, please.
Help us look for her wedding ring.
A wedding ring.
Could you please look for it?
I found it!
How did it go over there?
I don't know.
What?
You proposed to me first.
Let me propose to you.
Palm.
Get up.
Let me propose first.
-Don’t joke around. Everyone's looking.
-Stay still.
Palm, I said don't fool around.
Be with me forever, okay?
Of course.
What? Get up.
Are you crazy?
Why can't I be like them?
Go dump him.
I'm giddy.
Giddy for you.
We don’t want to be just friends.
We want to be hubbies!
-Yes!
Oh, it's cold!
-Goong-Gink.
-Ted.
Goong-Gink.
It's like you're playing with a dog.
Damn it!
Oh, no!
Just go be with her!
Louis!
Damn scary!
-Is this your first time in Krabi?
-Oh, we're just friends.
What did I ask her?
You look so evil.
Dude, you almost kissed me.
No one stopped him.
Ten years!
One more time.
It's too normal.
Ten years!
I don't believe you.
I'll keep doing it.
One. Two. Three.
Have you asked if it is off-key or not?
I have to say very badly!
Subtitle translation by Karina Suvapataya