What brought me to this point?
Friends? Girls?
Or greed?
Fuck it.
Now I'm in trouble.
Actually,
I'm in deep shit.
I'm hungry.
Is that the forest? The sea?
Sorry!
Motorbike!
Coming through!
Girl!
Hey!
Come on, girl.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Hey.
You're still using a film camera?
And a cassette player?
So--
Come on. Don't talk to a punk.
-What?
-Come on.
-Let's go home.
Come home sometimes.
These assholes will drag you down.
Hey, where have you been?
Come play with me.
Sim is such a noob. I'm struggling here.
And you're a turd who hides behind a post.
That's all I have. Take it.
Hey.
Don't you know how to say "thank you"?
I'm not your servant.
Why was your brother here?
He has a punchable face.
Don't mind him.
At least he gave me some money.
Are you sure that is enough?
You can't even buy items in the game.
Hey! That's my money!
Skinny, where are you going?
That's my money.
It's 500 baht.
We should share.
Help me, Sim.
This way. Everyone, follow me here.
-This is how we make a living.
-Over here.
Work that doesn't require much.
Can you see me?
It only needs teamwork.
We do what we are good at.
It might sound stupid,
but it's not so easy.
If one man could do it,
we wouldn't need a plan.
Hello, miss. Miss.
What took you so long?
I've been waiting for a long time.
Who are you?
Do not fall behind.
To execute a plan,
our team needs
a kick-starter.
A distraction…
that is so slick.
And we need secret players
that are ready to close any deal.
Moron.
Next time, put the oxygen--
-Put the oxygen in there next time.
-Who?
-Come out!
-Shut up!
Oh, yes, baby.
-Cheers.
It's a damn cheap piece of junk.
It breaks when I bite.
Nine minutes, forty-five seconds.
-Still can't beat the record.
-Shit.
-Check this out.
-Hey.
Why are you showing off?
Did you borrow from a friend?
Yes, Chok.
All right, man. See you.
Guys, let's go collect coins.
To us,
Chok is fucking cool.
The more scars on his body,
the more intimidating he is.
If there is someone
that everybody in this city respects,
Chok is one of them.
Our job is
to collect the money for Boss.
This pendant
tells those motherfuckers
that we represent him.
Boss acts as the middleman
who clears the way
and makes all businesses run smoothly.
Not anyone can do this.
Boss must be the one
that everyone respects.
Hey, Chok.
He said you can wait here.
There are still a lot of customers.
Please wait.
Hey.
Have a cigarette while waiting.
Just let them clear out.
It's short.
Count carefully, Chok.
Shit, I counted three times already.
Well, if it's short,
Mr. Chow said it's all he has.
You just take that for now.
What's so hard about that?
Here, have some chicken with me.
This is our recommended dish.
-Pay in full.
-Shit.
What the fuck is with you, Chok, huh?
I'm having my meal.
Don't you get it?
I said this is all I have.
If that's not enough,
you want some more,
here it is.
Bastard.
Here, take it.
Pick it up and get your ass back
to your boss.
You fucker, I just want to eat.
What are you looking at? Pick it up!
Isn't that what you want?
My chicken is fucking cold, shit!
You denied my chicken offer,
maybe you want to taste my foot instead.
Hey.
Let me ask you this, Chok.
Is your boss
a real man or a beggar, huh, Chok?
Running around and begging
for money from all these different places.
What's up with that?
Get some coins from my office
to donate to them.
So they can leave my restaurant.
Just let me eat in peace.
Fucker.
-Bastard.
-Hey!
-Fucker!
-Motherfucker.
What the fuck are you doing?
Fucking eat it!
Motherfucker!
Get him!
-Chok, let's go.
-Asshole.
You asked for it, asshole!
-Boss.
-Are you all right, boss?
Chok, this way.
Chok, go.
-Boss.
-Chok, you motherfucker!
Motherfucker!
-Shit! He's got a gun!
-Get back here!
Motherfucker!
Chok, I'll get you!
Shit! We are so cool!
Damn! I punched three of them!
Fuck yes!
All right, I'll see to it.
He's dead.
I'm sorry, boss.
That fucker Koo cussed you out.
Chok.
So what if he cussed me out?
Would that kill me? No.
He would have to pay me anyway.
Do you know they're changing leaders?
It's Johnny.
Johnny?
Mr. Chow's son.
The one who was arrested
for drugs and went to--
Shush, quiet.
You remember Johnny, don't you?
Yes.
Boss doesn't let us talk about it.
You know that Johnny won't let this slide.
Of all the people, Chok,
you killed someone in his family.
If you aren't here for a while,
will this be enough for your wife?
More than enough, sir.
All right.
Come with me.
What the fuck is going on?
-Shit.
-What the hell!
Chok.
We are even.
That's the rule.
You, you, and you.
Don't you dare challenge me.
Understand?
Yes.
Tee.
You will take over for him.
Chok.
Just like what Chok told us.
Whoever runs a business in this city
has to follow the rules.
If you pay, you won't get hurt.
If you want to get hurt,
it will never end.
But if you want it to end,
Boss will end it for you.
Salute!
What a cool guy.
Do you think I'm cool?
What?
Give me a minute and we'll do it again.
No. I just lost money on a bet.
I'm in a bad mood.
Just wait for me.
Hey.
You said you wouldn't be back.
Why are you so surprised?
Did you go to school?
So?
Are you still with this bastard?
Watch your mouth.
I'm older than you.
But this is my place.
You stay here, don't go.
Let go. What is wrong with you?
I'm your brother.
Why would you let him beat you up?
That's between me and her.
Fuck off.
-I'm her brother, you fuck off.
-Oh, really?
-Motherfucker. What?
-Stop it, Tee!
-What?
-Tee, stop!
You bastard! Stop!
What's your problem?
I'm your brother!
It's between us, fuck off!
He beats me up.
It's my body.
What's it to you?
Do you think you treat me better?
What kind of brother are you?
I haven't been to school for months.
When was the last time
you paid for my tuition?
Why should I go to school?
I'm embarrassed!
Tee. You will take over for him.
What kind of brother are you?
Damn it!
When was the last time you paid
for my tuition?
That's the rule.
Don't you dare challenge me.
Don't overthink.
One day we will have to do that.
Aren't you going to wait for
Chok's wife to come out and get it?
Damn! Chok just died in front of us.
How can we look her in the eyes?
Let's go.
Why are you sleepy at the party?
Babe, wake him up.
Make him happy.
Joy, my dear.
Don't be nervous.
You can just chill here.
I know everyone here,
and everyone knows me.
Hey, busboy.
Busboy!
Baldy.
-Come over here.
-Just a moment.
Yes, sir. What can I get you?
Do you know me?
Yes.
See? He knows me.
I told you I come here often.
Come here.
I want a "snack." Do you have it?
Go get it.
Calm down, everyone. We'll have fun.
Fun and happiness is coming.
Happy vibes.
Just like old times, right, Joy, my dear?
Hey, where is my snack?
Sorry, it's out of stock.
Out of stock?
Then go get more,
why are you here telling me?
It's your job.
Go get it.
Do you want a snack?
If I didn't want it,
why would I be angry, Joy, my dear?
Does that mean
you don't want me anymore?
If I can have you,
I don't want anything else.
I'll fucking throw it away.
What if I take a snack but not you?
Is that okay?
Your job from now on
is to collect coins.
The main gangs
you have to visit are these guys.
Do you know Kim's gang?
They run a sex business.
When you see
a bunch of foxy girls standing outside,
that's their lair.
As for Sharif's gang,
they own big casinos.
I'm sure you have heard about them.
You've delivered to them before, right?
Next is Jaden's gang.
They forge all kinds of documents.
-Okay?
-They like to keep to themselves.
But they do go all in when fighting.
Muller's gang
owns brothels.
They find prostitutes for expats.
When you collect coins, count carefully.
They are damn tricky.
Last but not least, is Jacob's gang.
They are the most problematic.
They do every illegal business.
Let's say,
if there's anything,
you should talk to his brother, Evan.
He is about your age,
so you should get along easier.
What the fuck are you looking at?
And we are here today
because when these gangs have a problem,
we always meet up here to settle it.
Every issue ends here.
What he said--
-I don't agree.
-Me neither.
We all have to pay Boss.
I don't know about you guys,
but it's just a model I'm proposing.
Let's just say
we continue as we did before.
Jacob,
can you give your word
that you won't step into others' turfs?
Boss, if you say so,
how can I be against it?
Good.
Jacob is trying
to take over the whole city, isn't he?
Yes, but you know what?
He cannot succeed,
if Big Boss doesn't allow it.
Brother, Johnny is here.
That's great.
Congratulations.
Hello, Boss.
Johnny,
when did you get out of jail?
Why didn't I know?
Well, your right-hand man…
Chok, let's go.
He broke the rule.
It was death that he deserved.
And the rest--
they are all little punks.
How would they know shit?
Come on, it's all in the past.
Johnny is so arrogant.
He must think that his dad is your peer.
If he doesn't want to be anyone's bitch,
he has to prove himself
that he is above Jacob.
I've got to go.
Goodbye, Boss.
You should be more respectful to us,
and you better watch over your turf.
Do you want to try me, motherfucker?
-Calm down.
-What?
What? Come on.
Evan is just Jacob's barking dog.
That dickhead.
But a dog like him might be useful for us.
Bastard.
-Ready?
-Ready.
-Clear!
Let's go!
I'll wait outside.
We have to be careful.
If it goes south, you have backup.
Backup, my ass.
Now that you have to deal with tough guys,
your legs are shaky.
Stop picking on him.
Let him wait here.
It's our first time.
We have to be careful.
-Take it.
-What?
Come on.
Chok is gone.
Boss sent us instead.
I'm sorry.
He sent you punks
to collect money from me.
Isn't that a bit weird?
If you're lying,
I'll kick your ass.
Kid.
Yes?
Pick up the cigarette for me.
Here.
Why don't we call Boss?
Just to be sure. Hey, get me my phone.
Shit, if it went like this
when we collect coins from others,
Boss would take phone calls all night.
Hey, you don't need to call.
We are not lying.
If you're not doing anything wrong,
why are you afraid?
I told you not to call!
Oh, gosh.
You bitch!
Why did you kick me?
We are here for Boss.
To collect money.
Even if you call him,
you have to pay me anyway.
Yes, you are right.
Tell those two to put their guns down.
Put them down.
Who are you? MIB, huh?
They're my bodyguards.
Show us some respect.
Do it the easy way.
-Hand over the money, we go home.
-You're right.
-You go back, that's it.
Sure. Of course.
-Do it the easy way, will you?
-Can't you do it the easy way?
Yes, pay me!
Yes. I got it.
-Shit.
Who hurts my friends, you die!
-You guys--
-Don't make fun of him.
-"Who hurts my friends…"
-Come on.
Let's try this one.
Don't be chicken, guys.
I'll lead.
Not on my level.
Hey! Wasn't it too easy?
Why was it so easy?
You are the worst.
You are insulting me right now.
-Moron. Who is it now? That's not Boss.
-Yes.
Boss, are you still coming?
Boss?
-Shit.
-You're the worst.
Hey, Boss. Don't forget my money.
Don't forget me when you're rich.
I didn't do it.
-Didn't do what?
-I didn't do it.
-Do what?
-Fuck, this is bad.
Must be some rough stuff.
-Don't joke around.
-Boss.
-Shit, get her.
-Let me go.
-There's only you here.
-I didn't do it.
-What did you do to him?
-Boss, wake up.
-Get in there.
-Shit.
Boss, wake up.
What did you do to him?
-I didn't. He just went like that.
-Boss.
-I didn't do anything.
Hey, do something.
Boss, wake up.
-Boss!
-Tee, let's call the cops.
Boss!
I didn't do it.
-It wasn't me.
-Not yet.
I didn't do it. I didn't.
Come here.
Get in there!
No, I don't want to!
I think we can own this place.
Kid, you are unbelievable.
What are you talking about?
Come to think of it,
I think Kid is right.
Boss has no family.
And nobody knows that he is dead
if we don't tell.
What are you thinking?
This is wrong.
And you think what
we do every day is right?
There is nothing right or wrong.
But this is an opportunity.
I don't know about you.
If you want to tell the cops,
then go ahead, I won't stop you.
But think carefully, Tee.
Please, I didn't do it.
Please let me go.
What should we do with her?
I have an idea.
Tee, enough.
Trust me.
Let's do it this way. Who's with me?
Sure, whatever.
I'm in.
All right, me too.
Yes, that's it, man!
To take Boss's identity,
we first have to know what he was doing
or what he was thinking.
Make a turn at the corner.
Go to the other side, off you go.
Hey, give me more.
And turn everything of his
into ours.
Stay focused.
What, there's more?
Are you tired? Stay awake.
Tee, don't forget to collect coins today.
"Tee, don't forget
to collect coins today."
Go play somewhere else.
All we do is for Boss
to still have a presence in this city.
Don't forget to collect coins today.
Hey, you dumbass.
Hey!
Hey, it's open.
-Hey, it's open.
-It's open.
Look, it's open.
You did it.
Good job.
How cute. Let me give you a kiss.
Hey, Sim. You asshole. No.
No, Sim. Shit. Sim.
-What's wrong?
-Tee, help me.
-What are you doing? Get off him.
-Tee, he's climbing on my legs.
-Tee, help me!
-Get off.
You're drunk, Sim.
Sim, get off.
Sim. You are so heavy. Sim, come here.
Let go.
-You're so heavy.
-Guys, look at this.
Come on!
Cheers!
Loser.
What did you say?
You are a loser. Small dick loser.
Right.
Limp-dick.
You limp-dick.
You're a limp-dick.
-Sim.
-What's with you?
He is going to kiss me.
Hey.
Piss off.
Joy!
I'll be right back.
Hey, wait.
-What?
-He has to take a shit.
My dear Joy.
-Will you stay and talk to me?
-Hey.
Let me go!
Hey, you hurt me.
Aren't you going to apologize?
Apologize for fucking what? Let me go!
That's quite a mouth you have. Come here.
Wait.
Why do you grab me? Go get her.
How dare you do this to me?
Asshole!
-Asshole?
-Yes!
Feisty. I love it!
Let go. Let go of me.
My ride is coming.
We will have fun tonight.
-Okay?
-Fuck off!
Hey, get in.
Let me go.
Just get in, you'll have fun.
Who's that?
Hey, calm down.
Whoa, so heroic.
All right.
Goddamn!
Bastard, I'll get back at you.
Thanks for helping me.
Yes.
You should be more careful.
Since you saved me this time,
you better save me again.
Are you leading me on?
No, I'm not.
Just kidding.
But really, thank you.
I'm Joy.
Oh, hell, I know.
I'm Tee.
“Hell”?
You are talking to a girl. Be polite.
Sorry.
I'm used to speaking like that
with my friends.
And
what school do you go to?
I don't go to school.
I see.
Sorry.
Why apologize?
I don't feel anything
about not going to school.
And
how old are you?
Who are you?
A detective?
Then do you have a girlfriend?
Just in case.
You are so bold.
Can I flirt with you?
Seriously,
if I'm in trouble again, will you help me?
Sure, if it's right in front of me.
But I won't always be there with you.
I can't take care of myself well.
Just keep an eye out.
Aren't you afraid of coming with me?
Why would I be?
That's great.
Most people are.
Damn. Why are you knocking?
Is your dad a drummer or something?
Hello.
What I did, I didn't mean it.
You had it coming, shit face.
You're tough, huh?
Joy.
Dad wouldn't like it
if he heard about this.
You are just a brother,
stop snooping around.
I want nothing to do with you.
Good, keep to yourself then.
Can you stop being a slut then?
You're embarrassing me.
And you went to jail.
Is that not embarrassing?
Joy!
For the shit you did,
you'll die a painful death.
Is that Boss's voice?
Do you think you can get away with it?
Where is it coming from?
Hey, don't panic.
Gosh, it sounded exactly like him.
How did you do it?
I used this app.
I used Boss's phone to call this one.
The voice you heard came from this.
When we use this app,
the other end of the line
won't catch it.
Hey, Johnny.
Yes, Father.
Where are we with Jacob?
Finish it.
Yes, Father.
If you can't do it,
I'll give the job to someone else.
I promise.
I'll pay your money back.
For Tee's sake, please, Jacob.
Let us go.
Tee?
Who the hell is he?
Does he think he is Boss?
You have to pay your debt anyway.
Do you know
Russian Roulette?
Look at this.
I said look at this.
Look at this closely.
Here, your turn.
Holy shit!
What is it, Kid?
-What happened?
-Shit
-What?
-It's the due date to pay the bribe.
What? Don't tell me--
To Big Boss.
Damn, we are in trouble.
BIG BOSS
-No!
Hello, Boss.
Hope you didn't forget our meeting.
Shit.
Hey.
We are going to Big Boss,
don't act like a kid.
How am I a kid?
I'm not a kid.
Hey.
Don't be nervous. Damn cool.
What the Big Boss says
is what you must do.
Take it.
How strange.
Boss normally doesn't send anyone else.
Shit, do you think that's him?
I don't think so.
What do you think?
Listen to his voice, it's definitely him.
What?
Well, Tee just means that you look so good
that we can't believe our eyes.
Are you sure?
-How does Boss trust you with this, huh?
-Here it is.
All small notes.
Didn't he tell you?
I only want 1,000 baht notes.
Damn it. Show me your face.
Take it off.
Strip off and get in here.
I won't get in.
-No way, I won't.
-I won't either.
You get in alone.
-Damn it!
-Shit!
I won't get in. Never!
Definitely not!
It's all right.
I don't take it personally.
Do you really think
that you can fool me?
I know. I have connections.
I know everything in this country.
And next time,
only give me big notes.
Seeing small notes irritates me.
Bring my gift to Boss.
Why are you all quiet?
Come on.
Laugh.
Hey, Tee,
I think I should go visit Boss some time.
I think this is too risky.
They'll catch us sooner or later.
I agree.
These people are not stupid.
We must change to lower the risks.
The old method that Boss used,
we should change it.
We have to find a better payment method.
That's easier said than done.
It's not easy like playing games.
But it's not that difficult either.
Shit, I got it.
After you topped up 10k?
It's my money. Piss off.
Hey, I think,
to be able to control everything,
we must build it ourselves.
What do you mean, Kid?
At first, I didn't get what the fuck
Kid was talking about.
What's in your mouth? Throw it away.
He asked for a budget to upskill himself.
He enrolled in things
we never thought of learning,
be it conventional
or unconventional.
We use graphs.
It's easier to look at these graphs.
The graphs are all integrated.
This is the latest game model
that I developed.
He didn't stop at just one skill.
He asked for more budgets to go further.
We will use the game
that we play every day.
We will exchange money in the game.
And with this password,
everybody can log in to the game.
-It's our rules. We created them.
-Put it in.
From now on,
everything happens in the game's world.
But there will be a secret mode
for the gangs,
not open to the public,
via the phone's flash drive.
And we'll collect the money from there.
In exchange for discounts
on the purchase of items in the game
via the characters we created
to represent the gangs.
Here, we are gods.
-You like it?
-Yes.
We don't have to meet them.
They still benefit from us.
It's a win-win.
Do you like it?
-Yes.
-You like it?
Pay for these two for me.
-Bye, see you.
-Bastard.
Guys!
The balance is climbing! Look!
The balance is climbing!
Today is the day they have to pay us.
You guys just wait.
We'll get more later tonight.
I'm rich.
It's hot, isn't it?
Don't you miss me at all
that I haven't been here
for several days, huh?
You're fighting back?
The offer you gave me--
I can't take it.
It's shitty.
Good. Very honest.
I have something to show you.
Look.
I know what you are thinking.
I'm not stupid.
I won't jump in to be fed on.
These animals are predators.
No matter how well you tame them,
they are still dangerous.
I've been busy lately.
I didn't have much time to feed them.
They must be very hungry now.
Don't get me wrong.
Seeing how you've been under
your brother's shadow for so long,
I just thought you might want
to build something for yourself.
Building something for myself
like you said,
I would have to betray my own brother.
I wouldn't do it.
Jacob must know
that these alligators
can't be tamed like dogs.
Eat up.
Hey.
Johnny, how dare you?
Johnny! Let me go!
Johnny!
Don't go.
How could that be an accident?
What a fucked-up way to die.
Evan was not a kid.
How could he just fall into the pit?
That's right.
And if that's what happened,
who could have gotten that close to him?
Hey, guys.
Jacob called.
He wants Boss at Evan's funeral.
We're fucked.
What should we do, Kid?
Why should we be afraid?
We will go.
Isn't Boss here yet?
He'll be here soon.
Hello, Boss.
Everyone is waiting.
Hello?
Are you okay, Boss?
I'm sorry.
I'm not feeling well.
I haven't been out much.
Your voice sounds terrible.
I'm fine. I'm okay.
Shit, he's almost here.
I'm all right. Don't worry.
Shit.
I think you should go back and rest.
I'm so--
Shit, he hung up.
Goddamn.
Smooth.
Jacob.
Pick it up, moron.
Cough.
Yes?
Hello, Boss.
Are you on your way back?
I'm on the way. I'm almost home.
How come you are so fast?
Just kidding.
I'm ill. Everything is a blur.
I forgot to tell you.
Let me deal with this myself.
You stay out of it.
Say something.
Hello?
Boss.
You won't even let me do this?
Okay, we'll talk about it later.
Who is he?
Hey, are you Jacob's guy?
I don't think so.
No, I don't think he is.
Shit! He is running. Follow him.
We need a weapon! Understand?
We need a weapon!
Stop! Shut the fuck up!
Sim!
Hey, you.
Is he still in shock?
See the state he's in
yourself.
Take him to take a bath.
Maybe he'll feel better.
Hey. What are you doing?
I'm done with the body.
So tired.
Will you check on Sim?
Yes.
Did your sister come back?
I don't know.
She wants to be with a man, let her.
Won't you try to bring her back?
She never listens to me anyway.
I'm not her father.
I guess I just need to let her go.
What about Joy?
Are you serious with her?
Don't forget
she is Johnny's sister.
Damn you, Tee.
Why are you asking for trouble?
Come on. Smile.
-No.
-Smile.
-Let's see.
-There you go.
No. It shouldn't be exposed to the light.
What? Where is the film?
There's no film.
How do you take pictures?
I'm just playing with it.
I don't need film.
Here, I got you a new cassette player.
It should keep you entertained.
Where did you get it?
-Not that hard.
-I've been looking for it.
What? There's no tape?
You just play with it.
You don't need a tape.
Cheeky.
Want to listen? Here.
-Come on. Just play along. Come on.
-What?
What is this?
Hey, Tee.
Come here.
Just come here. Quickly.
-Come on.
-What is it?
Someone wants to talk to you.
You bought so much ice cream,
give me some.
Give me one, come on.
Now I remember.
It was you, wasn't it?
You told the police on me.
It was you?
Stay away from my sister!
Out!
Get out!
SOLDIER KILLS GIRLFRIEND
Sim.
-What?
-Look.
What?
Look.
-It's Tee's sister.
-Moron.
What about Tee's sister?
Shit, yes. Shit.
Tee, wake up.
I found your sister.
Where?
Killing each other over debt?
Really?
SOLDIER KILLS GIRLFRIEND
Our game is going well.
And our lives
are what we want them to be.
This is for you, Mom.
Open it.
You don't have to struggle anymore.
Here.
Call me if you need more.
Tuek, where did you get this?
Want some? I saw that you liked it too.
Your story is incredible,
but it sounds fun.
At the end of the day,
everybody is looking for happiness.
Sim.
Tuek.
They spend money on indulging themselves
without having to worry
about making ends meet.
But for Tee,
his happiness is different.
Let's run away together?
Are you kidding?
Why?
It's nothing to worry about.
Just leave everything we are used to.
Are you serious?
How could we do that?
Everything is here.
It started here.
How could we run away?
Of course we can.
Just go farther than we've gone.
Like you said,
just never come back.
There you go.
-Then what?
-This way.
Take control, you are the rider.
Look, it's on fire.
Hello?
What's up?
-Boss.
-What?
Tee is still seeing Joy.
-What do you want us to do?
-Follow them.
Don't lose sight of them.
Find a chance and get rid of him.
Make sure my sister is safe
and bring her back. Got it?
Yes, boss.
Shit, it's pigs.
Bastard.
What took you so long, you dog flea?
You know, my family,
we started from selling pigs.
So whoever used to sell pigs,
are good at butchering.
I'm curious
if a pork consumer like you
knows how to butcher.
Pig butchering
is not my expertise.
Butchering humans, however,
I'm pretty good at.
Respect me like others do.
I want you to fear me
like others do.
I hope you come to me in peace next time.
If Boss was here, he'd be delighted.
To know that Johnny
gave most of his turf over to me to run.
This is reconciliation, isn't it?
I have to thank you, Johnny.
Since you and I are now partners,
let's forget about the past.
I'll keep this between us.
Jacob.
Do you think you treat me better?
When was the last time
you paid for my tuition?
LOAN AGREEMENT
What kind of brother are you?
This is mine.
I don't want yours. It's full of brothels.
-Great. I like that. You can take it.
-Here.
All of you are filthy scumbags
like this shitty city, assholes!
-What the fuck?
-You're scumbags.
All of you.
What the hell?
-Are you crazy, Tee?
-Let go.
-Tuek, open it.
-Let go!
-Get in there, Tee.
-Don't.
-Get in there, asshole.
-Let go.
Damn it!
What should we do?
What do I do with you guys?
Johnny,
we don't have bad blood.
Don't we?
Where is Boss?
What's in there?
Cat got your tongue?
There's nothing.
Don't pretend you don't know.
Don't pretend to be naive.
Shit.
Sim, you didn't bury Boss's body?
I'm sorry.
How dare you do all of this?
Tee.
I'll expose
the shitty business you assholes did.
Damn it.
Johnny came here because of you, Tee.
What the hell?
You didn't bury Boss, now you blame me?
-We might be spotted.
-Wait.
-Get back.
-Shit, it's the cops.
The cops are here. Get back.
We better bring Boss's body back upstairs.
You guys drive that woman home.
Just give her a lot of money.
-Shit.
I'm tired.
Damn you, Sim.
I thought you got rid of Boss's body.
Why did you put him in the wine barrel?
You can't just blame it on him.
We all made mistakes.
Yes, if the two of you hadn't fought,
we would have been done with the body.
What do you want?
Do you have a better idea?
-Well, say it.
-It's because of you
we carried it up and down like ten times.
So what?
You always blame it on me.
Sim, get up.
-Asshole.
Hey, my arm.
Shit.
-Thank you.
-Shit.
I don't think we will survive this.
Of course we will.
Why won't we?
How could we?
Who would believe we didn't kill Boss?
What about that woman?
Do you remember where she lives?
Just take her back here.
We can't do that.
She's dead.
Shut the fuck up.
What the hell are you talking about?
Hey.
Are you guys hiding something from me?
The issue about Boss is not bad enough?
What the hell happened? Tell me.
What happened?
Damn, Tee and Kid are such dictators.
Why are you complaining so much?
Just follow Kid's plan.
What else do they want from me?
-Hello.
-Hello, Sim.
Don't take her home.
What if she talks?
We'll be all doomed.
What did you say?
You want us to kill her?
I don't want to do that.
No!
Shit, she jumped out.
-She ran away.
-What's happening?
Shit, Kid, she jumped out.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
-She's fucking dead.
-Calm down.
Shit. She's dead.
-Hey, calm down.
-Kid, what should we do?
Follow my plan.
Don't let Tee know.
This fucking door can't stop me.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm done running.
We'll just end up dying.
What then?
I'll fight back.
I'll fight like a desperate dog.
Asshole.
You are out of your mind, Tee.
Our chances of winning this fight
are very low.
But if we run,
our chance of survival is zero.
-Jacob, we need to talk.
-Hello?
-Let's meet.
-Pardon?
-It's about Johnny.
-Johnny?
If it's about him,
just wait for a moment, Boss.
I'll be right there. See you.
Where is Boss?
Tee, you bastard,
you stabbed me?
-Shit.
-You stabbed me?
Sim, get him.
You motherfucker.
Motherfucker.
Motherfucker, what are you doing?
Sim!
Motherfucker.
You hurt my friend.
You killed my sister, you bastard?
Bastard.
Sim.
Sim, are you all right?
Sim!
Sim.
Sim, stay with me.
Sim!
Sim.
Fuck!
Bastard!
Find them.
Tell everyone.
We used to be kids who were full of fear.
Because Boss put fear in us.
Now we are ready to face it.
You won't survive this.
What the fuck is this?
We know what we did was wrong.
It's the gift we gave you.
The gift that makes all of you satisfied.
JACOB
The gift nobody else
was able to deliver before us.
The two feet that stomped on you,
the two hands that took advantage of you.
I only did what you all wanted to do
but didn't dare to do.
If we hadn't done it,
would you have had the guts?
Fuck!
What should we do with them?
I'll kill them!
Who killed Boss?
You all deserve to die.
You have to thank the system
that you created.
It keeps you alive today.
An unexpected twist,
it's like we are born again.
And whatever your job was,
just go back to do the same.
Got it?
There is nothing complicated about it.
The last gift box,
which was sent to Big Boss…
Damn it.
…is the evidence of the shit
-Jacob's gang did.
-What are you waiting for?
Yes, take them all.
Leave no one.
Especially of them breaking the rules,
invading others' turfs.
We just used it against them.
It's all about benefits.
In this game,
"Boss" doesn't mean being the leader.
But it is the representative of
a special relation.
Only a special person
can forge that connection.
What we did was savage,
but we wanted it that way.
We rattled this city,
and it has done what it's good at.
It has swept our wrongdoings
under the rug entirely.
The silence takes the place of
the shout of our victory.
Damn.
Are you getting famous?
Johnny.
What should I do with you?
I can't kill you.
And yet you are my enemy.
Then learn to respect me.
So you don't have to be my enemy.
Oh, Johnny.
Bastard! I've had enough with you.
Bastard!
Can you tell me now
where my sister is?
You were with her before she was taken.
The van that took my sister
was found wrecked
at the bottom of the cliff.
There was nothing inside.
There was no one.
Who?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Then you are useless!
Everything almost comes to an end.
It will end with my life.
For my friends who survive,
they will be at the top of the food chain.
Here. I trust you.
Joy.
What took you so long?
I should have left you to die.
It's not a miracle.
I have something crazy for you to do.
I like crazy.
What is it?
We'll provoke people in this city.
Especially
Johnny.
You guys follow them.
Don't lose sight of them.
Tuek, go.
Don't worry about him.
Right, Tee is tough.
Don't worry if he's going to die.
Stop suspecting me.
If I was going to do anything that stupid,
I wouldn't hide it, all right?
We will start new lives together
and let people of this city
forget us for good.
You guys are crazy.
You guys are fucking crazy.
Let me see your face.
Gosh.
Take me to the doctor.
Yes, you need that.
It's like I have a new boyfriend.
I can give you more than those punks.
But you aren't one of us.
Subtitle translation by:
Thanatcha Saksiamkul