CHAPTER ONE, THE WORDLESS SCRIPTURE
GRAB THE WEALTH TO BE GRABBED
OR LIVE TO REGRET!
You are such a loser!
Enough, stop laughing at him!
Can you stop it?
Let's go to the Guan Yin Temple
before we go back home later.
I've already told you.
You're very unlucky this year.
Stop mentioning it!
This is not the first time anyway.
NO ENTRY
SILVER NEEDLE NOODLES, MOUSE
That's all that's left of my dad?
So? Do you want us to clean it?
Hey! What the heck! What's this?
Sulfuric acid?
SULFURIC ACID, BAIJIU
I'm so sorry!
Right.
I have a question.
I have always wanted to ask you.
What is it?
Are you really your dad's son?
What did you say?
Nothing, I just find it weird.
His dad gave him a very horrible name.
Bad Luck Lim.
It's Lim Dao Mei.
It means beautiful in Chinese.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Are your names very nice?
-Let's eat.
-Eat.
Don't finish all the vegetables.
Leave some for me.
Someone jumped off the building!
Hurry!
What took you so long?
-Run Fa.
-What?
Why did you come in with your shoes on?
Also, Dao Mei plucked my red flower again.
Yes, I want a flower bath, okay?
Help me with it.
Why are you still here?
Someone jumped off the building!
I'm sorry.
It was a nightmare.
Is he okay?
Don't be so nosy!
Aren't you supposed to be
on the night shift?
Hey, Jia Hui. Let's go for supper.
No, thank you. I want to sleep.
My hair will fall out
if I don't sleep enough.
You guys go ahead.
Let's go!
Hey, handsome.
These are tomorrow's jackpot
winning numbers.
Quick. Go and place your bet.
I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?
Hey, Jia Hui.
Jia Hui!
Wake up!
You're so noisy!
Hey, are you playing a prank on me?
Jia Hui, stop playing with me!
What happened?
You're the one who woke me up!
Who is playing a prank now?
Hey, try saying this,
"I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?"
Come on, say it.
"I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?"
Can you be more serious?
-One more time!
-What?
That is not the right tone.
The tone is wrong?
"I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?"
Can I sleep now?
Was I dreaming?
Impossible!
Hey, it's drawing now!
If I win the jackpot,
I will be very rich!
If you really do win,
you need to do some charity work.
-Great!
-Come.
-Let's make a donation tomorrow.
-Shut up!
And 17.
Crap!
You don't have to curse.
If it's yours, it's yours.
If it's not, it's not.
You're not the one buying.
Of course it's easy for you to say!
Stop fighting.
Let's eat, the vegetables are fresh!
Hey, what are you doing?
You won the jackpot?
How many numbers did you win?
Three? Four?
Or five?
All!
You got all the numbers?
You won the jackpot?
But I didn't bet.
You didn't bet?
I saw the numbers in a book.
Then I heard a voice saying
these are the winning jackpot numbers
and asked me to bet on them.
But I thought I was hallucinating,
so I didn't bet.
That was obviously the voice
of the God of Wealth,
but you didn't bet!
You should have given your blessings
to someone more intelligent!
But then again, you're quite lucky
to be able to spot
the winning numbers.
Maybe if I made that bet,
it wouldn't have been drawn.
You said that
you saw the numbers in a book.
Where is the book?
I think I've thrown it away.
I'm sorry.
I've emptied the bin.
You've thrown it away?
My goodness!
What are you still doing here?
Go get it back!
Cindy.
You really impressed me!
I'm amazed you could still find it
in such a dirty place.
I'm even more envious of you!
Where did you find such a good girlfriend?
I'm even more impressed by you two!
How can you two talk to her
when she is so smelly?
What are you still doing here?
Go take a bath!
I'm warning you,
if you can't get rid of that smell,
you'll sleep in the toilet!
I've gone through it a dozen times,
but there's nothing.
Don't give me that.
You are the one
who got his girlfriend dirty.
Explain it to him.
It seems like that's a wordless scripture.
What is a wordless scripture?
Didn't you watch movies from the past?
You needed to go through a lot
if you wanted to know
the secret inside.
Nonsense!
You shouldn't play with knives
even if the fire doesn't work!
That's how it is in the movies.
When fire and water fail,
-blood is the next best solution!
-Don't play with it!
Give it to me!
And you! What numbers?
You must be playing a prank on us!
What?
Did you see that?
What did you see?
The numbers!
Inside the book!
There's nothing there!
Is there something wrong with your eyes?
No, there are really numbers in the book.
I think you're out of your mind!
Crazy!
I really saw the numbers!
Do you think I am crazy too?
No!
But if I trust you,
then I'm the crazy one.
I'm tired, I'm going to bed.
I'M NOT CRAZY EITHER!
Sorry, I really didn't see it.
I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?
Stop looking for me. You won't find me.
I'm asking you, are you going to bet?
Don't you understand Mandarin?
I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?
I've already given you the numbers.
I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?
Can you stop staring at me?
-I'm shy!
-I'm saying,
aren't you going to bet?
How many times do you want me to ask you?
Are you going to bet?
I'm sorry.
Give me a set of newspapers.
I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?
Idiot, I'm using the toilet!
I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?
Are you having nightmares again?
Is it that terrible?
The lady, Indian guy, and even myself
are telling me this.
"I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?"
"I've given you the numbers. Aren't…"
It's terrifying!
So is it the lady,
the Indian guy, or yourself?
Are you sick?
I think you are possessed.
He's sick!
He's possessed!
-He's possessed!
-He's sick!
He's possessed!
This is what happens
when you daydream too much.
If your features look good,
you'll have ten years of good fortune.
What do you mean?
Stress can cause hallucinations.
You already have everything you need.
You are perfect in every way!
It's good!
I shall give you some tranquilizer,
and you'll be fine.
-So I'll be fine?
-Yes, you'll be fine.
You are the luckiest person around!
How can it be?
This is the best pick!
You are completely in luck!
Everyone wants to win the jackpot.
If you want to win, then bet.
Have you bet on numbers recently?
So go and bet on the jackpot numbers!
If anyone gives you any numbers,
you must go and bet on them!
You're destined to win!
Why are you sleeping here?
I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?
They…
I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?
Hey, handsome!
Are you trying to hide from me?
Do you think you can hide so easily?
Who are you?
I'm the spirit of the magical book.
You can call me Fairy Godfather.
I'm here to bring good fortune
to you unlucky losers
so that you'll never have bad luck again!
Really? Never?
Really? I won't have bad luck anymore?
Can you make me wealthy?
Don't ask me. Ask yourself.
Do you want to be rich?
I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?
I will bet.
Are you really going to bet?
I will!
You'll still bet
even if there is a price to pay?
No matter what price I have to pay,
I will bet!
Good! It's your own choice,
I didn't force you.
Everybody saw it, I didn't force you!
I will bet…
It's so easy to tell an idiot
by the looks.
Qiang Qiang, Wang Wang, come and eat.
Come…
Hey! Can you stop walking around?
I'm telling you, you won't win.
If you win, I'll help you wipe your ass
for one month.
It is time for the broadcast
of this week's jackpot number.
-The winning numbers are…
-Listen.
-4.
-14.
-24.
-24! That's three matches!
-34.
40.
-41.
-41…
-The special number is…
-44!
44!
-It's 44! Jackpot!
-Really?
-All of it? Let me have a look!
-Jackpot!
You won RM600,000!
I won RM600,000!
This is my first time winning the jackpot!
Congratulations!
Thank you for your blessing.
Thank you for your grace.
Don't tell me you didn't bet on it again.
Nonsense! What is this then?
Right.
My stomach is aching.
I need to take a dump.
WIPE HIS ASS FOR ONE MONTH
Wait.
Can you smell it?
No.
What?
DID YOU FART?
Money! The smell of money!
-Tell her.
-Hello, miss.
Hello, gorgeous.
We are here to collect our prize.
We won this week's RM600,000 jackpot.
Please queue there.
What? So many people won?
Yes. There are a total of 12 winners
including you.
Twelve people?
What is that supposed to mean?
It means you will have to share the money
with 11 other people.
That is RM50,000 each.
RM50,000?
Well, it's still lots of money.
Let's queue up.
I'll treat you
after I get the prize money.
Okay.
I'm not sure
if I should pity him or praise him.
Loser!
What? Do you think you're the winner?
Don't come for the celebration later.
No way! We're brothers,
we should celebrate together!
Loser!
CHAPTER TWO,
MONEY IS THE ROOT OF ALL EVIL
EVEN BIRDS OF THE SAME FLOCK
WILL PART WAYS?
You have no ambition!
One should have dreams.
Just like this!
No!
It should be like this.
My goodness! You're such an idiot!
You two are the idiot ones!
Can you afford such cars
with only RM50,000?
It's not even enough
to pay for the four sport rims!
Since you have such a lucky windfall,
you should use some of the money
to do charity.
-So that--
-Are you crazy? Nonsense!
You're the one who's crazy!
Bean sprouts.
Vegetable, bean curd.
Mixed vegetables.
We don't want those.
Prosperity abalone.
Wealthy shark's fin.
And also Buddha Jumps Over the Wall!
Hey, I only won RM50,000, not RM600,000.
Hey, it's RM50,000!
You can afford these dishes!
You're so calculative!
One more. A bowl of bird's nest!
Hey! You're a little too much!
He won RM50,000, not RM600,000.
Also, is bird's nest a vegetarian dish?
Yes!
I also want a bowl.
My RM50,000!
You still have a fortune
after such an expensive meal.
Come, let's go party!
It is as if the money belongs to him.
We've been here for a while.
Why are there no girls talking to us?
Maybe if we order expensive liquor,
we will be able to attract the girls!
No sight of anyone coming.
Maybe this is not good enough.
Shall we order a better one?
There is still no one.
I'm sure these liquors
are not expensive enough!
Shall we get more expensive ones?
Of course! Let's do it!
Our table is full now,
but there are still no girls.
It must be the price!
I suggest we get a super expensive bottle!
Stop ordering.
Have you ever thought
that it might not be the liquor,
but the matter of looks?
Why do you look like that?
There's even a fringe on top of your head!
Compared to both of them,
you are handsome.
Let's go.
My RM50,000.
Now, I'm left with about RM8,000.
Can't I spend it slowly?
Do you want…
to earn back…
all the money you've spent?
We'll get it back!
Get it all back?
Check!
Game!
Double check!
Royal flush!
-Thank you. Please come again.
Didn't you say you wanted to help me
to get my money back?
We lost RM8,000 in less than two hours!
Come on.
Money is just a material thing.
If it's yours, it's yours.
If it's not, it's not.
But it seems that
my money doesn't belong to me.
Whatever wasn't yours became yours!
You're spending my money like it's yours!
Didn't you have a part
in spending the money?
I brought you to play mahjong,
but I never asked you
to lose all your money!
Fine.
It's all my fault.
Hey, where did you say
the numbers were from?
The book from the guy who jumped.
But you never believed me.
Hey.
Why don't we try it again?
Stop fooling around with the belongings
of the dead!
Gosh!
Didn't you eat the bird's nest too?
Okay!
Let's do it one more time.
Are you ready?
Is there anything?
-Anything?
-Nothing.
Really?
Nothing?
I told you.
Don't fool around with the dead's
belongings. But you never listen.
Have another look!
-It's here!
-You saw it?
Wait! Let me grab a pen!
-What is it?
-"You."
"Go to…"
"Hell."
That's not funny!
No, it really says, "Go to hell."
Are you still mad at me
for spending all your money?
No.
We're brothers!
How could you ask us to go to hell?
No.
You saw the numbers,
but you said you didn't!
If you don't want to share
the fortune with us, just say it!
You don't have to tell us to go to hell!
No, there really weren't any numbers.
Hello. Jia Hui. Yes?
Job? Sure, we'll be right over.
Hey, there's a job. Do you want to go?
Of course!
Someone is pretending
not to see the numbers.
He even told us to go to hell!
Going to work is always better
than going to hell!
Let me explain.
Come on, let's go! Let me get changed!
I am really speechless.
I…
Shit.
I'm so pissed off right now.
We are long-time friends.
How can he tell us to go to hell?
You shouldn't blame Dao Mei.
Some people change
when given wealth!
He should be the one going to hell!
Don't talk nonsense here!
Gold!
Now, this is what we call fate.
There's so much jewelry buried with her.
Like I always say,
if it's yours, it's yours.
If it's not, it's not.
Well, not really.
Hey, never take from the dead!
You have done the right thing.
Some wealth is not meant for sharing.
Friendships these days
are not worth a penny!
It's a passe term already!
I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?
If it's head, then forget it.
If it's tail, then I'm all in!
These are treasures!
How can I not take any?
Sorry, ma'am.
These are supposedly yours,
but now, they are now mine.
-Thank you.
-Run Fa!
Don't take from the dead.
It's very bad luck!
See!
Even the heaven
is against putting them back!
Hey, don't take it.
One shouldn't take from the dead!
It's bad karma. Do you hear me?
Okay, let's flip for it.
If it's an auspicious sign,
then we'll take it, okay?
Bear in mind. We'll only take it
if it's an auspicious sign!
It's not! So you can't have it!
-Best of three.
-How could you?
See! It's still not! Let's forget it!
-It's not auspicious!
-Best of five!
You…
Look! Three in a row!
No means no!
One shouldn't be so superstitious!
Don't you remember what our job is?
You…
Don't take it!
Finders keepers!
My goodness.
And it's beautiful!
Hey, don't!
I'm sorry.
It is time for the broadcast
of this week's jackpot number.
The winning numbers are…
The special number is 7.
The jackpot-winning numbers
are brought to you by Biao.
1.5 million is enough
to let you live a happy life.
What? Not enough? You want more?
Again? Not enough?
Again?
Don't tell me you are using the money
as your wallpaper.
Aren't you worried that Run Fa
will spend all your money again?
I know you are going to throw a tantrum.
Be careful. When I…
It hurts!
How could you ask me
to let you win every week?
I might not be human,
but I could also get tired.
Let me introduce an agent to you.
He's very good at money laundering.
He can definitely make you richer.
All right?
Hello, Mr. Lim. How are you?
I am a senior investment agent
from Prosperity Investment.
This is my name card.
Our company has a lot of investment plans
catered to help you make more money.
Let's discuss inside. Come on!
A lot of Middle Eastern bosses
are waiting for you.
Do you know how to invest?
Did the property investor teach you?
How would people like us understand
such money-making theories?
Be careful. Watch where you're going.
Game!
Didn't I tell you?
How would we know about money-making?
Pay me!
Sir, you have one less card! You lose!
You lose!
-Money!
Book Spirit, do me a favor!
-Which car should I choose?
-Of course the big ones.
You'll have enough room to make out in it!
This one.
This one too, and that black one.
This one is even better.
I'll take all of them!
Hey, Dao Mei.
This is really weird.
Why is it that the more you spend,
the more money you have?
Hey!
Don't run every time I talk about money.
I just want to help you make a donation!
For what?
I just wanted to remind you.
Since you've been making a fortune,
have you done any charity?
Is there anything better
to talk about between us?
Not every day is a good time for charity.
We need to wait for the moment.
This is the moment!
Look at all these pitiful elderlies!
Since you're so lucky lately,
why don't you buy from them?
You may win even more!
Nonsense!
It's unethical to do charity
with the aim of making a fortune!
I don't need this kind of luck!
Besides, I once heard
these vendors on wheelchairs
are often conmen.
-You…
-I'm leaving.
Dao Mei!
Of the many condominiums you've seen,
which one do you prefer?
The first one is posh and steady.
Jacky Wu is your neighbor.
The second one is near the city.
It has very meticulous security.
This one has perfect feng shui.
It will help you make a fortune!
Hey.
Which one should I buy?
The first one. I like Kang Kang.
What's so good about Kang Kang?
He looks like a toad.
I can't believe someone would marry him.
Moreover, that house belongs to Jacky Wu,
not Kang Kang.
Well, Kang Kang and Jacky are buddies.
He may come to visit.
No, I'm not talking to you.
Hey.
Which one should I buy?
Jacky Wu has been down on his luck lately.
It's better to buy the one
with good feng shui for your business.
Okay, I'll take this one.
-Thank you.
-Dear, I don't want this one.
This one is good.
CHAPTER THREE, MADAM BUTTERFLY
THERE IS ALWAYS SOME GHOST
SCARIER OUT THERE?
Didn't you say everything is already sold?
Why is the jade pendant
still on your neck?
Don't you think we are a perfect match?
I told you, but you didn't believe me.
Never bring this wicked stuff with you.
Don't you remember what our profession is?
Must you be so superstitious?
Superstitious?
Let me tell you, I used to have a friend
who found a jade pendant on the floor.
In the end--
He was haunted by a female ghost, right?
He was repeatedly raped by the ghost
and eventually died, right?
Stop talking nonsense!
You're the one talking nonsense!
Are there so many ghosts
in the world for you to meet?
Ma'am, you almost scared me to death!
Do you want to buy some tissue paper?
No! Go away!
I have loads of them back home!
I'll buy some from you.
Thank you.
Hey, are you hungry?
Come, let's eat together.
-Thank you.
-Have a seat.
We ordered a lot of dishes.
We can't finish them all.
Come and help us eat.
Here are the chopsticks.
Have a satay.
You have a very beautiful pendant.
I used to have one too.
Ma'am, stop bragging!
This is an antique jade
from the Qing Dynasty.
If you really had one,
you wouldn't be selling tissue paper!
I'm serious.
I really had an identical one.
But it was stolen by some villains.
People nowadays are so unethical.
They could even steal from the elderly.
What could I do?
You suffer when you grow old.
It's all because of these two idiots
who stole my jade.
Actually, I would rather die
than let them take my pendant.
At first, they could not
take it away from me.
But then, they barbarously broke my arm
to steal my pendant!
My broken arm is still in pain.
In fact, it still hurts now.
Ma'am.
Are you sure it's just two,
not three of them?
Well,
can you describe how they stole your jade?
Shut up!
Because you are the one who broke my arm!
You!
Idiots!
My arm really hurts…
I'm still in pain!
My arm is still in pain!
Idiots!
My arm really hurts…
I'm still in pain!
Did you hear that?
Idiots!
It's all your fault!
I told you not to steal from the dead,
but you didn't listen!
Ma'am.
I will never do it again.
Please don't come for me.
Ma'am, please don't come for me.
What happened?
It's you. You scared me!
Why are you sitting here?
What are you doing?
We were waiting for you!
Why are you so late?
Why is it so wet here?
-Earlier, he--
-Why are you asking so many questions?
Don't you stink?
You'd better clean up fast!
I'm going to bathe.
It's been too hot lately!
Hey, are you sure this is the right place?
This place looks too high class.
That lady looked really poor.
She couldn't have afforded this place.
When you stole her things and sold them,
did you think that she was poor then?
Be sincere.
Okay.
You've been nagging since we left home.
Aren't you tired?
I've asked a master.
Usually, for situations like this,
pray sincerely and return the items,
then everything will be fine.
Really?
The master even wrote it down.
Take a look.
But the jade pendant and I
are a perfect match.
What if I return it, but she still comes?
Wouldn't I be at a loss?
Let's go.
It's right in front.
Who are you looking for?
We are looking for Madam Chou
who was previously buried in Semenyih.
She recently moved here.
She was my elder sister.
Are you here to offer prayers for her?
We came to apologize.
Bid farewell!
Actually, we were
your late sister's good friends.
I'm giving you a chance to say it again.
We really are her good friends.
You rogues.
You really don't know
who my elder sister was?
Who?
She was the renowned Madam Butterfly.
Madam Butterfly?
You've never heard of her?
Of course, we've heard of her.
Actually, we wanted to--
Stop talking nonsense.
Actually, we've offended your sister.
You offended her?
No, we…
We unintentionally took her things.
Can you stop lying?
It's true, we're not lying!
Those who stole from my sister
would usually die
or suffer a painful fate.
Quick! Apologize to Madam Butterfly!
-Sorry…
Sorry, I won't do it again.
We are sorry.
How would we know if she has forgiven us?
We'll flip for it.
Quick.
Please.
Be sincere. Quick!
I told you to be sincere. Quick!
There's no one here.
Where did everyone go?
How would I know?
I beg for your blessings.
Let's go, hurry!
Hey, just leave it! Hurry!
Do you have other girlfriends?
No.
-Really?
-Yes.
What about in the past?
I had one.
Why didn't you stay with her?
Her family opposed it.
-Her family? Who? Her dad?
-Yes.
-No.
-Her mom?
Also no.
Then who?
Her husband.
You are so bad!
Go. Cross the road.
Darling, what are you doing?
-Darling.
-Why did you tell me to cross the road?
I didn't tell you to cross the road!
I wasn't talking to you!
You should be careful. You scared me.
You should go. Let's meet again.
What the heck?
Book Spirit! Where are you?
Come out! Stop hiding!
Where are you? Book Spirit!
Wasn't that fun?
A lorry that big couldn't run you down!
Fun?
You told me to cross the road!
Answer the call first.
I'll get back to you later!
David.
A buyer for my lucky house?
Offering 30% more than the market value?
Of course I want to sell it!
The higher the price the better!
-Where were we?
-See?
The price of your lucky house is soaring.
Didn't I tell you it was a lucky house?
Then why did you try to get me
run over by a vehicle?
Have you forgotten
there is a price to pay for your fortune?
You'll still bet
even if there is a price to pay?
No matter what price I have to pay,
I will bet!
Then what is it that you want from me?
Be my replacement and take over
as the new book spirit!
Become the new book spirit?
How do I replace you
as the new book spirit?
Die!
Die?
I don't want to die.
I don't want to die!
-You have no choice.
-I don't want to die!
I don't want to die!
That's the price
you have to pay for your wealth!
Why?
Why me?
If you don't replace me
as the Fairy Godfather,
I won't be able to reincarnate!
That's none of my business.
You chose to eat at the place I jumped.
And you even took the book home!
You were the guy
who jumped off the building?
Your reward is to become my replacement!
Do I have to die now?
No, that was just a warning.
You are unlucky,
but you should live until 60!
But I made you rich and you became greedy.
So your lifespan has been shortened.
You only have one month left to live now.
One month?
That's how it is.
This is the rule of the book.
The more you gain from the book,
the shorter your life will be.
David.
What?
My house is sold?
You made me a profit of RM200,000?
Thank you.
Thank you for making me richer.
Do I really have just one month left?
Sorry, you just made another fortune.
You're now left with three weeks!
Three weeks?
What?
My stock made an RM300,000 profit?
Handsome, go do what you have to do
before it's too late!
Take care, bye.
Mr. Lim, your Singapore shares rose
by 40 times!
The Middle Eastern bosses
are rewarding your good service
with an RM500,000 commission!
Boss, we just signed Jeremy Lin!
We're going to be filthy rich!
Run Fa!
Open the door!
You also met one?
So? What do we do now?
This should be able to help for a while.
Will it really work?
It should be fine, right?
It should be fine.
Is it really fine?
Hey, come out! What are you doing inside?
It's all your fault we suffered so much!
What? What's wrong with my face?
It's all your fault!
You have nothing better to do!
You stole from the dead!
Now you got my head shaved by a ghost!
Don't blame me! It's Dao Mei's fault.
I wouldn't have flared up
if he didn't curse us.
If I didn't flare up,
I wouldn't have stolen the things!
It's all his fault!
We can no longer live here. What do we do?
Call that idiot.
He has a condominium.
We should all move in.
We'll live there for a year or two!
Hello. The line is busy, please wait.
Satisfied?
You've been to France
and visited the Eiffel Tower.
Can you finally rest in peace?
If I say I can't,
can I die later?
There are still many places
I have not been to.
Have you been to the moon then?
Do you want to visit the moon fairy?
No, thank you!
The moon fairy
will most likely be you anyway.
-What did you say?
-Nothing.
I got a call.
MISSED CALLS FROM CINDY AND JIA HUI
Jia Hui.
Run Fa.
Cindy.
Why are you in such a bad state?
There are ghosts here.
A lot of them!
It's Madam Butterfly.
She locked us in here.
It's all his fault!
He stole from the dead.
What Madam Butterfly?
She's a female ghost.
She would touch me every night.
She would touch me here and there.
Sometimes, even here!
It's very scary!
Whenever she touches us,
we would have a butterfly marking
on our body.
-Look.
There are some on my arm
and some on my head.
There's more. I--
Hey!
You don't have to show him!
I think we should seek professional help.
YING, THE ONE BROW MASTER
CHEE, THE MONKEY KING MEDIUM
MADAM ANNIHILATE, THE IMPERIAL NUN
PROMISE, THE HOLY LAMA
Do you think they are powerful?
SCRIPTURE
Run Fa.
Stop touching me.
There's a lot of people here.
I didn't touch you.
Don't look at me.
It can't be me.
What are they doing?
You are too naive.
Will hiring some clowns
to perform magic tricks
be enough to appease me?
I'm Madam Butterfly.
Whatever debt you owe must be paid,
whatever wrong you've done
must be avenged.
When Madam Butterfly strikes,
no one can live!
You were the ones who stole my things
and broke my arm.
Now you're getting help to attack me?
Where is the justice?
But we already apologized at your grave.
Apologized? Listen well.
In our Butterfly Clan,
if someone steals,
we would chop off their arms.
If they break our brother's hand,
we would chop off all of their limbs!
But we're not members
of your Butterfly Clan.
If you guys are not members,
then you're the enemies!
Madam Butterfly, we know we're wrong.
But why only hit me
when he is the one talking
and stealing from you?
Don't you know
how loan sharks collect debts?
You're his best friend.
Did you stop him when he stole from me?
Did you not feast with the money he made
from the things he stole?
-Don't I deserve to hit you?
Don't I deserve to hit you?
Crap.
I just wanted to share my wealth.
Can you just shut up?
Do you think my face
is not swollen enough?
Madam Butterfly.
We know we're in the wrong.
How will you forgive us?
Return all the things you stole from me!
I am only left with this pendant.
I've already sold the rest.
Then all of you have to die!
I'll give you a lifeline.
By right, if you become poor again
before your deadline,
you should be spared.
But by left, it depends
if you have good fortune.
Good luck to you, handsome.
Mister, this is your bag, right?
There's a lot of money in it.
Is it?
Don't flaunt your fortune, mister.
It's very dangerous. You might get robbed.
Here you go. Don't lose it again.
Be careful.
That's a lot of money.
Could it be ransom money
for some kidnappers?
-I think so.
-Could this be a movie shoot?
Don't take any.
There must be police somewhere. Let's go!
It must be some candid camera TV show.
It's so embarrassing to be seen! Run!
Who says men are greedy?
No one picked up any of the money I threw!
Do you want to make a donation?
CHAPTER FOUR, GREEDY VERSUS DEATH
IS THERE KARMA?
Will ten lorries each of gold and silver
be enough?
Shut up!
If the master says it will work,
then it will work!
I hope everything will be fine
after this praying ceremony.
There are RM200,000 worth
of hell notes to be burned.
I'm sure we'll all be fine!
Sorry, ma'am.
I am Cindy. I never went to school.
I am young and ignorant.
Please forgive us
and stop caressing my butt!
Madam Butterfly.
I am Liang Jia Hui,
a vegetarian who never commits any crimes.
Not stopping Run Fa
when he stole your jewelry
is my fault.
I hope you will forgive me.
Madam Butterfly.
I, Zou Run Fa,
brought ten lorries of gold and silver
to beg for your forgiveness.
I hope that you will forgive us.
Also, I hope you would bless me,
so that I can strike the jackpot again!
Then I won't disturb you anymore.
-Thank you!
-Are you nuts?
Why are you still spouting rubbish?
Come on.
Since Dao Mei is paying for the ceremony,
we might as well make full use of it.
As long as we're safe, whatever goes.
There are more than RM200,000 worth
of hell notes here.
Everyone will be fine.
Master, you may begin.
Okay.
God bless.
It won't burn.
Is the dead unwilling to accept them?
Madam Butterfly, we're so sorry.
I beg for your forgiveness
for Run Fa's nonsense.
We are going to burn ten lorries
of gold and silver for you.
Please bless us. Please.
We are sorry.
Do you think us ghosts
would be so forgiving?
But we have already returned
the money to you!
There is a price for being greedy!
I'm so sorry!
Can you please not touch me anymore?
Stupid woman!
How could you be
with this unworthy lousy idiot?
Why don't you come with me?
Hurry!
Hey, what are you doing? Let go!
Let go!
Are you rebelling?
Let go or I'll hit you!
Let go?
I was thinking of chopping your arms off!
Madam Butterfly, I'm sorry.
I won't do it anymore.
If you like my girlfriend's body,
you can have it.
It's free of charge.
Feel free to take it for any usage.
I don't need it anymore!
You heartless rascal!
Rascal!
You like burial items, don't you?
I'll give you all of them!
Burn him to death!
No! I don't want to die!
I'm sorry!
Cindy, I know I'm wrong!
Run Fa, what are you doing?
Where is Madam Butterfly?
Do you want to meet Madam Butterfly?
I'll tell her to come.
No!
Quick, pray.
Hurry!
The hell notes are for burning,
not for decoration.
-Hurry!
-Is it ready?
-Master, you may proceed.
-Okay.
Master.
Can you help me burn this as well?
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Master, please help me burn
this jade pendant as well.
Madam Butterfly, I have returned
everything to you now!
Don't haunt us anymore!
-It's gone!
-What's gone?
Your butterfly markings are gone!
-It's gone!
-Hey, it's gone!
-Everything's fine now!
Thank you!
Bless us.
-Cheers!
We finally escaped from the hauntings!
Here's to our new life.
-Yes!
I'm also back to poverty!
Let's eat.
There's prawn here!
After the ghosts left,
my hair is starting to grow again. Look.
-Cheers!
Come to think of it,
isn't life
very weird?
When I was poor,
I always dreamt of making it rich.
When my pockets were empty,
I felt so pitiful
and sad.
But when I got rich,
I kept worrying every day.
But now, look.
My account is empty.
I'm penniless.
But here we are,
drinking and celebrating!
Don't you think
life is strange?
-Come.
Let's drink.
Let me tell you.
Life is more valuable than money.
Although you are broke,
you managed to keep your life.
It's worth it!
That's why Jia Hui always says…
-If it's yours, it's yours.
-If it's not, it's not!
Come.
The charity show is going to start soon.
What charity?
It's a TV show.
Donators will stand a chance
to win a house worth RM800,000!
-I donated RM5!
-It's finally time for our lucky draw!
-Yes, it's our turn to come up!
-Quick, let's see if I'll win.
I am Jeremy, Guo Liang.
Guo as in rice pot,
Liang as in shining like a shoe.
My name is Wang Fei.
Wang as in queen, and Fei as in fly.
And I already have the winner's name
in my hand!
The winner will win a mansion
worth over RM800,000!
That's right!
So how much did he donate?
He donated a lot of money.
How much is a lot?
He has donated…
one million ringgit!
Do you want to make a donation?
How much should I donate?
Any amount as you wish.
It's up to your sincerity.
You can have all of this.
Donate a million
and get an RM800,000 mansion?
He is such a philanthropist!
Look! This is so lame!
Who would donate a million
to get an RM800,000 house?
Stop teasing. Who is this winner?
Let me bring him onto the show.
In the studio? Then it can't be me!
He did not come to the studio,
but we are here below his block!
That's right, we are getting closer
to the winner's house!
Isn't that our block?
-Tenth floor?
-And there's no lift.
No lift?
Just kidding. Let's go.
We are over-running into the news!
That's right, let's go have a look.
-Let's go!
There can't be such a coincidence.
Don't scare me!
No, I'm not…
Don't tell me
you are that idiot.
They stay here, but they have one million!
Hey, they are really on our floor!
We're almost there!
This is so nervous.
Hopefully, the winner is a hunk!
Give us some hints.
I'll give you a hint. His surname is Lim.
The winner is your neighbor, Mr. Lim!
Congratulations to Mr. Lim Jun Jie!
Hi, ma'am. Is Mr. Lim Jun Jie home?
Yes, I'm Ms. Lim Jun Jie.
It's a woman.
Can't a woman be named Lim Jun Jie?
Of course, you can!
That's a very nice name!
I thought we won!
It would be a disaster
if Dao Mei really won!
That's right. As long as Dao Mei is poor,
everything will be fine!
-Dao Me is safe!
-Everything is fine!
-I didn't win the prize!
-Yes!
-What should we buy?
Beer!
Also roast meat, roast chicken,
and roast duck.
Are you nuts?
We're celebrating, not praying!
-But those are very good!
-Buy them!
What happened?
Dao Mei.
He stopped breathing.
THE LATEST PHILANTHROPIST IS IN TOWN
Besides, I once heard
these vendors on wheelchairs
are often conmen.
-You…
-I'm leaving.
Dao Mei!
On second thought,
you're right.
I should do more charity.
That's right, let's buy them.
Dao Mei!
-Miss, I want to buy lottery tickets.
-Hi, sir.
-How many do you want?
-Ten pieces.
-Sure.
-Here.
Thank you, sir!
The more you gain from the book,
the shorter your life will be.
This is the rule of the book.
One and a half ball.
Manchester United?
It's a sure win!
Two to two and a half ball.
I'm a bluff?
I make you lose money?
It may be your own issue, you know?
Fine, stop disturbing my peace.
This is heavy.
It must be a big catch! Come to me!
What is this?
What? A book?
How am I going to bet in the future?
These are the winners
of this week's matches!
Go bet on them.
It's a sure win!
Really?
A sure win?
I can't believe
Dao Mei actually had insurance.
It's hard to believe that his beneficiary
could get RM10,000,000!
It's RM10,000,000!
I never thought that his beneficiary
would not be me!
Yes, it's Jia Hui. It's the same!
Shit!
Why am I always left out
from the good stuff?
That's enough! Stop cursing.
Me getting the RM10,000,000
is the same as you getting it.
The most important thing is,
how do we spend the money?
Since we're here,
we should get a new place!
Are we here for hot pot?
What are you doing here?
It's always a good time to diet
when you're poor.
It's such a waste
to leave all these fruits here.
A fruit a day keeps the doctors away.
Are you really that poor?
Yes, I am.
Now that I can't see the numbers,
I can't win the jackpot.
When I can't win the jackpot,
I don't have money!
If I eat a piece of bread for every meal,
it can last me until next week!
You must finish this water
made from flower petals.
The four of us?
Not the four of you together.
One must finish a barrel each.
Hang these on your body
and you will be blessed.
Absolutely blessed!
I've bought a lot.
Are you just here to watch?
All of them are very beautiful.
I don't know which one to get.
Can I buy all of them?
If you do more charity,
you will be blessed.
Our temple looks a little old.
If all of you could…
You are bound to be blessed eternally.
I've given you the numbers.
Aren't you going to bet?
Yes, I'm talking to you. Place your bet!
But not from illegal vendors!
Only then will you win!