ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS,
EVENTS, AND OCCUPATIONS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Sang-hee.
Oh Joo-hyung, you're under arrest
for the charges of murdering your wife.
-Let me talk to her for a moment.
-Take your time.
How could you kill your wife?
You do look like a wife-killer, though.
Thank you for your cooperation.
He said he'd get divorced,
so I trusted him.
But this is what happened.
Come with us to
the police station as a witness.
You can testify about what happened.
Later.
I…
I don't think I can do it right now.
I'll take my stuff and leave.
Sure.
SAE-BOM
Hey, Sae-bom.
Where are you?
I'm locked up inside.
Don't fight them trying to get in.
If my mom calls you, tell her I'm okay.
What does that mean?
Where are you locked up at?
I'll be
watching our apartment.
Sae-bom, tell me what's going on.
Damn it.
I was going to tell you later…
I thought I was left alone.
Sae-bom, I have to catch that jerk.
It's okay. No one can get out.
Who is this?
Hi, did you order rice cakes?
Enjoy and order more, okay?
Are you a police officer too?
How did you know?
You saw this.
I'm not someone suspicious.
I'm friends with your neighbor.
So you have two jobs.
But why did you bring a gun?
Someone bad lives here,
so I'm going to arrest him.
People need to see my gun
to know that I'm a police officer.
-Can I see it up close?
-No, it's dangerous.
To be honest, I've never actually used it.
I'm just carrying it around.
Because it looks awesome, doesn't it?
I'm home.
Are you dead?
You don't even look at me when I'm back.
Hey, here's your hamburger.
And you get up right away because of food!
Thanks.
You said it's a hamburger.
It's still bread. What's the problem?
If you don't want it, then forget it.
Honey, I'm not saying that
I don't want it…
Did it get chapped again?
No.
My goodness.
Apply something on it! You're old now!
No, it didn't get chapped. This is…
I sprained it a bit when I fell yesterday.
Don't overreact.
Honey, aren't you even curious
about what happened? I got hurt.
Did something happen?
Yes.
Yesterday, on the sixth floor…
Mom, why didn't you wake me up?
I have a meeting!
Hey, how are we supposed
to know about your appointments?
We're not telepathic!
Dong-hyun, want this sandwich?
You two eat it and live a happy life.
Hey, take this…
That rude brat!
Good grief.
I MADE MONEY THROUGH YOUTUBE!
What in the world…
I got more than 1,000 subscribers.
At this rate, we can surely make a profit!
No, you just need to pay the initial cost!
Can't you trust me?
All right.
I'll be there soon. All right.
Why can't I go out? Hey, mister!
What the heck?
I can't believe this.
Can't you hear me?
What's going on?
I don't have time for this!
-Even the smallest room is pretty big.
-It is.
SY HOME CLEANING
Nice weather.
You can't smoke indoors.
This is an electronic cigarette.
Happy now? Are you satisfied?
Jeez…
Honey, can't we fire him?
He's weird.
Just let him be.
He doesn't mind getting paid
lower than the minimum wage.
His name is weird too.
Andrew?
Is that a fake name or what?
Seriously.
That's been going on since this morning.
Is there a fire?
If it was a fire,
we would have known already.
I've been in a fire before.
You don’t know unless you smell it.
Your house caught on fire?
Yes.
I heard the sirens outside,
and the fire trucks
were lined up on the road.
I opened the window
and looked around to see where it was,
and someone from the apartment
across the street yelled at me.
-What did they say?
-"Young lady, come out!"
"Your apartment is on fire!"
The top floor of
my apartment building was on fire.
It's clearly visible from the outside,
but you don't know when you're inside.
No way.
Hello, this is Lawyer Kook Hae-seong.
Hi, I'm your next-door neighbor. Unit 601.
I need urgent legal consulting…
Yes, hi.
You must be worried
because of your wife, right?
I'm home now. Are you home?
Would you like me to go to your house?
No, I'm outside right now.
I see. Okay.
Then please tell me. What's going on?
The police arrested me without a warrant,
but an arrest without
a warrant is illegal, right?
What are you being charged with?
Murder.
You evaded arrest and escaped, right?
Help me, please!
I live in Building 101.
I'm a doctor! A specialist!
We're from the police.
You can just keep going.
Young lady. Or old lady?
Anyway, he's your husband?
I'm going to report you
for human rights violations.
What are you waiting for?
Hit him where it won't show.
Just come with me.
And put your shoes on.
They're locking us up?
-I can't believe it…
-What are they doing?
-Why did they set those up?
-What's going on?
-This is so scary.
-They're so big.
This is nonsense.
I'm so disappointed in you.
Hey, I'm your only older brother,
and you can't even give me 150 million?
I have no money.
You do have money.
You know what the price for this place is.
-You won the lottery.
-Are they doing construction work outside?
Or how about we live together?
It would be great for my kids
to study in a house like this.
You have a lot of rooms.
Give one each to my kids.
And honestly, you get lonely
when you live alone.
Have you heard of lonely death?
Yes.
That's why I read newspapers.
So people can find out when I die.
To be honest, you've been living here
with Father's deposit.
And thanks to that, you got the house.
But you inherited the fortune,
in cash and lands!
But I got them ten years ago.
-Ever heard of inflation?
-Be quiet.
Greetings, all residents of Building 101.
I am the building representative.
I'm sure you are confused
because of all the noise.
The entire apartment complex
is now separated from the outside.
-What?
-And the government
has something to tell us
about Mad Human Disease.
A resident meeting will take place
at the basement gym at five.
With the government admitting the
existence of Mad Human Disease,
three nursing homes,
two homeless facilities,
and one apartment complex in Seyang
have been put into cohort isolation
due to Mad Human Disease.
Hey, was it like that when you came in?
Yes.
I thought they were
just doing construction work.
The government revealed
that it was an inevitable action
to prevent additional infections,
and stated that they will prevent
the spreading of infection
through accurate diagnostic tests
and establishing countermeasures.
I'm sure we can get out, though.
Nice place.
-My mom is inside.
-Let me go in just for a moment.
-No.
-My kid is all alone.
Your mom must be worried too.
But she'll call you soon, so…
-Mom?
-Seo-yoon, are you okay?
-Did anything happen to you?
-No. I'm at our neighbor's.
I'm in front of the apartments.
I'll go inside somehow,
so just hang in there.
They're not letting anyone out,
but letting people in won't be a problem.
Okay.
Can I speak to that lady
if she's with you?
Hello?
I'm so glad we have you.
Thank you so much.
I'll be heading inside soon.
Please take care of Seo-yoon
for a little while longer.
Don't worry.
I love hanging out with Seo-yoon too.
Seo-yoon…
has a heart problem.
She has mitral regurgitation.
Blood wells up inside her heart.
She must never do vigorous exercise,
and she must never bleed.
Last time, she injured her fingernail
and she was hospitalized
and got an antibiotics injection.
I will watch over her.
I couldn't stay with her
just because of some money…
I got a call earlier,
but I couldn't answer.
I will try and find out
if there's a way to let Seo-yoon out.
Thank you so much.
It's not your fault.
Don't worry, I'll take good care of her.
Okay.
Mom, can I eat the rice cakes?
MS. KIM BOK-NAM
Hi, Mom.
You said you're okay. What's going on?
That's your apartment
getting locked down, right?
It's a preemptive action
to control the infections. Don’t worry.
They say many people got infected,
so just stay home.
Don't go poking around.
I want to stay put, but…
someone has to do something.
-What?
-I'm busy. I'll call you later.
LIEUTENANT COLONEL HAN TAE-SEOK
Lieutenant Colonel?
We need to meet.
What do you mean, when?
As soon as possible.
You knew your wife
was taking drugs, right?
Did you take that drug too?
Did Min-ji become like that
because of drugs?
You can't run away now anyway,
so just stay here quietly.
If you want to consult a lawyer,
then do so.
What about me?
I'm not even a resident here.
No one can go out, and no one can come in.
You're a police officer.
Can't you do something?
I can't get out, either.
Anyway, there's a resident meeting.
Come with us.
No.
I'm sure everyone knows
what happened here.
What would the others think about me?
Then would you like
to stay here with Mr. Oh?
Hang on.
What now? What?
I'm worried about Ms. Woo, that's why.
I'll uncuff this later, so get some sleep.
Why would you do this?
Why are you doing this to me?
Then what about the bathroom?
Should I just pee in the room?
Make sure you don't spill.
Damn it.
You're not going?
I want to go too, but…
you know how sensitive I am.
If I go to a crowded place
with Mad Human Disease going around,
I can't use 100% of my abilities.
Then what about me?
You think I'm not scared?
That's why I only trust you.
Clients will line up on days like this.
This lockdown has
a high possibility of legal issues.
Okay. I'll go and promote you.
-So-yoon.
-Yes?
You can do it!
Hi.
I heard you arrested the man next door.
Where is he now?
He's at home.
Because of the lockdown.
I cuffed him, so tell him to go
and consult him if he wants to.
Is there evidence for murder?
You should ask Mr. Oh about that yourself.
But if I were you two,
I wouldn't defend him.
Sang-hee.
Sang-hee. You're out there, right?
We need to talk!
We're soulmates! Come on!
No.
Do you think you can be happy on your own?
Everyone knows we had an affair,
and you're locked up in here.
You have no money,
and you'll get fired from the clinic.
I am the only one
who understands you, Sang-hee.
You know me, right?
Sang-hee, I'll give you money. Okay?
Sang-hee.
How much are you going to give me?
Hi, I'm the wife
of Lawyer Kook Hae-seong, Unit 602.
If you have legal problems,
please call this number.
He said he doesn't know
anything about drugs.
He got all upset,
saying that he doesn't use steroids.
Is the meeting just for our building?
Just the units that end with 1 and 2.
Looks like we're meeting separately.
Dear residents of Seyang Forest Le Ciel.
Due to the dangers of
additional infections in the complex,
the entire complex will be
in cohort isolation for one week.
Hey, young lady!
I don’t even live here!
Am I locked up too?
We will compensate for all damages caused
by the lockdown
until we can manage all the infected.
I'm not talking about that…
We will make sure
you won't suffer any inconvenience,
so please wait until then.
And if you need anything else,
discuss it among the residents
and let us know.
That will be all.
-No, it can't end like this!
-Hey, wait!
Young lady! Wait!
I'm sure all of you are shocked,
but I believe that we,
as the residents of Seyang Forest Le Ciel,
can remain calm and overcome this crisis.
It's not about remaining calm…
I can't hear you
if you all talk at the same time.
I will give you a chance to speak in turn.
Is it because of someone
getting infected yesterday?
Then they should separate those
who were in contact!
I've never even seen that person!
The lady from Unit 302 bumped
into the lady from Unit 601 and fell.
Didn't you hear about it?
Really?
It seems your family hasn't had
any proper conversations.
By the way…
If it's contagious,
then we shouldn't gather like this, right?
You watched the announcement.
It doesn't spread through the air,
so don't worry.
How can we believe that?
But what happens
if someone's infected here,
and tries to bite us?
With all of us gathered up in this
small place, we will all bite and kill
-and eat each other…
-Oh, my head.
Honestly, I don't think there are
any more infected in our building.
Everyone's sophisticated.
And thankfully, we have a detective here.
Detective.
Don't look at me, I'm suffocating. You go.
There are symptoms
that show before the disease occurs.
The infected feel extreme thirst,
and the pupils get smaller,
-making the eyes look white.
-What?
And they also show compulsive behaviors
like hitting the wall
when they're alone in an empty space.
Please meet others
in a group of two or more
and try to keep the doors open.
If you see suspicious behavior,
ask for help right away.
I live alone. How can I stay in groups?
-Hold on.
-It's one week.
You just need to endure this for one week.
The kids were at school,
and you stopped
the school buses from coming in.
You wanted a lockdown without kids, right?
It looks better that way.
There's a kid who didn't go to school.
Let her out.
You can do that at least, right?
Park Seo-yoon.
We're testing her parents.
They have a high risk of infection.
Are you sure?
I'm sure they took the drugs to stay awake
because delivery work is tough.
They're telling their daughter
that they love her and miss her, right?
It's no use.
You never know how people can change
in times of crisis.
Lieutenant Colonel.
You can talk about
your pessimistic views to someone else.
So what?
I'm saying it's better for Seo-yoon
to be here with a good guardian.
We don't know…
what will happen outside.
Mr. Police Officer.
I think I'll be able
to jump over the walls outside.
Will I get punished if I jump over it?
Well, the reporters
would love seeing that at least.
If you're lucky, you might end up
on the evening news.
-I see.
-What about food?
Do we eat on our own?
We'll give you boxed lunches,
starting tomorrow.
Do you have enough food for dinner?
But where are
the Management Office people?
We got isolated at 9:30 a.m.,
but no one came to work by then.
And the person on night duty
is at the other meeting.
Absolutely ridiculous.
What?
Then are the other buildings
having a meeting without us?
The first infected came from our building,
so they're scared.
They are abandoning
their responsibilities.
Then we have no one
from the Management Office here?
No, we don't.
Something unfathomable has happened.
But she's right there.
I was living in the US with my husband
but returned because I fell in love with
the so-called K-Quarantine.
Excuse me, building representative.
We do have someone from
the Management Office, outside.
Our apartment complex
teems with corruption.
They secretly fixed the elevators
because they didn't pass the safety test.
And they collect recyclables
only once a week,
and they're wasting money to fix
the roadside trees in the complex.
If you trust and follow me,
I will become the resident representative
and solve all these unreasonable issues
in the apartments.
Then let the public rental floors
use the gym too.
My husband graduated from
the College of Theology in Kentucky.
-But I said…
-I know some of you are worried
about worships
because the apartments are in quarantine.
Hallelujah!
-God is always with you.
-Amen.
Believers, please come to me.
If you're having difficulties calculating
your losses due to the lockdown
or are in need of legal consulting,
please let me know.
We will provide
high quality legal consulting service.
Please come to Unit 602.
Hey.
Hurry up.
I hate this.
I heard you're also
something like a police officer.
You should be cooperating
with maintaining order in the apartments.
I'm in a completely different field.
I only learned
how to suppress terrorist attacks.
If you need cooperation, talk to me.
Will I get a raise if I do this?
I don't think so.
But I'm sure it will help
with my promotion.
Hey, I didn't know until I came here.
I want to go home
and deliver rice cakes too.
What is this about?
You should tell me so I can help.
-Why are you locking the door…
-Let us ask you something.
Are you close to him?
Joo-heon?
No, I work every other day,
so I didn't even see him much.
He stopped coming to work a few days ago,
so I've been filling in for him.
You're drinking too much water.
Do you keep feeling thirsty?
I always drink a lot of water.
Can you open this for us?
I'm from the SOU.
Okay.
Look all you want.
Your co-worker sold drugs here.
And the government thinks
those drugs cause Mad Human Disease.
You know the symptoms, right?
Extreme thirst.
Hallucinations.
Be honest. Did you take those drugs?
No, I only took supplements.
But you know who took them, right?
If you don't tell us now,
you could be charged with selling drugs.
I really don't know.
Hiding it won't solve anything.
This entire complex
is on lockdown because of you,
you know that?
I told you, it wasn't me!
You two keep talking
as if I'm the bad guy.
But I seriously did not take those drugs.
We're behind on
our cleaning schedule this week.
Isn't there a way to solve this?
SY HOME CLEANING
Sir, I came in here
and suddenly got locked in too.
They said they'll compensate
for financial losses, so let's be patient.
Do you two have a place
to sleep, at least?
No, we don't.
I have a kid at home too.
-How old is your kid?
-A sophomore in high school.
A sophomore in high school…
I will find out and see if you can sleep
at one of the houses you clean.
By the way, is he from your company?
He's our employee, but…
What's your name?
I'm Andrew.
What?
Excuse me.
He's a bit dumb, but he's nice.
He has a deep scar on his face
from an injury when he was little.
So he couldn't go outside
and only stayed at home.
But no one thinks it's weird
to wear a mask these days,
so he mustered up the courage
to start working.
I see.
Do you all have your IDs with you?
-Yes.
-Can you please give them to me?
They said they need
a list of those who are inside.
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD: AHN KOOK-JIN
I erased it.
Ahn Kook-jin.
Why did you say your name was Andrew?
Because I wish I could have superpowers.
There was a TV show about it.
Who were you calling,
and why did you hang up so quickly?
I just called my friend.
Shall we tie him up?
We don't know yet.
We won’t tie you up,
so just stay here, okay?
Mr. Kim, if we catch you outside,
then we really will
consider you as an infected.
As for water…
Just hang on until morning.
DO NOT ENTER
RISK OF INFECTION!
You'll get thirsty if you stay up,
so put the phone down and go to bed.
UNIT 601
UNIT 1202
UNIT 602
It's a relief that
the public rental residents
weren't allowed to use the gym.
There's a fewer number of
possibly infected people.
You truly are…
a detective.
Of course.
I did go to the gym a few times,
but besides that, I was always home.
I won't leave my house
until the lockdown is over,
so don't mind me.
It's not about that.
The people downstairs
need something, that's why.
Blankets.
You have military blankets, don't you?
I can bring you the T-shirt tomorrow.
Thank you.
ARTICLE 1003
ORDER OF INHERITANCE OF SPOUSE
You remember
that I live downstairs, right?
If you make noises on purpose,
I'm coming for you.
What are you going to do, then?
Mister.
Even if you die on the run,
no one would say anything.
Lots of people would talk.
This is illegal confinement.
Well, more than that,
your name wasn't on the gym register.
Don't you exercise regularly?
I breathe. And I play golf sometimes.
My wife went to the gym.
Why?
Did Mad Human Disease spread from the gym?
Stop trying to play tricks
and just repent your murder
if you have time for that.
If you're a human being, at least.
Ms. Woo, we prepared
a change of clothes for you
and a place to sleep on the fifth floor,
so come with me.
I just want to stay here.
I got angry and gave false testimony.
To be honest,
I didn’t see or hear anything that day.
I'm sorry, Detective.
Sang-hee got tricked by you
and thought that I really did something.
I explained to her that
Min-ji's death was an accident.
LIEUTENANT COLONEL HAN TAE-SEOK
What is it?
Unit 302 is livestreaming
about what's happening in the apartment.
Stop him immediately.
If not, we will cut off the Internet
and all TV signals.
Hey, get up for a minute.
Why?
Did you…
meet someone infected yesterday?
Did you figure that out now?
-Did you get scratched?
-No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
My goodness.
Stop it!
I said I didn't!
Pretending to be concerned
when you never bothered before.
You were lying down for this?
It's not even serious.
Just drink some soju.
If you drink, the pain will go away.
Gosh.
What is it?
Is your son home?
I think he went outside earlier.
Do you know where he went to?
I'm sure he's in the complex.
Anyway, he's not here.
I know where he is.
I told you, I won't be talking
about stocks today.
Today's contents are real, no fabrication.
Giro, good to see you.
It's Giro, our biggest sponsor.
Good to see you!
All right, everyone.
Can you guess where this is?
This is where
the first infected person was found.
The family is still living here,
so I'm going to meet and talk to them.
Shall I ring the doorbell?
Ring it? Or not?
Shall I ring it, or not?
JUST RING IT ALREADY
Ring it or not?
-Oh, my gosh…
-Shall I punch him? Or not?
Punch him? Or not?
I'm getting lots! Lots!
We're turning this off.
Go to bed, everyone.
What the heck? How do I turn this off?
-Streaming off!
-What is this?
Thank you.
Is this something you should thank us for?
-I got 500,000 won!
-This is driving me nuts…
-Damn it!
-Why did you do that?
Mister, come here.
Today's been such a long day.
Right.
What about the clinic consultant upstairs?
She got coaxed by Oh Joo-hyung.
She said she'll just stay there.
Should we try persuading her again?
No, she's an adult.
She can make her own decisions.
I'm sure Oh Joo-hyung
won't cause any more trouble.
Let's just check on them
from time to time.
-I'm so tired.
-All right, then.
About our beds…
Where should we…
Where should I sleep?
Hey, Yi-hyun. Smile.
All right. One, two.
What are you doing?
My wife told me to send her a picture.
She thinks I went fishing.
Why won't she believe me?
I can't believe it, either.
Can't believe what?
That I'm here with you right now.
Things seemed so nice today…
There you go.
Here.
You just need to wait for a few more days,
so think of it as staying
at a vacation house, okay?
Okay.
Are you praying?
I changed my prayer today.
I prayed that the lockdown
would be over when I wake up tomorrow.
Right. I'll pray for that too.
-Good night.
-Okay.
You have a good night too.
Let's have a good night.
Yi-hyun.
What?
I have a bad back.
-All of a sudden?
-Yes.
Jeez. You can sleep on the sofa.
Thanks.
-This is mine, so take that one.
-Okay, thanks.
I got treated by a bad acupuncturist.
I'M SORRY I KEEP CALLING YOU
WHEN YOU MUST BE WORRIED TOO
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR MARRIAGE
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE, SO DON'T WORRY
STAY HEALTHY
DON'T BECOME LIKE ME, AND BE HAPPY!
YOU SHOULD BE HAPPY TOO, MOM
COUNT ON US FOR
A CURE FOR VIRAL PNEUMONIA
THE DARK SIDE OF ATUM THERAPEUTICS,
TEAM LEADER HAN TAE-SEOK ASSAULTS CEO
Jung-kook.
I know you’re not asleep.
-What?
-About Han Tae-seok's assault…
What happened to the CEO of that company?
What are you talking about?
If it was an assault,
that means he's not dead.
So I'm wondering
what happened to him after that.
DOMESTIC AND FOREIGN MARKET TRENDS
You look well, Mr. Choi.
I heard you revealed Mad Human Disease
and locked the apartments down.
It's chaos worldwide.
The article will be released tomorrow
and the borders will be closed.
I recommended you to the higher-ups
because you said
you could take care of it quietly.
I'm sure they'll be disappointed.
Someone was releasing Next
into the market.
That's why I failed.
Who?
You.
You took out all of the stock
left in the storage, didn't you?
I didn't buy those.
Someone told me where the storage was
and told me to take them all.
Why would I do that?
Because the more infected there are,
the faster the cure can be developed.
Aren't you the type
who would rather see the world end
than face your death?
Tae-seok.
Your wife's life also depends on this.
And the baby is still in her womb, right?
Two tenacious lives.
Did you know that
your wife's blood tasted the best?
That thirst…
it's hard to hold it in, isn't it?
Lieutenant Colonel.
It's okay.
That old man did release it.
I'll get the numbers of his entourages.
Track them down.
We must block
all possible routes of infection.
Is it okay to leave him like that?
Do you have an alternative?
We should quarantine him too.
His status is way too high for that.
Once the cure is developed,
he'll get the shot first.
Even if he gets cured,
he might still bite people.
Because he's tasted blood
and learned that he can get away with it.
-Then we should…
-The most important thing is the cure.
Whether or not he survives after that…
is a whole different matter.
It's still the same.
This morning, the government announced
that they put two more nursing homes
into cohort isolation.
Places in cohort isolation include
one apartment complex,
three nursing homes,
and two homeless shelters,
making it a total of eight
in only two days.
There are also suspicions
of Mad Human Disease
spreading overseas as well.
Russia closed its borders
due to infectious disease,
and its customs…
Did you sleep well?
Of course.
Did you sleep well too, Mister?
Yes.
Let's go.
-Go where?
-To get boxed lunches!
Right.
Hi.
-You're up, Seo-yoon.
-Hi.
-Did you have a good sleep?
-Yes.
Sae-bom, you look really happy today.
Yi-hyun was tossing
and turning all night long.
People are happy when
they are looking forward to something.
What do you mean?
Aren't you curious
what kind of food they'll give us?
Right.
Why?
I bought this apartment with my money!
Why can't I go out?
Open it!
Sir, you're a public rental resident.
You got in here with the taxes I paid.
I'm still a resident here!
Damn it!
They're from the Management Office
and the other buildings.
What's going on?
We can't go outside anymore.
The other buildings voted for this.
Lock it up.
What do you think you're doing?
This is all because
there was someone infected here!
I heard you also locked up
someone infected in the gym!
How do you know about that?
We can see it from the Management Office.
So you've been spying on our building?
For the sake of
this entire apartment complex,
the residents of this building…
should stay home for a week!
And our lunches?
We'll bring the necessities for you.
It's hard for all of us. Don't do this.
It's not like you can get infected
through airborne transmission.
This building has
the most public rentals, right?
Yes.
What does that have to do with this?
It means it's unfair for us!
If more people get infected
and the apartment price drops,
-it'll only damage us!
-That's right!
You can just live here for ten years
and buy it for a low price!
Are you doing this on purpose?
Mr. Kim, please help.
I can't even persuade my wife.
They told us not to go outside,
so let's not go outside.
Not that.
-Let me borrow your gun.
-Hey!
Want me to break out,
or will you just open it?
The key.
Seo-yoon, you must never learn
to do things like that.
She's so awesome.
Every day I'm losing my love for humanity.
We just need to hold on for six more days.
How is time flowing slower
than during our drills?
You people are so heartless.
We made these boxed lunches
with extra care, though.
With lots of protein.
What about the other buildings?
Is this it?
They said they'll take theirs
after your building residents are gone.
Sometimes they're brave,
and sometimes they're cowardly.
Human beings are just so puzzling.
Did you bring enough?
We'll take these and go inside first.
Go inside and wait.
-Okay.
-Seo-yoon, let's go.
Do you need anything else?
Then…
A T-shirt. Large-sized, for men.
Something that looks extremely rare.
With the logo of a special unit…
You don't have an SOU T-shirt, do you?
Are you the only one working here?
Yes, the owner and his wife
went out to get things, so…
Not much is left.
The other buildings bought
everything last night.
A few from Building 101 bought stuff too.
You're pretty calm
considering the situation.
I'm getting three times my original wage.
If I work for 12 hours a day
and get paid for working on holidays,
it'll be a huge amount.
Aren't you scared to be alone here?
I'm sure they'd go mad in their homes,
not at a supermarket.
When we run out of stock,
I'll lock the door.
No parcel deliveries?
I was supposed to get something today.
Bye.
I'm vegetarian.
Isn't there a vegetarian option?
-Vegetarian?
-Yes.
Just take it and shove it in your mouth.
ARMED FORCES MEDICAL COMMAND
It's genuine.
I know someone there.
And I'll get you the SOU T-shirt
when the lockdown ends.
-I like it.
-Right?
Have you been on the rooftop?
-It's nice to be out here, right?
-Yes.
It's nice to be in an open space.
It feels like we're on a picnic.
Right.
Let's stay like this for a while.
-Let's eat.
Help yourself, Seo-yoon.
This is actually pretty good.
-It's good.
-Yes.
Have some more of these.
Thanks.
-Jung-kook, have some dumplings.
-Thanks.
Eat up, Seo-yoon.
What?
We have three boxed lunches left.
Are you sure you passed them
out to everyone?
Yes, even the cleaning lady took hers.
Right.
The gym.
Mr. Kim, we're sorry.
You should've called
and told us you're hungry…
That punk must have run away.
Hello?
The guy in the gym disappeared.
Make an announcement
and tell everyone to go home.
I was just about to tell you this.
The Management Office
won't answer the phone.
They must be upset
about what happened earlier.
They're trying to have
a meeting without us again.
Okay, I'll call them then.
What? Hello?
Does this jerk think he's above me?
That worthless cop…
EMERGENCY CONTACT NETWORK
A SHELTER IN THE MIDDLE OF A BUSY CITY
WELCOME, NEW RESIDENTS
Hey, where are you going?
They're not answering. What should we do?
Where are you going?
I'm sure he's hiding here somewhere.
Wrong card.
Let's go inside.
Is he here?
No, he isn't.
What is that?
Hey!
It's blood.
-Let's go.
-Let me see what's going on first.
Sae-bom!
I don't want to get scared
without knowing what’s going on.
Hey Mister, come out!
-Shouldn't we take him?
-Come out if you don't want to die!
Damn it.
Why isn't this working?
Please try again.
Thank you.
What?
What's wrong?
I…
I really just went to my car for a moment.
I didn't drink water.
Then why were you running?
I ran because you two ran.
Let me go, please!
Come on.
Can you see them?
See what? Is something out there?
This is crazy…
Let's go up.
Help!
Help me, please!
Ma'am!
Are you okay?
I'm fine but the couple from that house…
Mom, I'm doing fine.
MOM, I'M DOING FINE
MOM: SEO-YOON, I LOVE YOU…
Hey!
This is our chance.
Yes.
I'm sure Hyun-kyung
is feeling troubled too.
Let's stay strong, okay?
Hey, we have to find a house
within two months!
Where will you live with our kids, then?
A tiny studio?
Ma'am, you shouldn't go outside.
Stay still. If you run away again…
What are you doing?
-Is something going on?
-Be quiet.
LIEUTENANT COLONEL HAN TAE-SEOK
Ms. Yoon, are you all right?
Now do you see
why a lockdown is necessary?
Who's that?
The other buildings are all done for.
I know.
If it's dangerous,
you shouldn't hesitate either.
Don't open the door.
But they all got infected already?
That makes no sense!
What if this doesn't end
even after one week?
We have to have as much food as possible.
Instant noodles.
We just need to silence
the couple downstairs.
Are you thirsty?
We should not let them pity the infected.
We must make them fear them.
Open the door!
If you're a human being,
you should have responsibility
at the very least.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee