Minimalism is like...
a Buddhist philosophy.
Okay.
It's about letting go.
I see.
When I was working in Sweden,
I really liked this style.
When I moved back,
I wanted to apply it to this place.
What was this place before?
-A home.
-I see.
My mom and brother are living upstairs.
-I turned downstairs into an office.
-I see.
Yes.
What did you do with your stuff?
I threw them away.
-Everything?
-Yes.
Don't you feel attached to them?
Personally, I feel that things
we no longer use are unnecessary.
So we should throw them away.
As for things I have use for
and are in good condition,
I think...
they will be here.
They're not going anywhere.
I see.
Then...
Can you give us some tips
on how to get rid of things?
Excuse me.
Come on, you cheap ass.
Are you for real?
I only need three pages.
Will they sell me three pages?
This isn't a damn library.
Don't be stingy.
I'm designing a minimalist house.
Why should I buy books on minimalism?
It's the era of cloud storage.
You don't need to spend minimally
on a minimalist house.
Let's go.
Hey, won't it be easier to rent
an office space?
Do you have the money?
This is actually a nice area.
You can take the Skytrain
when you're in a rush.
That's true.
If clients come here for meetings,
there are parking spaces in the daytime.
It's quite spacious.
-They can park in the alley.
-I see.
We're here. This is my home.
I think it can be turned into an office.
-Definitely.
-For sure.
Let's have a look.
I'll walk you through.
Close the door.
My house used to be
an instrument repair shop.
My dad also ran a music school.
Mom, my friend's here.
Mom.
Hello.
Can you turn it down?
I need to talk business.
Okay.
I think I'll get rid
of everything downstairs
and turn it into the main office.
Take a look.
My house gets lots of sunlight,
but it's blocked by all these walls.
There is too much wood.
I want to make it more minimalistic.
Why do you keep this bumper?
Go ask my mom.
Stop taking photos.
I think we have to tear down some walls.
This is Jay, my brother.
-This is Pink.
-Hi.
Hi.
Right.
I will turn this room
into your home studio.
What studio?
Your own home studio, you know?
My home studio?
Does your mom sing one song all day?
You need to put in
lots of soundproofing for me.
You want a minimalist home,
but this clutter in this place
is the fucking opposite.
Can you do it?
I can fix up the house.
What I can't do for you
is to talk to your family.
-Your brother doesn't even know...
-I know.
-his room will be gone.
Have you told your mom?
I will.
You'd better, Jean.
I've seen this before.
You'll get a broken home
before you get a new house.
You'll be wiping out your whole history.
You want a minimalist Stockholm house.
Have you asked your family here?
I wouldn't have come back
if I had a choice.
I don't care. Just be nice.
From the timeline you sent me,
you need to send me references and
clear everything out before New Year's.
We can start working after the holidays.
Okay.
Minimalism is like a Buddhist philosophy.
It's about letting go.
Are you nuts? You want an empty house?
Things will be more organized.
Let's start over.
Take this room, for example.
It's so cluttered with stuff, right?
We'll clear out what we don't need
and we'll have more space.
Our lives will be greatly improved.
And when people come in,
-they will see...
-Where will the living room be?
It will be on the second floor.
You can sing your heart out all day.
-I'll turn it into a karaoke room.
-Not the second floor. No.
-Why not?
-I don't want the second floor.
The first floor will be my office.
You have to move.
I don't want to.
-It's so messy here.
-No.
-I'm always here.
-We'll all move.
You will have your own room.
Just tell me what you want.
-You name it.
-You go. I won't.
Are you going to sleep on the chair?
You can't. It's weird.
How is that weird?
I always sleep here.
-You can't.
-Why not?
I've done it for years.
Doesn't it give you a backache?
You can't sleep here.
It's because of my shoes.
What does that have to do with it?
You're not listening to me.
Do what you want,
but the living room must stay.
It can't. It's not minimalistic.
Minimal what? This is my house.
Jean, don't do it.
-What?
-It's too much of a hassle.
Jay, we've lived here since we were ten.
We're almost 30.
Everything is too small now.
What about your online clothing shop?
Don't you want storage space
for your clothes?
Damn.
It feels so cramped here
now that you said it.
I felt fine before.
Well, take a look around.
This belongs to the previous generation.
Everything is out of date.
Why are old people afraid of change?
I don't get it.
This is our time.
Yes, you have a point.
The floor plan is set.
We can't change anything.
We're so used to it
that we don't think about it.
That's what I'm saying.
This is our time.
It's our generation's time.
HOW TO DUMP
STEP 1
SET YOUR GOALS AND FIND INSPIRATIONS
Your office is amazing.
Thank you.
If you have questions, feel free to ask.
Sure. I'm a fan of your work.
Thank you so much.
Yes, I can.
Actually, it's being built right now.
I hope it will be finished by next month.
I guess it will have to be.
Well...
I hope we'll get to work together.
Excuse me.
Are there more garbage bags?
There's no more on the shelf.
We're out if the shelf's empty.
Isn't this enough?
The world is campaigning against plastic.
Trust me. It's worth it.
What are you getting?
Cleaning supplies.
What's that book?
I don't know.
It's a Japanese book. It's funny.
She says tidying up the house once
will set you free.
It's a best seller. It might help.
Just download a PDF file.
Books take up space.
No. PDF files hurt my eyes.
Let's go.
All right.
I've been waiting to do this.
HOW TO DUMP
STEP 2
DON'T REMINISCE THE PAST
Publishing is dead.
It's the era of Apple Music and Spotify.
God! This was before cell phones.
A VHS tape rewinder.
I haven't heard that word in ages.
Do you want this pencil case?
Toss it.
Shit. Good old days.
Shit. Did you steal this from a temple?
You did. Don't blame it on me, Jean.
The Shang Dynasty invented it.
You're throwing things away mindlessly.
Don't throw away important documents.
THAI-CHINESE DICTIONARY
THAI FOR BEGINNERS
REPORT CARD
THOUGH JEAN IS A STUBBORN KID AT HOME,
SHE'S KIND AND SHE LOVES TREES.
SECOND SEMESTER, JEAN READS MORE
ERIC LIU - PARENT
Why are you tossing stuff so fast?
Did you throw away your report card?
That's sad.
That's the use of garbage bags.
Think about it.
Do you remember
what you've thrown into the bags?
Garbage bags are like black holes.
When you throw things in, they're gone.
Out of sight, out of mind.
It's so damn easy.
It's a done deal.
How will you fit the piano in the bag?
Are you really okay
with me throwing it away?
Toss it out. It takes up space.
It doesn't.
It does, Mom.
No one plays it anymore. Do you?
I do. Okay?
It's not yours.
Are we clear?
Don't meddle with other people's things.
Dad isn't here anymore. It isn't anyone's.
Take it easy, Jean.
We can clean up our rooms first.
It's easy to throw away everyday stuff.
Personal items are hard.
I'll help.
You're all so emotional.
What are you watching?
It's the lady who wrote about tidying up.
I want to see what she looks like.
She's a devil in angel's clothing.
Isn't she right though?
It's good you're watching it.
I don't know.
Everything I touch sparks joy.
I tried.
Do you want my help?
I'll snap my fingers
and everything will disappear.
No, thanks. Are you Thanos?
Look at this.
I can't throw out any of these.
These souvenirs are so tacky
and so touristy,
but it's the thought that counts.
Just toss them out.
Being emotional only brings trouble.
CONGRATS ON YOUR GRADUATION.
TAKE GOOD CARE OF IT. - CHERRIE
HOW TO DUMP
STEP 3
DON'T FEEL TOO MUCH
CONGRATS ON YOUR GRADUATION.
TAKE GOOD CARE OF IT. - CHERRIE
Should I throw out the computer boxes
in your office?
Yes.
BLANK ALBUMS - TRASH
Hey, is this yours?
Shit.
Did you really throw everything out?
Are you that clean-freak lady's fan?
It's a lifelong collection from the past.
It's full of germs.
This isn't all. There's more.
Look.
Damn, that's scary.
Here, I brought you more references.
I marked the ones I think you would like.
Thanks a lot.
What clutter.
You're right.
Wow. Are you throwing all this away?
They're still in good condition.
Look. This is a cute vase.
Why don't you donate it
or sell it as second-hand?
Turn your past into money.
No. I'm tired.
If I throw it out today,
it will be gone today.
It's such a waste.
Pink.
Yes?
Can you get me more references?
These are almost right.
But I once saw a reference
that's exactly what I wanted.
I can't remember where I saw it.
Are you tossing this out too?
No one uses CDs anymore.
Keep it if you want. It's useless.
What?
FOR JEAN, HAPPY BIRTHDAY
YOU WANTED IT, SO I GOT IT FOR YOU - PINK
Doesn't my gift spark joy anymore?
Wait. Hold on.
The thing is, you see
how cluttered my house is.
I can't keep more stuff.
I have to get rid of them.
It's impossible to keep everything
people give you.
You have to throw things away
eventually, Pink.
You have a point there.
You're absolutely right.
It's my fault. I'm being too emotional.
Do you understand what I said?
What's with you?
If you don't want it anymore,
and you're brave enough
to return it to me,
I might just feel sad.
I wouldn't be mad.
Okay. How about this?
If one day you have to throw stuff out
and you find something from me,
you can toss it out. I won't be mad.
You're not mad because you don't care.
If you don't want this CD, I'll take it.
I'll take it back.
Pink.
Hello, Pink.
Are you free tomorrow?
Do you want to grab some food?
Do you realize you've never changed?
You pretend like nothing has happened.
Have you ever asked anyone
if they can let go like you?
What do you want me to do?
You know what you have to say,
but you won't say it.
Learn to have compassion, will you?
Say it now, asshole!
Okay. I'm sorry.
Good. That's all.
Some things won't go away just because
you pretend to forget all about it.
It has to come from both sides
for it to be over.
HOW TO DUMP
STEP 4
DON'T WAVER. BE HEARTLESS.
Think about what I said.
Bye.
Sure. Okay.
I'll give you 200 baht for all of this.
It looks like there are more.
I'll come back later.
Mister!
Stop!
Damn it, Jean. What's with you?
Why did you bring them back?
I'm not sure.
I suddenly feel guilty.
I feel like I'm throwing too much away.
Thanos took off the gauntlet.
What's gotten into you?
Sorry.
Damn it.
It does hurt when it happens to me.
I thanked it before throwing it out.
I just didn't thank you
for knitting it for me.
It's all right.
Thank you for making me understand.
Do you have Pin's, Toey's,
and Bam's number?
I just want to return some things to them.
GENG, SUN, JOMJAM, PLOY
TOEY, TEN, PIN, AOM
Holy shit.
Is this what you wanted to give me?
Is it mine?
Yes, it's yours.
I totally forgot about it.
You didn't have to do this.
It's no big deal.
I found it while cleaning the house.
I remember it's yours.
I have to return what I borrowed.
How could you remember?
Thanks, anyway.
You're such a good person.
GOOD PEOPLE WILL BE FORGIVEN
Jean!
This is yours, Toey.
Holy shit.
I asked you to get this from Japan
in freshman year,
but you said it was sold out. Remember?
Yes. That's why I'm bringing it to you.
I looked everywhere and couldn't find it.
BAM
What do you want?
Nothing.
I'm just returning your double bass.
You asked me to repair...
You didn't have to return it.
Just throw it out.
That day you didn't wait for me,
you had no idea what I had to deal with.
Just leave it there. You can go.
Customer number 175,
please go to counter five.
EMS REGISTERED MAIL
TO AIM
Mail it, please.
This address is just next door.
You can walk there.
Mail it.
Mail it?
Are you sure?
Excuse me.
Is this your car?
Yes. Am I blocking you?
Does the stuff in the car belong to you?
Why?
I'm Noon.
I'm an antique collector and buyer,
but I'm not a dealer.
Are you interested in selling them to me?
I'm about to return those things.
They're not for sale.
I'm returning them all to my friends.
Too bad.
How about this?
I'll leave you my name card.
If you change your mind and want
to sell them, contact me anytime.
It's not often I come across good stuff.
Don't worry about the price.
I'm open to negotiation.
Okay. Thank you.
I'll call you if there's anything.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Sure.
Hey, where have you been?
I went to do good deeds.
PACKAGE REFUSED BY RECIPIENT
Well? Is that the top dog?
I'm exhausted, Pink.
You said returning stuff
would solve things.
When was the last time you spoke to him?
Three years ago,
before I boarded the plane to Sweden.
I told him...
I would see him soon,
and I never contacted him since.
That's how I dumped him,
like tossing things in a garbage bag.
Jean...
Dumping a person
isn't like dumping things.
It will all be over
if I throw it away now.
I have no reason to go see him.
Why should I look for trouble?
Shouldn't we get on
with renovating my house and office?
Problem solved.
I don't have to care about anything.
If you didn't care,
you wouldn't be in this situation.
Your things would be
with the junk collector.
TO AIM
Jean.
I happened to pass by.
I wanted to return your camera.
I just want to say that, Aim,
I'm sorry I've been gone.
You really don't have to say it.
-Please let me finish.
-It's really fine.
-It's all right.
-I've waited so long for this chance.
Let me finish.
I'm sorry for disappearing
after I moved there.
When you e-mailed me,
I saw your e-mail, but...
I didn't want to reply.
I didn't want to know
what would happen next.
So I blocked and unfriended you.
I...
At the time, I thought...
since I felt that you weren't the one,
that was on you.
It wasn't my problem.
Why should I be responsible
for other people's feelings?
I was just...
choosing what was best for me.
But you know what?
When I went to the city,
you asked me to take photos
with your camera,
I felt guilty.
I didn't even bring your camera.
I hid it in a box at home,
hoping it would get tossed out
when someone cleaned my room.
I came here to tell you that...
I'm sorry I didn't say goodbye.
I'm sorry for never getting
in touch with you.
I'm sorry I never asked about your life.
I'm sorry I'm like this.
I'm sorry for never saying sorry.
Can you yell at me?
I feel worse when you say nothing.
I'm happy to see you.
How can I yell at you?
How about this?
Make me some corn soup.
It's been so long. I miss it.
Make yourself at home.
I'll get the ingredients.
Isn't your mom home?
No.
What about your aunt? Is she here?
She moved out last year
to stay with her kid in the South.
Why are you taking photos?
Why can't I?
It's a home, not a museum.
I love flipping through that magazine.
Jean, that's Mi.
Glad to meet you.
Aim talks about you all the time.
It's like I'm meeting a historical figure.
I see.
I must be from his Dark Age.
I'm making soup.
Join us.
Sure.
Thanks.
It's good.
You can't find it anywhere else.
You are exaggerating.
Thanks for taking care of my bonsai.
It's pretty. It's not about you.
Thanks, anyway.
Are you relieved?
Don't be a know-it-all.
I have to go.
Okay.
Good luck.
Let's have a meal sometime.
How was it?
I felt relieved. It's over.
He's moved on.
But actually...
when I was standing there,
I kept beating myself up.
Hey.
I'm not heartless anymore, right?
That's why I feel like this.
All these emotions are tiring.
Come on. You returned everything.
It's finally over.
You should be relieved.
Yes, you're right.
But I don't think
I'll keep in touch with him,
so I stole something of his.
What?
What did you steal?
PRETTY, I LIKE IT.
The reference that I told you I loved.
What?
It's from a magazine
I used to read at his house.
Shit. It's like in Inception.
He planted it in your head.
I don't know. I feel like...
lots of things that I like,
they are all from him.
Well, seeing him was worth the trip.
I can get back to work.
As for the rest of your stuff,
hurry up and return them.
So you can move on to other things.
He was the hardest one, right?
It's good. This can finally be over.
The rest should be easy.
Hello?
Jean, it's Korn.
Korn?
What's up, Korn?
I just heard you're back.
I'm getting married...
to Yok.
Little Yok?
Did you get back together?
Yes.
I saw from Toey's posts
how you've been returning
old things to people.
I remember you still have a photo of mine.
It's a photo of me and Yok.
A photo?
Which one?
Did I take it?
Yes, you did. I remember.
It was our first photo together.
I want it for the wedding.
Shit.
It's been ten years.
I don't know if I still have it.
Well, can you find it for me?
Okay. I'll try.
I LOOKED EVERYWHERE.
I THREW EVERYTHING AWAY.
KORN, I'M SORRY.
AIM
Hello, Jean. This is Aim.
Hello.
Are you free tomorrow? Let's have dinner.
Mi is coming too.
I can go.
I can make it.
Hey.
It's been ages.
The place hasn't changed.
Yes, it's still the same.
What's that?
It's the stuff you left at my house.
I want to give them back.
These are your clothes.
These are your other personal items.
I separated them.
HOW TO DUMP
STEP 5
DON'T ADD MORE THINGS
Thanks a lot.
You aren't mad, right?
Not at all. I understand.
I'm clearing out my house too.
We should get rid of things we don't need.
We must learn to throw stuff out
and keep only what's important.
Have a drink while we wait.
We ate all the appetizers.
It's like we're just here for water.
It's always like this.
We always wait at least an hour.
I don't know how we could wait.
I thought that too
the first time you took me here.
But it's worth the wait.
I really like their braised beef.
Aim takes me here all the time.
You complain about this mess,
yet you bring more stuff in.
I know. I'm throwing it away.
Like hell you are. It's in your room.
Throw it out. Don't open it.
BONSAI FOR BEGINNERS
JEAN'S PLAYLIST FOR AIM
HAPPY NEW YEAR, DEAR.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
COME HOME SOON SO WE CAN HANG OUT AGAIN.
HAPPY NEW YEAR 2017 - MOM
Aim, is your mom home?
Can I talk to her?
I want to thank her for the card.
Jean...
My mom passed away last year.
Why didn't you tell me that day?
YEAR 2017 - MOM
Take me to her right now.
MRS. NITRA THAMRONGKUL
DIED JUNE 20, 2018
Tell me about her last day.
Do you really want to know?
You don't have to know.
Just tell me.
Okay.
I kind of knew it was her last day.
I stayed with her
at the hospital since early morning.
I got her everything she wanted
to eat or have.
Towards the end, she wanted to eat...
your soup.
It was late at night...
when she passed away.
That's all.
Why didn't you contact me?
I had to move on.
I had to do it on my own.
I wasn't supposed to contact you.
When I had good news,
I was dying to call you, but I couldn't.
When I had bad news
and I had no one to turn to...
I couldn't call you either.
The New Year card Mom wrote you...
I couldn't send it to you
and I couldn't throw it away.
I had to keep it in a drawer.
I felt so alone.
All I could think of
was that I had to move on.
I have to move on by myself.
This is the end of the road.
I'm really sorry.
If there is anything that I can...
help you with...
you can always call me.
I'm here now.
I'll be right back.
Mi, I didn't mean anything by that.
I don't want you to...
Hey, I understand.
No worries.
But...
it's like I don't know him.
I didn't know some of the stuff
you were talking about.
When he said he felt alone,
it makes me feel like
I can't help him at all.
But I understand.
Everyone has a past.
He has one.
I have one.
You do too.
Hello, Korn?
Hi, Jean.
Did you find the photo?
I've gone through half of it.
Just wait.
You need it by next Saturday, right?
Actually, it's this Saturday.
You know, I already asked you once
for this photo,
but you never gave it to me.
I'm begging you.
I need it now. Please find it for me.
It should be in here.
Those photos should be with you
if they're not with me.
-Can I?
-Sure.
It's like taking a time machine.
I've never seen these before.
I'll sneak a peek later.
I'm kidding. Take your time.
I'd better find it and leave.
I'll let you two be.
Actually...
just copy any files you need.
I'm moving to Singapore soon.
Moving...
permanently?
Yes.
Why?
It's nothing.
Brian has been asking me.
The timing was right,
so I accepted his offer.
What about Mi?
She's going too.
I found it.
These two were always
on and off back then.
I never thought they would get married.
What a surprise.
It seemed like an ordinary photo.
Now, it's priceless.
It's good that I kept it.
I'm done. Thanks.
Why don't you take all of them?
It's okay.
I'll do it later. You hold on to them.
You're good at keeping things.
Mi.
Mi!
Bye.
Thanks.
Sure.
Dude, thank you so much
for keeping the photo.
I never thought I would get to use it.
Thank you for finding it for us.
I'm glad to see you happy.
It makes me happy too.
Congratulations.
Okay. If we're done here, I have to go.
I have to work.
-See you at the wedding.
-Sure.
The past is our enemy.
It's the hardest thing to let go.
My advice is
try to forget it and let it go
if you have no use for it anymore.
Lady, please stop talking.
Houses here are much bigger
than Japanese houses.
We have no earthquakes.
Don't throw everything out.
We can keep some.
She's just doing this for the show.
You're a damn traitor.
-When did you become like this?
-What?
Fuck.
-You were such a big fan.
Now, you hate her.
So? I want to be a better person.
Can't I change?
Are you calling yourself good?
Man...
Right. I found this photo
behind the cabinet.
It sparks joy.
I'll keep it.
It doesn't take up much space.
When was this taken?
Can't you remember?
I still remember that day.
It was your birthday.
Dad played "Happy Birthday" and you sang.
Auntie took the photo.
Was there this much love in our family?
I forgot about it all.
Come on.
At least it's a good memory.
But I think if we had remembered this
when our family were fighting,
we wouldn't have fought so much.
Seeing this photo makes me think...
Dad wasn't so bad.
We just forgot about this.
Some days, I sit staring at the piano.
I think I miss him.
Will you really throw the piano away?
HOW TO DUMP
STEP 6
DON'T LOOK BACK
Well, if we keep it,
it will look like this.
It will clash a bit.
Damn it. It really isn't nice.
It will take up a whole room.
What should I do?
Well...
it's up to you.
Anyway,
I think you have to cut down the cost.
Your spending is off the roof.
I've tried to stay within the budget.
Pink.
Don't underspend on a house.
It's a big deal.
We might as well go all out.
I'll take care of the money.
Your dad has good taste.
This is great stuff.
I'll take that one too.
I wired you the money.
TRANSACTION COMPLETED
150,000 BAHT
Excuse me.
Is that for sale?
I think... I won't be selling that.
I'm keeping it for now.
Do you still play?
No, it belongs to my dad.
I see...
I like it very much.
If you change your mind, let me know.
Since it's your father's,
I'll give you a good price.
Sure.
Thank you.
TRANSACTION COMPLETED
150,000 BAHT
Should I call him?
It's okay. I should do it.
If not, I'll have to keep running away.
It's Jean.
I'm just calling to ask
if you still want your piano?
If not, I'm going to sell it.
Goodbye then.
He left us like...
he didn't have to think twice.
If I had sold the damn piano,
it wouldn't have hurt this bad.
I called Dad last night.
Stop talking.
-He didn't recognize my voice.
-Stop.
Jean, stop talking.
-He said the piano...
-Jean!
He said we could sell the piano.
-He's not coming back.
-I said stop talking.
-Just throw it away.
-Watch it!
Why do you want to keep it?
No one plays it anymore.
-Dad isn't coming back.
-Don't say that.
-Dad isn't coming back!
-Shut up!
-Do you hear me?
-Sell the damn thing!
He's not coming back!
Why do you want to keep it?
No one plays it!
I still play it!
I play it!
I play...
I was minding my own business.
Why did you have to bring this up?
What if I forget him?
Will you be responsible?
I don't want to see you
going around in circles like this.
Mom.
If we don't try to forget,
we will never do.
Stop being selfish.
If you want to forget, go ahead.
Why are you forcing me to?
Do you know
you're being selfish right now?
If you want to remember,
do it on your own.
Jay and I don't want to remember.
Stop bossing people around.
Hello, Jean? This is Nao.
I just met up with Korn.
He said you found a photo for him. Right?
It reminded me
that you still have my belt.
Really?
Which one?
What brings you here, Mi?
Is something wrong?
We might not see each other again.
I want to return this to you.
I saw the photos saved in the hard disk.
I didn't know it was your shirt.
I think I should return it.
Aim never told me.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
You knew...
since the first time we met, didn't you?
But I understand.
It must be hard to say.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Singapore isn't that far.
If you're back, just give me a call.
We're friends now.
Sure.
Well...
I'm not going to Singapore.
Mi, I'm sorry.
I didn't want it to be like this.
I'm really sorry.
Should I call him and talk to him?
It isn't your fault.
Actually...
if I hadn't refused the parcel you sent...
you wouldn't have to come yourself.
Things would've been different.
Deep down, I was afraid
you would come back.
That's why I did that.
Damn it.
I made it worse.
I really want to hate both of you,
but I don't have any reason to do that.
You just wanted to apologize to him.
I understand.
Aim was being honest with me.
He did the right thing.
We have to choose
what's best for ourselves.
I really get it.
Mi.
I am...
I'm really sorry.
Hey.
I'm truly sorry.
It's okay.
This shirt was the last thing
of yours in his house.
He returned everything to you.
Goodbye.
It's Mi's stuff.
She may come back for them.
Why are you doing this?
You said it yourself.
Let go of everything
that you don't need anymore.
I did exactly what you told me.
You're actually right.
Just keep what's best for you.
Don't you know you're throwing away
what's best for you?
I tried. It isn't right.
Call Mi now.
-I'll help.
-You're wasting time.
I'm doing this for you.
You're doing it for you.
You returned my stuff to me for yourself.
You apologized to me for yourself.
You're helping me with Mi for yourself,
so you can dump me with no guilt.
Jean, seriously...
when you came to apologize,
I was mad.
It was like...
you were off the hook
after you apologized.
So I had to forgive you, right?
If I don't forgive you, it's my problem.
It's no longer your problem.
It was like...
you took all your guilt
and dumped it on me.
Then you just left.
I just wanted to apologize
because I really care about you.
Then don't apologize.
Live with your guilt.
Don't run away. Can you do it?
I...
Everything is already in the past.
Can't you let it go?
If you ever truly loved someone,
you would know it's easier said than done.
Have you ever truly loved anyone?
I really shouldn't have come back.
Jean.
Just admit that you're selfish
and move on with your life. That's all.
You don't have to worry.
Everyone is like this.
They have to choose
what's best for themselves.
We see what we want to see.
We remember what we choose to.
That's all there is.
Just get on with your life.
But I said I was sorry, Aim.
I said I was sorry.
I said sorry. Damn it!
What are you doing here?
Are you free the day after tomorrow?
Yes.
Can you take Mom out?
Are you really going to do it?
No one knows how to play it, anyway.
Why should we keep it?
Aren't you coming?
I have work.
Do you want anything for dinner?
No.
Thank you so much.
When you finish renovating,
please let me know.
I would like to check it out.
Take care.
Jean!
Open the door and talk to me!
Where's the piano?
Bring it back!
Do you think I'm stupid?
Do you think I'm stupid
tricking me like this?
How could you?
Open the door and talk to me!
Why are you like this?
You're selfish like your father.
Do you know that?
Do you know that you're selfish?
Bring back the piano!
Pink, I want the original plan
for the office.
I sold the piano.
Sorry about that. Thanks a lot.
What's up?
Jay, I'm going away.
Can you clear out my room?
How am I supposed to know
what you want to keep?
TEE, TUM, OAK, POM
JEAN'S PLAYLIST FOR AIM
Toss everything out.
It's too much trouble. I can't do it.
I put the important stuff
in my luggage already.
Sure. I'll take care of it.
Right.
Don't bother calling me.
Throw everything out.
Snap your fingers for me.
I'll come back after New Year's.
FRIENDS
UNFRIEND
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT
TO UNFRIEND AIM THANA?
CONFIRM
Damn, Jean. I'm happy for you.
You did it.
Once you've decluttered your house,
it's really spacious.
You can do a lot with it.
Anyway, how are things with Aim?
Is everything okay?
Well...
I...
I think he really got over me.
The last time I talked to him,
we talked normally.
I think we can be friends.
I guess...
we all have to move on.
Also, he's moving to Singapore soon
with his new girlfriend for work.
That's cool.
Are you glad? I'm happy for you.
Subtitle translation by Karina Suvapataya