ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS,
EVENTS, AND OCCUPATIONS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Why didn't you tell us that
Andrew was a murderer?
I thought we were just going
to threaten them a bit!
You said you didn't care about
anything as long as we got the food.
I just opened the door because
the building representative asked me to.
I had no idea
that it was something like this!
I didn't know, either.
Mr. Oh suggested this plan.
Who are you?
I'm Andrew. I've always wanted
to have superpowers.
Sae-bom!
Jung-kook, wake up!
Good luck treating him.
I'll protect Seo-yoon.
I'll come to get you. Just wait a bit.
You don't have a scar on your face.
All of you, go to the gym.
I'll bring those two later.
Can't we take the food now?
There are people in there.
Let's go wait there.
It's not a pretty sight for us to see.
This is a bad environment
to be in with a kid…
Mr. Lawyer.
Stay here for a moment.
You heard that noise, right?
Is your brother all right?
It seems you go see him often.
You didn't go with her, did you?
My brother is totally fine!
He's extremely careful,
and his wound made by the infected
hasn't changed at all, either.
Now, let's go down.
We have to discuss Unit 501.
The others will join us
when they're done with their business.
Let's go.
This is bothersome…
Yi-hyun, bring the first-aid kit
and clean water.
Mr. Kim, let me take a look.
Hang in there for a bit.
You'll be okay if you go to the hospital.
But still, if I die,
tell my wife…
that I said I'm sorry,
and that I love her.
You tell her face to face.
You can go out and get treated.
Really?
Do you really think I'll live?
You will.
It's just a small hole on your side.
Is it really a small one?
Is it true?
Yi-hyun…
Jung-kook, hang in there a bit.
Sae-bom, Jung-kook…
Yi-hyun.
Yi-hyun!
Look at me.
We will get out of here alive…
and we will arrest
all of them.
Jung-kook got stabbed
with a knife on his side.
And Seo-yoon can't breathe well,
so have the medical staff ready.
We can go inside.
No, Seo-yoon is taken hostage.
It'll be dangerous if you come in.
Mr. Jung.
I thought about the reason
you're doing this.
Sae-bom has…
the antibody, doesn't she?
What if I say yes?
Then you should give us what we want
for Sae-bom to get out.
Mr. Lawyer, stay with this kid
for a moment.
I'm not a bad guy.
What's your name?
I know who you are.
Where are you going?
You have to get tested!
The hospital.
WANTED FOR MURDER
CHOI JONG-WOOK, AGE 33
You killed the real Ahn Kook-jin,
didn't you?
How many did you kill
with your face hidden like that?
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD: AHN KOOK-JIN
The infected are the same, though.
They hide their real selves to hide
in the crowd and seek victims.
They're ill because of the disease,
and you're just insane.
Hey, Mister.
How long have you known this?
I heard you started it!
It's been a few days.
I saw Andrew "taking care of"
the cleaning lady.
Hold on!
Wait.
Andrew, the 11th floor is vacant.
Wouldn't it be better
to hide the body there?
If you do this on the neck,
you can make it look like
it was done by the infected.
So I told the building representative
right away.
I have an offer for you.
There's a way
to get rid of those we don't like.
The building representative said yes,
so I told Andrew.
I told him we'll help him
so he should help us too.
You should all be thanking me.
I know you'll not like me saying this,
but I'm a top elite in society.
I even did some acting to trick the couple
on the fifth floor, for all of you.
How did you get into…
Kim Se-hoon's house?
I mentioned you,
and he opened the door for me.
Ms. Yoon got hurt.
Do you have a first-aid kit?
You would've suffered less
if you just listened to me.
I'LL LEAVE THE REMAINING FOOD AND WATER
Andrew.
This is limestone,
and it can get rid of
the smell of blood completely.
Stay there and talk.
You're making me uneasy by moving.
Mr. Kim is hurt.
He has to go to the hospital.
After you two do what you must do.
You can go outside, right? And…
Are you communicating
with someone outside?
What in the world
are you all talking about?
Please explain so we can understand.
We told the cleaners and the lawyer,
but we didn't get to tell you two yet.
You told my husband too?
Yes, I visited him once.
When he heard the 5th floor
and the 15th floor had a lot of food,
he loved the idea.
Mr. Jung had it.
You've been secretly reporting
about the situations going on in here?
You must've received something
and kept it to yourselves.
Under the condition
of monitoring us in here, right?
Hello?
Is anyone there?
I'm the building representative
of Building 101.
I'm in charge of managing
the apartments, so talk to me…
Hello?
Anyone there?
I told them everything.
What did you tell them?
Did you spread your delusions to them?
Yes, all of them.
I'm sure the people outside
will decide what happened here.
You two will go to prison
for aiding and abetting murder.
And aren't you ashamed to see your son?
I just did it
because they said they'd give out food!
I didn't know anything! I really didn't!
Food doesn't just fall from the sky.
You knew that someone was going
to get hurt, didn't you?
You were going to
get something if you ignored it.
So you accepted it.
No…
You don't need to be worried so soon.
What matters now is to hang in there
until the lockdown is over.
And…
The couple at Unit 501 promised
to turn on the emergency power.
Right.
Yes, you must turn on the
electricity and take the kid.
If they ask you about why this happened,
just tell them a lunatic
with a gun did it.
So…
are you telling us to keep quiet
about a crime?
What?
I didn't say anything wrong.
Don't mess with those
who have nothing to do with this!
If we attack you at the same time…
you could die too.
Yes, you two have a lot to do,
so you shouldn't fight.
Ms. Na, you don't need
to be here. Go home.
You too, Ms. Shin.
Your husband is at our house
with Seo-yoon right now.
She must've been shocked,
so please protect her at Unit 602.
I will.
Go turn the electricity on.
Then I will let Seo-yoon
and that detective out.
Do you want to come with us?
Seo-yoon, I'm fine.
I'm fine, so why don't you stay outside?
I'm worried because I might've
been infected, that's why.
Stay outside. It's okay.
Mr. Lawyer, can you please
take Seo-yoon to your house?
I don't think she should stay here.
Right.
Stop taking deep breaths,
and come with me. Come.
If you stay here,
that scary guy will come back.
You don't want to get in trouble, do you?
What are you doing?
So-yoon, you came just in time.
Her name sounds similar to yours,
so you persuade her.
Andrew has a gun and he threatened
the couple on the fifth floor.
Yes, he's totally insane.
He must be a murderer or something.
Let's turn a blind eye.
We just need to hide
until the lockdown is over.
Did you help too?
Hey, do I look like someone who'd do that?
I just heard about it from
the building representative.
She said I just need to help them a bit…
This isn't who you were.
When you were a public defender,
you helped those who have been wronged,
and took your time to investigate.
So what did I get from doing that?
I should find a way to live too!
Where did she go?
Kid, let's go. Come here.
Come here.
I want to go with her.
Yes, Seo-yoon, let's go.
But Mr. Kim…
Seo-yoon said
she wants you to come with her.
I'm sorry,
but I don’t think I can climb the stairs.
Please take care of Seo-yoon.
I'm sorry.
We'll go down,
so be careful not to get killed by Andrew.
And think about how you can live
in a less shameful way.
Aren't you going to give us any weapons?
Like baseball bats?
You said the infected
are human beings too.
Talk to them.
When you're done, come here.
We should go see Seo-yoon together.
Wait.
I'll come with you.
It's the senior citizens' center
in Building 103.
-Mr. Kim, wait here.
-What?
It's dangerous. You don't need to go out.
Stay here and go up
when the lights are on.
Is it okay for me to do that?
Why did you follow us?
It doesn't look like
you're here to film stuff, either.
That's my car right there.
I have nowhere to go.
So I want to try breaking out
by hitting the shutter with my car.
Good luck.
All right.
Let's go.
Wait.
That way.
ELECTRICAL ROOM
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Yi-hyun.
EMERGENCY POWER SUPPLY
The infected will swarm in
when they hear the noise!
This way.
Why did we come this way?
Andrew might try to kill us if we go up.
He'll be waiting at the elevator
or the stairs at our building.
He won't imagine we'd come down
from the next building's rooftop.
There was nobody on
the 15th floor of Building 103.
We just need to take Seo-yoon
and Jung-kook and get out.
Let's go.
What's wrong with this?
Why isn't it working?
Please!
No!
Andrew, you've done so much work for us.
Shouldn't the gun be managed
officially by the entire apartment?
Andrew.
When the fifth floor couple comes up,
you'll get rid of them, right?
You're going out
when the lockdown is over, right?
Yes, I must go to other apartments.
Everything that happened here
is all your doing, Andrew.
And we knew nothing.
Understood?
You two are okay with it too, right?
Of course. We know nothing.
What are you doing?
We have to go turn on the water.
Get in. You must go
to Unit 501 to get food too.
We'll go there after we go
to the second floor first.
Go ahead.
Why? That Andrew is nothing.
Are you nuts? Do you want to get killed?
Andrew, why have you been
covering that good-looking face?
Go upstairs.
I'm going to kill the cop couple
when they come up.
After we save the others,
can we get them out?
What if Han Tae-seok doesn't take them in?
He will take them in.
You have the antibody.
I do?
So he's trying to take you
by using Seo-yoon as an excuse.
Because you're the only one
in this world who has the antibody.
Stay in there!
Yi-hyun!
What are you doing? Get inside!
Yi-hyun, is this…
I'm sorry.
I couldn't tell you.
I'm sorry I couldn't keep my promise.
I always wanted…
to only show you my good side.
Don't come close to me.
Whenever I see you,
my heart thumps and I feel thirsty.
I do too.
Because I like you.
Come with me.
You will get better.
Because I'll make you get better.
You must have a reason
you're obsessed with this incident.
Even by locking up
the infected in freezer trucks
and sneaking into the apartments.
I got infected.
This will be my last favor.
Yes?
It looks like the emergency power
was turned on inside the apartments.
Remove the parking lot barricades
and block it again
after Ms. Yoon comes out.
Jung Yi-hyun is infected.
Tell them to fire
if he threatens Yoon Sae-bom.
Bo-ram.
Lee Bo-ram!
Bo-ram, open the door.
What are you going to do now?
Is there a way to get rid of Andrew?
The resident-representative-to-be.
I'm sure the police will take care of it.
We can just send him to prison
when things get better.
We didn't know that jerk was a murderer.
-Are you going to say that you knew?
-No. Have it your way, then.
Get lots of food and be happy and healthy.
You must be happy because
you have plans laid out like a movie.
Aren't you taking anything, Mr. Oh?
I have something else to take, so I must…
If you see any drugs, call me right away.
Anything like health supplements
or vitamins.
I was just playing.
I'm just going to find
the drugs and get out.
Want me to give you some if I find them?
If you take it,
then it'll be very hard for you to die.
Hyun-kyung, hurry.
The air conditioner.
Hey, is the lockdown over?
It's absolute chaos outside.
Andrew! That crazy piece of crap!
Why?
He threatened the fifth floor couple
to make them turn on the emergency power.
But didn't Andrew like you?
Damn it! Shut up.
What should we do?
We can't just sit here like this.
Hey, of course we can.
We just need to hide here,
enjoying the air conditioner.
We're powerless.
And I got the disease.
Still,
they did help us.
LOG IN
NO INTERNET CONNECTION
What are you doing?
It's nothing.
You still haven't given up?
The Internet is still out.
What are you trying to do?
You should charge your phone too.
Bring it here.
Go to Unit 501
and bring some water and food.
Me?
Then do you want
to stay here with Seo-yoon?
When everyone takes them,
there will be nothing left for us.
You go next time.
So-yoon, what is this? What are you doing?
You don't care about sacrificing others
and you only care about yourself.
And you justify yourself
by saying you had no other choice.
I'm sick and tired of you!
Hey, So-yoon!
Shin So-yoon!
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Just bring Mr. Kim out safely.
Wait, is this because of Sang-hee?
I told you she and I are not
in that kind of a relationship!
Oh Joo-hyung invested all the money
he pocketed in cryptocurrency.
We were going to share it, that's why!
So I can make you live in luxury.
The world is about to end.
Do you think that'll be worth anything?
No, you obviously don't know anything.
Don't you know what a blockchain is?
That's the value of the future.
Values like that shine more brightly
when the world is in chaos.
What the heck?
Let go! It hurts!
All right. Let go.
Ms. Shin So-yoon, it's me.
Open the door, please.
Sae-bom?
Darn it.
So-yoon, tell her
that it's a misunderstanding.
I protected the kid! That's a fact!
Hurry!
Just let him go.
He's too cowardly to fight back anyway.
Darn it.
You really did come back soon.
I kept our promise, right?
Does your chest still feel stuffy?
But Mr. Kim seemed to be in a lot of pain.
Yes.
He'll be going out with us.
What about Andrew?
I'm sure he's waiting down
there somewhere.
You guys can't get out of here anyway.
We're all trapped in here.
Are you going to kill me here too?
Just like my husband?
Help!
I'm going to die here!
I'm not going out, so don't worry.
Just wait here for a bit.
If we let her take the kid,
that psycho Andrew won't forgive us!
So you want to give the kid to a murderer?
Ms. Shin, we're going to go out.
Want to come with us?
Mr. Kim!
Seo-yoon, I'm happy to see you too,
but I'm in pain. Take it easy, okay?
So-yoon, calm down.
Let's go home and lock the door, okay?
I got to see how filthy
your nature really is.
We're done.
So-yoon!
This is yours.
Thank you.
Damn it, I said I won't!
You saw the look in his eyes.
-Please stop it!
-Let go!
We collected all that money for our kid…
Andrew. We were just…
Stay here. When the fifth floor couple
comes up, hold them.
I… Andrew.
I'll pay you by the hour,
at least. Please.
I can take you down
if you don't have this gun…
Honey! You can do it!
Go!
Hey, get off of him! Damn it!
Let him go!
Oh no!
Should I pull it out? What do I do?
Should I pull it out?
Ma'am, don't pull that knife out.
He'll die if you do.
This is some serious diet.
We're almost there. Hang in there a bit.
Bo-ram, do you want to come with us too?
Can I do that?
Yoon Sae-bom.
I'll keep him here, so go!
What are you talking about?
You should come with us!
I'm sorry I can't go with you.
Yi-hyun!
Sae-bom.
I was truly happy…
to be with you.
What are you saying?
Open the door, now!
Go.
Never give up.
Yi-hyun!
I think someone's coming up.
Don't mess with Yi-hyun.
I'm going to be back soon.
Let's go.
Hey.
That's a new model, so it won't break.
Wait.
Want this?
Jung Yi-hyun throws a pitch,
and the ball hits the mitt!
Andrew, the batter, can't do anything.
That was a fast pitch. It was fast.
Jung Yi-hyun is back after a long hiatus,
and he threw the best pitch of his life!
Hey, if I didn't get injured,
I could've gone to the Major League.
Your wife ran away,
and you're okay with it?
Yes, this is great.
I started liking her
after meeting her at a place like this.
On a sunny day…
with a beautiful blue sky.
And it's great
to let her go…
on a day like this,
and at a place like this in the end.
That's no fun.
Look at me.
Where's the fun in killing
if I can't look into the victim's eyes?
What does this even say?
Sang-hee, So-yoon ran away.
That's good.
There's something you must do for me.
About Oh Joo-hyung…
What the heck?
It must be high blood pressure.
He suddenly collapsed.
Look at this writing.
What does this say?
-Hey.
-What?
Right.
Isn't that cursive for doctors?
For writing prescriptions.
Don't you know? You worked at that clinic.
I only do consultations.
Don't you have your phone?
I left it at home…
He's alive.
Mister, is that something
for your blood pressure?
Here.
Read it carefully.
If we get it wrong ten times,
then we can't get the money.
Okay, I'll read it carefully.
You have to get up!
Put some strength into your legs!
You need to get up!
I can't put any strength into my legs!
Get up!
Building representative, please help!
My husband is hurt!
Please help us!
What happened?
Andrew stabbed him.
Don't talk to her!
It's all her fault! Damn it!
What about the others? Have you seen them?
What about Andrew? Where did he go?
To the 15th floor.
Hurry and get in.
It's okay.
They're all on our side.
Give me a gun so I can go bring Yi-hyun.
Let go of me!
SEYANG CITY HALL, SEYANG NEW TOWN
Yi-hyun…
Has the Martial Law been lifted?
And you kept it from us?
I'm sure it was to manage
the quarantine areas effectively.
And then…
you realized I had the antibody,
and pulled me out.
We gave you the antidote,
so you'll feel quite dizzy.
Lie in bed for a while.
Here is your phone.
-Where did you get this?
-From Detective Kim Jung-kook.
He told me…
that Mr. Jung told him
to take it with him.
I have to go find Yi-hyun.
Is it really worth it?
Wasn't it a marriage of convenience?
There are a lot of people outside
that you should protect.
Remember what you said to me?
That if something goes wrong,
the world may collapse.
I'm sorry about what happened to Mr. Jung.
But when the cure is developed
and things are resolved,
you might not lose…
the things you wanted.
Tell the world it'll have to wait.
I have to see Yi-hyun.
If I lose him…
my world may really collapse.
I want to show someone to you.
Is she infected?
Her seizure stopped,
thanks to your plasma,
but she won't be able to last.
We brought you with the excuse
of excessive tranquilizer injections.
We'll check your condition today
and tomorrow, and if you're okay,
you'll go to the governmental lab.
To a lab with Biosafety Level 4,
where outsiders can't enter.
What do you want?
She'll be cured only if she gets
one more injection of your plasma.
Then let's help each other.
I'll give you my plasma
or anything you ask for…
so help me go back home.
And keep the electricity on
at the apartments until then.
The emergency power
can't last that long.
Do you think…
Mr. Jung is alive?
Of course.
ALBUM
TO SAE-BOM
Ta-da! Hi, Sae-bom.
I'm sorry I couldn't propose
to you properly.
It must have seemed
like I agreed to marry you
because of the house.
But that's not why.
I was just worried
that you'd misunderstand
because I said yes so quickly.
I'm not such an easy guy, you know.
Of course, the house is important, too…
but what's really important is
whom I'm going to be with, right?
Mister, what are you doing
with Sae-bom's phone?
Seo-yoon, act like you didn't see that.
They're being lovey-dovey…
Wait, no. Just think
that he's invisible now.
Let's go.
I hope we can go out safely
and watch this video together.
When that happens, I'll tell you properly…
that I like you.
Ta-da! Hi, Sae-bom.
I'm sorry I couldn't propose
to you properly.
It must have seemed
like I agreed to marry you
because of the house.
But that's not why.
I was just worried
that you'd misunderstand
because I said yes so quickly.
I'm not such an easy guy, you know.
Of course, the house is important, too…
WONJUNG DORMITORY
I bit Andrew.
If he's alive, then we must catch him.
I'm sure he hid Andrew's body
and lied to me.
I can kill him too if something happens.
The antibodies are decreasing.
So we should kill the detective?
They're infected.
You people are the monsters,
not those with the disease.
I will take care of Yoon Sae-bom.
What about Yi-hyun?
Is he alive?
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee