ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS,
EVENTS, AND OCCUPATIONS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
I hope we can go out safely
and watch this video together.
When that happens, I'll tell you properly…
that I like you.
The call cannot be connected.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Your message
will be charged after the tone.
(I AM) THE LIFESAVER
Seo-yoon.
Sae-bom!
Yi-hyun is still in the apartment.
I'm going to go get him.
How do you feel? Are you feeling better?
I'm here to see my mom.
They said she's here.
Seo-yoon, wait here for a moment.
-Seo-yoon!
-Mom!
Seo-yoon!
Yes, stay there.
I caught a cold.
You're here with the police officer lady.
Are you badly sick?
No, just a little bit.
But I don't want you to catch it too.
I heard you decided to get surgery.
Yes.
You shouldn't get sick
before surgery, okay?
Good luck with your surgery,
and listen to
the police officer lady, okay?
So our family can be healthy
and meet again.
Seo-yoon, you have to listen to your mom.
See you after the surgery.
Mom…
Bye.
I heard that Seo-yoon
can get surgery thanks to you.
You sent us Seo-yoon's letter too, right?
I was able to hold on by reading it.
If I hadn't received it,
I would've ended up like my husband.
I know I'm shameless, but please
look after Seo-yoon a little more.
I don't know what might happen to me, so…
You should go now.
Hurry.
These are typical questions,
so don't be nervous.
Okay.
How many are infected in the apartments?
If Detective Jung Yi-hyun
is infected too, then…
There are two.
There's Mr. Na Soo-min
from the fourth floor.
And there are two who died while infected?
Please tell us everything you know
about the infected.
It might help in developing the cure.
Good luck with your surgery.
I promise I'll come
visit you with Yi-hyun.
My mom got the disease, didn't she?
She's just ill, then.
Like me.
Of course.
So both you and your mom
will get better soon.
Seo-yoon's mother…
She's been enduring it until now
so she can see her daughter,
but she's reached her limit.
She'll be moved to a freezer storage
in one or two days.
These were made with your blood.
The antibodies in your body
are decreasing.
So?
These are the last
effective injections we have now.
These must be amplified
and used for research purposes
in order to develop the cure.
Then you just need…
to yield them to the world.
The Commander of the AFMC
is here to take you.
It means he's going to take
both you and the cure to the lab.
So…
Are you going to break your promise?
What are you doing?
Stop him!
It won't take long.
Do you even know what you're doing?
Of course, I do.
I'm done.
Where's Yoon Sae-bom?
And the remaining cure?
She just left. Didn't you see her?
If you go out the back door on
the first floor, your car will be there.
There are gifts in the car,
so make sure to take them.
But is it okay to do this?
I thought you were a greedy man.
I have plans, so don't worry
and do what you must.
But if you get caught in the act,
I won't take responsibility.
Don't worry.
You will get better.
What did you just do?
That was the cure, right?
Yes.
I tried to just leave, but I couldn't.
Are you going to shoot me?
What are you going to do now?
Even if you get out of here,
you used the cure already.
I'm not that special.
I'm sure you'll find
more people with the antibody.
Yi-hyun has me, but Seo-yoon…
doesn't have anyone.
I just need to be with Yi-hyun until then.
Hurry and get out.
They'll only check
those in quarantine suits.
They won't pay attention to you.
I always knew there was
something between us.
Wait.
You can't just go.
No.
If I look totally fine,
people will suspect me.
Are you sure?
It'll hurt.
Do it, before I change my mind.
Close your eyes and take a deep breath.
Not the face.
Do it where it won't hurt much.
People will suspect you.
And the swelling on the face
goes away more quickly too.
Okay.
In one blow.
ENTRANCE PERMIT
Thanks for the gifts.
Yoon Sae-bom escaped.
You know this won't end
with just your resignation, right?
Are you going to execute me, then?
I thought you were smart.
Why did you do that?
If you only stole one cure for your wife,
that could've been forgiven.
I did all kinds of things
to reduce the number of infected.
Lockdowns, quarantines, destructions…
I got enough blood on my hands.
But thanks to that, you succeeded.
You saved many people too.
I only saw people through the lens
of efficiency and numbers.
But seeing Yoon Sae-bom,
I learned that there are
other ways to see them.
Yi-hyun.
I didn't know how precious you were
when you were by my side.
I'll come and get you, wherever you are.
Salute…
Yoon Sae-bom put your uniform on
and ran away?
Yes. She threw me…
Enough!
Where do you think she went?
It looks like she's trying
to run away overseas with the cure.
It'd be good to put her on a wanted list
mainly around airports and piers.
I'm sure she went to the apartment.
Her husband is there.
Lieutenant Colonel.
Keep going.
Someone in the apartments
has the antibody.
Give me full authority.
Then I'll bring the cure.
Would this really be okay?
Hey, it's okay.
The news said it's fine outside too.
People at Unit 501 all left too,
except for that detective.
But if we go outside too, then…
It's better for us not to be here.
We'd be helping them if we go outside.
What?
Who is that?
Hey, wait.
-Who is that?
-Wait.
Hey, Unit 501! The wife from Unit 501!
Open the door! Hurry!
Hold on.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
-Did they tell you to go back in?
-Please calm down.
What about Yi-hyun? Is he safe?
Is he alive?
ONE DAY AGO
Yi-hyun.
Get up.
We have to meet again.
Sae-bom.
Mister, are you okay?
You're bleeding badly.
I'm okay.
Let me get some sleep.
Okay.
Are you sure about this?
You said this seems right too.
I told you, it'll be done for
if we get it wrong ten times.
We have to consider
all possible variables.
Damn it.
-So-yoon?
-Who is it?
Help, please. Call the doctor.
My husband got stabbed with a knife.
He is conscious,
but I think he bled too much.
-Mr. Oh isn't here.
-Please. We're sorry about everything.
I said there is no doctor here!
What are you doing?
Yes, there's no one here…
-Doctor!
-Seriously…
Open the door!
But who did that to that man…
-Seriously…
-Open the door, please!
Please! Open the door!
Open the door!
Open the door! Do you think
you'll be safe after we all die?
I'm going to burn this place down!
Doctor.
Are you okay?
Hi.
Hey, did you see that?
He was shot in the arm and leg.
But his bleeding stopped already.
Then it's good. What's the problem?
The smell of his blood is disgusting,
and I don't want to drink it.
It means he's infected.
Then what about my blood?
Did you want to drink my blood?
Hey, listen to me when I say something!
Don't change the topic!
He is infected!
You can't deny it, though.
You even want your sister's blood.
How can you call yourself my brother?
What?
Are you okay?
-What are you doing? Go get water.
-Right.
What brings you two here?
You kept bleeding,
and I couldn't do anything all by myself.
I made him put it on,
just in case the disease might occur.
Here.
Don't you feel thirsty?
It's a lot less these days.
I do feel thirsty,
but diabetes runs in my family.
What about Sae-bom?
What?
She's not in the building.
The other detective
and the kid aren't here, either.
Those people got out, right?
We saw on the news
that the outside is totally fine.
And they said Martial Law has been lifted,
except for quarantine areas.
Maybe the gates are open outside as well.
I don't know much, either.
Don't move.
You have two holes in your body.
I bit Andrew.
What?
He's a murderer so if he's infected,
he'll become even more dangerous.
If he's alive,
then we must catch him.
Let's look for him on our way downstairs
before he kills more people.
Okay.
While the CDSCHQ
is minimizing the infections
with quick diagnoses
and bold local quarantines,
it looks like the prevention of
Mad Human Disease will be possible soon.
According to the authorities, the vaccine
currently being clinically tested
seems effective,
and they said they will request
the public health authorities
to give it emergency use authorization
as soon as it shows optimistic results.
Drink this.
You should eat something to get energy.
They decided to maintain quarantine
until the cure is developed.
Therefore, the current lockdown
on nursing homes, apartments
and so on will continue,
and additional local--
Look who's here. It's the brave detective.
By the way, did you get hurt
in the electrical room?
Is someone injured?
The moving-in cleaner couple
on the second floor.
The husband got stabbed by Andrew,
so I'm treating him right now.
I see neither Andrew
nor the building representative.
-Do you know where they are?
-I guess they went outside.
Where's your wife?
Andrew is dangerous right now.
Never open the door for him.
I'm going to make all three of you
get punished by the law, if possible.
You mean our neighbor? Unit 602?
Sang-hee had an affair
with the lawyer of that house, and…
Look at this. They did this to me.
Shouldn't you arrest them first?
We're coming from Unit 602, okay?
The lawyer showed us
the bite mark on his arm.
Right, I got the disease.
But there are a lot of people
who got the disease.
Biting someone
wouldn't be punishable, would it?
Mr. Oh.
You didn't get the disease.
I know because I got the disease.
I am holding in my desire
to bite you right now.
I took the drug too!
Taking that drug
doesn't always give you the disease.
Some get it late…
or never get it at all.
Where's Mr. Ko?
Here.
Doctor, his condition is worsening.
Can't you do anything?
Of course his condition is bad,
with that thing in his body.
Honey, I'm okay. I will recover soon.
So, tell that jerk
to get out of here, please.
Tell him to get out.
Hey, this is my house!
How long can Mr. Ko last?
If we pull out the knife,
he'll die right away.
If we leave him be,
he'll last maybe two days.
Let's find a way to send them outside.
Treat his wound until then.
I gave him painkillers and my bedroom!
What more can I do?
You kept Mr. Ko and Ms. Ji here
for when you feel thirsty, right?
What do you take me for?
How dare you say that?
Did you take that? And that's why
you thought you were infected?
Yes, I was keeping them
as my boxed lunches! So what?
I took it because
I felt like I could die too!
Just treat him well.
If you cause any more trouble
then I'll lock you up in the basement.
Do you think you can lock me up?
Do you think
you're King Solomon or something?
Honey.
Take this.
If you take this drug,
then your wound will heal quickly.
Did you swallow it?
You love me, right?
You won't bite me
even if you get the disease, right?
Hey.
Sir, are you okay?
I'm not okay.
You don't look okay either, young man.
How's your wife?
We're okay, so…
Just look after our son, please.
He's still not back?
What? Isn't he on the second floor?
He said he wanted to go outside, but…
If you see him,
tell him to come back home. We're fine.
Home is a place where you can go back to
when you're having a hard time.
Okay.
If you see Andrew…
If you see an unfamiliar man,
don't open the door for him.
He's very dangerous.
Okay.
Why would he come here, though?
It's just two old people here.
Sir, do you have enough food?
Would you like us to give you some?
Don't give them food.
We barely have enough for us.
I'm going to share mine.
How can you be so mean?
You two, stand back.
He's infected.
I saw him biting Andrew.
But I'm infected too.
Building representative,
this is no time to fight.
There's a high chance
of Andrew still being in the building.
Andrew is dead.
I was going to go outside
and meet the person in charge.
But the infected are at the entrance too.
Still, we caught the killer,
so we just need to wait quietly.
So, did you get rid of Andrew's dead body?
It's on the rooftop.
You bit him to death, Mr. Jung!
There's no one on the rooftop.
It looks like you're trying to trick me.
Do you think I'm stupid?
I'm not!
I'm normal.
I'm not like you infected people!
It's dangerous to go alone,
building representative.
Is it okay to just let her be like that?
She lost her family.
I'm sure she needs someone
to blame and hate.
Oh, gosh.
I'm sure he hid Andrew's body
and lied to me.
I can kill him too if something happens.
It looks like Andrew
and Kim Dong-hyun both went outside.
What?
Hey.
What are you doing?
What if the infected crowd in?
Don't come out.
Okay.
But…
Are you okay?
How long has it been since you got bitten?
Hey, isn't that
the jobless guy on the third floor?
It looks like he's hurt.
Hurt? He got bitten!
Didn't he…
get the disease?
It hasn't occurred yet.
I'm sure he can endure a bit more
if he's with his family.
Dad, I'm sorry.
My goodness.
Honey.
Dong-hyun is home.
Moon-hee.
What?
Are you okay? Are you coming to?
It hurts less.
Who gave you that drug from earlier?
How about we pull this out, Moon-hee?
Okay.
Wait.
Do you have more of that drug?
Give me water.
Let's pull it out.
I'm going to pull it out.
Moon-hee, you know…
I can't just leave this place
when I'm such a mess.
Let's take this house.
How?
Doctor.
Why? Did your husband die?
I pulled the knife out.
Seriously?
I told you not to pull it out!
Did he bleed a lot on the floor?
Why didn't you listen to me!
Doctor…
you don't have any family, do you?
Doesn't this look a lot
more swollen than before?
How many times
do I have to tell you it doesn't!
Are you sure?
I am.
Stop touching it!
That's what's making it more swollen!
Are you sure this is okay?
What should we do with the cryptocurrency?
We have the passcode,
but we don't have the laptop.
The laptop!
Sang-hee! I'll give you money,
so open the door.
Open the door, Sang-hee!
Isn't he trying to bite us again?
I'll give you money.
-How much will you give me?
-Hey!
That cleaner asshole has gone totally mad!
He's insane!
Stop!
If Mr. Ko is in a critical condition
then we must send him out.
-We can't just let him die like that.
-Detective Jung!
Detective Jung, help me.
I almost got killed.
What now?
He gave us the drug.
He said my husband would get better.
Are you nuts, old woman?
It's not true!
Why would I make more monsters?
Is Mr. Ko okay?
He's still in pain.
He's lying down right now.
Can you please chase him away?
I'm terrified to be with him.
They're the ones who should be kicked out!
Don't you trust me?
We're residents of the same apartment.
This is the first time hearing you say
we're residents of the same apartment.
I warned you, didn't I?
-You're going to the gym.
-The laptop!
Tell them to give me my laptop!
My laptop!
-Get the elevator.
-Right.
Are you happy that I'm leaving?
What the…
What are you doing?
Where are you taking Dr. Oh?
He's going to be in quarantine.
If you don't want to end up like him,
you should be careful.
Honey. This is all ours, right?
Of course.
That jerk doesn't have any family.
I almost got killed by that asshole.
We just need to demand this house
for compensation.
But he'll never give it up.
We'll get rid of him
before the lockdown is over.
They'll think that the infected did it.
Right?
Moon-hee…
Give me some water.
Okay.
Just take this too.
I'm really thirsty for some reason.
How much is all of this?
One, two, three…
Why didn't you go outside with your wife?
I had to watch the house
until Sae-bom got back.
We got this as
a special provision for public officials,
and it was hard to get it.
We know what you did for us.
If it wasn't for you,
something terrible would've happened.
Thank you.
I should look for Andrew once more
after getting some rest.
It can be dangerous,
so you two should go home now.
We can help too.
I can be dangerous too.
Mr. Na seems much better now…
but I'm not.
Be careful.
Sae-bom.
How are you doing?
I miss you.
We were saved thanks to Mr. Jung.
He's infected, but…
So he's home now?
It's dangerous.
Don't go outside. Stay home.
-The lockdown will be over soon.
-What? Really?
See? I told you not to go outside!
Great.
That's awesome.
Hey! Sang-hee. I knew you'd come.
Let me go! Let me go and talk!
What are you trying to do without the key?
Building representative, please help me!
I only came here to help…
Are you mad, old woman?
Isn't it better to get rid
of that detective jerk on our own?
The woman ran away,
so we just need to get rid of him.
So are you saying
we should kill the detective?
He's infected.
This can break that thing, so do as I say.
Help!
Mr. Oh…
Calm down
and let Ms. Woo go.
Mr. Jung, just kill everyone uninfected
and say it was all because of the disease.
Yes.
The monsters did all of this.
You people are the monsters,
not those with the disease.
Aren't you thirsty?
Let's see who the real monster is.
Go.
Jung Yi-hyun!
Doesn't the blood smell good?
Don't hold it in! You must've been
holding it in all this time!
Jung Yi-hyun!
Come out!
Hey, come out!
Why aren't you listening to me?
These apartments are mine! Listen to me!
Calm down.
I'm not here to catch you.
You killed my husband.
I caught the murderer,
and I'm not infected either.
I deserve to be the representative.
Okay.
I'll vote for you
when you get released from prison.
-Thank you.
-Come out!
-Hey, come out!
Come out!
Just come out! Bite me! Change!
My disease will occur soon too!
You're so dead!
Yi-hyun.
I'm here.
I realized it after I heard what you said.
What's really important is…
who I'm going to be with in my house.
So I'm going to stay with you.
Stay with me.
I'm fine with whatever state you're in.
Are you sure that someone
in the apartment has the antibody?
Someone testified.
Please tell us everything you know
about the infected.
It might help in developing the cure.
I don't know much, but…
Ms. Na said
her brother's wound didn't change.
She said it neither gets worse nor heals.
You relied on that
and asked for full authority?
Ji-soo.
We never had anything
to rely on from the start.
Hae-seong, please open the door.
I got the cryptocurrency!
It's been hard for you, right?
Sorry for being so sensitive.
SO-YOON, ARE YOU SAFE?
I MISS YOU SO MUCH
Come on, we did this
so we can all be happy.
Hae-seong, are you listening? Hae-seong!
SHIN SO-YOON
Hae-seong!
Darling, we can be happy now!
-Open the door.
-So-yoon?
I'm really sorry. It's all my fault, okay?
-Hae-seong!
-Don't ever contact me again.
-No, I…
-Hae-seong, you're in there, right?
I really regret what I did. I mean it.
-Okay?
-Can you hear me?
-Come here and open the door!
-But I really am repenting…
We can be happy!
Hae-seong!
-The call cannot be connected…
-Darling!
Hae-seong, what we had was good.
It'll be even better now, okay?
Open the door, will you?
Right, I can have her instead.
Damn it.
Were you bitten on your arm?
Is the Internet working now?
Hae-seong! I'll share this with you.
-The passcode.
-Okay.
LOG IN
WELCOME TO OPBIT
Over here.
TOTAL ASSET
TOTAL PROFIT
The future still looks gloomy
for various economic indexes.
The stock markets all around the world
are dropping every day.
The number of stocks at its lowest price
exceeded 30 today.
The prices of oil, gold,
-Honey…
-and raw materials plummeted.
The national oil price is now…
The cure will be out someday, right?
It'll be out in no time.
Suddenly, the people
from the Community Health Center
could come to our house
and ring our doorbell.
The cryptocurrency market value today…
What…
What?
Mom, they're here! We're saved!
I told you they'd come, didn't I?
Careful.
We're saved!
Honey!
Thank you.
No, I didn't bite anybody.
I'm telling the truth.
I don't feel thirsty, either.
Give me water, then. I mean it.
I really don't feel thirsty.
I swear I didn't bite anybody.
He really was totally fine.
Maybe he's all better.
No, I'm sure he's all better.
Right, Soo-min?
I am. Because I'm not thirsty.
Nothing's wrong, right?
-I don't feel thirsty.
-Don't talk too much!
I'm telling the truth.
We found the holder of the antibody.
We're taking him now.
And I will take care of Yoon Sae-bom.
It's up to you.
Just bring the holder of the antibody.
Take him safely.
Find Yoon Sae-bom and Jung Yi-hyun
and take them to the dorm.
Yes, sir.
No!
This is our house!
What are you doing? No!
I said, stop!
Honey, what are they doing?
-No! This is our house!
-No!
No!
-This is our house!
-This is mine!
-No! I'm taking these!
-No! Let go!
-No! These are mine!
-This is our house!
-Let go!
-This is mine!
-No! This is our house!
-No!
I can't leave them here!
-I won't go!
-Let go!
-I'm taking them!
-This is our house!
-Those are mine!
-Honey! This is our house!
Stay here.
It's hot but you can't help it.
Don't you dare think that this is the end.
Sae-bom, you will vote for me, right?
I will.
Let's go.
We shouldn't leave…
Kim Se-hoon like that, right?
Let's put him in his house.
I'll open the door.
Call Yoon Sae-bom.
Drop your gun, Ms. Yoon.
Just shoot him.
It's okay if I get shot.
Drop your gun if you want
to save Jung Yi-hyun!
I'm fine, so just shoot!
Here, fresh blood.
Yi-hyun!
I told you I'll be the bad cop.
So you…
keep being the good cop.
Hey.
Hey!
Yi-hyun!
No!
Jung Yi-hyun!
CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
DEFENDANT
Mr. Lee Seung-young.
Careful.
Are you okay after all that running?
I'm totally fine.
Really?
Should we start some real workouts, then?
How about the gym?
All residents can work out there.
I have plans, so I have to go home now.
What?
Goodbye.
What plans?
Seo-yoon.
Now then, let's go.
What are you thinking about?
Last year, when we got locked up in here.
It was tough, wasn't it?
Still…
it was all right because I had you.
Since when did you start liking me?
From the very start, I told you.
Why won't you believe me?
I knew you were my destiny,
and we'd be together until the end.
So you never gave up?
Why do you think I became a cop?
Hey, did you become a cop because of me?
I thought about going to the US,
but what you said kept coming to mind.
You said there's no limit to our futures,
so I should just do it.
-But then you joined the SOU.
-Hey! I didn't know.
So are you happy?
Of course, I am.
When I'm with you.
-I'm not that happy without you.
-You liar.
The winner is exempt
from taking out the trash for one week!
You cheated! Hey!
And food waste too!
I won't lose!
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING HAPPINESS
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee