ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS,
EVENTS, AND OCCUPATIONS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Mr. Kim.
Mr. Jung.
Does Sae-bom have the antibody?
Unfortunately, she doesn't.
Then why did you suddenly call me?
Let Seo-yoon out.
We decided to accept minors
from the lockdown areas,
in terms of humanitarianism.
But it's dangerous out there too.
We'll keep her
in the safest place available.
But the problem is coming out
of the apartment complex.
Can I let Sae-bom go with her?
If you two come out together,
we're willing to accept you,
but you will have to cooperate
with what I'm doing.
I'll discuss it with Sae-bom and call you.
Do we have to keep the truth
from Mr. Jung too?
Don't you find it odd?
He asked if Yoon Sae-bom can go out too
while saying
it's dangerous outside as well.
He's someone who's willing
to come out himself if it's dangerous.
What are you doing?
Oh, this was at Seo-yoon's house.
I was a Jenga master when I was in school.
9th degree rank in Jenga.
Would you like to join us?
No, I have to go to the 15th floor,
so I'll play later.
Okay?
You mean to Sae-bom?
You saw her just now.
But I miss her,
even if I see her all the time.
Gross.
Yi-hyun, we have trouble.
What is it?
This.
It was on the table.
I did something wrong
that cannot be undone.
I tried to hold it in
by staying home,
but I don't think I can do that anymore.
I'm going to leave the apartments
and ask for help.
I'll leave the remaining food
and water for all the residents to share.
Here.
Don't they look different?
Well…
Your handwriting does change
when you're anxious.
We need a detective.
But can you believe it?
He's going to go outside and ask for help,
but we can share the food…
That's weird.
What did he mean by a wrongdoing
that can't be undone?
What can he do
when he doesn't leave his house?
Well, there is something.
The gym.
You're still thinking about that?
I told you, he's not someone
who'd take drugs.
What is this?
WHITE LIMESTONE
Does he grow a vegetable garden, too?
If you put it in the toilet,
it blocks the odor.
I'm in the SOU, you know.
-I used it during outdoor drills.
-Right.
What's going on?
He does have a lot of medicine.
But these drugs are all authorized.
It's Next.
-Seriously, this place is…
-What?
What the heck? You two were in there.
-What's the house owner doing?
-Why are you here?
We're here to finish
yesterday's conversation.
We're all struggling now, so…
-You received something.
-This is…
We live in the same building,
so we should help each other.
We're talking to him,
so please wait.
There's no sign of trespassing,
but we found Next.
"Something that cannot be undone."
Maybe that means he's infected.
I don't know.
He takes selfies and he's always happy.
Even if he was infected,
he'd just stay home.
There's no way
that homebody would've gone outside.
Then where would he be?
Someone…
must've locked him up.
What about his note, then?
He wrote that because he was threatened.
Or maybe not.
He's not in the building,
and the lobby door is unlocked.
He might've really gone outside.
But there are soldiers everywhere outside.
He's rich. He might have paid someone
to unlock the door for him.
Come on, open the door, please!
Sir!
I don't hear anything. Are you in there?
What are you doing?
You're here too.
Everyone asked me for help.
I heard he has a lot of water,
so wouldn't it be nice to share some?
I know, right?
So we just want to talk to him.
Someone saw him going outside too,
so we must check if he's infected as well.
-Who saw him?
-Me.
I saw him going out early in the morning.
Really?
Are you sure it was Kim Se-hoon?
I couldn't see his face,
but he's the only person
who wears a quarantine suit.
I'm sorry,
but we do need a plan
because we're short on water.
And the people on the 2nd floor
put a ridiculous price on it.
Gosh.
So you had the key too.
They even brought out
a shopping bag with something in it!
It's mine, okay?
Oh, my goodness.
He said to share the things in his house.
So the house owner gave permission.
Then why didn't you say anything earlier?
More than that,
what's "something that cannot be undone?"
Did he have legal problems?
Anyway, it's a finders-keepers situation.
Honey, take this water first.
Take it.
-Let go.
-Please calm down.
Let's share some of the food first.
Not all of them. Just some of them.
We don't know when he'll be back.
And leave some for those who aren't here.
Who are you to decide that?
All right!
Call the others! Tell them to come!
Detective, look at this!
Call everyone!
I said, call them! I got it!
Let me go! Come on!
It's heavy.
I'm glad we got water.
Let's turn this light on
in the bathroom too.
What are you so displeased about?
Hey, we only got this much.
That place had lots
of survival equipment too.
Still, the detective
on the 5th floor divided it fairly.
Hey, did you say "fair?"
If he really wanted to be fair,
he should've given us more!
Those who paid more
to get in here should get more stuff!
Isn't that common sense?
You're talking nonsense.
Right. That's true.
By the way, that guy on the 5th floor…
Wasn't he weird today?
He was stuck to his wife's side like glue.
I guess he loves her very much.
You love me very much too, right?
Hey, it's hot. Get off me.
But there was a lot of food there, right?
Yes.
The house was big,
and it had a lot of weird things too.
What are you looking at?
What brings you two here?
It's about Unit 1501.
The owner left all his stuff behind.
It's a waste to leave them there.
The residents are suffering
from a shortage of necessities.
Hey, leave us.
Are you telling me to go out?
Then should I go out?
Stay outside.
Hurry!
Come in.
So Kim Se-hoon went outside, right?
I think so.
He's not in the building. That's for sure.
He must've been lonely.
I saw it on TV.
There's this thing called solitary death.
He has neither family nor friends,
so that must be why he went outside.
My mom and dad are together,
so they'd be okay, right?
Of course.
We would've been lonely too
if we didn't have you, Seo-yoon.
Your cute dimple!
Thanks.
Isn't it spicy?
You're good
at eating spicy food, Seo-yoon.
You dipped that much?
Isn't it spicy?
It's okay.
It looks spicy.
Mr. Kim.
What?
Yi-hyun isn't here.
When did he go outside?
I don't know.
Do you miss him
even if you see him all the time?
Go back to sleep.
I've been there, so I know.
Will you marry me?
I wanted to have herringbone flooring,
but it's new flooring,
so I can't rip it out.
Still, this is neat.
I can't believe this.
I have a house now.
I thought I was left alone.
Hey.
Where have you been?
Why aren't you sleeping?
-Well…
-Does the walkie-talkie work?
Give it to me.
Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok.
Lieutenant Colonel Han.
Hey, Han Tae-seok!
I'm sure he's asleep.
What did he say?
Do I have the antibody?
You don't.
I knew it.
I've never even gotten 5th in the lottery.
Still, I'm glad that I didn't get
the disease at least.
Hey, did your wound open?
No, it got much better.
No, it didn't.
It'll be awful if it gets infected.
I…
It does look much better, but…
I told you. I'm a human vitamin
and a human antibiotic.
You don't have additional injuries, right?
If you do, tell me. Okay?
Okay.
Good.
What did Han Tae-seok say?
He told us to let Seo-yoon out.
He said they'll take her in.
-Really?
-Yes.
So?
I told him I'll discuss it with you.
Wouldn't it be dangerous outside?
So I was thinking…
Why don't you go outside with her?
If you're with Seo-yoon,
I'm sure she'll feel relieved too.
We should all go out together.
And you should get some antibiotics too.
I think…
it's better for Seo-yoon
not to go outside for now.
We need to know
what it's really like out there.
Right.
Is Kim Se-hoon outside?
Not officially,
but he said he'll look into it
since someone could've helped him.
I thought about it, and…
He may be in here.
But we checked everywhere in the building.
There's one place we didn't check.
He tried to go outside,
but he got scared of soldiers
and the infected, so he came back in.
He's hiding in here now.
I'm sure he doesn't know
the passcode, though.
Still, we have to check.
Sae-bom.
KIM SE-HOON, UNIT 1501
Did you enjoy it?
Of course, I did.
You two.
Stop it and come out.
You just need to keep that in mind.
I was giving some legal consultation.
Don't do that in places
where there are no people.
Legal consultation.
You may run into the infected
if you wander around secretly.
Will you keep this a secret?
Mr. Lawyer, you should tell the truth.
Once trust is broken,
your relationship can't last long.
Can we go now?
You two.
Don't ever come here again.
Wait.
Don't forget to take this.
That's not ours.
Mr. Kim.
Mr. Kim?
Can you hear me?
Are you doing this
because you feel thirsty?
-This powder…
-It's limestone.
It was at Kim Se-hoon's house.
Mr. Oh.
You're a real doctor, right?
Come out. You need to take
a look at someone.
But my license got suspended.
Who is it? Who's sick?
You'll know once you come.
We know nothing. We're serious.
We were just having a legal consultation.
You don't need to talk about that anymore.
Just tell us about
the situation when you got in here.
Didn't you feel anything strange?
Well, I don't remember.
Didn't you go into the master bedroom?
We did go in there, but…
You see…
It smelled like cement,
and flies were buzzing in there,
so we stepped out.
If we knew there was a corpse,
we wouldn't have stayed here.
You're not suspecting us, are you?
I'm a lawyer. Please keep in mind
that I'm not that stupid.
What about Jung-kook?
I told him what happened.
He'll bring people.
What are you doing here?
This way.
Wait here for a moment.
DO NOT ENTER, RISK OF INFECTION!
What are you looking at?
Whenever I see this,
I feel a bit more relaxed.
I can't be a shameful father to my kids.
I only looked at this,
but the battery's running out.
Here.
Hey, don't you need this
to write your novel?
I have paper and a pencil.
That's what's good about being a writer.
It doesn't cost money.
Thanks.
All I do is receive stuff from you.
I'm so ashamed as your older brother.
Hyun-kyung, even so…
if something bad happens to me,
then please look after my family.
No way.
Just think of getting out of here safely.
Hey, you know I'm ill.
I'm begging you, so please…
You seem much better now.
Hi.
You gave us food last time.
I'm repaying you for that.
What? What's all this?
What?
By the way, is it okay
to give us all this?
Of course. It's all mine.
You two were here.
Well…
You should come with me to the 11th floor.
Why? What happened?
You see…
Someone died.
What? Who?
Why would you do this to me
when I've just woken up?
That really scared me. Jeez.
But you're the only doctor
in this building.
Then you should've told me
what was in there.
Wait.
What? Did you suspect me?
Did you make me go into that room
because you thought I killed her?
That doesn't seem to be the case.
Well, you're so good at lying.
You think I'm a murderer?
Forget it.
Just tell us
your opinion as a doctor.
She was obviously bitten to death.
Her neck was completely torn.
It stinks.
Can't you tell us something
more professional?
Professional?
Judging by the blood coagulation
and rigidity of the body,
it's been more than two days
since she died.
The killer tried to get rid
of the smell with limestone.
It's that limestone
from the 15th floor, right?
Damn it. These flies…
These things come first when a human dies.
They lay eggs in their eyes and nose.
This is why it's better to be alive
even if your life's a mess.
Go out there and explain it to the people.
And don't talk about the flies.
That scared the crap out of me. Darn it.
By the way, did those two
find the body first?
Together?
It's a misunderstanding.
I felt weird, so I asked him to come here.
Because the cleaning lady
was crying in my dreams…
-I mean it.
-Right. Of course.
Don't.
It's okay.
I'm really okay,
but I'm worried about the lawyer.
Your wife will be really shocked,
won't she?
That superpower jerk
stabbed us in the back!
Detective, Andrew took our food
and ran away!
He's been caught in the act!
Don't you have to arrest him right away?
Please calm down.
Someone died.
That's not important right now.
The food is gone!
The cleaning lady
who was at your house died!
Ms. Lee Deok-soon!
What…
Seriously.
I checked the body,
and it looks like the infected did it.
Her neck was bitten.
It must be the man on the 15th floor.
It was written on the note.
"Something wrong that cannot be undone."
Right.
That was a confession.
That means we can share
the remaining food, right?
We don't have evidence saying
that Kim Se-hoon did it.
Who else can it be, then?
There aren't
any other infected people here.
Now, when you take a look at it…
If there's a victim and a runaway,
we naturally know who the culprit is.
Mr. Jung, you're a detective,
so you'd know, right?
We need to investigate more.
Especially about how the victim left
the second floor and was found here.
We will hear more from you two
as the witnesses later.
Honey.
The corpse was really scary.
Unit 1102 is a crime scene,
so no one's allowed in there.
We changed the passcode too.
So keep that in mind.
When will you give out the food?
That bastard Andrew
took ours and ran away!
Sae-bom, Yi-hyun.
Mr. Ahn and the writer are here.
It's so damn far away.
-What happened?
-Did the cleaning lady really pass away?
You damn thief!
How could you do this?
-Stop it.
-Let go! You jerk!
Honey, are you trying to kill him?
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
Hey!
Young-in.
The symptoms won't stop.
-What about the tranquilizer?
-We injected the maximum amount.
Her body won't be able
to hold out anymore.
Do we have samples
of the plasma cure we made?
There's one,
but the higher-ups are taking it.
They told us to submit everything
being tested.
Lieutenant Colonel.
Didn't you say you'll keep it
a secret from Ms. Yoon?
If we take the cure now,
the higher-ups will notice it's important.
I know that.
Leave it here.
Lower your gun.
Lower your gun!
Please calm down.
We're all on the same side,
and Lieutenant Colonel
Han Tae-seok is in charge here.
Ask the Prime Minister's office.
He's doing what he needs to do.
Get out of the way.
Check her condition,
and report right away
if there's a problem.
What happened just now…
The higher-ups will find out.
Also, that you kept it
a secret from Ms. Yoon.
We just need to report it first.
-What?
-Report to the higher-ups
that she has the antibody.
And that we confirmed it
by testing it on my wife's body.
Then…
Tell them I'll take
Yoon Sae-bom out tomorrow.
It will only buy some time.
They will suspect you.
That's what I need.
Time.
Andrew is the last witness.
No one else saw her after him.
So the estimated time of death
is around that time too?
It means she was killed
on her way upstairs.
But…
Do you think Kim Se-hoon really did this?
Sae-bom, give me some water.
I'm thirsty.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
I'm getting a lot of exercise here.
I'm thirsty.
I'm so thirsty. Thanks.
Where are the other residents?
They're asking why we're doing nothing
when it's obvious who the killer is.
They said we should
just break into Unit 1501
and share the rest of the things in there.
Let's go. If we do nothing,
they'll get more agitated.
But I just sat down…
We're only sharing the food.
You can't take anything else.
And we'll leave some, just in case.
We'll give them out to each of you,
so come in one by one.
Come in.
They said everyone gets a portion.
-Shouldn't we get Andrew's portion?
-We can just take it.
We take Andrew's portion too, right?
We can take it.
But shouldn't they give
Andrew's portion to us?
Why didn't they give it to us?
He took so much!
I won't let this slide. Just wait and see.
Gosh, how could he
take everything like that?
Is Dong-hyun here?
What?
He was here, but he left.
I carried all this heavy stuff by myself.
Seriously…
So-yoon…
I really was just giving
that woman legal consultation
in a quiet place…
Stop it.
I'm sick of hearing that.
Can I really stay here?
Only for a while.
Don't wander around.
The man on the 2nd floor
is out to get you.
But he won't come up here
to the 15th floor.
This place is too far away.
Thank you.
I'll stay here only until Mr. Kim returns.
Well, if he does return.
Get some rest.
And take those goggles off
when you're alone.
It's uncomfortable, isn't it?
Try to stay inside.
Seo-yoon.
Seo-yoon, what's wrong?
Do you have chest pain?
What's wrong?
I just coughed.
If I do this for a bit, it gets better.
But why were you hiding like that?
Don't you have medicine for it?
I get a shot if I go to the hospital,
but it hurts a lot.
I just need to cough a bit.
It'd be better to let Seo-yoon out, right?
It may be dangerous,
but they have doctors and medicine.
I'll talk to Han Tae-seok about it.
Don't worry.
I'm sure my husband
would want me to do something
for this apartment too.
He was worried about all of you
until his last moments.
You all know…
that the infected killed
the cleaning lady, right?
They may still be inside,
so please be careful.
Do your best to stay at home,
and if you need to move,
stay in groups of two or more.
We should discuss securing
the doors of this building
and distinguishing
the infected from now on.
In the case of my husband…
If we had found out a bit earlier…
It's important to actively find
the infected.
And persuade those
who are not coming out
of their houses to test them.
Yes.
Right, we have to find the infected.
Whose blood should we use today?
Should we draw straws?
I think you should just do it.
No.
A doctor should do it.
So you can treat yourself when you bleed!
Get away from me!
Hey, stop!
Don't do this!
-Someone will get hurt!
-Stop it!
Someone will get hurt for real!
Stop this, will you?
More than that,
shouldn't we discuss food and water first?
If you have any ideas, please tell us.
We're going outside.
If Kim Se-hoon really did go outside,
that means there's a way out.
So we're going to go outside
and see if we can get food or water.
There's emergency power
down in the basement.
Rather than going outside,
if you go down
and turn on that emergency power,
the electricity will come back on,
so we can cook,
and the water will start again too.
Building 103 has EPS,
Emergency Power Supply,
in the electrical room
under the senior citizens' center.
It's made to turn on
emergency lights for elevators.
If you turn on the general power,
the electricity and water
will be turned on.
But honestly, I'm more worried that
you could just go outside
and never return.
Right, that's true.
Mr. Detective,
you're close to that military man.
Like Mr. Oh said, it'd be better
to take care of things here first.
Let's do that.
We'll go down and turn on
the emergency power.
Mr. Oh.
How did you know
about the emergency power?
Anyone who lives
in an apartment knows that.
I know you hate me,
but this is a time of emergency.
So take a look at things with
a broader point of view and cooperate.
We should live
like civilized human beings.
Are we really going
to the electrical room?
It sounds a bit fishy, but it's necessary.
That's true, but…
It's a chance to let Seo-yoon out too.
Let's send her out
before we go down to the electrical room.
What should we tell her, though?
We can keep that a secret.
She may refuse if we say
that she's getting out alone.
That's true.
She's actually quite mature, so…
Going down is one thing,
but how will we come up?
Remember how he said
it's really noisy when it's turned on?
The infected will rush toward us
when they hear the noise.
And they'll chase us here.
If the entrance is breached,
it can get more dangerous.
Then we can come up using a different way.
Let's go.
Get some more sleep.
Get the infiltration team ready.
If they don't call by morning,
we're going in.
There are a lot of severe variant patients
in the apartment.
If we go in without any arrangements,
there will be casualties.
We just need Yoon Sae-bom safe.
Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok.
Have you decided?
I will let Sae-bom…
and Seo-yoon out.
They will be at the underground
parking lot at 1:00 p.m.,
so get ready to take them.
What about you? Aren't you coming?
Someone has to stay and watch the house.
We may have disagreed with one another,
but I know that you sincerely
tried to stop Mad Human Disease.
Please help us
so Sae-bom
and Seo-yoon can live safely.
Jung Yi-hyun is infected.
That's why he's trying
to let Yoon Sae-bom out.
See?
Let's play one more round.
You want to play again?
Until I win.
-Yi-hyun.
-What?
Let's talk for a minute.
I talked to Han Tae-seok,
and the soldiers are coming
to the underground parking lot.
We can go down to the electrical room
after we send Seo-yoon out.
You have eye boogers again.
We talked about this already.
We promised to tell each other
when we're sick.
If I get infected, feel thirsty,
and want to bite people too,
then I will make sure to tell you.
So…
you should also tell me
if anything happens.
Are you okay?
Of course, I'm okay. Why?
Are you worried
my wound might be infected?
I thought about it,
and the wound
on your palm healed too quickly.
You don't drink water, either.
It does look much better, but…
I told you. I'm a human vitamin
and a human antibiotic.
It's not like that.
It still sores like crazy.
I'll show you.
Look.
I was shocked seeing Lee Deok-soon's body,
so I must've not known
that it burst again.
Thank goodness.
I was worried sick, you know.
Then you should've told me.
Why were you worried?
How can I not be worried? We have no cure.
What if the wound gets infected?
I told you to be careful.
Okay, I'll be careful from now on.
Hey.
Lieutenant Colonel Han,
I know you're there.
Prepare lots of antibiotics,
disinfectants, and bandages.
Yi-hyun is injured.
We will prepare them.
I'm so glad to hear your voice.
What about Kim Se-hoon?
You have to be careful.
He may be infected.
Kim Se-hoon isn't outside.
He may still be there, so be careful.
Once he tastes human blood,
he'll continue to target and hunt people.
Thank you.
Let's look for Kim Se-hoon again.
Sure.
Mr. Kim, don't open the door
for just anyone.
Kim Se-hoon may still be inside.
Okay, don't worry.
I have my gun.
-We'll be back.
-Okay.
Kim Se-hoon may still be here.
People can even make bunkers.
He may have a secret space in his house.
But even so…
He may be hiding in here.
We don't even know
the structure of this place.
Andrew.
Why don't we investigate
after letting Seo-yoon out?
What if someone gets hurt again?
I'll go down and look for Andrew.
You look around here.
Okay.
Ms. Yoon, can you hear me?
First Lieutenant, I'm happy
to hear from you, but…
I'm a bit busy right now.
Ms. Yoon, this is something important.
We got the background check results
for those in the apartment,
and something's weird.
Ahn Kook-jin was found dead in his house.
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD: AHN KOOK-JIN
I erased it.
Administrative work is on hold
due to Mad Human Disease.
It took a while
for the report to reach us.
What about his face?
Does he have scars?
No, not at all.
Are you in danger?
It'll take four to five hours
to get there,
so wait at your house.
We'll go and take care of things.
Ms. Yoon, are you listening?
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD: KIM SE-HOON
LEE DEOK-SOON
I found…
Kim Se-hoon.
Wait.
Take your time. Relax, okay?
What is it?
I saw Kim Se-hoon.
Open the door. He may come after me.
Wait, did he get the disease?
I'll tell you if I need help,
so wait there.
What are you doing? It's your turn.
What do you think you're doing?
My husband…
died because of you two.
Jung-kook!
Jung-kook! Wake up!
It's me. I'm here.
Who are you?
I have an offer for you.
There's a way
to get rid of those we don't like.
I know who you are.
Go turn the electricity on.
Then I will let Seo-yoon
and that detective out.
The infected will swarm in!
We will get out of here alive,
and we will arrest all of them.
Block it again after Ms. Yoon comes out.
Jung Yi-hyun is infected.
Tell them to fire.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee