ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS,
EVENTS, AND OCCUPATIONS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Hey, what is this place?
Is this a military base?
Why are we here?
Sae-bom is here.
Then you should've dropped me off earlier!
I have to give out rice cakes!
Damn it.
Do you want one?
I'd like that.
STOP
WONJUNG DORMITORY
Now!
No, don't open it!
Check if other vehicles are locked, and…
-We have to get Seung-young out.
-What?
He was fine until a moment ago!
Seung-young!
Are you okay?
Yi-hyun.
How did you get here?
I'm glad I wasn't too late.
Open your mouth.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I did that either.
I felt it was too unfair to die in vain,
so I wanted to do something at least.
Did something happen in there?
I went inside,
and everyone in there…
was completely mad.
I saw that.
Sae-bom.
What if I end up like that?
My wife and my kids…
I'm disappointed in you, First Lieutenant.
Ms. Yoon Sae-bom.
Five of our fellow soldiers got infected
while trying to take care of them.
What else could we do?
How did you know
a flash grenade would work?
Those soldiers must have had
a reason for carrying them around.
They weren't suppressing
a terrorist attack.
They were watching the infected.
Some of the infected
tried to escape from the facility.
That's when I found out.
So you lock them up
and wait until they die?
What else can we do?
They lost their minds, and they only want
the fresh blood of healthy people.
Shall we offer them living sacrifices?
But aren’t they living human beings?
You should hold out, no matter what.
We're holding out the best we can.
We protect those with mild symptoms
and put severe patients into quarantine.
Listen, Mr. Han.
What if that happens to your family?
Be honest.
You're seeing those people as monsters.
You're shooting them
without any guilt at all.
Do you know what we learned
through COVID-19?
What, that we should wash our hands often?
It's that living our lives
is more important
than a few people biting
and killing each other.
I'm holding out as much as I can
to protect my family.
How long are you going
to do this in secret?
You should reveal this to the public
and discuss what to do with the infected.
I am going to do that.
The media is already getting suspicious.
Hurry up and do it.
If not, I'm going to reveal everything.
And let's try not to see each other again.
And…
they're holding out too,
as much as they can.
SCAN QR CODE FOR CHECK-IN AND PAYMENT
PREVENT INFECTIOUS DISEASES
FROM SPREADING
I can finally breathe now.
I saved up money
and planned to go on a trip.
I can't believe this is happening.
Give me your hand.
Hey, it's almost healed.
It's going to sting.
Is it okay for me to be
the only one who's fine?
I'm relieved that at least you're fine.
The cure and the vaccine will be out soon.
This outbreak will pass by
in the end.
So don't worry.
Will those people
be able to go back too?
I hope they can.
Oh, hi.
Did you ask about the T-shirt? Size large.
I was a bit busy today,
so I'll bring it next time.
Hi.
Mom, she's the SOU lady
who lives next door.
Hi, I heard you looked after Seo-yoon.
Thank you.
It was nothing.
Wasn't that place nice?
Your husband?
He's handsome.
SEYANG HIGH SCHOOL BASEBALL TEAM
Found it.
All right.
Are you okay?
It's just…
It feels weird to be back
to everyday life so easily.
Should we just do it later?
No, we're doing this
to protect our daily lives.
Let's do this.
By the way, will she believe
that we're getting married?
Of course. She'll think
we're madly in love, so don't worry.
First, chamomile. It warms you up.
-Do I look okay?
-Yes.
You didn't even see me.
Okay, let me see.
You look nice. You look pretty.
But who would think that
we're getting married for an apartment?
Everyone would obviously think
we love each other.
Sae-bom.
Hi, ma'am.
I knew you two would end up together
when I first saw you.
You looked so cute
when you were sitting
in that ambulance together.
What? That picture is from that day.
It's so we won't forget our feelings.
Sae-bom, there's something
I want to say to you.
Yes, go ahead.
Son, can you please excuse us?
I have something to tell Sae-bom.
Tell me later.
I'll relay the message to her.
Do you guys have noise issues?
Goodness, that's troublesome.
Go tell them to be quiet.
Go ahead, ma'am.
Sae-bom, thank you so much.
Thanks to you,
Yi-hyun is living a normal life.
Ma'am, Yi-hyun has always
been a great guy.
He's nice,
but he loses his temper sometimes.
After he became unable
to play baseball anymore,
he hung out with bad kids.
So we tried to immigrate to the US,
but he said he wouldn't go
because he couldn't speak English.
It seems being a detective is
the perfect job for him.
He catches bad guys too.
I was wondering what was
going on at this late hour.
-I'm sorry.
-I'm not trying to get an apology.
I'm really worried, that's why.
Are you sure it's nothing?
Well, it's…
Hi.
We live downstairs, and it's a bit noisy.
I'm sorry.
What…
I couldn't tell you yesterday,
but my wife is ill.
She keeps throwing things and yelling.
Then who is she?
She's a consultant
at my wife's dermatology clinic,
and she came to help us
because she's worried.
My wife took a sleeping pill,
so she'll be fine.
Does she bite or scratch by any chance?
It's not that bad. She just gets
sensitive from time to time.
We won't cause any more noise. I'm sorry.
What is it?
Well…
What's the name
of that dermatology clinic?
I think we have to hold a wedding too.
But who's going to officiate it?
Jung-kook?
That does sound reasonable.
But can he speak well
in front of a lot of people?
No.
We can just go out there and say hi,
and say that we will live well together.
That sounds good too.
Seung-young is a good singer,
so it'd be great
if he can get better by then.
Do we have to go on a honeymoon too?
Where should we go?
Where you always wanted to go.
Hey, what if I ask for a buffet tour
for our honeymoon, then?
I can't leave until I eat
at least ten plates per buffet.
Excuse me, I was a baseball player.
I eat so much it's scary.
Thinking of food makes me hungry.
Let's go to sleep.
Right, good night.
-You too.
-Okay.
Patients of the so-called
Mad Human Disease,
which makes them bite people
and drink blood, are increasing in number,
but the government still states
that the existence of the disease
-has not been confirmed yet.
-Honey.
-In the meantime…
-Honey!
We don't have money for that!
Then are we going to just live like this?
What are you going to do if she collapses?
Why do you have to be so pessimistic?
She's been okay until now.
She just needs to maintain her condition.
We're already being discriminated against.
What if people hear about her illness?
I'm going to our next-door lady.
We can say she's studying abroad,
and go quietly.
No one would know.
Honey.
How would we get that money?
Hi. It's me, Seo-yoon.
Hi. We have some rice cakes left.
Want some?
Is it okay for me to eat it?
Love has its times of crisis too.
It must have been a serious crisis.
Where's your husband?
He went to work.
He said he got orders from higher-ups.
SKIN AND HAIR DERMATOLOGY CLINIC
DIRECTOR PARK MIN-JI
-Hello?
-Hello.
Is Director Park Min-ji there?
Director Park is on vacation for a week.
We accept appointments
with her starting next week.
Then is the consultant on vacation, too?
Consultant? Which consultant
are you talking about?
She has long hair down to her waist,
and she has double eyelids…
Ms. Woo Sang-hee? She took the day off.
Here she comes. Hang on.
What is it?
Do you want dermatology treatment?
Our upstairs neighbors were irritating so…
Noise issues?
That drives you nuts.
By the way, the car wash…
They told us to stop investigating it.
Our Chief said some other department
is taking care of it.
Han Tae-seok?
Are you sure this is okay?
Isn't it a dangerous disease?
MS. KIM BOK-NAM
Hey, Mom. What's up?
Are you okay?
I heard you got tested
for Mad Human Disease.
I'm okay. They said it's not serious.
But still, I have to be
in self-quarantine for a while…
Turn on the TV.
It's total chaos right now.
Is anyone there?
They're not humans. None of them are.
The footage you just watched
was obtained exclusively by us.
I repeat.
This footage, exclusively obtained
by our broadcasting station,
was recorded by an anonymous informant
who snuck into
a secret government facility
and filmed this with his phone.
-Are you watching the news?
-The disease
that was only treated as
a rumor by the government,
Mad Human Disease,
which makes patients bite people
and drink blood, does exist.
-The government may be concealing this.
-I'll call you later.
This is the only evidence we have for now.
The informant has been out of reach
after sending us the video.
Our reporters are now
doing their best to find out
what has happened to the informant.
Damn it.
What is this?
We just opened our shop.
Are they going to restrict
gatherings again?
I just want to bite everyone!
-Send me to a hospital.
-You just said it's COVID-19.
It's Mad Human Disease!
Don't say anything dangerous.
Take it easy.
Are you okay?
Hey, where are you going?
You have to get tested!
The hospital.
The order will get mixed up…
Are you going camping?
There aren't many people here
despite the emergency texts.
We get emergency texts every day,
so we can't react to them every time.
Unless some people die
and about 1,000 are tested positive.
Would you like us to deliver them for you?
-Just the water and rice, please.
-Okay.
ANNOUNCEMENT
A RESIDENT IS BREAKING DOWN DOORS
That's me.
What's going on?
I'm the building representative.
I live in Unit 1202.
I censored your face
to protect your privacy.
Please be careful from now on.
What if there's a fire
when that door is blocked?
That door is called a firewall, you know.
So the fire won't spread.
But what if you leave it open?
Then the fire will spread.
But you should just close it.
You shouldn't block it.
We'll be trapped in a fire.
It's a decision made
by the apartment's fire safety manager.
The fire safety manager
must be from an outsourcing company.
And that's their official opinion, right?
Who are you?
I live in Unit 401.
A public rental…
You know the doctor
who lives in Unit 601, right?
She's having a hard time
because of people randomly visiting.
Her husband said she canceled
her appointments and is lying sick in bed.
Did they say that?
When they were
stomping like that last night?
Young lady, the noise
doesn't follow certain directions.
We don't know
which unit is making the noise.
Don't fight, and come to church.
God knows everything.
The lady in Unit 601
must be having a hard time.
She needs to depend on God.
Then she will find peace.
She has her husband,
so I'm sure she'll be okay.
I'll talk to them about the emergency door
being bent and let it slide.
Thanks a lot.
-Oh, you're carrying a lot.
-Thank you.
Hi.
Is the Director still sick?
Yes, she's going to rest for a while,
so she told me to get her stuff.
She must be quitting.
You brought all her stuff.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm from the police.
Think carefully
before you answer my questions.
What's going on
in that house right now?
Is your wife really okay?
Yes, I'll admit her to the hospital today,
so please be patient.
What is this?
Did you get bitten?
Did your wife bite you?
Ma'am!
What are you doing?
Why are you entering my house
without permission?
Trespassing is illegal!
Report me, then.
I'm from downstairs.
-Are you okay?
-Don't do that. Don't!
How long has she been like this?
Since a few days ago.
She attacks people.
I was thinking of calling
a psychiatrist friend of mine.
What about her eyes?
Her eyes were white.
The disease isn't always active,
so since the noise stopped,
she might be normal right now.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, it's okay.
You can get better.
Your husband is worried
so please come out…
Sir!
Ma'am.
Please calm down.
Hello? 911?
It looks like my wife
has Mad Human Disease,
and the lady downstairs
seems to be in danger.
-Do you want to get out?
-This is Unit 601, Building 101…
-I'll open the door for you.
-Seyang. That's the address.
No. Unit 601, Building 101.
No, listen to me!
It's Building 101, not 102!
Please hurry and send them.
It really is an emergency!
Please hurry!
Someone could die!
Please hurry! Please!
Come on! It's urgent!
Please…
Hey.
Min-ji.
Hey, Min-ji!
Damn it!
-Hey, Sae-bom.
-What is it?
Don't go upstairs, even if they're loud.
I'm upstairs already.
I'm fine but the couple from that house…
Mister! No one's home…
Mister!
Seo-yoon! Run! Now!
Someone, help!
Are you okay?
Yes, I think so.
What's wrong with her?
She's just very angry, that's all.
It's okay.
Her husband is over there.
Hey.
You live downstairs, right?
Is everyone okay?
Are you okay?
You're lucky that I'm the one who hit you.
If it was Sae-bom, you would be dead.
Breathe.
Over here.
He must be shocked by his wife's injury.
You should have seen it
with your own eyes.
We need weapons.
No, not gas pistols.
Something more powerful.
Are you just leaving?
Aren't you doing anything else?
We're going to disinfect this place.
Refrain from going outside,
and please follow
the government's instructions.
Mom, let's go.
NOTICE ON DELAY IN DELIVERY
Honey.
Honey?
Honey, today…
Where have you been?
You haven't made me food!
Well…
-Everyone!
-Oh, Dong-hyun.
I told you that the green candle
is proof of external forces.
-Dong-hyun.
-You shouldn't just buy
bio-themed shares
because of Mad Human Disease.
All right?
Dong-hyun, I was on the sixth floor today…
Mom, can't you see I'm streaming?
Later, okay?
-Hey.
-My mom is a bit dull.
Here is the announcement
on Mad Human Disease.
Our organization has found out
that there were patients
biting people at nursing homes
and homeless facilities,
and while analyzing the patients,
we found out that Mad Human Disease
really does exist.
Based on the analysis, it's assumed
to be a type of mutated virus.
Once the disease occurs,
the patients only attack humans,
try to bite their necks,
and claim to have extreme thirst
before the symptoms occur.
If you have any of these symptoms
or find someone who shows such symptoms,
please call the CDSCHQ's
main number right away.
He's famous now. He's even on TV.
He didn't talk about
the quarantine of the infected.
Because Mad Human Disease
itself is shocking news.
For now, how you get infected
and when the cure
will come out will be the main topic.
Hey, more than that…
Don't go into someone else's house alone.
Tell me first.
I was going to.
I was going to check
if it was the disease and call 911.
By the way, that woman upstairs…
She only chased her husband.
I'm sure there's something about her.
He didn't push me by mistake either.
I'll look into it,
and if there's anything, I'll arrest him.
Okay.
It's great having a detective friend.
Of course.
Want to go for a walk?
We have never gone out together
since we came here.
Are you going outside?
Yes, what's wrong?
I'd like to ask you to keep
what happened today a secret.
Don't post it online or spread any rumors.
But a lot of people saw it.
What can we do?
They're all residents of our apartment.
It's hard for outsiders to come inside.
We just have to keep quiet
and make it so it's no big deal.
Would that really make it no big deal?
Bad rumors don't help with house prices.
You're thinking of house prices right now?
You're going to live here
for ten more years, at least.
Wouldn't it be better for you two as well
to say that you live
in an expensive apartment?
The building representative is right.
It's absolute chaos outside,
but it's peaceful here.
I'm sure they want to enjoy
their house prices
and happiness in here.
Even by getting rid of the infected.
I am so damn thankful
for what you did earlier today.
Did they tell you to go home?
The results were clean, so they
told me to self-quarantine at home.
So please understand
even if it's noisy at night.
You will be quarantined in jail soon.
So don't worry.
Jail?
When my quarantine is over,
I'm suing you first!
You messed with the wrong person!
I'm the master of lawsuits
and accusations!
This was found at the infected's house.
It looks like your people took care
of the car wash dealers too.
Those drugs cause
Mad Human Disease, right?
I'm sure you didn't come
all the way here to ask that.
Is Ms. Park Min-ji here?
I'd like to meet her now.
Be careful.
Ms. Park Min-ji.
Shouldn't she have returned
to normal by now?
She's supposed to be dead by now.
The disease occurred just before she died,
and she's alive, thanks to the virus.
Then if she turns back to normal…
She'll die.
Her mind has turned into a huge mess.
Perhaps she's in that condition
because she knows that too.
Perhaps it's because she's resentful,
and she wants to reveal who killed her.
Ms. Park Min-ji.
Don't worry.
I swear I'll catch the asshole
who did this to you.
Damn it.
I'm late, aren't I?
I had a lot of things to take care of.
What is this place?
A place to lock up guard dogs,
to borrow your expression.
Your friends are back there.
Don't wake them up.
An ordinary woman in
an ordinary apartment got the disease,
and this was found at her house.
Seyang Forest Le Ciel…
is your territory, right?
If I tell you…
will you let me go?
Why do you think you're here?
If…
If you promise you won't kill me,
I'll tell you everything.
If you truly want something,
you won't surrender to thirst.
So…
think carefully…
about what you really want.
Aren't you going to cook?
How long are you going
to be lying on the sofa?
I have no energy.
Maybe from shock because of yesterday.
You're so weak.
Goodness.
I'm going to eat outside.
Honey, I want a hamburger.
You should eat rice!
Bread can't make a good meal!
My goodness. Unbelievable.
Hello?
Ms. Park Min-ji died just now.
She was all blank in the end,
not attacking anyone.
Thank you for letting me know.
Here's the NFS report.
Let's go.
Now? Will it be okay?
It's not even certain yet.
There's someone who can help us.
Hey, be careful!
If we can't catch him after doing that,
it'll be troublesome!
We're from the police.
Excuse us.
Why are you all just
pushing yourselves in?
How can both you and your wife be so rude?
Ms. Park Min-ji…
is dead.
She…
She suffered her whole life…
What?
Why? What is it?
Goodness, you must have cleaned
the house more after that.
I hate the smell of blood,
and I'm worried about the virus.
So I cleaned. Why?
By the way,
did you clean the golf club too?
Your wife's head was
almost completely crushed.
The part where you hit her
with a golf club, Mr. Oh Joo-hyung.
It was self-defense.
She was trying to bite me.
What else could I do?
If it wasn't for Mad Human Disease,
you would've gotten what you wanted.
-Right?
-What?
She was supposed to die
when you hit her with a golf club,
but the disease suddenly occurred,
and she didn't die.
If it wasn't for that,
you'd have been able to discard the body
and make it a perfect crime.
Perfect crime? What are you talking about?
This is the NFS report
on the bloodstain from the golf club.
"A hard blow by an adult male
with all his strength."
"Occipital bone fragments
and cerebral tissues found."
"The weapon was swung
with the intention of murder."
I told you, I was scared.
She was trying to bite me
with her eyes all white.
If you were me, would you just
get bitten to death by your wife?
Do you love your wife that much?
So I looked into your trial records too.
You really are something else.
Illegal procedures, cancellation
of certification, and bankruptcy…
And you handed over
the clinic to your wife too.
You must have thought that
you could start over
if your wife was gone.
So what? What does
that have to do with anything?
Dozens of people saw my wife
walking around totally fine.
How are you
going to prove
that I killed my wife?
We have a witness.
Sang-hee.
Oh Joo-hyung, you're under arrest
for murdering your wife.
Honey.
We're stopping them all, as we planned.
Lieutenant Colonel.
If we're late,
even more people will get hurt.
Excuse me…
I'm going to get surgery.
So it's decided?
My mom is pretty worried,
but the disease spreading
in the apartment is worrisome too.
When I get wounded,
it doesn't heal very well.
I take antibiotics too.
We decided to go out quietly
and get surgery.
When are you leaving?
I'm going to go get checkups
when my mom comes.
Hey, he's the man who was on TV.
Is he your friend?
No, he's just someone I know.
What is it?
Mad Human Disease is spreading
in the apartment.
But there was only one infected person.
Are there more?
We interrogated the dealer,
and he said he sold
the drugs at the apartment gym.
He sold them by saying it helps
with diets and concentration,
and one of the purchasers
was Park Min-ji from the sixth floor.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Hi.
-How have you been?
-Fine.
-Well done.
-Thank you.
Thank you. Enjoy your workout.
KANG JOO-HEON: SENIOR TRAINER
I'm sure many in the apartment
are going through the same thing.
Some might be living quietly at home,
hiding the disease.
So the numbers will grow little by little,
and blow up all at once.
What are you doing here, then?
You should start investigating.
Do you think that's going to solve it?
There's no cure or vaccine for it,
and we don't know when they will turn.
Where can we keep them to watch them?
We can't even kill them all
like pigs infected with swine fever.
Then what are you going to do?
Is there another way?
There…
is a way.
What is that?
Why are you putting those up?
What are you doing?
Thankfully, only the residents
can use the gym,
and less than half
of the houses are in use.
The nursery in the apartment complex
isn't open yet, either.
So you're going to lock down
the entire complex?
Until we get the manpower
and location to watch the infected.
You should tell the residents, though.
They need to prepare themselves.
They won't prepare themselves.
They'll run away and spread the disease.
You can get out, Ms. Yoon.
We always lack decisive people
when it comes to matters like this.
It's my fault.
When I found out what you
were doing at the dorm,
I should have revealed everything
through the media.
That wouldn't have changed anything.
We have to…
have priorities for things like this.
Like who is more needed
and what is more needed.
So I'm someone needed?
But I decided to live here
and this is my house now.
Whether it's noise issues
or Mad Human Disease,
I'm not the type to run away
in the middle of something.
Goodbye.
Yes, I'm in front of your house right now.
Hey, how can I go back
when I came all the way here?
Yes.
What is this?
This is our apartment. What's going on?
If you go in now, you can't come outside.
What? What does that mean?
Yes, what floor are you on?
Okay, I'm going in now.
Yi-hyun, I'm locked up inside.
Don't fight them trying to get in.
If my mom calls you, tell her I'm okay.
What does that mean?
Where are you locked up?
I'll be…
watching our apartment.
Sae-bom, tell me what's going on.
Damn it.
I was going to tell you later…
I thought I was left alone.
Sae-bom, I have to catch that jerk.
It's okay. No one can get out anyway.
Let her out.
They have a high risk of infection.
We don't know what will happen outside.
Did you take that drug too?
But you know who took them, right?
You never know how people can change
in times of crisis.
What do you think you're doing?
We can't go outside anymore.
The other buildings voted for this.
Ms. Yoon, are you all right?
It's blood.
Come out if you don't want to die!
Help!
Within 72 hours we'll be done for.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee