ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS,
EVENTS, AND OCCUPATIONS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
6 MONTHS AGO
…kids' products were 50% off.
I bought one because it would look
great on our baby.
But we don't know if it's a boy or a girl.
She's a girl who looks just like you.
I say that every day, tapping on my belly.
But if she's a girl,
she shouldn't look like me.
Oh, the CEO must be here.
All right, I'm nearby too.
-Okay, see you soon.
-Okay.
Yes.
-Hi.
-Yes, hi.
Here.
So, the Ministry of Food and Drug Safety
gave the final authorization?
Yes, they'll announce it tomorrow.
The condition is to use it
only for adult ADHD patients,
and if it's proven effective,
they'll add more patients.
Well done.
I was wondering
if I had to take all of the Next
piled up in the storage.
I can make more money
thanks to you, Mr. Han.
It failed as a cure for pneumonia,
but we think it's possible
to use it to treat adult ADHD.
Yes, it's already known
for enhancing concentration.
Many people around me
are taking it already.
-Is that Next?
-Yes.
-Haven't you tried it, Mr. Han?
-No.
Take it when you're not doing so well.
It makes me feel truly alive.
It's great.
Hello.
-Hello, I'm Park Young-in.
-I heard a lot about you.
-Go ahead, have a seat.
-Okay.
-Is this it?
-Wait until you see it.
So, is your baby a boy or a girl?
Our baby?
I think she's a girl.
That's good.
People these days say that one daughter
is better than ten sons.
That's what they tell me.
-Please excuse me for a moment.
-Okay.
So, when will
the little baby princess be born?
It's been twelve weeks,
so about six months later?
Did you say, "bite"?
Are you sure he's not taking other drugs?
The final authorization
will be announced tomorrow.
Hospitalize him and silence everyone.
This must never spread.
Who cares? He's not even dead.
Offer medical fees and compensation, then.
I'll call you again.
Honey.
It's a call from
the Prime Minister's office.
Where are they going?
To a landfill.
We're short on facilities
for patients with minor symptoms.
Do you still not understand
why I'm doing this?
I do understand.
I made a choice
about how much damage I should prevent.
You will soon have to choose
how much blood to have on your hands.
What about the cure?
We sorted possible candidate materials
and injected them into the infected,
but they all died.
Keep trying until it works.
I will do the enduring.
Then what should we do now?
The infected are everywhere,
and there may be no more aid from outside.
We have to break out!
They even installed screen fences
on the walls.
Even if we do break out,
where do we go next?
We can just break out
and go into the most expensive apartments.
Then what can they do?
Would they lock that place up too?
Lots of high-class people
must be living there.
We are suffering because
these apartments are cheap.
Are you sure the patients
are really out there?
The building representative
and Mr. Oh are not here.
So only the public rental residents
are here again?
I'm saying that many of those
who went outside are not here.
If you want to go out,
then go ahead and go out.
Though I can't guarantee
that you can come back.
Now then, I'll take that as
you all understood.
The items and food we brought
from the supermarket are in Unit 201,
so go there if you need anything.
But they might be short
on some things too,
so the condition
is to exchange items for them.
Hey, but if the infected
become more serious,
won't they smash the doors and break in?
If they ram the glass doors with a car,
they'll break.
They'd find an easier way to get inside.
That's how all crimes start.
They say they got in because
the door was unlocked,
and took the bicycle
because there was no lock on it.
But it's not easy
to decide to break the door
and get inside just
because they want to drink blood.
It just means
we shouldn't give them an excuse.
The doors are all locked…
What?
The rooftop.
I'm the only one here.
It's not too late, is it?
Let's hope it isn't.
Andrew, you really don't
get startled that easily.
When you were outside,
and over here as well.
I'm just happy
that people don't think I'm weird.
Be careful, both of you.
You too, Andrew.
Let's take a breather and go.
I'm tired.
Seriously…
This reminds me of the past.
When?
You mean that day?
Hey.
I thought I was actually flying.
You did fly.
I guess I did.
If I could fly,
I'd go to the nursing home to see my mom.
I've been delaying it
because it's uncomfortable to see her,
and things turned out like this.
What do you think happened
to the infected?
Would they be hiding somewhere…
and holding in their thirst?
I'm sure they're frightened
that they'd bite someone
who's closest to them.
That they'd turn into monsters completely.
But still, they'll fight
until they surrender to their thirst.
Would they all be okay?
Sure.
We just don't need to get hurt, okay?
Then we can all meet again later.
So don't do that again.
How could you put that blood on your hand
without knowing where it came from?
Then was it okay to put it
on Oh Joo-hyung's face, then?
You didn't force him to drink it.
I'm sure he wouldn't have sucked on it.
Of course not.
He seems like
he cares so much about himself.
But seeing
how he didn’t come down earlier,
I think he's a little intimidated.
The building representative
didn't come either, right?
Are you okay?
Of course not.
Look at this.
I must've been so startled.
Why don't we just give up, then?
That would be better.
It seems like you can't make money here
even if you become
the resident representative.
And if we get out?
If we get out of here,
it'll be dirt cheap!
Should we suffer the loss, leave,
and start over at another apartment?
I'm just saying there's no other way.
You said Seung-beom at the gym
might be infected.
You went to the gym every day.
What did you even do there?
You should've watched
for things like that.
I didn't think he'd do that.
Once the lockdown is over,
the entire complex should be repaired.
Let's tell them the interior materials
of the elevators should be replaced,
and the outer walls should be removed.
That made the lockdown easier.
And let's tell them to plant
trees on the outskirts too.
Didn't you say you know
a landscaping company?
We should do some serious disinfecting.
Because there were infected people.
Yes, that's it!
If you think outside of the box,
you can get tons of ideas.
But do you think you can become
the resident representative?
I must recruit
some influential people on the inside.
My father had schizophrenia.
He passed away two years ago,
so I get shocked easily
when I see illnesses like that.
Sae-bom isn't home now.
Damn it.
I see, you're the little girl
from Unit 502.
Then are you home alone?
Where are the people from Unit 501?
-Can you open the door?
-The people from Unit 501 are here.
My goodness.
I'm sorry about
what happened earlier today.
But…
you should've told me
that you were really okay.
Anyone can misunderstand
when they see blood.
Don't you think?
It must be hard for you too.
Still, aren't you glad that
you have someone to look after you?
I really am glad.
I'm so glad that we're downstairs.
Aren't you sad
you can't enjoy your newlywed life
because of this incident?
I also started at the first floor
of a small house with my husband,
and all of a sudden there was this flood.
All that trouble we went through…
How did you two meet?
Oh, my.
You must have a deep connection.
Why don't you sit down?
I can't trust her.
-Me neither.
-Then why did you let her in?
Keep your friends close,
and your enemies even closer.
Where's Sae-bom?
She's talking to
the building representative.
She came to apologize or something.
Apologize? Isn't her apology annoying too?
Right.
That's because she's not sorry.
But she asked me if I'm trying
to become the resident representative.
She must be trying to become that.
Why would she do that? It sounded
like it'd get her a lot of money.
All contracts regarding the apartment
are signed by the representatives.
Elevators, walls, rooftops, parking lots,
electricity, landscaping, everything.
-That's all money.
-Everything?
Don't you have more?
I actually exercise, you know.
Give me some more kimbap.
-Kimbap?
-Yes.
Mister.
You won't cuff me tonight, right?
It cuts my blood circulation.
-Mr. Kim.
-Yes?
All the residents here
are extremely anxious.
Nobody has noticed yet,
but some people
will start suspecting your condition.
So?
I'm telling you to be careful
so people won't get scared.
The handcuffs cannot be helped today,
but if you're okay for the next few days,
we'll let you use this gym
comfortably at least.
You're not threatening me today.
I hope that you're not infected.
Even without you…
this apartment has a lot of problems.
Seriously…
Damn it.
I'm going to kill him.
I swear, I will…
Hey, what are you looking at? I'm fine.
Look. I'm clean, aren't I?
Aren't you the one who's scared?
You were nearly peeling your skin off.
Hey!
What are you taking?
HANGOVER RELIEF MEDICINE
I thought you were taking something bad.
Pour me a glass.
Did you see Min-ji…
taking drugs at the clinic?
You know,
like health supplements or tonics.
She did take some when she was tired.
What drugs were they?
I don't know.
They were just some kind of pills.
She said they were health supplements
she got from the gym.
The gym?
Your name wasn't on the gym register.
My wife went to the gym.
Did Mad Human Disease spread from the gym?
Why? Is it something important?
Don't drink too much.
Alcohol damages everyone.
Where are you going?
Somewhere. It's none of your business.
-You go in first.
-Why?
I left my wallet.
Why are you carrying your wallet?
I'll be back soon. You go inside first.
COMMUNITY CENTER
GYM, INDOOR GOLF, READING ROOM
Who is it?
You really are here.
Mister.
Are you locked up here?
Yes, I got locked up here.
The cop who lives
on the fifth floor locked me up.
Mister.
Please help me.
There's nothing wrong with me.
I'm totally clean,
but that cop who lives up there,
he did this…
You sold the drugs to my wife, didn't you?
The female doctor on the sixth floor,
who died of Mad Human Disease.
I'm not trying to threaten you,
or take revenge.
I'm actually grateful.
Mister.
I want to buy that drug.
I really don't know anything about it.
You don't?
I really don't know about it.
-You really don't know?
-I don’t.
-You don't?
-No.
Seriously…
This is pissing me off.
I'm going to kick you out
for being infected,
you crazy bastard!
Damn it.
Wait.
You don't know?
-Why are you doing this to me?
-You don't know?
I really don't know, Mister!
-Wait!
-I really don't know!
What?
-Mister!
-You don't know?
Are you Lawyer Kook Hae-seong?
Yes, I am.
I live in Building 102.
I called after seeing the elevator ad.
But I heard that the other buildings
are full of patients.
No, there are a few,
but they're all in quarantine
at the children's library.
Building 101 is being sensitive
and restricting entrance.
So it's not that serious right now?
Yes, can I talk to you in person?
It's about my grandfather's mountain.
Where are you right now?
The first basement floor.
Can we meet here and talk in person?
The Internet works here.
And it's easier to show you the map here.
Stay there. I'll be there soon.
Didn't you just talk to someone?
No, it must've been from outside.
I'm going out.
Where are you going?
It feels stuffy here.
Let me go for a walk and get some air.
VIEW VISITORS
NOW VIEWING. PLEASE WAIT.
Are you Lawyer Kook Hae-seong?
What is it?
-Hi.
-Oh, hi.
My husband went to meet someone
from a different building.
And I heard there are many
Mad Human Disease patients out there.
Where did he go?
I hoped that he wasn't infected…
-Do something about this crazy jerk!
-Why should I?
This world will be better off without you.
Hi, Mr. Kook.
It's hard to go out and get a consultation
when you're in lockdown.
Right, please wait.
The Internet doesn't work here.
You have to come out a little bit more.
This way.
How do I open this?
Consider yourself lucky.
If it wasn't for Sae-bom,
you would've been dead.
You see that camera?
If you tell anyone about him,
I will leak
the video of him attacking you.
Then you'll be a Mad Human Disease
patient too. Get it?
So just stay home
and do nothing but breathe.
Why did you hide that he's infected…
Why did you hide that?
Because he's a human being.
Mr. Kim, calm down.
You can go back to your normal state.
Mister, the apartments are
in lockdown right now.
Go home and get some rest.
What are you doing? You scared me.
Hold still.
If he breaks in, then we're in trouble.
Mister.
We told you that you shouldn't go outside.
He was a client asking
about his grandfather's mountain.
He was totally fine.
I just saved you
from getting buried in the mountains.
I just lost one client because of you!
How can you say that?
Honey.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Did you tell her?
-What?
-What's wrong with you?
You try to backstab others
whenever there's a chance.
I might just throw you to him
and get you infected.
-You know what?
-What?
I am…
super…
super lucky, you know.
Eat this, you bastard.
That's disgusting. What are you doing?
There is…
someone outside, you bastard.
Just in time.
Your husband is totally crazy!
Did you mess with him?
What is wrong with all of you?
Your husband hit my face
with my glasses on!
It was attempted murder…
No, he tried to kill me!
Come here.
He tried to kill me…
by using that monster or beast thing!
What is that?
-What is that?
-Are you okay?
Mr. Kim's disease occurred.
Hey!
It's dangerous, so don't go near him.
Did you know that there was
a patient in the apartment?
Then you should've told us.
The trainer at the basement gym.
I think he's got the disease.
Did we have someone like that here?
How is he?
Was it around 10:45 or 10:46 p.m.?
He stopped banging his head.
You go up first.
I'll go up after I check the situation.
Be careful.
Are you awake?
You're awake.
I'm sure they're talking about
kicking you out up there.
I only took it twice, I swear.
Because I heard it helps when I'm tired.
Why did you go outside?
To find the remaining drugs.
When I take it,
my concentration gets better.
You thought of taking drugs
during all that chaos?
I told you, I only took it twice!
Do you remember what happened
when the disease occurred?
A little bit.
A man from the sixth floor
came in and picked on me.
I tried to hold it in,
but he didn’t stop…
You'd better hold it in more from now on.
As the disease occurs more often…
you'll lose your mind completely.
I told him about the drugs.
That they're in the gym car.
I'll take care of that.
Did you feel joy?
Do you feel joy when the disease occurs?
Are you excited and thrilled?
Then you won't be able
to hold it in for long.
It's cold at night. Put a jacket on.
What about the gym guy?
He's back to normal.
The disease lasts for 15 minutes,
and they're back to normal.
There will be a vote tomorrow.
What vote?
A vote on whether
to kick Mr. Kim out or not.
The lawyer on the sixth floor
said we should vote,
because we live in a democratic country.
I honestly thought
I had a really nasty personality.
But that's nothing
compared to everyone else here.
What did the building representative say?
She only cares about becoming
the resident representative.
She said she will exempt us from
maintenance fees if we take her side.
Jung-kook was right.
By the way…
about what Oh Joo-hyung said…
It's not true, right?
What?
That I tried to kill him? That's not true.
That bastard was threatening
Mr. Kim first,
so I scared him a bit.
-Right?
-Of course.
I was just a little concerned.
You know I can't keep
my thoughts to myself.
I know.
Sae-bom.
There's something called
good cop, bad cop.
What?
One shouts and scares someone
as a bad cop,
and the other persuades them
with kind words as a good cop.
Carrot and stick.
-So?
-I'll be the bad cop,
so you be the good cop.
-No.
-What?
You've been a bad cop enough times.
I want to be the villain now.
I'm going to beat up
everyone who gets on my nerves.
So you should
just be nice, okay?
Hey.
I'm worried you might get hurt.
The bad cops
are the ones who get hurt.
We must kick him out.
That's the only way we can survive.
Are the others fine?
Has no one been bitten?
We don't know yet,
but when the disease occurs,
we must kick them out.
Mr. Lawyer.
Can you send me the video?
-Do you agree with kicking him out?
-Yes. I saw that mess outside too.
Why are you snatching it
when I'm still watching it?
Please cooperate with us.
The situation is pretty serious.
I told you I saw something like this!
Do you now understand why I did that?
Is that important right now?
Hey, look at his eyes.
Where's Mr. Oh?
I think he's still washing.
If you want,
we have an empty room too,
so you can stay at my house.
Thank you for your concern.
Did you have to go this far?
Of course.
If I opened the door,
I would've been killed
by that jerk from the other building.
He tried to kill me,
talking about mountains and so on.
And if we get infected too…
Why would we get infected?
We didn't do anything wrong.
You don't get a disease
for doing something wrong.
Anyway, I'm not going outside
until the lockdown is over.
Just five minutes.
If you just take five minutes,
you can save someone.
Are they even humans?
The Mad Human Disease patients, I mean.
Of course. If you go down,
you can talk to him.
Perhaps someone might die
because you're hiding here.
Think wisely.
Think wisely…
What are you doing here?
I was just waiting for you.
Where have you been?
To the 15th floor.
To tell them to come vote tomorrow.
Have you ever regretted
anything in your life?
I have.
When something happens
and it ends when I didn't do my best,
I can't help but feel regret.
And they keep lingering in my mind.
It makes me feel so uneasy.
So you don't want
to regret anything this time?
I don't.
This time,
I won't avoid things.
What?
Let's go!
Mom, let me borrow your phone.
Why?
I'll just record a video
and give it back to you.
I lost mine.
Where did you lose your phone?
Wasn't that phone brand new?
Mom, you only use it to make calls, right?
The password… Oh, it's not locked.
Hey, when you're done taking pictures,
give it right back.
Okay!
-Let's go.
Thank you all for coming
though you're busy.
There's a law about emergency evacuation
on Article 22 of the Criminal Act.
I'll read it for you.
"An act performed in order to avoid danger
against a person's legal interest
shall not be punishable
when there are reasonable grounds."
"The preceding paragraph shall not apply
to a person with
duties not to avoid danger."
To put it simply, it's okay for us
to kick the infected out…
in order for us to survive.
You don't want to get infected
and go crazy like
the other building residents, right?
Let me show you this.
It's terrifying. Watch this.
My Lord!
Has anyone been infected
with COVID-19 before?
Why are you suddenly bringing up COVID-19?
None of you?
I was infected once, but why…
Let me ask you one thing.
Sir.
Did you get infected with COVID-19
because you did something wrong?
What does that even mean?
I didn't do anything wrong!
If only those old geezers
didn't ask me to eat with them…
Right.
Diseases are not something you catch
depending on who you are.
Remember what it was like
during the COVID-19 pandemic?
When someone got infected,
some people doxxed them
and pointed their fingers at them,
but most of the time, we were worried
about those who got infected,
and wished for them to get well soon.
That's not something you should
be kicked out for without getting treated.
This is not the same as COVID-19.
It's different.
It makes the infected
attack and bite people.
I understand
you're all scared and anxious.
I am, too.
But what if this happens to you,
or your family?
When you kick out Mr. Kim,
then who will you kick out next time?
Mr. Oh from the sixth floor?
Or the lawyer who was
in contact with Mr. Oh?
Shall we just play Musical Chairs
until only one person remains?
That's enough. Let's vote.
Who agrees with kicking him out?
It doesn't mean we have
to kick him outside.
It means we should not let him
blend in with normal people.
If we lock him up on a rooftop
and totally separate him,
then we'll all be safe.
Don't you think?
Just be honest and raise your hands.
You can be honest about your opinions.
Hurry up and raise your hands.
Raise your hands.
Yes, raise your hands. Come on.
Ma'am!
How can you do this to me?
You brought me here!
Looks like he feels betrayed
because I've been nice to him.
That's a total of eight.
So-yoon, what are you doing?
Raise your hand.
Hey!
Nine.
Then those who disagree?
One, two,
three,
four,
five,
six…
six,
seven,
eight,
nine.
The votes tied. What should we do?
Should we vote again?
I don't think that's necessary.
Let's not kick him out.
I vote for that.
Ten votes. It's done.
That's good.
I felt uncomfortable
about kicking out one of our residents.
Seung-beom, I don't have
any hard feelings for you.
You know that, right?
Now then, let's discuss
how to monitor Mr. Kim.
It's tiring for us
and Detective Kim to keep monitoring him.
Let's form groups of two
and check his condition.
Who wants to go first?
Do you want to follow
the rules of democracy
and vote?
We will do it first.
Open it, now!
EMERGENCY RESTRICTION
I heard you told
the Prime Minister's office
that the regions with a large number
of infected should be locked down first.
I told them it can't be stopped
when the number of the infected grows.
That's true.
There's no cure, either.
The only thing you can do now
is to keep the temperature low
and buy time with
tranquilizers and sleeping pills.
You don't have much time left either.
One month at the most.
Isn't it the same for your wife?
Wasn't she infected
around the same time I did?
I thought that's why you said
you'd develop the cure within a month.
I understand that you're anxious.
I will give up on all places
that are now in isolation.
There hasn't been
much support until now anyway.
Like you said, the number
of the infected shouldn't increase.
Cut off electricity,
and don't give them food.
The whole country is using
air-conditioners right now,
so there's no need
to waste more electricity.
So we should cut off the electricity
and wait until the infected are all dead?
Even if the cure is out,
it's still troublesome.
They've tasted human blood,
so we can't be generous
just because they were ill before.
And you're the one who got addicted
to the taste of blood.
Because it’s okay for me to be like that.
I'm just telling you beforehand.
Because you seem to have a plan too.
Shouldn't we stop him?
The water will get cut
if they cut the electricity,
and even those
who aren't infected will die.
Find out when the electricity
will be cut off.
Hey.
Why do you think I married you?
If you're a secretary,
you should play along with me!
But we're a married couple now.
You and I may think differently.
I don't think my opinion was wrong.
Will you take responsibility
when we get infected?
This is why I shouldn't have
married an ignorant girl.
I have made a mistake.
Dong-hyun, give me my phone.
Mom, I can't give it to you
unless I'm done recording.
You're pestering me way too much today.
Is there something on your phone?
Why would I have anything like that?
Then just wait.
I will go outside and see
if anything else is there, okay?
But Dong-hyun…
Mom!
I said I'll give it back soon!
I need something big
to get more views, seriously…
What is she doing?
Excuse me.
You lost your phone, didn't you?
How did you know?
You dropped it at the entrance
when we were coming in.
I mean…
How did you know I was looking for it?
You were filming with it yesterday.
And you're filming again now.
I thought you'd be looking for it.
Wait, Ms. Lee.
Can you please help me?
I won't go outside.
I'll give you money.
Don't you need money?
Please tell me if you need anything.
Can I get bullets too?
Are you serious?
But why are you so interested
in military items?
I'm interested in
end-of-the-world scenarios.
The Earth is in danger right now.
It's not just infectious diseases.
Extreme weather, global warming,
nuclear war, AI…
Extinction is coming soon.
Okay…
So I'm collecting
all kinds of survival gear.
I'm also collecting combat rations
from other countries.
Did you collect a lot?
Combat rations?
Want to see my collection?
Your collection?
Why not?
Wouldn't that break
if you put force into it?
I'm not sure.
If you break that,
your life will break too.
Be careful if you don't want
to get kicked out.
Are you here to mock me?
I'm here to clear our misunderstanding.
I wanted to help you too.
But you took the drugs.
When did you even help me?
Drink it when you're thirsty.
Only when you seriously cannot hold it in.
I'm here because I'm worried.
-Why did you tell me to go there…
-Shut up.
-Tell me if you need anything.
-I think you're mentally ill.
Are you nuts?
You call your sister "mentally ill"?
I'm saying you are.
-What a brother I have.
-Think about it…
MUIL GROUP CONSTRUCTION
IN COMMEMORATION OF SELECTION
I told you, shut up.
I comforted him
as the building representative
because it would be tough for him.
Goodbye, then.
By the way,
I voted for kicking him out earlier…
He would remember that, right?
There are people he'd hate more than you,
so you'll be fine.
It's not an airborne disease,
so don't worry about it.
If he gets extremely thirsty
while you're watching him,
don't give him water,
and just come up to the fifth floor.
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
And the key for the handcuffs.
Well, you might not need it,
but you never know.
I'll go talk to Mr. Kim for a moment.
Aren’t you scared?
Why did you vote for kicking him out
when you don't even live here?
What did the building representative
say to you?
Isn't there something else
you're more curious about?
I am curious about
a lot of things right now.
The ones who bought the drugs.
That man in the quarantine suit.
The last one to vote.
Muscles are formed when we exercise.
-Right.
-But if you take this pill,
it doubles the effect
compared to exercising.
You can see that they are
in the form of small pills.
The 15th floor.
It was there,
but I can't see it from here.
Go ahead and make it quick.
I'll be watching from here.
Let's remove these.
Young lady.
Are you looking for something?
Want me to help you?
Sae-bom, Kim Seung-beom said…
Seo-yoon, where's Sae-bom?
She went upstairs
with the man on the 15th floor.
IF YOU'RE BORED, WE CAN CHAT
Oh, my darlings.
Hyun-kyung, this is Jae-yeol,
and he plays the piano so well.
You can get advice from him
if you write music novels later.
Then just lend me money.
Aren't you worried about
your wife and kids?
Talk about things like that
when the lockdown is over.
I'm sure they're fine!
What could've happened?
I'm working now.
To be brutally honest, if you die here,
then this house becomes mine.
But I came here to help you.
That sounds like you want to kill me.
It's not the first time you tried.
I got injured
because you pushed me off the swing!
I can't show my forehead because of this!
You didn't do anything good to me, either!
You gave me hepatitis in high school
so I had to retake my CSAT!
It's not my fault
you had a weak immune system!
Do you know how it feels
to treat people my age as my seniors?
Let's talk outside.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm not plotting to do anything to you.
I just felt upset.
What are you so upset about?
You received the fortune when you married,
and our parents sent you to college,
but I only had my tuition paid, just once.
I paid for the rest!
But I never said a word and I held it in.
How could you act
like I owe you something, after all that?
I'm sorry…
but let's not be so harsh, okay?
We're still family.
So much for family.
This place is safe, right?
-Where are you going?
-What?
I hear something.
It's okay. It's safe here.
What are you two doing?
Run!
I don't think anyone's out there.
Hey, don't open it!
Stop talking down to me.
I'm still your older brother.
Are you scared?
Don't worry, your big brother is here.
Is something going on outside?
Sae-bom!
Yoon Sae-bom!
Sae-bom's here, right?
I'm a little busy right now.
She'll be out soon. Hang on.
Did you take the drugs?
The ones you bought at the gym?
If you messed with Sae-bom,
I'm going to kill you.
One person went missing because of you.
We need someone with power.
Someone who will follow our orders.
Even though I know
what I should drink to quench my thirst.
Na Soo-min's phone.
The electricity will be cut off tonight.
You stay here.
He's here to take Sae-bom.
I'm here to find even
the smallest possibility.
Even if it means
getting you bitten by the infected.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee