ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS,
EVENTS, AND OCCUPATIONS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
-Are you sure it's going to rain?
-Of course.
Trust me when it comes to weather.
My friend works
at the Meteorological Administration,
and even he asks me about the weather.
I'm more accurate than them.
I hope it rains a lot.
It'd be awesome if I can guess
the amount of rainfall too.
But if the infected break in,
we'd be attacked first, right?
That still doesn't mean
you can go into someone else's house.
Excuse me, you two. Please hear us out.
The second floor is dangerous.
Once the lobby is breached,
it'll be our house next.
So we want to move to that house.
Please tell her it's okay.
Some jerk dumped food waste
on the first floor, so it reeks.
You just needed to talk to me,
the building representative.
You're saying you want to move
to the 11th floor.
But isn't it locked?
We cleaned Unit 1102, not long ago.
The passcode is 8888. It hasn't changed.
We will clean the place
when we get out in three days.
So, are you against this,
building representative?
There can be legal problems later on…
And the 11th floor is a royal floor,
so it doesn't look good
to let the cleaners live there.
The residents won't like it.
Then let's hear their opinions.
We have a lawyer in the building too.
I'd like to say it's not possible,
from a lawyer's point of view.
If you go into someone else's house
without permission, it's trespassing.
If two people go in,
it's special trespassing.
It's not an offense unpunishable
over objection,
so anyone can report it,
even if they're not the owners.
You know…
I'm really sorry to say this, but…
If you two go up,
then our house will be at the lowest.
Why should we guard your house, sir?
Hey, don't look at me like that!
My house has two old people.
Can't you young people stay at the bottom
and help us feel safe?
Hey!
Mr. Oh, since you came all the way here,
tell us if you have any opinions.
I think you should just stay here.
If you can stay here like a guard dog,
the residents would feel safe,
and it'll be good.
What are you saying?
-What did you say?
-Calm down.
Don't.
Just calm down, and do the cleaning.
Now, it won't be longer than three days.
Let's endure it a bit longer.
Everyone's already having a hard time,
so we can't give privileges only to you.
More than that,
where should we throw out the trash?
We left it at the emergency stairs,
but it still stinks a bit.
Don't tell me
you threw it out the window.
Did someone really do that?
I hope not.
If you need more water,
put water containers on the rooftop.
I already told Unit 401,
but it'll rain tonight.
How do you know that?
Is the Internet working?
He's the human weather center.
He could've gone to the Major League,
but he had a knee injury…
-That's an exaggeration…
-Oh, dear.
That's too bad for a young man like you.
Do some thigh workouts regularly!
Yes.
I should.
Work out, okay?
Excuse me.
I have something to tell you.
It's my brother.
My brother isn't here.
Right? He's not here.
I was just worried.
My brother called me.
Through that yesterday,
before the electricity was cut off.
He looked fine, but…
He had a strong immune system
when he was a kid,
and he doesn't catch colds that easily.
Maybe… he's not infected.
I hope he isn't.
You really are the human weather center.
See? I told you it'll rain.
Get some more sleep. I'll go.
No, I'm awake.
I should go get water to flush the toilet.
It's been bothering me.
And I should put the container back out.
We never know when it might rain again.
When will it rain?
It's raining now.
Evil, begone!
He's driving me crazy, seriously…
What is this?
He's suddenly religious now.
He even prays before he sleeps.
Does he even know how to pray?
Let's just go to the rooftop.
Evil, begone!
It's raining.
Shall I go outside and get some water?
Heavy metals, fine dust, and pollutants…
I will never drink rainwater.
And I will never drink
the bathtub water, either.
We'll be able to go out in three days.
What's with you?
We never know.
Soo-min!
-Oh, gosh.
-Soo-min!
Soo-min!
-Is that you, Soo-min?
-Hyun-kyung…
What are you doing here?
Wait, no. Go away!
Wait, don't go! Let's talk.
Are you hurt badly?
Are you sure that you got the disease?
I'm not sure.
I just… feel weird.
What about food? Did you eat anything?
Excuse me.
Isn't that ours?
Don't you have water at home?
Drinking our water without asking…
Come on. Rainwater is free.
You can drink more if you want to.
Hey, you shouldn't just drink that.
It's okay.
I always drank muddy water
during tactical training, you know.
UNIT 1501 KIM SE-HOON
I'm sure no one will steal your water.
Do you drink rainwater too?
By purifying it.
I have purifying tablets,
so come over if you need any.
And tell your husband before you do.
I'll be the one going to his house.
Never go there on your own.
Don't worry.
He even drinks rainwater by purifying it,
so I'm sure he didn't take drugs
from the gym.
What do you want for dinner?
But we just ate.
I think of tomorrow's breakfast menu
while I eat today's lunch.
Then it's more delicious
due to my expectations.
-Hi.
Are you cleaning these days too?
It felt stifling just to stay at home.
The building representative
also told me to work
if I want to get paid.
She really is mean.
But I saw something weird.
Like what?
Where did you find this?
In a trash bag.
They didn't even fill up
half the trash bag.
It must be someone
with lots of trash bags.
What is this?
Where was that trash bag?
Between the third and fourth floor.
But it was fine until yesterday.
Don't show it.
Since I'm a detective,
I'll use an advanced technique
to interrogate her.
Speak nicely.
I'm sure she's still shocked.
Don't worry.
Hi.
Are you short on anything
or having other issues?
Not yet.
What brings you here?
We're here about the trash.
You threw this away, didn't you?
No.
I'm not injured. I mean it.
-See? I'm fine, aren't I?
-It's okay.
I didn't get bitten. I really am fine.
An advanced investigation technique?
Seriously…
Hey, it's better to ask directly first.
I don't think it was Ms. Na.
Her brother…
Where could he be now?
But why did you bring me
instead of Sae-bom?
You said you can't lend me your gun.
Sorry, I feel anxious without my gun.
That's why you're here.
EMERGENCY RELIEF GOODS
That's one of the boxed lunches
we gave out.
Why is that here?
Martial Law has been declared.
It's filled with the infected outside.
So?
Do we have to know everything
that's happening inside?
-There may be more infected people inside.
-And if we find them?
What will we do then?
Where would we lock them up?
We're locked in here too.
Yi-hyun, we can get out in two days.
Let's not stir up things
by investigating stuff, okay?
We never know. What if more people
get bitten one by one and get infected?
My wife…
is badly ill right now.
She got tested for breast cancer,
and it seems like it recurred.
We got a call from the hospital.
We started our shop
because we thought she was cured.
Yi-hyun.
I need to go to my wife.
You know how much my wife suffered, right?
Jung-kook is right.
There isn't much we can do.
Give me the whole thing.
Okay. Let's wait until
the disease control team comes.
Okay.
I don't think I can wait.
Among the candidate materials
for the cure,
Material 13 proved effective
in the clinical test.
How effective is it?
The period and frequency
of disease occurrence
improved for 72% of
the infected in serious conditions.
How's your thirst?
I don't feel it that much.
-What about my family?
-They're outside, nice and safe.
Lieutenant Colonel, not yet…
By the way…
did you always like meat?
No.
I was a vegetarian, but…
It looks like you've gotten a lot better.
Don't worry about your family
and just focus on recovering.
Yoon Sae-bom's blood analysis
isn't complete yet, is it?
No, it isn't.
Do the analysis in secret,
and leak the info
on Material 13 to the higher-ups.
But it's still at an early clinical stage.
We need more data.
That's why we're doing this.
Say that the clinical tests are over
and that only the final stage remains.
What did you do in there?
What?
It was nothing.
I was just feeling a bit stuffy,
and I heard this place was empty,
-I should try going in there too--
-Wait.
I'm sorry.
My brother is in there.
Mr. Na, are you in there?
Are you okay?
It's okay, Soo-min. You can talk to them.
They're my upstairs neighbors.
Yes, for now.
You ate a boxed lunch
at the basement entrance, right?
Did your sister give that to you?
No. The doctor from the sixth floor did.
He knew…
that I got infected.
Aren't you hungry?
What did Mr. Oh say?
He asked me to come inside with him,
but I refused.
Then he told me to think about it,
gave me a boxed lunch, and left.
Why did you refuse?
I'm sure you wanted to come inside.
I was scared…
that I might bite people.
Please stay home even
after the lockdown is over tomorrow.
-Okay.
-Both you and your brother.
We'll go out, explain the situation,
and bring the medical staff.
Thank you for understanding.
It's not because we understand.
We just have no choice.
We can't kick you out anywhere.
Still, we appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Bo-ram.
Come here for a second.
Just one second.
-Bo-ram.
-I'm telling you,
I won't take your money, so don't worry.
-I don't want to get involved anyway.
-No, that's not why…
You heard the thumping last night, right?
That's the sound made by the infected.
I think it was my mom.
I saw a selfie she took.
She had a wound on her back.
She said she bumped into
some infected woman on the sixth floor.
So?
What do you mean, "so"?
If my mom is infected,
then we can get infected too.
Wait, are you scared of that?
Not worried about her?
If you're that scared,
lock the door and don't come out.
That's not why. I'm worried about you.
Worry about me? Come on.
Just be nice to your parents.
I would give anything
to have parents like them.
When the lockdown is over tomorrow,
I should go see my mom first.
First Lieutenant Lee
said she's being protected, but…
She'll be fine.
I didn't expect to meet my mom like this.
Would the US be okay?
Hey, we're lucky
that we didn't schedule a wedding.
Right? If this broke out
while she was on her way here…
I would've been a bad son.
Do you think we did a good thing?
You mean the marriage?
Of course, it's a good thing.
No, I mean the fourth floor.
Oh, Mr. Na?
Well, his condition didn't look that bad.
-Maybe since he's at an early stage?
-Lieutenant Colonel Han said
the thirst can be controlled
if the person has the will.
Then I'll never get infected.
I'm a very determined man.
I'm looking forward to it.
What is this?
Is this food?
Indigestion meds.
I had a stomachache
whenever I was nervous about my game.
So I bought that
during the Italian Championships,
but it's disgusting, so don't take it.
I've never taken
any indigestion relievers in my life.
I envy you.
I can eat all the food here, you know.
-It's a lot.
-It is.
It includes portions for Seo-yoon too.
This is what we have
even after we gave food to everyone.
Let's put them back
when the lockdown is over tomorrow.
What if the lockdown
isn't lifted tomorrow?
We can eat those and wait.
You said you're very determined.
Thank you so much.
OUT OF CALL RANGE
NOT A SERVICE AREA
Mr. Kim.
Do you want to go outside,
or stay here with Seo-yoon?
Well…
Someone should stay with Seo-yoon, right?
Then let me borrow your gun.
Sae-bom.
I'm having a hard time these days.
Okay, you can keep it with you.
I asked you just in case.
Sae-bom, the phone's still not working.
Is it going to be okay?
Of course.
Stay home with Mr. Kim.
I'll go out and check the situation.
If you think you'll get hurt,
you have to run.
Don't worry. I have a good hunch
about things like that.
Hi.
What is this?
It was here when I got here.
YOU'VE GONE THROUGH SO MUCH
UNTIL THE END
I didn't know
there was someone so nice here.
This person must have a lot of water.
It must be the young lady
on the fourth floor.
She is kind and generous.
Did you live well on the third floor?
After you almost got us all killed?
I'm sorry.
What is this?
This is like an oasis in a desert. Nice.
Did you prepare this,
building representative?
You all went through a lot.
Can I drink more than one?
Yes, go ahead.
Here.
Take it. We're neighbors, after all.
But when will the doors be opened?
Let's go outside and check.
Who wants to go outside with me?
Let's go.
We'll have to go outside to find out.
Hey, don't drink it.
We never know
if someone put something in it.
No way.
Hey!
Seriously…
Are we out too early?
This is not a drill.
Citizens, this is not a drill.
Martial Law, originally scheduled
to be lifted today,
has been extended indefinitely as of now.
I repeat.
Martial Law, originally scheduled
to be lifted today,
-has been extended indefinitely…
-Oh, Lord.
-Why?
-Lord!
This is not a drill.
No!
I repeat.
Citizens, this is not a drill.
Martial Law, originally scheduled
to be lifted today,
has been extended indefinitely as of now.
I repeat.
This is not a drill.
Citizens, this is not a drill.
Ms. Woo said she needed
legal consulting, so came…
Where's Sang-hee?
She was here. Where did she go?
She's there.
You're here.
I suffered a lot from the lockdown.
I wanted to calculate the amount, so…
Okay.
Did you hear the announcement?
Yes, we were totally shocked.
Right?
Right.
Is the consultation over?
Yes, it is.
Okay, then…
All right.
If you need anything else,
contact me at any time.
Okay, goodbye.
Goodbye.
Hey, don't drink that.
But you put it out
so you can get along with everyone.
But we can't go out now.
Was he good?
What?
The lawyer.
His legal consultation.
It was so-so.
Where were you? You said you'll stay home.
I went to our neighbor's.
I provided consultation for Sang-hee
since the Martial Law would be lifted.
But then they said it won't be lifted.
I did it for nothing
when I can't even get paid for it.
What should we do now?
Look here…
Let's just go outside, okay?
We can't stay like this forever.
They extended the Martial Law,
so if we go outside,
we could get shot immediately.
By the way, about the thumping sound
in the building…
It may be from outside, or the basement.
My mom.
I think it's my mom.
My mom has a wound on her back.
I saw a picture of her back that she took.
You mean it?
Dad,
you know something's wrong
with Mom, don't you?
That's psoriasis.
When you get old, your skin gets dry.
It's from her scratching herself.
I put that on her back.
What is it called again?
You know, that thing. That…
Moisturizer?
Yes, that. Moisturizer.
I put moisturizer on her.
I saw it too.
She just has dry skin, that's all.
We should go check.
Let's hear them out first.
Don't you come into my house
without permission!
You do what you want to do outside!
My wife and I won't come outside anymore!
Damn you…
We should discuss issues
about necessities.
We have to give out food and necessities
from the second floor to every house.
What are you saying?
What can we eat, then?
Are you telling us to starve to death?
To be honest,
they don't even belong to you.
You just took them temporarily.
Hey! How can you say that?
Look here.
We risked our lives to bring those!
Who do you think you are
to just give them out?
You live here for free.
-Why are you shouting?
-What?
You flipped out last time,
going on about the "royal floor."
Will you charge us for breathing here too?
Should we pay for air?
I can't believe my generosity
gets repaid like this.
-Generosity?
-Calm down, everyone.
You should've gone outside that day, then.
-Calm down.
-We risked our lives to bring that!
We can't let her…
continue like this.
She'll keep causing fights.
-How can you say that?
-Please calm down.
Young lady.
You can't stay here any longer,
so go somewhere else.
-But I have nowhere to go.
-Go to the couple at Unit 501.
They're nice, so they'll find you
a place to sleep.
Goodbye.
Honey.
-Why did they summon people again?
-It's the same thing again.
You…
Just make some food. I'm hungry.
-Where's Dong-hyun?
-That brat…
I'm sure he's somewhere in the building.
Right…
There's a vacant unit,
so the supermarket lady will sleep there.
That's good.
I thought we'd be able
to take the elevator now.
I must do something about those cleaners.
They have no manners.
But we can't kick them out.
Wait!
My arm!
What is it?
We have something to discuss.
-Let's talk outside.
-Okay, thank you.
Look here!
What?
We're already inside, so let's talk here,
where it's comfortable.
We're not done cleaning yet.
Are you sure you moved in to live here?
We ordered furniture
and appliances in collections,
but they're not here yet.
Your refrigerator and microwave
are very simple.
We have to live for now, at least.
Maybe that's because
you weren't thinking of living here.
This is yours, right?
-No.
-Right here.
It says "Muil Group Construction
in Commemoration of Selection," right?
They gave them out when it was chosen
to construct this apartment complex.
Everyone who bought
an apartment here has it.
The regular apartments, I mean.
Not those who got it for free.
We know you gave water to Kim Seung-beom.
Who said that?
Your job is to become
the resident representative
and embezzle apartment funds, right?
And Mr. Kim came in here
to help you with that.
Do you have evidence?
Let's go.
Ma'am.
I'll promise you one thing.
You will never become
the resident representative.
The advanced investigation technique!
It was pretty good.
See? You should ask directly.
If you don't, they play dumb.
Right.
Mr. Kim.
Are you guys here to pray too?
I don't have a religion.
I see.
What about Seo-yoon?
Bo-ram from the supermarket came up,
so I asked her to stay with her.
She said she left the third floor
and had no place to sleep.
-Then Seo-yoon--
-Make it quick.
-Okay, I'll be back soon.
-Okay.
We'll head home first.
What about Bo-ram? Should we tell her
to stay at Unit 502 for a while?
After we ask Seo-yoon first.
That's obviously a cult. I'm worried.
He needs something to depend on, at least.
I did that too
when I couldn't play baseball.
Did you pray too?
No, I did something else.
Do you have drinks?
The ones in plastic bottles.
Not the ones that are high in calories.
Here, give me 50,000 won's worth.
I see you still haven't learned
your lesson.
You jerk…
Just go!
Hey.
Why…
Here. 100,000 won.
You still won't sell them?
It's 200,000 per bottle.
Are you trying to get rich
by selling them
in someone else's apartment?
Why?
Am I not allowed to get rich?
I want to make money and live here too.
You called me a guard dog.
Go bring the money.
If you don't want to,
then scram!
Okay, I'll just go bring more money.
Did you see how he got scared
and ran away when I barked?
What?
Did I do something wrong?
That jerk looked down on me first.
No.
People don't carry
that much cash these days,
-so let's take jewelry as payment too.
-Right.
The building representative
seems like she'd have jewelry, right?
I swear I'll get them from her.
With all that's going on,
we should earn as much money as we can.
We have to send Seung-hui to college too.
Ma'am, listen.
You should stop following
the building representative's orders
and clean this place instead, okay?
And we're giving you expensive pastry
and water, so be thankful.
Let the unjust ones commit injustice,
leave the filthy ones filthy,
let the just ones practice justice,
and leave the holy…
My arm!
…ones holy.
Amen.
-Amen.
Is Ms. Yoon all right?
-What?
-I saw a wound on her hand.
So I'm worried she might be infected.
And it seemed like something was going on
with her and that military man.
Right?
We have flash grenades, and…
You got a lot of things.
We have handcuffs too.
And…
What is it? A walkie-talkie?
He said he can't give us guns
and gave us these instead.
How do I turn this thing on?
Hey, turn it on.
So I can find out what's going on outside.
Seo-yoon, you're here. Have some snacks.
Okay.
Let's do this later.
If Jung-kook sees this,
I'm sure he'll feel uneasy again.
Did you have a good prayer?
Oh, yes.
Are you worried because you can't get out?
That's not why…
You went outside once
with Han Tae-seok,
and got blood all over your body.
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
I'm okay.
This…
When did you get this wound?
I got scratched by my friend…
a while ago.
When you went to the dorm?
Then isn't that an old wound?
It won't heal easily.
Mr. Kim, don't worry too much.
If something happens, I'll tell you first.
Come on, do you think
I'd bite you or Yi-hyun?
Okay…
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
And what is this one?
What the heck?
You got up at this hour?
Sir.
Please let me live here.
My mom is infected.
How can I trust you?
Go somewhere else.
I'm really fine.
I was outside all day long.
And look at this.
I'm really fine.
I will clean, do the laundry,
and do everything else.
And I brought food.
I brought all the food we have.
You and your wife are really nice people.
You two are very kind.
Please help me.
-Hang on.
-Okay.
When it comes to food,
the more the better.
We don't know how long
we'll have to stay here.
Where would he sleep?
We don't have any extra rooms.
What if he attacks us at night?
-Gosh.
-I'll leave.
Where would you go?
I'll go to the fourth floor first.
If that doesn't work,
I'll go to other units.
And in return…
just give me some food.
Ma'am.
Are you sure you're going to be okay?
The other houses may not accept you.
If that doesn't work,
I'll go to the basement lounge.
I think it'll feel better
to stay there alone.
Be careful.
People are getting meaner and nastier.
Thank you.
What now?
I found something.
Something you'd be
very happy to hear about.
What did you find here?
Something you need right now.
What's the passcode?
It's 8888.
Things are going well
because we're cooperating.
What's in there? How do you know
when you don't even know the passcode?
I saw someone
putting something in here secretly.
The ones from the second floor?
Did they hide food in here?
You'll be shocked if you see this.
Did you eat anything?
Who's in there?
I told you, you shouldn't live here!
Mister, who are you?
Let me see your face.
Can anyone hear me out there?
First Lieutenant Lee Ji-soo?
Hey, Han Tae-seok!
I'm sure they didn't give up
on this place.
They probably need time
to organize things.
Right, we might run out of batteries.
Let's try again later.
-Hey.
-Yes?
Since we're up here,
tell me about your baseball days.
When I won?
I got in during the third inning…
Not that. Tell me about yourself.
What did you depend on,
if it wasn't a religion?
You said people need something
to depend on.
You.
-What?
-To be honest…
I felt totally lost back then.
I acted like I was fine in front of you.
But I really thought I was nothing
when I couldn't play baseball anymore.
Then after I heard what you said
and fell to the ground…
I thought, "Am I going to die like this?"
And suddenly, my mind was clear.
I realized that it wasn't a big deal.
I found peace in my heart, thanks to you.
Why are you saying that in front of me?
That's embarrassing.
If you're grateful,
then return the favor in secret.
I've always been grateful.
You two are together.
-What's going on?
-Why do you care?
Na Soo-min was hiding
in the apartments, infected.
Is it true that you two hid him?
Can I go inside for a second?
Mr. Na.
Can you hear us?
There's no noise,
so I don't think the disease occurred.
Soo-min!
Mr. Na, are you okay?
Please help me.
I really didn't bite anyone.
I only looked
at that building representative.
I swear.
I have to see my kids.
The infected must be in quarantine, right?
Just hang in there a bit.
We'll check on things and be back soon.
Please protect Hyun-kyung
so she won't end up like me.
I didn't make the thumping sound.
It's not too late.
You two can be accused of being infected
because you made contact with them.
I also heard you made contact with
someone in the early stages of infection.
We should trust each other and--
You want our support
to become the resident representative?
Is this the right time to talk about that?
Then when is the right time?
There's no "right time" in making money.
You know that Oh Joo-hyung
is a lunatic, right?
How can you fight Mr. Oh
if you're so soft?
Is Mr. Oh home?
You should step outside for a moment.
It won't be a pretty sight.
I heard you found Na Soo-min.
I put in some effort
for the safety of the apartment.
Drink a bottle each.
I heard the infected feel more thirsty
when they drink water.
You've been with Mr. Na, so I'm worried.
So you're looking
for the infected among us?
Then you should drink too.
Thank goodness.
All three of us are healthy.
You should do something, Detective.
That's the only way to prevent
any potential damages.
You want to remain healthy
when you meet your family, right?
In order to do so,
you must also do
what you don't want to do.
There is something you can do,
so why are you avoiding it?
What…
What can I do?
Arrest the infected
who are pretending to be humans.
And restore order here.
That jerk must be throwing up.
Shouldn't we throw up too?
It did taste a bit bitter.
I never threw up before. How do I do it?
Just wait a bit.
Min-ji became like that
because she took drugs, right?
These are the drugs the fitness trainer
was secretly selling.
Did you spike the drinks with this?
You were the one
who put the drinks in the gym, right?
To get everyone in the building infected.
Because if all of the residents
either die or get the disease,
you can be cleared of your murder charge.
How could you come up
with such a crazy idea?
No.
I just need you two dead.
The rest are just bonuses.
More people should be infected
for the cure to come out soon.
This is just ridiculous.
You're confessing your crimes now, right?
So just go home and never come out.
If you get accused
of being infected and die,
it'll just be your loss!
Just stay home and live quietly
until the cure is developed, okay?
You killed Park Min-ji too, right?
No.
I didn't kill anyone.
You two should just shut up and stay home
if you don't want to kill someone.
If not, just go outside and ask
that Lieutenant Colonel guy for help.
But the thing is…
This…
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Why did you take that? Spit it out!
It's bitter.
It's an indigestion reliever
I took when I played baseball.
What is this? Is this food?
Indigestion meds. I had a stomachache
when I was nervous about my game.
I was worried about what you'd do,
so I replaced them.
Damn it!
And you've been caught
on the dashcam taking the drugs out.
Mr. Oh,
you can't get away with it this time.
So what?
What do you mean, "so what"?
A killer should be in quarantine too.
Sae-bom.
I'm really sorry, but…
I can't get the disease.
Mr. Kim.
Oh Joo-hyung committed murder.
That has nothing to do with us.
What matters now
is if you're infected or not.
You've been in contact
with the infected all this time.
And Ms. Yoon, you got scratched by one.
I think you two should be in quarantine.
We're getting a rare shot,
so we'll get better soon.
We should get well soon.
We're getting the shots already?
This is nice.
Hey.
It'll be done in no time.
There were a lot more infected
than I thought.
Did all of you take Next?
This shot greatly improved my condition.
Well done.
You should give it to your wife too.
I should.
I heard that Material 13
is hard to produce.
Yes.
We can't make a lot of it.
We should maintain
Martial Law for a while.
We must maintain the lockdown
to reduce the number of the infected,
and then release the cure.
It would be troublesome to let those
who may have killed someone live.
You're right.
Whether the issue gets solved or not,
it's better to get rid of those
who may cause problems.
People like you.
What are you talking about?
You took the cure
that just began clinical trials
by using your money and power.
You should be responsible
for your wrongdoings.
What are you going to do about it?
Thanks to all of you,
I can get more help in collecting data.
Have a good time.
WONJUNG DORMITORY
Lieutenant Colonel,
there's a problem at the CEO's ward.
A mass infection among
the politicians in high positions…
They stole Candidate Material 13
and got injected with it.
But that failed
at the second clinical stage.
We were discarding all of it…
I guess they didn't know.
They're in high positions,
so tell them to capture them alive.
We have to use them
as clinical test subjects.
Honey.
I'm thirsty.
Young-in.
We're almost there now.
I'm running out of patience.
Are you thirsty too?
They hide their thirst well,
and we can't tell just by looking.
Be careful.
You must never trust those people.
Should we look for the infected?
You just need to say the woman
on the fifth floor seems infected.
When I'm in danger,
I'll take that drug too.
I'm sure there will be casualties.
I only have one choice.
You killed him.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee