ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS,
EVENTS, AND OCCUPATIONS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Sae-bom's here, right?
I'm a little busy right now.
She'll be out soon. Hang on.
Did you take the drugs?
The ones you bought at the gym?
If you messed with Sae-bom,
I'm going to kill you.
I think you're mistaken about something.
Then open the door!
Where's Sae-bom?
Sae-bom!
What?
Yi-hyun, are you hungry too?
No, I'm here because I missed you.
-Help me.
-What?
-I said, help me. Get up.
We're newlyweds.
And I missed her so much.
He says he's worried
even if I'm away for a moment.
You must…
love her very, very much.
Of course.
What is it? What's going on?
Want some?
There are so many amazing things
in this place. Look.
There's a lot of food too.
Didn't anything happen?
Bye.
Thank you for the food.
Why did you do that?
He seems like the type to hold grudges.
The gym sold Next to him.
Don't look back.
He might be watching us right now.
No way. He's not a spy or anything.
Let me see. Did you get hurt?
Did you get scratched or feel a sting
on the back of your neck or anything?
This isn't healing well.
It's all healed now.
It's not even that visible.
More than that,
wasn't there anything weird in there?
Aside from the interior design…
His father is a diplomat,
so he's been to Africa
and the Middle East and stuff.
That's when he realized
that doomsday is approaching.
He is weird.
Still, he's nice.
He gave me these too.
These are really delicious
when you're hungry.
Everything's delicious when you're hungry.
Who is it?
Hi.
Kid, are you alone?
Who are you?
Don't you know me?
I'm a friend of your mom.
Can you open the door, please?
This…
Kid, what are you doing?
I hurt my arm.
I'm sorry. Can you open the door?
I'm not a bad guy.
Are you listening?
Do you have ointment?
How did you get hurt?
How did you get in here?
The door to the first floor was open.
I wasn't trying to do anything bad.
I didn't even bite anyone.
I was just so lonely and frustrated.
Why don't you wipe
the blood off your mouth first?
Who did you bite?
It was just a slight bite…
I didn't bite him hard.
And he survived and ran away…
Get out before I count to three.
One,
two,
three.
Seo-yoon, it's me.
Seo-yoon. It's me, Sae-bom.
Is he gone?
Yes.
-Where's Mr. Jung-kook?
-The second floor.
He went down because we were
out of dish soap and toothpaste.
Okay.
I'll be back soon,
so don't open the door to anyone,
just like you did now. Okay?
Seo-yoon, you did great.
Eat this and calm yourself down.
-I'm going now.
-Okay.
-I'll be right back.
How did he get in?
There may be more inside.
We have to search for them.
More than that, whose blood did he drink?
Ma'am, I'm not infected.
I'm really not infected.
You see, I came here
because the lady at Unit 1202
said she would pay me.
But a lockdown and infections?
What is all this?
Ma'am, I will help you.
I'll help you so we can get out together.
Think about it. Did I do anything weird?
I didn't, right?
I've just been staying here quietly.
Aren't you thirsty?
No. Look.
I'm fine, right?
I'm totally fine.
I look fine, don't I?
I promise I'll help you. Ma'am!
You can never get out of here alone.
Ma'am, please help me once.
Thank you.
I'll trust you just this once.
Are you okay?
What…
What am I supposed to do when I am
still thirsty after drinking water?
Ma'am, I'm all better now.
Come here. We should go up together.
Are you going to stay there…
until the infected come here?
Ma'am, just trust me!
Yi-hyun.
Let's hurry.
It's Na Soo-min's phone.
MUIL GROUP CONSTRUCTION
Even after drinking this much water…
my throat is dry.
Where are Na Soo-min and Na Hyun-kyung?
I don't know, either.
Mr. Kim, take a deep breath
and breathe out.
If you just breathe well,
your desires will settle down.
Do you know how hard it is
to feel thirstier and thirstier
the more I drink water?
Even though I know
what I should drink to quench my thirst.
What do you think
would quench your thirst?
Human blood?
But how did you know that?
Who told you about it?
I just know.
When I see a pale neck,
my thirst gets worse.
We weren't using our guns for a reason!
Why are you here?
I'm here to help you two.
Where's my brother?
We'll go look for him.
For now, just get some rest.
I'm sure he's blaming me now.
I volunteered to do it…
It's just a disease.
He just needs to endure it
until the cure is out.
Lieutenant Colonel,
the cure is almost complete, right?
These are sleeping pills.
Take one when you need it.
Take one now and get some rest.
We should go outside and talk.
Couldn't you have just comforted her?
Why did you shoot Mr. Kim?
He was capable of having conversations.
The outside is full of people
who lost their families.
Mothers bite their kids,
and husbands bite their wives.
If you don't want to lose someone
close to you, then don't hesitate.
Why won't this heal?
I know you looked at me
when I gave her water, so be honest.
The virus is still lingering in your body.
It's like the remains.
Then I can end up biting people?
That's why we need
to keep collecting your blood.
We have to keep checking.
Is that why you're here?
Because you want to collect my blood?
About Seo-yoon's parents…
Did something happen?
Her father has been infected.
Her mother is still fine,
but she misses her daughter badly.
So you're here to take Seo-yoon?
Mad Human Disease is getting worse.
Not only in here
but also in the entire world.
I have to announce
some follow-up measures,
so let's gather the residents
after making sure this area is safe.
Lord…
Isn't it over?
They turn back to normal and switch
back and forth if they drink blood, right?
Maybe they bit someone,
turned back to normal, and went home.
Is everyone okay in there?
Open the door.
Anyone in there?
Yi-hyun, are you okay?
You're not tricking us
after you got bit, are you?
This is not something out of
The Wolf and the Seven Young Goats!
Stop being ridiculous
and open the door now!
He may be lying.
That's a lie.
Never be deceived by a handsome face.
Lord…
Sir, I can hear you.
-Open the door, Jung-kook!
-Don't.
What's taking you so long?
-Yi-hyun.
-What's your problem?
I almost got killed!
Hey!
Damn it!
This is crazy.
By the way, Jung-kook,
what in the world is going on right now?
You see,
I came here to get
dish soap and toothpaste,
and some guys with white eyes
suddenly attacked us.
Is anyone hurt?
No, thanks to the pastor.
He has spiritual powers.
-Now what kind of nonsense is that?
-It's true.
No way.
I didn't have a gun at that time…
Right, where's my gun?
Jung-kook, just calm down first.
Who opened the door to the first floor?
You see…
The guy upstairs.
He left the door open
with the supermarket lady and went up.
Yi-hyun.
Who locked the door earlier?
Would the people downstairs be okay?
If someone got hurt…
Then we just need
to get our stories straight.
We can just say that we ran away
when we saw the infected.
Then no one can hold us responsible.
Hi.
Oh, my.
You're such a beautiful young lady.
What's your name?
I'm Lee Bo-ram.
Thank you for the treat, ma'am.
Mom, here.
We're busy. Get out.
Fine.
Tell me if you need anything.
Okay.
Bye.
Don't they look cute together?
Don't get your hopes up.
Who would like a jobless loser like him?
Who cares? I married you too.
What?
I think someone's here.
Remember, just stick to our story.
Don't say anything stupid.
I mean it, okay?
We will talk on our own,
so just do your thing.
You two opened the apartment door, right?
What door?
We've been here this whole time.
It's a misunderstanding!
We went to the first floor,
and the door was already open,
so we got scared and ran away.
It's the truth.
Did you get bitten or scratched?
We just got scared and ran away.
That's all.
I'm fine, too. See?
Why did you go to the first floor?
Did you go outside because of this?
Give me that, I have to stream with it.
I risked my life to get that back.
One person went missing because of you.
If you're a human being,
you should have responsibility
at the very least.
Are they all okay?
Well, for now.
I really wanted to punch him a few times,
but I held back.
Where's Han Tae-seok?
At the rooftop.
He's going to look for the infected.
Is something wrong?
Seo-yoon's father
is infected.
That's why Han Tae-seok came in here.
I'm here to help, so don't worry.
Yes, it does seem so.
Haven't the infected come up here?
Two of them came up,
but I told them to go down over there.
I smashed that.
Did they just go down
when you told them to?
There aren't any infected
inside the building.
And it seems like Na Soo-min
went outside, infected.
You know their names too.
You must've done your homework.
Why did you come in here?
I'm sure you heard it from Ms. Yoon.
Yes.
I heard you're taking Seo-yoon.
But isn't it weird?
The Han Tae-seok I know
isn't that humanitarian.
You shot and killed someone a moment ago.
I don't know what you're thinking,
but I'm doing this to stop
the Mad Human Disease situation.
I'm sure…
you agree with me on that.
Is Sae-bom really okay?
Her wound won't heal.
There's no need to worry
unless the wound changes color.
Mad Human Disease is harmless
until it reaches the brain.
Besides Sae-bom,
there are a lot of people
who recovered from that state, right?
There were four of them.
They were confirmed to be infected
through recent tests.
It's just a matter of time.
They couldn't avoid the disease after all.
When will the cure be out?
We're looking for antibodies
that can get into the brain.
We can't develop the cure
until we find that.
So that means…
The situation…
will keep getting worse…
until we find the antibodies.
What are you doing?
We gathered the residents, so come down.
I'll tell Seo-yoon first.
There's a message from Seo-yoon's mother.
Can I talk to her alone, please?
You're Seo-yoon, right?
You're the man who was on TV, aren't you?
You talked about Mad Human Disease.
Yes, you're very smart.
I get that a lot.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Would you like something to eat?
We have combat rations.
Mister?
Yes?
Let's eat that next time.
I'm just here to check on you.
I made a promise to your parents.
Do you know my mom and dad?
Park Yong-chul and Kang Eun-ji.
I saw them this morning.
Do they miss me?
A lot.
Do you want to see them?
You can get out if you want.
Can Sae-bom go out with me too?
Of course. Ms. Yoon's mother
is outside too.
I'm sure she misses
her mother a lot, just like you.
You make the decision. I'll help you.
-Yi-hyun, you--
-If Seo-yoon gets out…
You go first.
What would you do if you get the disease?
What disease?
Mad Human Disease.
You know, you could get infected too.
Of course.
Of course, I can get infected too.
It's not like it's a crime.
If I get infected
and feel thirsty and want to bite people,
then I will make sure to tell you.
So…
you should also tell me
if anything happens.
I will.
I'm done talking to her.
Let's go meet the residents.
Old man,
your son could've gotten us all killed!
How dare you look at me like that?
You little brat!
Aren't you infected?
Does it look like I'm infected?
Stop it already!
-You rude brat…
-Who did this?
Who told you to gather without
the building representative's permission?
I heard someone came in from the outside.
Has anyone seen that person?
Have you? Who is it?
He's a military man.
Are you sure you saw it right?
You look like you can't see well.
Are you kidding?
Can you please get out of the way?
He was on TV.
I'm Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok
from the Crisis Management Center.
Sir, is the lockdown over?
-Really?
-It's over, right?
-Can we get out?
-When can we get out?
The whole city will be in lockdown…
and the electricity
will be cut off tonight.
Why would you cut off the electricity?
Are you trying to get us
all killed or what?
We're planning to fix it
as soon as possible.
Then you should lift
the lockdown at least!
You should let
healthy people out, at least!
-This is a violation of human rights!
-We don't even live here!
You should let us go home at least!
Lieutenant Colonel.
People are exhausted.
Locking us up in here won't do anything.
I have a friend who's a one-star rank.
Give me your phone. Let me make a call.
Sir…
It'll be over when I call him.
That's not what's important right now!
What?
What the heck?
What's going on?
This is not a drill.
Citizens, this is not a drill.
As of now, Martial Law
has been declared all over Seyang.
Martial Law?
This is not a drill.
Citizens, this is not a drill.
I'll go check on Seo-yoon.
-I'll go to the gym.
-Want me to go with you?
No, I'll go with Jung-kook later.
Be careful.
If it's dangerous,
you shouldn't hesitate either.
If something happens,
I'll take responsibility.
Don't worry.
The spread of Mad Human Disease
also brought the spreading
of false rumors,
crimes such as panic buying, theft,
and assault, as well as other forms
of extreme disturbance in society.
Therefore, to restore public order,
to protect the lives
and properties of the people,
and to end the crisis and maintain order,
the government
has declared Martial Law in Seyang.
Sae-bom.
From this point onwards, we ask citizens…
It's okay.
They're just trying
to make it sound scary.
As you heard,
it is also dangerous outside.
Just four days.
In four days,
the Martial Law will be lifted
and the lockdown level
on the apartments will be lowered.
Why cut the electricity, though?
Some people in
the power plant got infected also.
Except for a few necessary places,
it'll be cut off everywhere else.
-What?
-And the entire city
will have restrictions on going
out of the house, like this place.
Is the situation outside
that bad right now?
There's an overall shortage
of necessities and drinking water.
And violence is breaking out
around the city as well.
Well then, it might be safer inside.
Come on, we've been enduring it
quite well until now.
Four days?
That can actually be pretty short,
don't you think?
Trust me, and let's endure it
just a bit longer.
About Mad Human Disease…
I heard that there's a drug
that causes it if you take it.
Is that true?
We're still checking
on its relations to the disease.
So it is true.
Now, go home and charge
what you need to charge,
and fill your sinks
and bathtubs with water.
Once the electricity is off…
the water will be off too.
Don't worry.
Koreans are known for being able
to overcome national crises quite well.
Thank you, Mr. Kook.
I'll fill the bathtub at my house too.
Seo-yoon.
You talked to that military man, right?
I don't know how
the outside world is, either.
It may be better than here,
or worse than here.
Seo-yoon, do you want
to see your mom and dad?
I don't drink water that much.
It's not because
I think of you as a burden.
But if you want to stay here,
I will do my best to protect you,
and help you meet your parents.
I'm only asking you how you feel.
I want to see them…
But that military man is a bit weird.
Why? How?
It's just… he seemed like
he was interested in you.
He asked me how you were
and if you were sick.
Would this be enough?
It may be dangerous outside.
I'll be right back.
What about Seo-yoon?
She wants this given to her mom and dad.
If you're worried
about Seo-yoon going out alone,
then you can go out with her.
We don't know when
-she will be able to meet--
-Why are you here?
I'm here to find even the smallest
possibility of solving this situation.
It looks like you're here to take me,
but I don't know why.
Does it have to do with this?
I guess I can say that.
We found an antibody in your blood.
We must check
if that antibody is effective first.
Even if it means…
getting you bitten by the infected.
Don't shoot!
What?
Didn't you just hear the sound of gunfire?
Martial Law was declared.
I guess that was a warning shot.
Hey, Yi-hyun.
You're close to Han Tae-seok, right?
-No.
-Hey.
Can you please tell him
to take me with him when he leaves?
I'm having a hard time.
Is it because you're worried
about your wife?
Okay. I'll talk to him about it.
I'm sure your wife is fine. Don't worry.
Didn't you say Kim Seung-beom is dead?
He's there…
What the…
They cut his brain open.
Why would they do that to a dead person?
We're looking for antibodies
that can get into the brain.
We can't develop the cure
until we find it.
This isn't healing well.
There's no need to worry
unless the wound changes color.
Mad Human Disease is harmless
until it reaches the brain.
He's here to take Sae-bom,
to find the antibody.
You stay here.
If Han Tae-seok comes,
stop him, no matter what.
Seo-yoon, why are you outside?
It's dangerous. Stay inside.
I heard the sound of a gun.
Is Sae-bom okay?
She went outside with scissors in her hand
to deliver my letter.
Let's go inside first.
She's a better fighter than I am.
You know that, right?
So you don't need to worry.
Go inside and lock the door.
I'll be right back, okay?
Sae-bom!
Ms. Yoon is in pain. Get out of the way.
Sae-bom is injured.
Han Tae-seok took her.
Damn it!
Target secured. Going up.
Don't pity the infected too much.
They can control their thirst
if they have the will.
Hey!
If you messed with Sae-bom,
I'm going to kill you.
Don't move, if you don't want to die.
That tranquilizer was strong enough
to knock an elephant out.
I guess I'm better than an elephant.
I'm going easy on you
because you didn't kill that guy.
Sae-bom, are you hurt?
I'm fine. Totally fine.
Calm down.
Long time no see, First Lieutenant.
Tell them to lower their guns
if they don't want
anything ugly to happen.
Lower your guns.
Ms. Yoon,
what should we do to get you tested?
You jerk!
Hey.
I'm not doing this
because I like you people.
I'm doing this
because it'll help with the cure.
Thank you.
Wait.
Prepare boxed lunches
for the apartment residents,
with lots of meat.
And I heard you took…
Kim Seung-beom's body.
I know you will need to handle it
as part of the procedure,
but at least let his family know.
The situation is bad outside,
so it will take time to contact them.
And my mom…
Your mother is doing fine
at the nursing home.
Lieutenant Colonel took care of it.
Don't worry.
But why did you cut Mr. Kim's brain open?
Are you looking for antibodies?
I told you that Mad Human Disease
works on the brain.
We sometimes find antibodies
in the blood of dead infected people.
But they can't penetrate the brain.
The body has the antibodies,
but they can't get into the brain.
So you cut the brains
of the infected open?
To see if they have
antibodies in their brains?
Then what about Sae-bom?
Were you trying to cut
Sae-bom's brain open too?
No.
I must collect her blood.
The test can be done with her blood.
Can you make the cure
with Sae-bom's blood?
A new kind of monoclonal antibody
was found from Ms. Yoon's blood.
We'll have to do more tests.
It may be able to penetrate
the blood-brain barrier
and enter the brain.
That means Sae-bom is very important
to the Republic of Korea.
It is possible.
Then give me a few weapons
so I can protect Sae-bom.
Will you be okay?
What do you mean?
We're not sure about her antibodies.
Her disease can occur at any time.
That's why I should be by her side,
so I can watch over her.
Yi-hyun!
Hey, I'm done!
The blood has been collected.
Let's go. I'll get you the items you want.
But why are you going so far for this?
Even sneaking into the apartments.
Don't say nonsense like
you want to save the infected.
It's because of money.
Many rich and powerful people
got infected too.
That's why we're handling
all this in secret.
If they hear about it,
they're going to have
themselves cured first,
even if it means taking
all of Ms. Yoon's blood.
Then the development of the cure,
which will make the real money,
will get delayed.
You care about money,
and I care about Sae-bom.
Don't mess with us ever again.
And when this is over,
I will reveal what you did,
so keep that in mind.
Go ahead.
I'll take responsibility
for everything I've done.
Mr. Kim, no smoking.
Open the door.
Jung-kook, are you okay?
Yes.
The blood on Sae-bom's face…
That wasn't Sae-bom's blood.
Don't worry.
-Yi-hyun.
-Yes?
My gun.
Right.
Thank you for this.
I heard something serious
happened at the gym.
Is the woman from the fourth floor okay?
I will tell you if we need help.
I'll take these.
I told you to just take it
and shove it in your mouth!
I'm checking the expiration dates, okay?
Jeez.
I thought he'd kill him,
but he just shot him on the shoulder.
And he didn't wait
until I got bitten, either.
Don't shoot!
Still, he's a bad guy.
I know that, but…
he seemed desperate too.
Four days. We just need
to endure it for four days.
Then everything will be back to normal.
Are you going to cooperate…
with that weirdo on the sixth floor?
No, he's totally hopeless.
We need someone.
Someone who has power,
but will follow our orders.
Where would we find someone like that?
Hello?
Is the pastor inside?
I want to thank him
for saving my life and pray together.
Hi.
Come in.
Okay.
Are you just going to keep watching that?
Then what else can I do in here?
Go take out the trash.
You said you hate it when it stinks.
Jeez.
There's no other husband like me on Earth.
Hi, Mr. Kook.
Hi.
You must be here to take out the trash.
Yes.
Mr. Oh shouldn't be making
his guest do something like this.
Give me that.
We can't take them out properly
until the lockdown is over.
What is it?
Should I take them downstairs?
I'm just so scared.
What happened?
Is Mr. Oh harassing you?
Please help me, Mr. Kook.
What should we do with the food waste?
Should we put it in the freezer?
The freezer isn't a trash can.
Give me that.
Is there a place to throw it away?
You must be out of your mind!
We pay the maintenance fee.
Oh Joo-hyung killed Director Park.
Really?
He told me.
I'll be dead too if you don't help me.
I thought I'd just wait until I got out,
but Martial Law has been declared.
Of course, I must help you.
I'll protect you, Ms. Woo.
I knew you would help me out.
Everything's okay…
What were you doing outside?
I took out the trash.
Dressed like that?
This is how I'm always dressed.
I can't wear
Director Park's clothes all the time.
Are you thirsty?
I'm not infected, so don't worry.
What should we do with Ms. Yoon's blood?
Test it only at the labs
with Biosafety Level 3.
Yoon Sae-bom got up
after being injected with a tranquilizer.
That wasn't a quantity
a human being can handle.
Perhaps the virus is in her brain already.
Fast recovery is
a characteristic of the infected.
But the test result was clean.
Maybe the antibody has formed perfectly.
Be careful so the higher-ups don't notice.
No one can get their hands on her
until we get something. Okay?
Yes, sir.
How are Park Seo-yoon's parents?
The father is now a severe patient,
and the mother still has minor symptoms.
Show this to them
when they're in a better condition.
TO MOM AND DAD
It'll help them a bit.
Seo-yoon.
Yes, I'm coming.
Is this okay to eat?
Will the electricity really be cut off?
Yes, it will.
This refrigerator was treated
like a priceless heirloom.
It's useful in times like this.
Is the soybean paste
in the veranda okay to eat?
I'm the one who made it.
It's better than the ones sold in stores.
Why?
Ma'am, sir, I must get going.
Dong-hyun isn't coming out?
Do you have a place you can go to?
I should go down to the second floor.
But I heard you caused trouble there.
Is it okay for you to go there?
Then, take care.
But…
Okay, then. Goodbye.
You're just so heartless.
Dong-hyun takes that after you.
Young lady.
We have an empty room,
so stay here if you want to.
Really? Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Soo-min!
Hey, Hyun-kyung.
I'm fine. I'm here to tell you that…
Do you have a place to sleep at?
I'm a bit scared, but…
I can't go inside your house.
I don't know what I might do to you.
Soo-min,
I'm sorry…
Hey, don't be.
Why are you sorry?
It was my fault.
Hyun-kyung, can I…
ask you a favor?
If something terrible…
happens to me…
please take care
of my family.
Soo-min,
you'll be fine.
They said the cure will be out soon,
so just wait…
Soo-min.
WIFE: COME HOME SOON
I HAVE TO MAKE A HOSPITAL APPOINTMENT
BUT I'M SCARED TO GO ALONE
JUST WAIT A BIT, OKAY?
Just wait a bit, okay?
It's delicious.
Really?
Let me take a bite too.
It's not bad.
See? Trust me when it comes to food.
Seo-yoon, be careful with your hands.
It's still hot.
You eat so well.
-Isn't it delicious?
-Yes.
There may be more infected people inside.
I saw something weird.
Where did you find this?
I saw a wound on her hand.
Dad, you know something's wrong
with Mom, don't you?
Someone infected
is hiding in there, right?
It's better to get rid of those
who may cause problems.
Did you spike the drinks with this?
I just need you two dead.
The rest are just bonuses.
How could you come up
with such a crazy idea?
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee