ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGIONS,
EVENTS, AND OCCUPATIONS
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
JUNG YI-HYUN,
THE PRIDE OF SEYANG HIGH SCHOOL
HIS KNEE IS BUSTED!
HE'S DOOMED!
The megaphone.
Jung Yi-hyun!
I know how you feel.
I was in Little League too.
So come down and talk. Come down.
You can just talk from there.
-What did he say?
-I couldn't hear him.
Then give him a megaphone too.
I'll go up there, so wait a bit.
Let's talk when I get up there.
Where are the stairs?
He's just not coming down.
Focus on your books.
If you focus, you can't even hear
a bomb exploding next to you.
But classes are over.
Why aren't we going home?
No one can focus right now anyway.
Do you think Yi-hyun would be
happy if you ran out in a crowd?
He's already mentally unstable.
And if he jumps off impulsively
after seeing you guys,
I'm sure that'll help you focus
when you get home.
So you'll send us home
if he comes down, right?
Yes, I'll send you home right away.
The police are negotiating with him,
so don’t provoke me.
Just lie on your desk and sleep.
You've been a student for a long time.
It must be hard for you too.
-I'm going to the restroom.
-Hey, I told you not to provoke me…
Well, let's just keep quiet, please.
Hey, all of you, focus!
Focus on your books.
The bomb is being dropped.
I will make sure
that you're all cured, okay?
If that can't be done,
I'll make you a cop at the very least.
So trust me and come down, okay?
I don't want to be a cop.
All right!
I'm his friend. I was told to come up
so I can help negotiate with him.
Talk here. I won't go. Talk here, okay?
Calm down first.
Yoon Sae-bom?
Hey!
Hey, young lady!
Wait!
Who are you?
-Are you his girlfriend?
-No.
Hey, we can't go home because of you!
Mister, I will persuade him,
so wait there for a moment.
What's wrong with
the students at this school?
Are you upset you can't play baseball?
That's not what it is.
I just came up here
because I was frustrated,
but ambulances and police cars
suddenly arrived.
Which idiot made a report?
I'm just waiting to see
how far this will go.
I have nothing to do anyway.
Don't you have anything to do
besides baseball?
I don't.
I did it my entire life.
I was really good at it too.
And I ended up like this.
Would you be okay if you were me?
I did nothing my entire life,
but I was okay.
Hey, doing nothing is way better.
I was hospitalized for a long time.
And you know, it all just becomes
a good memory later on.
I can't play baseball ever again.
My life is over.
I don't know what to do in my life.
What about you, then?
What are you going to do?
I wanted to be a nurse until last week,
but a public official seems nice too.
I would need a monthly paycheck,
but I keep changing my mind.
See? You're feeling unsettled too
for being two years behind.
No.
I'm saying there's no limit
to our futures.
It's okay, so just do it,
and think that it's fine
even if it doesn't work.
Like me.
No, Mister.
I planned to make him fall
onto the cushion.
Okay, let's talk when we get there.
-Let go of me!
-Hey!
Jung Yi-hyun!
Tell him that you don't want me
to get punished.
He's going to arrest me.
Hey, Yoon Sae-bom.
Do you want to be my girlfriend?
12 YEARS LATER
SPECIAL OPERATION UNIT
Salute!
What are you doing? Treat him!
What are his injuries?
He got shot in the chest,
and he can't breathe.
It's a pneumothorax.
The air's leaking
from the hole in his lung
-and creating pressure--
-Don’t explain. Treat him!
TRAINEE LEE JONG-TAE
Do I really do it?
Don't think. Just do as you learned.
Instructor!
You're going to break my ribs, you jerk.
Instructor.
That was my clavicle, you idiot.
Trainee Lee Jong-tae,
you just killed your teammate.
You get a deduction on your TMP course.
TMP: A TACTICAL FIRST AID TRAINING COURSE
TEST SCORE
TMP COURSE
Your acting was great today.
-Did I do great?
-Yes.
Wear your gloves, or you'll slip.
Bye.
Are you really deducting points?
Yes, he's slow in making judgments,
and he's cowardly.
Based on your standards,
everyone in the world is slow, Sae-bom.
SPECIAL OPERATION UNIT
TRAINEE YOON SAE-BOM
-Salute!
When someone gets shot and can't breathe,
what are you supposed to--
What the…
Hey, don't do that!
Yoon Sae-bom!
What are you doing?
They had to make this because of you.
You stabbed his chest directly with it
and had Team Chief Choi
demoted to a patrol division.
He called me recently
and said it's the perfect place for him.
Really?
He sent me a gift coupon.
Then what about me?
Why didn't he send me one?
I'm sure he had a reason.
I'm hungry.
Let's go eat.
MOTEL
Hello, this is the front desk.
Yes, I can hear it too.
The second floor?
Okay, I'll go talk to them.
What are they doing
at this early hour? Seriously…
Excuse me, you have to pay
if you damage the motel's property.
Do you want to get beaten up?
It's hard to endure weather
that's gradually getting hotter,
but we're happy for being able
to breathe without wearing masks now.
The world has changed a bit
from before the COVID-19 pandemic,
but thanks to that, we learned
how precious normal daily lives are.
Dear listeners, I hope you can smile
looking at each other's uncovered faces,
take a deep breath
upon looking at the blue sky,
and have a great afternoon.
Dear listeners, have a great day,
and tomorrow…
COVID-19 MAY BE OVER BUT WE DON'T KNOW
WHEN ANOTHER DISEASE MAY BREAK OUT AGAIN
JUNG YI-HYUN
Here.
Hey, do you still want to play
baseball even with that knee?
I get paid to play for this team.
-What kind of a case is it?
-Murder.
You didn't even know what the case was?
I was told to come, so I came.
I even gave up my day off and my game.
-You should thank me.
-Oh, thank you so much.
People from the next room reported it.
-I heard the scream and--
-Excuse me.
-Who's the victim?
-The front desk employee.
Let's go.
-All I need to do is testify?
-I can't believe this.
What did they do to his neck?
Well, that looks like
it was done with a dull blade, right?
Perhaps they wanted him to suffer.
-Who's the suspect?
-The guest who stayed here.
There were a lot of complaints
because he was so noisy.
But who covered him with this?
-Did you meddle with the crime scene?
-No, we didn't touch anything.
-Any witnesses?
-None so far.
He said it was like this from the start.
Did they check the security cams?
Right. The security cams.
Hey, what about the security cams?
They're checking it now,
but they can't find the suspect leaving.
He covered the victim's face and ran away.
But the camera didn't catch him leaving.
I'm sure he did
an electronic access register,
but the CDSCHQ won't let us see it.
It's a breach
of personal information protection.
Hey, killers have no rights.
They should integrate
the information and arrest all of them.
I don't understand.
Oh, I didn't mean you.
Okay.
I'm sure they didn't
search in there, right?
Hey, I know you investigate recklessly,
hoping for good luck, but--
It can't even go near the "reckless" part.
I know someone who's even more…
Sir…
come out.
Are you kidding me?
If this is another joke,
I'm going to kill you today.
Damn it!
Our eyes just met.
Hey, we got the culprit. Don't come in.
Come in later.
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD, SUNG WOO-JAE
Did you do this, Mr. Sung Woo-jae?
I don't know.
Did you cover the body
because you were scared to see the body?
Then why did you kill him?
You don't remember that either?
I had a dream, but…
Was the dream about killing him?
You’re covered in blood,
so you couldn't run away.
You were panicking, but the police came,
so you must've hidden.
By the way, where's the weapon?
What did you kill him with in the dream?
Oh, that's right.
The court won't acknowledge it
if there's no weapon.
You see,
I was thirsty for some reason, so…
Did you bite him?
Give me one more.
ONE MAIN SIDE DISH PER PERSON
Were you doing physical labor or what?
Why are you eating so much?
I'm upset, so don't say anything.
Here.
If you have something to say, go ahead.
SEYANG FOREST LE CIEL
PUBLIC RENTAL APARTMENT NOTICE FOR POLICE
What are you reading?
They're developing
the National Police Agency's old location.
They're building apartments.
Three police officers' households
will get special provisions for that.
Really? What are the conditions?
My wife's dream is to move
into that new apartment.
They give extra points
for long-term service,
family members to provide for,
and newlyweds.
The biggest chunks come from
arrest records and work evaluations.
Once I'm chosen,
I'll get an apartment for sure.
It's like winning the lottery.
Who are we going to arrest? Terrorists?
You never know
what might happen in life, okay?
If I show something today…
What are you going to show?
I'm thinking.
Take it easy with sports.
Don't get injured again.
Okay.
(I AM) THE LIFESAVER
Sae-bom, are you religious now?
It's my friend.
The timing isn't very…
Hey, what is it?
Your unit was mentioned
during an investigation, so…
Why?
You're instructing
a training course, right?
He said he got drugs from an SOU trainee.
He said the drug was perfectly legal.
I'm sure he just meant
you wouldn't get caught.
Do you have any leftover drugs?
I received three or four tablets,
but I think I took them all.
-What's the name of the trainee?
-Lee Jong-tae.
Lee Jong-tae?
Salute!
TRAINEE LEE JONG-TAE
Anyway, we're sending the document.
I thought you should know.
Well done.
If I find the entire gang,
then I'll get an arrest record.
What are you talking about?
I'm just letting you know.
I'll be back soon,
so keep an eye on my food.
It's more important than food?
That's strange.
Don’t worry. I warned everyone
that they're dead
if they eat your pork cutlet.
What are they doing?
Are they actually having sex here?
Those punks…
Trainee Lee Jong-tae.
Trainee Lee Jong-tae!
Help!
What is that?
Lee Jong-tae, stop right there!
Seung-young, take him and go.
Next, it'll be your pelvis.
What is that?
How should I know?
I'll stay here,
so you take him and get him treated.
We have an emergency patient!
Anyone there?
This is not a drill!
Instructor, please call an ambulance.
Instructor!
Instructor…
Get the medical trolley.
Be careful not to get bitten.
(I AM) THE LIFESAVER
Hey.
You should've told me it was dangerous!
I almost got killed!
What are you saying?
Why would you get killed?
How could he not feel pain
even when he got shot?
Who shot who? Hey, are you okay?
I'm okay, of course, but…
How could you catch someone
like that without a gun?
I just persuaded him by talking to him.
How is that possible?
You could get through to him?
Hey, tell me what happened in detail.
Did you meet Lee Jong-tae?
Yes.
Did he… try to bite you?
So you do know about it.
What kind of nonsense is this…
Hello? Hey, Yoon Sae-bom!
Hey, are you okay?
Hey, answer me! Hey!
Yes?
Why didn't you answer? You scared me.
Corporal Yoon Sae-bom.
This is the ladies' restroom.
The guy you shot.
There's a possibility
he has an infectious disease.
What infectious disease?
We're currently investigating.
Sae-bom, who are you talking to right now?
Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok from
the Crisis Management Center at CDSCHQ.
Corporal Yoon will call you back.
Give me your gun and cooperate
with the disease investigation.
Who are you people?
-You can eat my pork cutlet.
-Sae-bom.
The National Police Agency
will send guidelines soon.
What happened earlier was an accident.
So keep this secret.
Corporal Yoon has the risk
of infection, so we're taking her.
(I AM) THE LIFESAVER
-Hello?
-Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok?
Wait, please don't hang up.
I'm Corporal Jung Yi-hyun
from Seyang Police Station.
Can you please briefly explain
what's going on?
Corporal Yoon has been in contact with
an infected trainee so she must be tested.
Does that mean she's okay now?
She's essential personnel,
so she's fully vaccinated too.
What infection are you talking about?
We'll have to find out. I'll hang up now.
It's Lee Jong-tae, right?
The infected trainee.
We also arrested a murder suspect
who was in contact with Lee Jong-tae.
Did you say murder?
He bit someone's neck.
Is that symptom related to the infection?
Did you say Seyang Station? I'll be there.
Wait.
Should all those who were
in contact be in quarantine too?
If they were bitten or scratched, yes.
SEYANG POLICE STATION
As long as you weren't bitten
or scratched, you're fine.
You're Mr. Han Tae-seok, right?
Where's Sae-bom?
She's being tested in a safe place.
THE 3RD WONJUNG UNIVERSITY
ANTI-REDEVELOPMENT RALLY
WONJUNG UNIVERSITY
DEPARTMENT OF ENGINEERING
STOP
LIEUTENANT COLONEL HAN TAE-SEOK
You're military,
but you're doing civilian work.
It's important to show that
the two can cooperate in times of crisis.
So this is an infectious disease
that makes people bite other people?
We're thinking that it's
a mutant virus that affects the brain.
When you're bitten, you either die
from excessive bleeding or get infected.
Gosh, droplets aren't enough anymore,
now the diseases even spread from bites.
The infection channels are limited,
so don't worry,
and just work hard
on your assigned duties.
Hang on.
We don't need to be
in self-quarantine, right?
You just need to write
and sign a confidentiality oath.
That suspect said that he did it
after he took drugs.
The drugs he received
from his SOU trainee friend.
Do you have that drug?
No.
Maybe it's just a side effect
of a hallucinogenic, not a disease.
There's no possibility of that,
but it may have had an influence.
Contact me when you find the drug.
Corporal Jung Yi-hyun.
Are you playing baseball again?
You were quite
a rising star in high school.
I can't run at my full speed anymore, so…
That's too bad.
He must be a big baseball fan.
He recognized you.
Did Sung Woo-jae get tested for narcotics?
Yes, we sent his hair to KCSI.
I'll give you a number,
so track it down and find where it is.
-Hey, where are you going?
-To find the drug.
Jung-kook, I found it.
I'm calling you
so you won't waste your time.
The test results just came out.
It's perfectly clean.
Oh, really?
Yes, I guess it really is
an infectious disease.
Would it be okay for me to go home today?
Hey, if I show my teeth to my wife…
-Wait…
-Then I'll lose all of them.
Then what about what I found?
Cold remedies, painkillers, vitamins…
There are all kinds of drugs.
Stop wasting your time. Just go home.
SUPER ROOKIE BASEBALL ACADEMY
Hey, Il-ho.
Hey, why didn't you play
at the game today?
Come inside.
You should call me
or answer my calls, at least.
Everyone nagged me about it.
Stop nagging me.
Hey, more than that…
Look at this.
What is this?
I think it's a narcotic.
Do you know what it is?
Why would you bring this to me?
Don't get the wrong idea
and listen to me, okay?
You got kicked out because of drugs.
I only took it by mistake.
You call yourself a friend?
No, you were trying
to get better at baseball.
I wanted to be good too,
but it didn't work out.
Don't even bring up the past.
Right. The past.
You later made up your mind
and studied very hard.
Sports medicine and computers.
This is really important to me, all right?
This isn't a narcotic.
Why not?
Do you see the serial numbers here?
No one does that for narcotics.
This was made by a pharmaceutical company.
You'll be able to find it
in the pharmaceutical database.
-Find out what it is.
-Me?
-Until when?
-Now.
Wake me up when you're done.
Are you collecting my blood, too?
What is this place?
It doesn't look like a hospital.
It looks like a school.
We can't set neck-biting infected free
in a place crowded with people.
Am I going to become like
Trainee Lee Jong-tae, too?
I was teasing. I won't bite.
-You'll get hurt if you do that.
-So please answer me.
I thought you were putting ointment on me.
What should I do now
until the results come out?
Testify.
Tell me about what happened today.
I saw Trainee Lee Jong-tae
attacking a fellow trainee,
and tried to stop him.
How did Lee Jong-tae seem?
He was in a bad condition.
Be more specific, please.
Both of his eyes were milky,
like he had cataracts,
and he tried to bite me like a beast.
I shot him twice, but it seemed like
he couldn't feel any pain.
Is this like some kind of rabies?
It's similar.
My detective friend said that
he might've been on narcotics.
If someone goes mad and bites a person,
the police would believe
that it was because of drugs.
Because that's the easiest answer.
And an infectious disease is
an easier answer for you.
Because people see what they believe.
But…
aren't you a police officer, too?
We specialize in dealing
with terrorist attacks.
We only get paid by the police.
Is Trainee Lee Jong-tae…
okay?
He's miraculously recovering.
We will get you a place to rest
until the test results come out.
Aren't you giving my phone back?
We'll bring a telephone to your room.
UNKNOWN NUMBER
-Hello?
-You got me into this mess!
Yoon Sae-bom?
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
It's cleaner than
the public official apartment.
That place is over 50 years old.
It always leaked
and the pipes froze in winter.
And they put three people into one house!
It's cold.
Can they afford to pay
the electricity bills?
How's your condition? Did you get tested?
Yes, I got tested for everything.
Goodness, I got this year's
health checkup all cleared.
I have to stay here
until the results come out.
I told your mom about you.
You couldn't wait for half a day?
Hey, no news is good news.
Don't worry, okay?
I told her you're busy
because of the training.
Well, you've got that much sense,
at least.
I'm also looking into this
to find out what's going on.
By the way, where are you?
I don't know.
It looks like a school dormitory.
Hey, don't worry.
I'm sure they won't kill me.
I don't feel particularly ill,
so I can just rest up
until the results are out.
We got the narcotics test results
for our suspect, and he's clean.
Really?
Is it really an infectious disease?
From what I see, it's narcotics.
You really are a cop.
What do you mean?
It's nothing.
Anyway, I'll catch the culprit
and let you rest without any worries,
so just rest there a bit, okay?
Okay, I'll look forward to it.
It's late. Go to bed.
LYTTA VIRUS RESULT REPORT
TEST RESULT: VIRUS NOT FOUND
POSSIBILITY OF FIRST ANTIBODY
NO SYMPTOMS
NO POSSIBILITY OF INFECTION
BUT NEEDS MORE OBSERVATION
YOON SAE-BOM
GRADUATED HIGH SCHOOL 2 YEARS LATE
ENLISTED IN SOU
AFTER DROPPING OUT OF NURSING SCHOOL
ALWAYS EXTREMELY CALM
SMART AND STRONG
EXCESSIVELY CURIOUS
SUPER ROOKIE BASEBALL ACADEMY
Hey, get up. I found it.
What?
You found it?
Let me see.
"Next."
"Next"?
What is that?
Oral medication for pneumonia.
Many antivirus studies
took place during COVID-19.
It came out then,
but the side effects were serious,
so it was quickly dropped.
Side effects?
Addiction, hallucinations, mood swings…
And enhanced concentration too.
It had one good thing about it, at least.
Then why did it pass the drug test?
Causing hallucinations
doesn't just make it a narcotic.
It's a narcotic only when
the law says it's a narcotic.
Hey, Il-ho.
By any chance…
what if this causes something like rabies?
There will be a frenzy.
This has spread widely already.
But that's not going to happen.
Why not?
Nothing has happened until now.
Why would things suddenly go wrong?
SEYANG POLICE STATION
Jung-kook, did you track down that number?
Oh, wait. Here.
They're at a university. Is it a student?
Isn't this a crappy university?
I guess they had terrible grades.
Thanks.
Hey…
Was I too harsh?
No one wakes me up
and I don't have to go to work.
How nice.
It's cold.
Ms. Yoon Sae-bom, please come out.
First Lieutenant, when did you…
Are the test results out?
We're testing you again.
First Lieutenant, please tell me
before you cut my flesh off today.
My feelings will be really hurt.
Are there other patients here, too?
Lee Jong-tae?
-Let me talk to him.
-No.
Ms. Yoon Sae-bom!
It won't take long.
Are you okay?
I feel a bit cold, but I'm okay.
Do you remember being shot by me?
Yes.
What about biting your fellow trainee
and attacking me?
I don't know.
You do remember.
Ms. Yoon Sae-bom, stand back!
It may be dangerous!
It's okay. He looks fine right now.
Did you go mad after taking a drug?
Where did you get that drug?
I don't know what you're talking about.
The guy you gave
the drug to got arrested already.
You know you'll get an additional penalty
because you're a police officer, right?
Do you see this?
You scratched me, Jong-tae.
They say it's an infectious disease,
but I'm not sure.
We have to find out if it's
a disease or if it's because of the drug.
Understand?
That's the only way
I can be relieved and get tested.
Can I have a drink of water, please?
Absolutely not!
I'm just so thirsty.
She said you can’t.
I'm thirsty.
Hey, what are you doing?
Open your eyes. I'm talking to you.
Hey.
Lee Jong-tae.
Give me water. I'm thirsty.
Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok,
are you there?
THERE ARE NO REDEVELOPMENT PLANS
DO NOT BE FOOLED
You are approaching your destination.
WE OPPOSE REDEVELOPMENT
You have reached your destination.
Ending route guide.
How can we help you?
Isn't this Wonjung University?
It was closed for being substandard
and now the military is using it.
I'm from the police.
Can I meet the person in charge?
This a classified military area,
so I'm afraid you can't.
Then please tell Lieutenant Colonel Han
that I brought the drug I told him about.
Let him in.
You made me meet Lee Jong-tae
on purpose, didn't you?
You even installed a camera there.
I wanted to know when he'd feel thirsty.
Thirsty?
The infected lose their senses
and bite people.
They feel extreme thirst…
but water can't quench it.
They keep feeling thirsty and going crazy
even after coming back to normal.
We're trying to find out
the conditions for that
and I was curious
about how Lee Jong-tae
would react if he saw you.
So you wanted to see how he would be
if he saw the one who shot him?
They can recognize their families,
so I wondered about the others.
That wasn't all of it.
His heart beat slower,
he seemingly felt less pain,
and his wound healed faster too.
If it can be controlled,
it can be lucrative.
So that's why
you're investigating it secretly.
It's not highly contagious,
but it can scare people.
Everyone's already tired of diseases,
so we don't need to make things worse.
So why do you turn
the air conditioners on?
The occurrence of the disease
slows down in low temperatures.
Is this a test too?
To see if I'm thirsty or not?
According to the test results,
you really are okay.
I'm usually not that lucky.
You need to get some rest for a while.
Here?
Wherever you want.
Really? Is that possible?
Just say you contributed to the nation
and got injured in the process.
And we have to collect
your blood every two weeks.
You're not showing any symptoms,
so it means the antibody
might have formed in your body.
THE ARMED FORCES MEDICAL COMMAND
I feel like I'm someone quite important.
One more thing.
I've contributed to the nation.
Then give me
top work evaluation points for this year.
What?
The apartments in Seyang
provided to the police officers.
The selection is based on points.
Newlyweds, family to provide for,
years in service, and work evaluation.
They're all added up.
You're powerful enough
to at least do that, right?
I think that would be possible.
You have a decent evaluation too, so…
I have the best evaluation.
I was born to subdue terrorist attacks.
I'm glad that we're on the same page.
-People don't shake hands these days.
-My phone.
By the way, don't you even offer
breakfast here?
Thank you. I'll enjoy this at home.
Do you have a boyfriend?
It's not that I don't like you,
but the age gap between us is way too big.
Work evaluation points won't be enough.
You'll need more points.
So I was wondering if you had a plan.
I can start making plans now.
Aren't you worried?
I will get the apartment,
so you don't need to worry.
I meant what you saw yesterday and today.
If something goes wrong,
the world may collapse.
Worrying won't change anything.
Perhaps it may not collapse.
First Lieutenant,
what about the clothes I was wearing?
We burned them.
Then should I go home in these?
Yoon Sae-bom? Hey.
Are you okay? Let me see.
First Lieutenant, can't you trust me?
I'm hurt.
They said I'm okay and told me to go home.
I'm sorry. This is because of me.
-You look thinner.
-Really?
It's because I didn't have breakfast.
How did you get in here?
-Did you get caught too? Were you bitten?
-No, I came to rescue you.
Wait here. I need to go talk to someone.
That punk.
I think you're good enough
to play baseball again.
Is this the drug?
Yes, I heard it's
a failed pneumonia medicine.
And I heard that tons of people
have taken that already.
I also heard that wasn't the cause,
but a promise is a promise.
Just because it was okay yesterday
doesn't mean it will be okay today.
Bye.
Come on. I'll take you home.
Yes, it was right next to me.
Yi-hyun.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Why are you asking that?
-Do you?
-I don't.
-Do you snore? Or grind your teeth?
-I don't think so.
Will you marry me?
Jung Yi-hyun!
Tell him that you don't want me
to get punished.
He's going to arrest me.
Hey, Yoon Sae-bom.
Do you want to be my girlfriend?
No.
I told you I was just kidding back then.
I'm not kidding.
I mean it.
If people suddenly start
to go mad like that…
Info on Han Tae-seok like you asked…
I seriously hate him.
I got a house.
It won't open.
The lower floors are public rentals,
and the upper ones are regular apartments.
I got a call from a journalist.
There's a way to make money,
and safety is guaranteed.
-Seung-young!
-We have a problem at the dorm.
Where are the seriously ill patients?
But aren’t they living human beings?
If we're late,
even more people will get hurt.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-lim Lee