Watch your nail.
How is it, Doctor?
This is just an early symptom
of alcoholism.
Chaba.
I'm not an alcoholic! I told you.
But he just said that.
I'm telling you I'm not.
Listen, Chaba.
If you're an alcoholic,
you'll be dizzy. Your hands will shake.
He isn't like that.
Right?
My name is Chaba.
My brother's name is Nun.
He's an alcoholic.
And I'm trying to get him to quit.
But I always fail.
But in the end,
do you know how he managed to quit?
Let's find out.
Let's start at where he got addicted.
It began with this girl...
Nun!
What's up, Ning Nong?
Let's stay away from each other.
I don't want to see you anymore.
Nun, you have no future.
I have to do what's best for me.
What is this?
You're just an AC maintenance guy.
I'm not okay with that.
Ning Nong!
But I love you.
Don't you remember?
When you're with me,
I do everything for you.
When your ears are itchy, I scratch them.
When your back is itchy, I scratch it.
When your butt is itchy,
I scratch it, too.
And when your...
Hey! Stop!
And let me go!
I won't!
I love you.
No! No!
Let me go!
You...
You want some more?
I don't want any,
but I don't want you to go.
If you don't stop, you'll eat this!
No! I won't stop!
I won't let you go!
Don't go!
Ning Nong! I won't let you!
Son of a bitch!
I'm right here.
Right on my face.
She's gone!
I'll call the cops on you.
Your car is not up to standard!
Ning Nong!
Are you really going to leave me?
If the word love
Has hurt you
Far too much
Can you tell me...
Listen to me.
You are valued.
And you don't need anyone.
Singh.
You just shut up.
-Hey.
-I was wrong again.
Listen to me carefully.
There must be something good.
This is how girls are.
They just pretend to be nice.
But a broken heart
does not know how to pretend.
Son of a bitch.
Shitty poem.
It doesn't even rhyme.
There are more girls than lizards.
They don't even care
when their lovers disregard them.
Toss that damaged heart,
get out of the shade.
Right in the heart.
Let's get wasted. Forget her.
Damn.
Cheers.
If the word love
Has hurt you
Far too much
Can you tell me?
Let me wipe your tear
That's it.
That's it with suffering.
I'll throw that away...
with this glass.
Yeah.
Hey!
From now on,
I will not suffer.
-You rock, Nun!
-Of course I do!
No more hurt feelings.
Only fun feelings.
We'll make merit by spreading liveliness.
Of course!
Almost dislocated my shoulder there.
I feel like I'm a hero now.
Hell yeah.
We are heroes of fun.
Cheers!
Whatever's next has to be fun.
I love you so much.
What's that?
HAPPY NEW YEAR HAPPY NEW YOU
-Hi, hello.
-Hi.
Sit down.
Wait.
-Uncle.
-Make yourself at home.
Hello, Uncle Cham.
-Hello.
-Who the hell are you guys?
Come on.
What kind of question is that?
I'm Nun.
Do I know you?
Why would I be here if you didn't?
I was here to fix your AC
five years ago.
Hey.
My AC only got installed seven months ago.
No.
The AC I'm talking about,
it was on the second floor.
My AC is on the floor downstairs.
You're messing it up.
-Why are you here?
-Well...
I heard there's a housewarming party.
For someone so close,
you'd be upset if I hadn't come.
Close?
We're close.
I'm bringing you some nice blessings.
-Okay.
-Well!
Come get your blessing.
He's not a monk,
but he's got some good blessings.
Okay.
I call for all blessings in the world.
Good, Singh.
Let you all be happy and well.
Let Uncle Cham be happy.
No suffering.
No poverty.
No sickness.
Only wealth.
Wealth!
Thank you.
Wait up, Uncle.
Let me ask you something.
Are they done praying?
Oh, they're done.
So what happens when they're done?
Well, they go eat.
I see.
Correct. And after that?
They go back to the temple.
What about the guests?
They also go home.
What? Before that!
They eat before that.
I see.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
Oh, come on! It's late! Why haven't you?
Why the fuck not?
What do you mean?
Remember? We're close.
-Right, I see.
-Just friends talking.
Then go eat.
Let me ask you frankly.
Are you okay doing this?
It looks like you're a bit uncomfortable
to let us go in and eat.
But that's okay. We can just go.
-Let's go!
-Hey. Wait.
Good luck, then.
Uncle!
What's that for?
Just kidding.
-Let's go eat.
-Which table?
Any table that's empty. Go find your seat.
I want some booze.
Okay. Sit down.
Hello, Father.
Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Bless you. We have the same hair.
Wow.
Who arranged this meal?
There's only chicken.
Here.
My gosh, how do you chew this stuff?
Right? Come on.
Let's go.
Let's get it.
The chicken is so chewy it's dangerous.
-What about this?
-That, too.
Oh, what's this?
That is chicken. And this is chicken, too?
Take it.
-Hey, what about this?
-Take it.
Fish maw soup? Pig skin?
They're dangerous for you monks.
It'll get stuck in your throat.
Why don't you take the rice, too?
If we do that, what would you eat, then?
Like you care.
I'm Thai, too.
-Hey, Cham!
-Yeah.
Who are they?
Close friends.
Are you close with them?
They are with me.
I actually don't know them.
How is that close?
What the hell?
And this soup. Would you like me
to put it on the monks' table?
Hold on. No.
-I'll give it to them.
-Okay.
-Cham.
-Yeah?
-Let's go.
-Let's go, then.
-Give it to them yourself.
-All right.
Wait, wait, wait!
-What?
-What are you doing?
Is this fish soup?
-Yeah, for the monks.
-Hey!
What were you thinking?
You killed a fish
to cook it for the monks?
This is a sin for us all. Are you crazy?
And we don't even know if this fish is
a daddy fish, a baby fish or a mommy fish.
What if someone killed your parents, huh?
Huh, Uncle? What would you say then?
Bring it here.
Hey. That's for the monks.
Hey! Bring it here.
No, that's for the monks.
I told you to bring it here.
For the monks.
Hey! My ceremony is fucking ruined.
Hey! You can't use that kind of language!
My ceremony is fucking ruined, sir!
That's nicer.
Chaba, your brother is causing
trouble here at Uncle Cham's.
-What?
-Come quick.
I'm going now.
Nun!
Wait. Help me!
Seab, get some water to clean him here.
Okay.
Quick!
You fugly face!
Please don't talk like that here.
Okay. You fugly face, sir.
That's nicer.
Seab! Who told you
to throw the water like that?
You did!
-You're talking back to me now?
-Why don't you do it yourself?
Hey! Stop talking back to me.
-Hey!
-Father!
-Hot!
-Water!
Father, come here.
-It's hot!
-Let's hurry.
What are you doing?
Come on now, jump.
Jump, Father! Jump!
Hey, Chaba.
-Yes.
-Over there!
Hey!
Come on, Father.
That must have been many gulps.
You can say "thank you" now.
I came down to help you.
He's so wet now.
Are these three your close friends?
I don't know them.
Why did you do this?
He could have died.
You didn't even know him.
Why did you even go there?
Oh, well. I know him.
I went to fix his AC once.
Fixing his AC once
doesn't mean you know him.
It means he's a customer.
You are so hard to be friends with.
You don't get it.
Thanks.
-You got it?
-Got it.
-Chaba.
-Oh, lots of snacks!
I didn't buy them.
This bag,
this comes from Noi,
the technique supervisor.
With a message.
"If you get tired of eating snacks,
you could come and eat me."
And this one,
this belongs to Peng,
the building supervisor.
With a message saying,
"Even if I look ordinary,
I'm groovy and serious about love."
Groovy, my ass.
Chaba won't be interested. You know why?
There.
Her bae is right there.
Hey. Come on.
-Chill.
-Always so flirty.
-Chaba.
-Yeah?
Yesterday, I saw your brother's gang going
to Aunty Sri's son's graduation party.
He knows a lot of people, right?
He doesn't really.
He's just there to get free food.
It kinda sucks.
Why?
Look at my brother.
What's going to happen when he's old?
He'll probably die of alcohol poisoning.
Sister Jim!
-Who's that?
-Hello.
Who the hell are you?
Here.
Don't touch me.
Don't you remember me? I'm Nun.
Nun who?
If you can't remember Nun,
then you must know Seab.
Seab who?
Look familiar?
I installed an AC at your house.
There are three ACs upstairs
and two downstairs.
But I don't know you people.
That's okay. What are you all doing?
-This is my brother's ordination ceremony.
-Is that so?
We're drinking now.
What are you drinking?
You wouldn't know.
Look, sister.
I can smell it from here.
Come on here.
Rice whiskey with red soda.
-So good.
-Come here.
How is it, Seab?
Chinese liquor and Pepsi.
Hey!
I don't know. You take care of him.
But you, Chaba...
I'll take care of you.
How would you take care of me, huh?
Well...
with my whole life.
What? Too cheesy?
I like it.
Really?
-What?
-Nun is causing trouble here.
-Just come quick.
-What? Shit.
What?
Hey! Where are you going?
Hey.
Hey, out of the way!
Move.
Let go of me.
I'm fine.
Jim, my dear, hello.
My dear, my ass.
We meet again.
Don't you guys have anywhere to go?
Everyone is here.
Is this your daughter?
My daughter.
-Do you dance at every ceremony?
-This is my first.
I see the daughter. I want to see the mom.
You want some?
Music!
Hey! Cool!
Stop!
Who the hell is this?
Jim, we only have one minute
of auspicious time left.
Say that to Father.
Wait for me. I'm having fun here.
No, you have to go in now.
That's easy.
-Seab.
-What?
Run!
Quick!
Let's move so they can make it.
Oh, my God!
-Fuck.
-Run!
Stop. Where do you think you're going?
We're done here, so we're leaving.
Leaving, my ass!
My brother's ordination is ruined.
You bastard!
Asshole!
Sinner!
-Your face looks like feet!
-Is that so?
I'll kick your ass.
Are you waiting for me?
I'm sorry.
Let's drink.
Happy birthday.
Cheers.
Happy birthday, my dear friend.
-Yeah.
-I wish you the best.
Get 10,000 baht while you sleep.
And more when you wake up!
You're so loud that I'm scared.
Amen.
If I do get 100,000,
I'll spend it all in one day.
Crazy.
-Who would spend that in a day?
-Right.
Have you guys forgotten?
I've got debts. My house, my student loan.
The interest is blooming
better than any flower.
Better than the one on your head.
Bitch, if it blooms more than this,
there's no point in working.
No wishes here.
I know you're already happy.
And you know I love you no matter what.
I'm going to throw up!
Okay, then.
Chaba.
What I told you
that I quit working here to go to Bangkok?
You aren't mad at me, right?
Nonsense. Why would I be mad?
I know why you want to go there.
You want to earn more money.
-I want to tell you...
-What?
Even though we're apart...
our hearts...
are together.
Am I still here?
Did I even come here today?
You two go sit upstairs, then.
Look at her smiling.
Chaba.
Happy birthday.
A ring?
Watch me.
This year...
I'm giving you this small gold ring.
And next year,
I'll give you a big gold necklace.
I hope you aren't just saying that.
-If you can't do it, it'll look bad.
-Yeah.
It's gold. Not some shit. It's not cheap.
Can you even do that?
Don't listen to them.
I believe you.
Thank you, Chaba.
It's quiet.
Damn!
Let me just fart to break the silence.
-Don't call it a fart.
-What do they call it, then?
They call it sending a message.
Hey, come on, let's get us some.
Hello!
Today,
it's my dear sister's birthday.
And what a coincidence.
It's also Seab's birthday.
Still single here.
That means today
is such a blessed day.
That makes sense.
-Nun.
-Yes.
Since it's my birthday...
-What's up, sis?
-Can I ask for a present?
You are my dear sister.
Don't just ask for one present.
Ask for many presents.
Tell me.
I want to ask
that you quit drinking for life.
Can you do that?
It's my birthday.
I ask every year.
-To quit drinking?
-Yes.
Well... okay.
You asked, so I'll have to do it.
I'll quit drinking for you, Chaba.
All right.
I'll quit for you. Hey, you guys...
Come.
Let's get our glasses together.
We will quit drinking now.
Can we still have beer?
Hey.
Please? A chilled beer tastes good.
-Don't say that.
-No more.
Thank you, Nun.
-We have to quit all drinking.
-You said it.
Yeah. I do.
Nun.
-Today is my birthday, too.
-Yes.
What do you want?
Can I ask...
that we all return to drinking?
Yeah!
You can't do that.
It's my birthday, too! Why not?
I was born today. No!
Wait. Everyone, stop.
Since it's my sister's birthday,
I'll give it to her.
Now my brother is asking.
Of course I'll give it to him.
Bottoms up!
What the hell.
Careful, you'll get drunk
on that green soda.
This is for you to snack on in the bus.
Chaba,
the reason I'm going to work in Bangkok
is for me to earn money to pay your debts.
Hey! But they're not your debts.
Your problem is mine.
I can do it. You'll see.
Come on.
Tee! Her debts are 100,000 baht.
You're daydreaming.
I only have you.
Of course I can do it.
Let's just say
it's our wedding dowry in advance.
You're going too far.
Are you serious?
I'll come back
and build a family with you.
Tee...
before doing that,
maybe you should check the time.
The bus is leaving, dude.
They're all waiting for you.
Are you going? Want a room here?
Go.
Take care of yourself.
You, too.
-Bye.
4 MONTHS LATER
Hey, did Tee get a job in Bangkok?
He told me he did.
I'm sorry. There's no job vacancy.
They said working in Bangkok is hard,
and life there is hard, too.
But he told me he's doing well.
Which company is he working at?
Right. He didn't tell me.
But he said he works at a big company
with a kind boss.
Hello.
Well, I'm happy for him, then.
Yeah.
WEDDING OF DAOREUNG AND AI-SOON
Hello, Joy.
-Hey, Chaba.
-Sis.
You look good today.
-Thanks.
-Congrats.
Ten and Piew couldn't make it today.
I have their gifts here.
That's nice, thank you.
Is there anything I can help with here?
It's okay. I don't want to bother you.
I'll help serve the drinks, then.
Is that okay?
Okay, Thanks.
It's nice to have good friends.
Thank you so much
from the bottom of my heart.
Thank you for coming here
to celebrate with us tonight.
We've been together for a long time.
And if you ask me
which part of her that I love the most,
I love...
her eyes.
The way she looks at me,
I can feel it instantly.
She's sincere
and she only loves me.
I love her.
Thank you to our honored guests
for joining us here
on our unfortunate event.
Fortunate.
Right.
Fortunate event
between me... and Joy.
Lastly...
I'd like to tell our guests...
please don't eat too much.
We'll check your gifts.
Just let them eat.
Enjoy the food.
Hey!
Honey.
Did you invite them?
No. I don't know them.
Actually, no one invited us.
But today is a good day.
Good day.
We'd like to make a toast
to the bride and groom.
Let me say this.
We know the bride, Chaba's senior.
But we're not so close.
The one who is close is...
-Nun.
-Hey.
Nun. Come here and make a toast.
Of course, I'm already here.
You don't have to.
Please give them a toast.
I didn't even finish pissing yet.
-Hello to the groom.
-Hello.
I'm not that familiar with the groom.
I barely know him.
-But Joy here.
-What?
I'm super close with her.
I've known her since she was little.
It is her.
She was a lot thinner earlier.
Now she's fat
and she takes too many pills.
This bitch,
she's been married three times already.
She ran away with a boy when she was 14.
She got pregnant,
and then he left her.
She came back to live with her mom
and brought a kid for her to raise.
Well, can you handle that?
Yes, it's all in the past.
That's good.
My dear.
Thank you.
After coming back to live with her mom,
she only stayed for two months
before running away to live in Pattaya.
Then she got together with a Black guy.
Can you also handle that?
Yes. It's the past.
-Wow.
-Joy.
You're a saint.
Thank you.
Your ex is also here. There in the front.
Hi.
Is that alright with you?
Bitch.
Why did you lie to me?
I didn't lie.
Who's that? Is that your ex?
I don't know him. Nun is lying.
-Nun!
-What?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You're ruining my wedding!
I'm just telling the truth.
Why did you do that?
Can you even handle the truth?
What the fuck is the truth?
Calm down.
Look.
Sis, I'm sorry.
-Chaba!
-I'm sorry.
-You get your brother down.
-He's drunk.
Please don't mind him.
Drunk, my ass! He's telling the truth.
Get out of here, Chaba!
-Get your brother out of here.
-I'm sorry, sis.
-Go.
-Go, Nun!
You bastard!
Dear.
Leave me alone.
You take care of this.
Take care of this Black guy here.
That Joy.
The rule is, no exes at the wedding,
and she invited him.
I think after this,
they should set a new rule.
What's that?
Not just no exes at the wedding.
Your brother's gang as well.
Look, I've said it so many times already.
And Tee doesn't pick up his phone.
Damn it.
Do you think he's got
a new girl in Bangkok?
Hey.
Have you been very busy lately?
You haven't picked up my calls.
Well, just now...
I just got promoted to assistant manager.
Hey.
Too much work and too little time.
He got promoted to assistant manager.
Assistant manager?
That's a quick move up. Seriously.
Is your boyfriend an elevator?
Yeah.
I see. I'm happy for you.
-Yeah.
-So...
you haven't come home recently.
Are you sure you're not seeing a new girl?
Come on. Nothing like that.
Are you coming back for the new year?
Of course.
I miss you with all my heart.
Okay, then I'll see you.
I won't bother you anymore.
Why don't you eat the phone, too?
Yeah.
Mom...
I miss you.
Can you somehow get Nun to quit drinking?
I don't know what to do anymore.
It's late and I don't know where he is.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
You can go over there to see him.
Poor woman. It's only her now.
She doesn't have a job.
She's just a housewife.
Yes.
Bad luck.
It was only her husband who worked.
And now, what's she going to do?
Quite difficult.
And this.
How much would the funeral cost?
How far can she even go?
I only gave her 20. I feel a bit guilty.
Hey, are we in the world of cartoons now?
I want to see her face.
I've only heard the voice.
I think this family is weird.
-Yeah.
-How's that?
They like to make the food
according to the name of the dead.
Remember?
His sister died and her name was Fish.
Fish died. Her funeral food
was fish maw soup.
And when Uncle Pig died,
it was pork porridge.
And what if his eldest brother dies?
Brother Dog?
Are we all going to have to eat dogs?
Shut up.
I really want to know,
who the hell are you?
Whenever someone in my family dies,
you're always at the funeral.
None of my relatives know you.
Quiet, this is a funeral.
I'm Nun.
Nun who?
Hey! I fixed your AC.
I'm the legendary AC guy.
You're just an AC guy.
You fixed it for me once
and now you think we're close?
So close that you're attending
my husband's funeral?
That's right.
Let me say this.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Is this how you look when you're sorry?
Give her some good quotes.
"When we leave this world, boy and girls,
only good things are left to ponder.
The bond will always be here
forever and ever."
Mom, I hope it's not about Nun.
Yes.
Chaba, come take care
of your brother at the funeral.
This is common.
You have to gamble at a funeral.
They say it's to keep the dead company.
So the dead won't be lonely.
Trust me on this one.
Two, three and four.
Two, three and four
Goddamn! You're right on.
Are you still here?
Let's play this then.
What's this?
This is one, six and four.
One, two and two.
All six.
All in! I'm not scared of losing.
-Wait.
-Hey, sis.
-What?
-I want number six.
All of this. 10,000 baht.
All in! I'm not scared, either.
You're dead. You're dead.
Fuck! Fuck!
The cops are here!
The cops are here?
-Where are you going?
-I'm going to pee.
Not yet.
-Gather here.
-Hold up.
-I'm gonna pee over there.
Stop! Stop!
I'll be really quick.
Nun! You asshole! Come and get some.
Hey, sis. What's this?
-I thought you said all six.
-I was just guessing.
Six, my ass.
Arrest her! She's using profanity.
That will be two charges!
I'm going to pee
and then I'll come back to you.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
A little lower.
-Get it in.
-Tee.
Hello, sir.
How are the lights
I asked you to fix at my condo?
All done, sir.
This evening, get my car
and go park it there for me.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Hello, Mr. Wat. How can I help?
Hey!
He bought a condo for a safehouse?
Is it true?
They said he likes to have fun there.
With the mistress.
I guess so.
How is he so rich?
He's the owner of a used-car dealership.
Of course he's rich.
I know he owns this,
but it just seems too much.
What's your problem with him?
Hey.
-What?
-I think the best way
is you take your brother to rehab.
The last time I saw him, he was like...
He was shaking like a generator.
He can't quit. I give up.
There are people who can quit, you know?
There are many good doctors.
I know someone.
Do you want to try?
Which doctor?
Why is everyone here?
We were told you can help us.
I want my brother to stop drinking.
You want him to stop drinking?
Easy, don't bother him.
He will stop himself.
Not drinking like that.
He's an alcoholic.
But before we start...
I have some amulets for sale.
This one is for protection.
I'll give it to you for 200 baht each.
Raise your hand if you want one.
Do you see any hands?
You want some, you get some.
That's pushing.
You want to quit drinking?
-Yeah.
-Give me your hand.
-Hey.
-Hey!
Shit! What the hell did you do?
No disrespect.
I'm starting the ceremony now.
I'm going to get the alcohol out.
I need to get the blood.
I will cast my spell on it,
then put the blood back in.
Hey! What are you thinking?
Is there any other way?
There are other ways.
-Why don't you use them, then?
-Well, you didn't ask.
What the hell?
-You're saying that to me?
-Hell yeah.
Damn it. I thought so. Let's do this.
Take this candy, and this rishi's mantra.
I'll cast my spell on it.
No sleep for seven days and seven nights.
Everyone's in on this.
All three parts, they're here.
Then it comes out. All for us. All right.
Open your mouth.
Oh, my God.
Give it a try.
Here.
I'm not an alcoholic.
Master! Why did you slap me?
Keep it in your mouth. No chewing!
Why didn't you say that before?
Well, you didn't ask.
-You have to tell me that.
-Do you want to do this?
Calm down.
Get the pig near the bear.
-The bear--
-Wait.
-What's this?
-This is a chanting spell.
To call the spirit of the pig and the bear
to fight alcohol out of the body.
Get the pig near the bear.
Put the pig's tail inside the bear's ear.
Pig's tail, bear's ear, look carefully.
Banana tree hanging low.
Bananas dangling around. Got it?
What the hell!
Pig, squid, shrimp. Cook, steam, boil.
Master!
Hey, master!
What the hell?
I'll kick you in the face.
If you don't have faith, get out!
Why did you hit me so many times?
I'm not your kid.
You want to be better?
Yeah. But I don't want it from you!
No disrespect!
I'll disrespect the hell out of you. Damn!
Go! Get out of here.
Go. Get up, Chaba.
I didn't believe it in the first place.
-I don't want to quit anymore.
-Come on.
-Somebody got murdered for a bit of gold.
-Hey!
I need someone to work
during the New Year holidays.
Something urgent has come up.
Someone needs to be here
to receive the parts.
My wife is pregnant.
I need to take care of her.
I have to visit my mom in the country.
What?
What about you, Tee?
If you don't have a plan, I want you here.
And get my car washed.
I'll give you some extra.
Well, actually--
It's only three days. Okay?
-Okay, sir.
-Okay.
Stop by my condo today.
The bathroom sink,
it's dripping. Check it out for me.
But go there after 1:00 p.m.
Yes, sir.
I'm off now.
James.
Shit.
What are you doing?
Looking for fucks to give.
Why are you like this?
Hey, I'm the head of security.
But I only see you on this floor.
-I like this floor.
-Why so?
There are many mistresses here.
So?
I only have to walk past.
Just the sound makes me feel good.
You're a creep.
Hey, don't call me a creep.
I'm more like a pervert.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Well...
my boss sent me to check the water pipe.
He said...
there would be no one here after 1:00 p.m.
Where did he go?
I can't reach him.
I don't know.
Then I'll...
wait outside, then.
-Hi, Chaba.
-Hello?
What are you doing?
I'm at the condo.
What's up?
I know.
You're never going to break up with her.
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you give me hope?
You said we'll be together on New Year's.
You won't be here, right?
Whose voice is that?
No one. It's the TV.
How does the TV sound so clear?
Well, the TV here is very big, Chaba.
So your condo...
is it that big and fancy?
Well, yeah.
It's arranged by the company.
But I don't like it so much.
That's weird.
What? Yeah, that's weird.
Are you finished?
I'm done now.
Can I see your face?
Hold on, Chaba. I'll pack my stuff.
What are you doing?
Quick.
Turn on your camera.
Just a moment.
Here, Chaba.
I'm at the condo.
Is this your condo? It's so fancy.
Well, the company I work for,
they also own this condo.
So I get the benefit.
I see.
I just wanted to ask,
what time are you coming back?
I was about to tell you.
Actually...
I have to work.
I can't go back this time.
What? Why?
FREE NEW YEAR PARTY 2020 FOR VIP
WITH CELEBRITY GUESTS AT MASTER VILLAGE
Well, actually,
they're having a party here.
And I'm the vice-chairman of the party,
so I have to be here.
So many celebrities will be here.
I have to come or I'll get chewed out.
I'll come back to see you
after New Year's.
What?
I have to go back to work now.
See you.
What the hell?
Why is he in such a hurry?
So obvious.
A woman's voice saying she's done?
Bitch, you don't have to stress me out.
He said it came from the TV.
You cannot trust guys on this.
Have you seen that soap opera?
That guy.
He has a mistress
while his wife is staying home
because she trusts him.
And what about that other soap opera?
Her husband leaves this girl
to join the military.
And then what?
He gets another wife.
Come on. You just watch too much TV.
You're overthinking it.
You look like you're way worse.
SANUN AIR-CON SERVICE
Okay, let's get our stuff.
What?
-Why is it so hot?
-Bro.
-Yeah.
-I won't be here for a few days
during the New Year holidays.
Where are you going?
I want to go see Tee.
What?
I thought he was coming to see you.
Yeah.
And now he's not.
He told me he needs to be at the condo.
There's a countdown party.
Something about a concert.
For New Year's?
Yeah.
Chaba. Are you serious?
I'm going, too.
I want to go to the party in Bangkok!
What's up, Chaba?
I'm coming to see you in Bangkok.
What?
You're coming here?
Yeah.
Can't I?
Okay.
But I'd also like to bring my brother.
Nun, Singh, Seab.
What? Everyone's coming?
How long will you be gone, sir?
Maybe three or four days.
What's up?
Nothing, sir.
What's up, Chaba?
Hello?
Tee, I'm here now.
What?
Are you in Bangkok?
The taxi is here. I have to go.
Okay, see you.
Damn!
Tee.
-Better be early than late, sir.
-What?
Dude. Is this a cab or a temple?
It's full of Buddha statues.
All the good ones.
Let's all pay some respect.
Where to?
Sathorn.
Come on.
Why Sathorn?
No parking, bad traffic.
Cops everywhere.
Why so grumpy? We're not from here.
Why do so many of you come here?
Jesus.
Bangkok wasn't like this before, you know.
Not so many people.
Now, with people coming from the country,
everyone is fighting to live.
Bangkok is full now.
The weather is bad, air pollution.
Do you know about this PM 2.5?
It's everywhere now.
People have to wear masks outside.
It's like that TV show, The Masked Singer.
Bro. Have you seen The Masked Singer?
-Of course.
-Which mask is your favorite?
-Bael fruit.
-Bael fruit?
-Is there one?
-Will I go blind?
They even have a durian mask!
Of course they have a bael fruit mask.
Are you from Bangkok?
Yeah. Since my past life.
A real Bangkokian.
There are a total of 50 districts.
-I see.
-This is Chao Phraya River.
It's right between
Thon Buri and Phra Nakorn.
5,680,000 people live here.
What are their names?
Go ask your dad!
How the fuck would I know?
Does that mean you know every place?
Every place I told you.
Do you know this place, His Fish Hill?
His Fish Hill, that's downhill.
There are many fishes there.
Many.
The owners of the land really like fish.
So they said, "It's his fish."
That's why they call it "His Fish Hill."
I see.
What about Hole Keaw Hill?
This grandma, Keaw, owned the land.
They dug a hole to bury her when she died.
So that's why they call it that?
-Hole Keaw Hill.
-Who is this Grandma Keaw, by the way?
Do I look like fucking Wikipedia?
Why are you so grumpy?
-The economy is bad.
-Yeah?
Times are hard. Poor people stay poor,
and the rich keep getting richer.
Rich people work hard. That's why.
They sell drugs, that's why.
How do you know that?
I buy everyday.
Are you using?
I'm not using, I'm a spy for cops.
A secret weapon.
Don't mess with me.
I'm a spy.
Spy, my ass.
You want me to help you pretend
that you're the boss?
Yeah. Please help.
I don't think so.
No. I don't want any trouble.
Bro, it's just three days.
He won't be here.
It's just between me and you, okay?
I'll give you 500 baht.
How about 1,000?
-1,500?
-Oh, my God.
-2,000 then.
-You can't buy me.
How about...
I could add some good porn links to that.
Son of a bitch. You know my weak spot.
Damn.
Can I just stay in the car? It's so hot.
Can you take my jacket?
Thanks.
What?
Chaba.
Tee.
Hey, Tee.
Is this where you live?
Yes.
Oh, my.
Would it be too big to walk around?
Let's go.
You keep the AC on all day?
James.
What?
This... This is my girlfriend.
And these are her brothers.
So what?
Say hello.
-Do it.
-Really?
Come on.
Is the chicken cooked?
Hello.
Looks like a human.
I like this one.
Is that a nose or some sort of pipe?
What the hell are you looking at?
Let's go.
Are you coming?
It's okay.
I don't like creeps.
Such a big room.
It's so fancy, Tee.
Who is this?
The previous tenant.
I told him to come get it,
but he hasn't shown up yet.
People who can't keep their word,
I don't like it at all.
Right. You can't talk to those people.
If you see them, just smack them.
Make yourself at home, my place is yours.
Can't take that back.
Let's go.
It's going to be fun.
Quick.
-These are expensive.
-Which one?
We have to start from wine.
I don't know if there is a wine opener.
Of course there is. Just keep looking.
Hey, Nun.
Let's pick this one.
Someone left it open. It's easy.
Okay.
Open it.
Quick.
Can you? I can't open it.
-What smell is that?
-Let's do this.
I'll go get the soap.
Then it'll come off easy.
Let's get to it, then.
There are so many skyscrapers.
-It looks really fancy.
-Yeah.
-Found it?
-No.
Hey, Seab.
What's taking so long?
What is going on?
I'm trying to open up here.
Quick. Come on.
Find it.
I can't find it.
Seab, this is taking too long.
It's okay, let's continue.
Hey, bro, I don't think he's okay.
Bro!
-What?
-He's having a seizure.
Can I ask...
have you brought someone here?
Hey. What makes you think that?
I never bring anyone here.
Seriously?
Seriously.
Look, Chaba.
I have only one.
Don't make that face.
I'm hungry.
Let's go eat something.
The cork!
What cork?
The wine cork!
Calm down, pull yourself together.
Slowly.
One, two...
-Stay focused.
-It's still in there.
-This is bad.
-This is bad, bro.
Hey. Lay down.
Pull.
Okay.
-It has to be this way, yeah?
-Keep his head high.
Like this?
Hold him.
-Relax.
-Now, bro.
-What are you doing?
-I'm watching you.
Are you hiding something?
No.
But you're acting weird.
How?
The woman's voice that I heard...
that wasn't coming from the TV, was it?
What?
That really was the TV.
I video-called you.
I don't think so.
Yes, sir.
Tee, where are you?
What's up, sir?
Get my keys and go to my condo.
My VIP customer is going there
to use the room.
Okay, sir.
What's up?
Are you full?
Who's that?
No need to look.
Open it.
Hey!
Are you here to plant
a bomb or something?
How come you people are in Joe's condo?
Joe?
Which Joe?
What? It's Joe.
The thin guy.
He's got a mustache.
He looks like a bad guy.
You must have the wrong room.
Oh, right.
We must have the wrong room, honey.
Let's go.
Wait up!
Since you're here,
are we the same kind of people?
You wanna come in and drink?
Is that okay?
Hey!
You sure? It's not our room.
-Singh.
-Asshole.
Shut your mouth. Look who he's with.
-Slap his mouth.
-Let's go.
Hey, wait. Asshole.
That's my girl.
Hey!
If that's how you think,
you're not open-minded enough.
And you can go.
Hey.
Ronaldo.
You really cut me off.
You're too much.
Can I go with you?
No problem.
If you want to be friends,
you must be open-minded.
Come on in.
You can't even walk straight.
-Where's my girl?
-Here.
Can't you see?
Still here? Hey!
This is a photo of Joe! This is him.
Who?
Don't bother. This is old stuff.
He moved out and left his photo here.
Why do you care?
He told me to come use the room.
Hey! Do you want to drink?
Don't bother about that Joe. Sit down.
-Hey, wait. What's this?
-What?
That's another box.
This is a cosplay costume.
Mr. and Mrs. Santa Claus.
I brought it to wear with her.
Can I see?
Hey, for you, no problem.
Hey!
Santa.
Hey. Let's play cards for fun.
Whoever loses drinks a shot.
We've been drinking a lot already.
Let's just say, playing cards,
whoever loses point...
takes off their clothes one at a time.
Hey, I don't mind.
But is she going to mind?
I'm all in. I don't mind.
-All right, let's start.
-Let's go.
-Open it.
-Ten!
Queen. It's mine.
What? I got two!
Queen of hearts.
Ten!
Eight.
Lower.
Bottom up.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven,
eight, nine,
ten.
You're great.
-Hey. Baby.
-Hey, old man.
-Old man.
-Baby. What?
What's going on? Is he faking it?
-He's in shock.
-Shock? What's wrong?
-Shock?
-I'm out.
-Hey.
-I'm leaving.
Wait! How can she ditch us?
Hey. Sir.
Hey, I think it's serious.
I can't even walk.
Let's take him to the hospital.
You can't die in here.
What about Singh?
Just leave him here.
Quick.
Oh, God. You drink too much.
-Damn.
-There are many more floors to go.
What do we do?
Let's take the fire exit.
This is taking too long.
Let's go.
Bro.
Hey.
Sir.
Hey! Sir.
Get him.
What's going on?
-Hey!
-Call an ambulance!
What's up with him?
Can't you see? He's in shock.
Call an ambulance!
Is he still alive?
I'm sorry.
Let's go back and drink.
Bye.
Hey.
What did you guys do?
-Yes.
-What happened?
This guy got the wrong room.
Then he invited us for drinks.
Then he went into shock.
He's off to the hospital now.
Everything is fine.
Nothing is certain about human life.
What's up?
James.
Your friends are getting messy.
Get them under control.
Nun, Seab.
What did you guys do?
Yeah.
What are you gonna do if he dies?
Funeral?
Easy to say.
How are you going to be
responsible for his life?
I'll get ordained for him for three days.
-Four, then.
-Not funny.
When he wakes up, if he does,
would he know who did it?
He won't remember.
He peed in the elevator
last time he was drunk.
And the next day,
I asked him if he'd peed.
He couldn't remember.
Really?
You guys almost became murderers!
Murderers?
Really?
Let's go find a new place to drink.
Seriously?
Are you still going to drink?
Where are you going?
This is Bangkok. Where can you go?
Chaba.
Don't even dare question me like that.
I'll find my own way.
Yeah. Be my guest.
You...
You're not my mom.
Tee.
I'm sorry about Nun and his gang.
I almost got you in trouble.
It's okay. I think it's fine.
How is this fine?
Look.
Trust me. It's fine.
Let's go. Let's go up to the room.
Hey! Follow me.
Let's keep drinking.
Tee.
What is this room?
Probably nothing.
Why is there a number pad here?
It's nothing.
Just...
another storage room.
Can you open it for me?
I don't remember the code.
Liar.
Are you hiding something from me?
No. It's really just a storage room.
Trust me. Please.
What is this room and what's inside?
Tell me.
Say it.
I said, tell me.
Hello, what's up?
Tee.
Come down here, quickly.
Your friends,
they took a motorbike and left.
Okay, I'm coming.
Wait here, I'll be right back.
Hey.
A date. His birthday.
Wrong password.
My birthday.
The first day we met.
Wrong password.
House registration number.
I'll just guess it, then.
-Where?
-They're gone.
Password accepted.
What?
Whose motorbike did they take?
How would I know?
I saw them talking just a moment ago.
They probably went for more booze.
Shit. What the hell?
Chaba.
Are you okay?
You said you have nothing to hide.
Why did you lie?
What lie?
What about this wedding dress?
I knew it.
You're seeing someone else.
Okay, I'll confess.
This wedding dress...
I got it for you.
What?
-How?
-Well...
I wanted to surprise you.
Really?
Yes.
I wanted to ask you to marry me.
But...
I guess it's not a surprise anymore.
I see.
It's still a surprise. I'm sorry.
Hey. This dress.
It's so beautiful.
Can I ask...
when are you going to propose?
Well...
I thought tonight.
But...
the plan is ruined now.
How is it ruined?
I was going to take you out for a drive,
then ask you to marry me
on New Year's Eve.
But that's not happening now.
It can happen.
Of course.
Let's just say,
I don't know about any of this, nothing.
Let's start again.
Walk in again.
Tee...
what kind of dress is this?
Does this work?
Yes.
Did you buy this for me?
That's so sweet of you.
Can we go take a drive?
Maybe you have something to ask me.
Let's go.
I want to go for a drive.
Wait here. I'll get us some beer.
Not a lot of ice this time.
Hey.
Is that a person?
-What do you think?
-Boy.
Please help me.
Can you buy my lottery tickets?
I haven't eaten since this morning.
I'm so thin my pants are getting loose.
Come on, man, pull them up.
Do it for me. I'm blind.
Damn.
I haven't showered for days.
There.
Please buy some.
Otherwise, I won't get to eat.
You got number 54?
No. I have 55.
Then 56.
I have 57.
-I want 58.
-Son of a bitch.
Are you messing with me?
If you don't want to buy them,
just say so!
Well, I don't.
I'd rather go get some liquor.
Go sell it to someone else.
Hey, I'm bringing you luck.
Who are you talking to?
I don't know.
Here.
Beer.
Hey!
-That sounds familiar.
-You.
Nun.
You have a good memory. Sharp ears.
-Is it you, Nun?
-This way.
Hey, it's really you.
What a small world.
What brings you here? A dog?
I'm working for the government.
Oh, Nun.
-Hey!
-You know him?
This is my master. The legendary AC guy.
He's a little cuckoo.
Look at how he dresses.
Son of a bitch.
Call me crazy and I'll shoot your ass.
This way.
Do you have a gun?
Hell yeah. Here.
Bang. Bang. Bang.
Better put that away.
That's funny.
Hey, you. Hold on.
-What are you doing here?
-Government work.
Selling lottery tickets
is government work?
This is just a part-time job.
So the government is your main job?
-Yeah.
-Where do you work?
MBK.
Hey. My friends go there a lot.
They never see you.
-Which floor did they go to?
-Every floor.
I'm up on the roof.
-What the hell, the roof?
-Sunbathing.
-How did you get here?
-I drove here.
You're blind. That's nonsense.
I used GTH.
-You mean GPS.
-Yeah.
So, when they say, "Turn left,"
I turn left.
Don't tell me.
That yellow car with a siren is yours?
Company car.
What about the net in the back?
That's for fishing.
Why is there a dog in the car?
-That's a police dog.
-What about the stray one?
That's the undercover one.
When he's sick, I have to go instead.
Wait, your lottery tickets,
are they selling well?
-I haven't even sold one today.
-What?
Not even one. They're all here.
Where do you get your money then?
Around here, I'm also a fortune-teller.
Are you crazy?
You're blind and a fortune-teller?
Yeah, I just feel it.
Feel what? How?
Like this.
My eyes! My eyes!
Wait.
I'll go blind, too.
Oh, my God.
Did you burn a monk's robe?
That's nonsense.
You got a wine cork in your throat.
Damn!
He's just guessing.
-And very recently...
-Why?
...you got kicked in the face by your ex.
Hey, you...
how did you know that?
And soon, you'll get shot.
-Me?
-Yeah.
Your face is shit and your mouth is shit.
So stubborn.
I won't believe you.
-Let's go
-Take me, too.
-Hey.
-I can't drive like this.
Right.
Nun.
Don't you believe me?
You'll get shot. Very soon.
This is your car?
Yes. For my position.
But I don't really use it. Too much gas.
Okay.
And...
where are you going to take me?
Where should we go?
Hello.
Hello, everyone.
Master Village's friends.
I should have
come to Bangkok long ago.
This is heaven.
We go big every year.
We hope that, for tonight,
everyone is happy.
It's gonna be a fun night.
Hey, the same taste.
I won't waste any more time.
Please welcome Deputy Not
to say a few words.
Say something? Does that mean two words?
Thank you.
Is that really a cop?
Yes, sir.
At first glance, you look like a fugitive.
Your body looks it.
Hello, everyone.
I am Deputy Not.
My full position is...
Deputy Commander of Narcotics Control.
I'm appointed to this area.
This New Year,
I promise to hurry and get rid of drugs
from this area.
I guarantee you,
this city will be drug-free.
Drug free.
I'm sorry.
When you say "drug free,"
does that mean...
that you're keeping the drugs
for yourself?
I must inform you...
we are officers.
We don't do drugs.
Let me ask you something.
What do you want to be called?
Whatever you'd like.
Hey, Not!
Criminals are everywhere in the city now.
How do the police plan to take care of it?
I want to tell our people here,
we need some more time
because our police are understaffed.
Hey, what about those police
who break their own rules?
What are you going to do?
We need more time on that as well.
Since we have too many officers,
we cannot take care of everything.
Too many or too few.
What is it then?
Well...
-Then...
-Hey, be clear on this, Not!
-Sir.
-Yes.
I think...
if you're drunk,
you should take care of yourself.
Come on. Be clear on this, Not!
-Sir.
-Yes.
Please respect the uniform and my rank.
Seriously?
Have you ever used a gun?
Why don't you answer?
Or are you keeping it for Songkran?
Hey.
Oh, Father.
-That's the police.
-He looks like a monk.
Sir.
Sit down.
Look at your gut.
We don't mind the crazies,
and we don't blame the drunks.
I will excuse myself now.
I want to dance.
Please enjoy yourself.
Okay.
Let's give Deputy Not a hand.
To not waste any more time,
our singer is here.
-Are you ready?
-Yes.
If you are, please welcome
Lumyai Hai Thongkam!
Lumyai! Lumyai! Lumyai!
Hello.
I'm Lumyai Hai Thongkam.
Let's listen to my new single,
"Girl Who Wants to Have Fun."
-Lumyai!
-I like her so much!
Let's hear it!
I'm the girl who wants to have fun
I'm not the girl who likes school
I don't work really hard
Always borrow a pen from my pals
I never do my homework
I don't know how exams work
I only know today and tomorrow
I'm waiting here to see
If you can
Break up with her
Would it be possible for us?
I'm not here to pressure you
I'm just here waiting
Can you please hurry and break up?
A girl who wants to have fun
She want to be yours
Lumyai.
Wait.
Why did you stop?
Sir, I'm sorry.
Could you please dance down there?
You're in my dancers' space.
They need space to dance.
You look so cute in real life.
Finally, I get to see you.
Thank you. You better dance down there.
I come from the suburbs.
Lumyai is so pretty in real life.
Thank you. Please dance down there.
My dancers need this space.
-Please.
-Damn. What?
They hired you here to entertain.
So just do it. Give it your all.
You're very drunk and talking nonsense.
I can't dance now and I also can't sing.
Am I choking you now or something?
You've gone too far.
I'm disappointed.
You're so arrogant in real life.
I'm not arrogant.
I really can't perform
with you bothering me. I can't do it.
-Shit. Take a video of this.
-Hey.
What?
If you don't stop now, I won't hold back.
Hold what back? What are you going to do?
Why?
Did you just slap me?
You're so arrogant in real life.
What do you want with me?
-What?
-What? You want to get some?
-Yeah?
-Such an arrogant bitch.
-Hey.
-Damn it.
-Seab!
I don't like her anymore.
Stop! I told you to stop.
I'll take care of this. No problem.
Miss Lumyai, I'm so sorry.
He's drunk.
Mister, please take care of this.
This is too much.
I can't perform like this.
-I'm sorry.
-Let go.
Let go now.
Seab.
Follow me. Go down.
Right now. You.
Always causing trouble.
Sit.
Hey.
Seab.
I told you to be quiet.
Okay. Quiet.
Miss Lumyai.
Please go on. Please continue.
He's drunk. I'm sorry.
I'm waiting to see
If you do
Break up with her
The stage is theirs.
They paid her to dance.
Why did you go up there?
I was just having fun.
Seab!
-What?
-I told you to stop!
-Are you listening?
-Hey!
Son of a bitch.
That one is not so loud. You, however...
What?
You are being so loud. I can't focus.
Me? Being loud?
Well, I'm sorry, then.
Once again. I'll lower my voice.
Continue.
I'm waiting to see
If you do
Break up with her
Would it be possible for us?
I'm not here to pressure you
I'm just waiting
Can you please hurry?
A girl who wants to have fun
She's waiting for you
Hey!
If you break up with her
I told you to dance down there,
understand?
What are you doing here? They can't dance!
What are you looking at? Go down!
-Can't understand a word.
-Are you crazy?
-No idea.
-Go dance down there.
-Stop.
-Why can't I dance here?
Hey, you.
Stop it.
-I'm sorry.
-I can't stand it anymore. Please help.
This is so bad.
-Hey, you. Hey!
-So arrogant.
Are you picking on a citizen?
Hey! I think you need help now.
Hey, Seab.
I don't care. I'm going to stay.
You have a problem.
Well, she started it!
Lumyai.
I'm sorry again. Okay?
I can't stand it anymore.
I told him to go down.
If you want to dance, go down.
This is my space.
I want to perform a concert.
Where are my dancers going to dance?
There's so much space.
What's wrong with him?
Why the hell does he want to dance here?
This is not his space.
I told him many times to dance down there.
He keeps being funny and loud.
Who on earth can sing with that?
I don't want to sing anymore.
Are you crazy?
Calm down. Let's talk it out.
-Seab! Hey!
-I don't care. I don't care.
-Why?
-I'm begging you.
What do you mean you don't care?
I'm just having fun.
-Stop.
-No one is having fun.
I'm just dancing.
-Hey.
-You stay out of this.
Hey!
Is he dead?
Not yet. So lucky.
He just jumped suddenly.
Let go!
Let's get him!
Get him out of here!
Get out!
What? What's this?
Hey.
This place looks so pretty.
Do you like it?
Well, I like it everywhere...
when you're with me.
Well, then,
come home and be with me.
You already have this much here.
If you come home,
we can build a really big house.
And what if...
What if I'm not rich?
Come on.
Are you testing me?
Just asking.
I promise you.
I'll have everything one day.
A house and a car.
But you have it all now.
Both a house and a car.
Hey.
Is it that time?
Are you going to propose?
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One.
Hey, look at that one. So pretty.
That one, too.
But this one is prettiest.
Stop it.
Are you ready?
I'm waiting.
There.
Are you going to propose?
Don't be shy. I'm waiting.
Hello. What's up?
Tee.
Something's up.
Have you heard?
Jenny overdosed on pills.
Really?
And there's more.
She poured acid over herself.
This is so scary.
She probably wanted to commit suicide
because Joe didn't see her
on New Year's Eve.
He went to see his wife instead.
You mean today?
Yeah.
She left him a letter.
She said, alive or dead,
she'll be waiting for Joe at his condo.
And she said to burn
the wedding dress with her
at her funeral.
That's it, then. I have to work.
You be careful.
Okay.
Is something wrong?
Hey. What's up?
We haven't finished.
Hey!
Someone is sleeping over here.
Come on.
Chaba.
Is that you?
Where are you?
Where'd she go?
What?
What's this?
A hat.
I see.
A bridal hat.
Let's try it on.
Looks pretty.
Hey!
Chaba! Don't do that!
I'm scared!
Everyone is looking.
It's because you're dressed this way.
All my life...
I've never seen Lumyai.
This was the first time.
Hey!
Where did it go?
Hey, mannequin!
Oh, my!
Hey! What's this?
Hey!
What's up with you, Singh?
-Wait.
-Let me go.
-I'm going home.
-What's with you?
-Singh!
A ghost!
-What?
-I saw a ghost!
A ghost, my ass.
Keep him still.
-Keep him.
-It's the ghost!
Get him. Don't let him go anywhere.
I'll be right back. I'll take care of it.
You stay here, Singh.
Seab.
You come with me.
-Okay.
-What ghost is he talking about?
I want to know, too.
Nonsense.
Seab, come.
What the hell are you talking about?
Oh, come on.
Seab! Why did you close the door?
You want to scare me?
Singh, did you close the door?
Singh!
Oh, my.
Why do you stop?
I... I don't want to stop.
But I can't go on.
You must see for yourself.
Is it the ghost?
Yes.
Fuck.
Why couldn't you say no?
Shit.
Left or right?
On the right.
Oh, shit!
Just hurry up. Do something.
Help me. Pray!
Shit! She can pray.
Where is your amulet?
-You have it. Quick.
-Here.
Go get it. Get it!
Shit, open the door.
Damn it! It's locked.
Hey.
She's not even afraid of it.
It's open.
Singh! It's real. The ghost!
She committed suicide, sir.
We should go back to the condo
and get our stuff
before the police arrive.
You need to pack and leave.
I'm flying back soon.
Fuck!
On both sides.
Gotta go straight.
Quick!
What is this?
Hey, let's go.
Hey. Who else?
Why are there so many?
Follow them!
So many ghosts!
Why are there so many?
Are they here?
Let's hurry.
It's here.
Run!
Hey!
What the fuck?
It's so cold.
Son of a bitch. This is cocaine.
Are you all scared?
Hey!
Who are you?
There it is. You.
Is this a toy gun from the fair?
Why is the fair so quiet?
The fair must be loud with fun music.
This is not funny.
I remember you.
You're the one in the photo. In that room.
Hell yeah!
You come to pick up the photo?
Hey. We should get it for him.
Quiet!
I will ask you one more time.
What were you doing in my room?
Well... it's not your room.
It's Tee's room.
He's the boyfriend.
He's my sister's boyfriend.
Are you a snitch for the cops?
What snitch?
I don't know anything about that.
Answer me!
Well...
Well, I...
I... I don't know, sir.
How could I answer if I don't know?
-Hey.
-Nun!
Hey, Nun!
Nun!
Tee!
Are you working for the cops?
No.
I don't know.
What is all this?
Don't!
They're not making any sense.
What should we do?
Take care of them.
Follow them.
What's up?
Look at you all weary.
You're safe now.
Nothing to worry about.
Thank you.
Bro.
How are you?
There was a haunting incident
at Master Village Condo.
It's suspected to be
the spirit of grieving mistress
of the infamous owner of a car dealership.
The police have investigated
and discovered...
Look at this news. At the condo.
...there was a hidden drug supply.
When did you become a liar?
Nun almost got shot to death!
What's that?
What's that, Tee?
-Chaba.
-What's that?
Chaba.
I'm very tired, you know.
You think working in Bangkok is easy?
I know you dream
about paying off your debt.
I know you dream about getting married.
And I really want to do that for you.
But it's so damn hard.
Have you ever noticed
what I've done for you?
What you've done for me, Tee...
I never asked you to do it.
You said everything yourself.
Promised everything yourself.
I'm so...
I'm so disappointed in you.
Chaba.
Nun.
I've decided...
that I...
I will be like you guys.
What does that mean?
You know...
no sad feelings, only fun feelings.
From now on,
I don't want to do anything else.
I want to become like you guys.
It's so good.
No stress...
plus free food.
Isn't that nice?
-I don't want you to become--
-Look.
No. No.
Don't try to stop me.
Why?
What's wrong with
becoming one of you guys?
Look. I'll stop being sad.
Singh, Seab.
Every party you go to...
you have to take me with you.
Because... I am so ready
to give away happiness.
Stop it, Chaba!
Hey.
-Stop!
-I want to drink!
I'm telling you to stop!
I can have a shit life,
but my sister can't.
That's funny.
When I asked you to stop drinking...
no matter how hard I've tried...
you still wouldn't quit.
So now...
why bother stopping me?
I'm sorry, Chaba.
You can ask me to do anything now.
You cannot get drunk like this.
If you want me
to quit drinking for life...
I can do that for you.
I love you, Chaba.
Brother.
From now on...
I won't drink anymore.
Both of you, too.
Top it up.
I have a date.
You? Really?
-I feel for your date.
-Why are you smiling?
Ten.
Can I have Tee's number?
Hello?
Tee?
Chaba!
Something's up with Ten.
Come on!
Where?
How could you do that to me?
How could you lie to me?
You're so selfish.
-Ten
-You've never thought about me at all.
Ten, what's going on?
Why are you smiling?
Talk it out, okay?
Chaba.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to tell you...
that I didn't succeed,
and that I lied.
Today...
I'm here to tell you the truth.
I might have lied that I succeeded,
but... I didn't lie
about wanting to have a family with you.
I might have failed...
at making money in Bangkok...
but I'll continue to fight.
I won't give up.
Just...
can you still stay by my side?
That's it.
That's all I want.
Does this mean...
you've accepted my apology?
What has already happened...
just let it pass.
Okay.
Yeah.
We must stay in the present, right?
We must have...
some scars and wounds.
Tee.
What?
I have something to tell you.
Yes?
So...
when you were away...
I slept with someone else.
What?
Are you serious?
But...
that's the past, right?
We should be in the present.
We must have some scars...
and some wounds.
Chaba.
I'm kidding.
-Look. Wait.
-What?
So whose plan was this?
You saw me?
Nun.
Here.
Chaba.
Did you sleep with someone else?
Tee's the only one.
I can't believe
the three of us quit drinking...
just because we don't want
someone we love to drink.
Yeah.
Singh.
Ning Nong!
-Ning Nong.
-Nun.
I'm sorry.
Ning Nong, you slut.
How dare you come here and apologize?
Do you really think
he'll forgive you, bitch?
Yeah.
You dumped him for someone else.
You don't deserve him.
He doesn't want you, bitch!
Ning Nong.
Listen to me.
I...
I can't be mad at you.
Son of a bitch.
And I was on his side.
Now look at me.
I want you...
Ning Nong, let's go talk upstairs.
I want to let go of something, too.
Let's go.
Come on up.
Come explain.
Look at them go. They're running.
Let's go.
Get in the room.
They're so hurried.
He's really horny.
Hey, it's falling off now.
Damn it, Nun!