PEOPLE SHOULD GET AT LEAST
SIX TO EIGHT HOURS OF SLEEP A DAY
MINISTRY OF PUBLIC HEALTH
That’s stupid.
Humans can go without sleep
for at least two days.
Today
is my third day.
DAY THREE
See? I'm still okay.
I’m not dead,
but it's been three days.
My body is heating up a little.
Let it cool down a bit.
The last time was also like this.
Jae, wait a moment.
I just need another ten seconds.
Ten, nine,
eight, seven,
six, five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
Why are you here?
Yoon, you have four hours left.
The client has been calling non-stop.
-How many photos left?
-Seven.
Seven photos. How many minutes per photo?
I don't know.
Seven photos in four hours.
We won't make it.
Yoon. Should I call to postpone?
I can postpone it. It won't look bad.
I'm serious. I'll call him now.
Jae, don't.
-I accepted the job.
-No, Yoon.
I told him I would finish it in time.
I must keep my word.
He's putting too much pressure on you.
How many times have we fixed it?
-This isn't the first or the second time.
-That's not the point.
For real, do you think you can finish it?
I don’t know. I promised them,
so I must get it done.
-So, you won’t postpone, right?
-Right.
You'll make it, right?
-Yes.
-Okay.
Hey, stop being paranoid.
I'm about to unleash a new power.
What kind of power?
Is there anything to eat?
I don't know.
Jae doesn't know that my new power is
about
to be unleashed in three seconds.
Three, two, one.
It's been 96 hours now.
Humans can actually go
without sleep for four days.
DAY FOUR
Jae, I'm done.
Jae, wake up.
Wake up.
-Okay.
-Wake up now.
-All right.
-Hurry up.
-Don't.
-Come on.
Wake up.
Yoon.
Your work is marvelous.
There’s not much time left.
My boss won’t change anything.
I think
it's okay, but it's still not enough.
But we did it according
to your instructions.
Yes.
I know. But...
it could look more elegant.
I believe it can look more elegant.
Let me ask you.
Are you happy with this?
Do you really like it?
How should it look then?
Listen. That's your job, not mine.
Otherwise, why would I hire you?
Am I right?
I’ll be back to have a look.
Make it quick.
Yoon...
Fuck.
I have one hour
to make these more elegant.
Paragon.
EmQuartier.
Emporium.
Yoon, are you almost done?
The print shop will give our slot away.
-Are you almost done?
-Just a bit more.
Yoon.
Stop it. It’s already perfect.
We are out of time.
They don’t look like
what I instructed at all.
-I...
-It's a lot better.
I love it. Print it now.
Good work.
If you ever quit working as a freelancer,
pay me a visit.
That felt so warm and romantic.
This time, it feels like I defused a bomb.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Your food is here.
Jae, what’s the date today?
It's the 27th.
Something's wrong with your brain.
It’s my friend’s dad’s funeral.
Shit. Should I go?
-Should I?
-How did he die?
He...
He died of old age. That’s all.
That’s okay, right? It's not a sad death.
He didn't crash his car or anything.
Give him an envelope
with 2,000 baht in it.
-Is that what's in your head?
-Yes.
He's my best friend's father.
Do you even have a best friend?
Of course, Pongsathorn.
When was the last time you saw him?
I don’t know.
I forgot.
Your best friend.
You should ask him
if he sees you as his best friend.
Of course, he does.
Sure. But the deadline is 8 p.m.,
I already sent you the file.
You have five hours to finish it.
If you were me, would you go?
-See you.
-If I'm going to lie,
what should I say? Anything except
being sick or busy with work.
-So?
-I don't know. Your deadline is at 8 p.m.
-I should go. Five hours.
-Wait. Where are you going?
I'm going to the office.
Pongsathorn, I’m sorry.
Does this temple have Wi-Fi?
What the hell, Yoon?
What do you need it for?
I have to submit my work from here.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Don't get upset. I'm sorry.
-I really have to.
-I don't know. Ask the monk over there.
Hello, Sir.
Does this temple have Wi-Fi?
-You can use the one from my house.
-All right.
The server is
Kaewking Temple House 1 Wi-Fi.
-What's the password?
-The password is
-Indiansubcontinent79.
-How do you spell that?
I finished it in the taxi,
but I only just got Wi-Fi
and charged my battery.
I have uploaded it already.
You can check it.
Yes.
Pongsathorn.
Please don’t be sad.
Death is a part
of this planet's cycle of life.
If you are too busy to attend the funeral,
you shouldn't have come.
I'm sorry.
Yoon, I always have to call you
to collect your checks.
Do you want your money or not?
I’m sorry. I'm very busy.
Here. Your checks are about to expire.
I see.
Thank you.
All done.
Wow. You've got many checks.
-It must be hard to keep hold of them all.
-Oh.
-Hello, Peng.
-Hello.
-How are you?
-I have been busy.
That's why there are so many.
How are you? I heard you stayed awake
for four days, right?
Actually, four and a half days.
Really?
I think with Jae’s type of work,
three days should be enough.
You are getting old now, you know.
You are right.
-It's...
-Hello, Peng.
Hello. You came at the perfect time.
Jerd, this is Yoon, your idol.
-Hello, Yoon.
-Hello.
Talk to him.
It's not easy to meet him in person.
I see. Yoon.
We often study your work in class.
You're my inspiration.
Wow. Thank you.
So,
is he working for you now?
Not yet.
I met him at a contest.
His work was good, so I recruited him.
I wanted to get to know him.
That sounds familiar.
You are right.
To be honest, when I met Jerd,
I thought of you.
He works hard like you.
His pimples gave it away.
Keep it up.
I might send some work your way.
-Thank you.
Peng, I have to go.
-I've got work to finish.
-Sure.
Peng.
If you have any work for me, just send it.
-I’ve been wanting to work with you.
-Sure, I'll give you a call.
All right. Goodbye.
Wait, Yoon.
What's wrong with your neck?
Fuck.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 2
What the hell are these dots?
Fuck.
My work rate has decreased by ten percent.
Damn it. Scratching myself
wastes a lot of time.
Oh, my god.
This is annoying.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 2.5
Yes.
I’m not on the computer.
Okay.
How is the overall feedback?
Yes.
I see.
FULL SPEED SERVICE
Okay.
Do I need to
fix anything?
Okay.
Yes, I can write it down.
Okay. I'm ready.
I think you should
check on the other stuff first.
I will do it as soon as I get home.
Did you decide to go with the first draft?
What about the 15th draft that I did?
Six thousand seven hundred
and eighty-five baht.
Wait.
I need to call you back.
What's the name again?
Are you Mr. Assanai Srisiri?
Yes.
Six thousand seven hundred
and eighty-five baht, please.
Do you have health insurance?
No, I don’t.
It's 6,785 baht then, please.
This is 1,500 baht.
I already have paracetamol at home.
This is 3,285 baht.
This is 2,000 baht.
Damn it. That's everything.
I just got this check.
ASSANAI SRISIRI
SEVEN THOUSAND BAHT
Take before bedtime.
May cause drowsiness.
Shit. My 7,000 baht.
I better take it then.
-Jae.
-What's up?
Send June's photo to me now.
Her stomach is hard to retouch.
-Now.
-Okay. Give me a second.
Hang on. I'm stamping it right now.
It's due at 9 a.m., right?
Damn you! Elephant tranquillizer!
Wait.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 2.5
Shit.
It's spreading.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 4
What's with the turtleneck?
Are you cold?
I'm using a MacBook.
Steve Jobs.
He died, you know.
Is it wrong to want to look cool?
Girls don't dig guys
who wear turtlenecks in summer.
-You got that shirt for free, too.
-Shut up.
I don’t know about anyone else,
but just so you know,
I won’t give you any work
if you are sick.
What's wrong with your finger?
Shit.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 5
Was the thing on my neck just a warning?
SIMILAR PICTURES
Pyelonephritis.
Mosquito-borne tropical diseases.
Drug allergies.
May lead to death.
Shit.
What the hell is wrong with me?
PUBLIC HOSPITALS ARE CHEAPER
"Public hospitals
are cheaper. They have better doctors.
You will definitely be cured.
Contact the Dermatology Institute."
WELCOME TO DERMATOLOGY INSTITUTE
ADMITTING 300 PATIENTS PER DAY
At 6 a.m.?
But it could save 7,000 baht.
DERMATOLOGY INSTITUTE
Excuse me. Where can I register
for the Dermatology Institute?
Window four. Down there.
Shit.
I didn't come early enough, did I?
Number 15.
Number 16.
Shit. Another 159 people.
Number 177.
I'm 175.
I called your number ten times.
You have to wait.
Your file went back to the records room.
You just passed my number by two.
Mr. 175. Don’t be selfish.
Take a seat and wait.
I will call you again.
And please pay attention this time.
Number 178.
Damn it.
If I paid 7,000 baht,
I would be done already.
Who said money can’t buy time.
Such a waste of time.
In three hours,
I could have removed 20 pimples
and retouched 30 more boobs.
Fuck this. Forget it.
Number 175.
I'm 175.
Please go to room number five.
Damn you, Doctor.
You'd better cure me.
-Good morning.
What’s your name?
-Assanai.
-Last name?
Srisiri.
JAE
I won't examine you if you pick up.
So, what is the matter?
I have a rash
-on my arms and neck.
-Let me look.
-I see.
-It's on my finger too.
How long have you had it?
I've had it for a while now.
What’s your occupation?
I’m a graphic designer.
A graphic designer?
Are you regularly exposed to ink powder?
No, I'm not. I work on a computer.
I retouch photos.
I see.
Something like resizing
celebrities' boobs for magazines?
I also remove pimples and stuff like that.
Whose boobs are the hardest to work on?
I’m not at liberty to say.
So, I guess you have seen
a lot of boobs then, right?
Guys like you are good at...
that program Photo--
-Don’t scratch it. Photoshop.
-Photoshop.
-Right?
-Yes.
I...
I tried once, but it was too hard.
You tried using Photoshop?
What for?
Well...
You know, sometimes I get pimples,
and I had to post some photos.
So, you know, it was embarrassing.
But in the end,
I couldn't work it out.
To remove pimples,
you should use the clone stamp tool.
-See?
-Touch it lightly and drag it.
It's over my head.
It's not hard.
Yes.
It is hard.
Let me see your finger.
Are you still in med school?
Yes, I am.
I'm doing medical specialty training.
If you
don't feel comfortable,
-you can change doctors.
-No, it's not like that.
I just imagined you would be older.
But you are not old.
I see.
Let me have a look.
So, you don’t really sleep much, do you?
How do you know?
It’s obvious.
I can see it in your eyes.
Shit! Why am I blushing?
Oh, no.
Stop sweating right now. Please stop.
Are you hot?
What?
Are you hot? Because...
-you are sweating.
-Am I?
Yes.
Or...
I don’t know.
You are really not well.
Now, pull up your t-shirt.
Why?
I have to examine you.
Don’t be shy.
It’s okay.
Pull it up.
This is the most fucked up
moment in my life.
You said it was only on
your neck and hands.
Did you scratch here?
Yes, you did. Look at them.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 13
Shit. I wish I could do some sit-ups now.
Does it itch anywhere else?
Well...
There are some on my stomach
and some on my arms.
How about your penis? It’s important.
Oh, man.
Come on.
Your penis is just an appendage.
It's like your arms and legs.
No, it's not. How are they alike?
I can do an infographic for you later.
Come on. You are already 30 years old.
-You can't wait. No.
-It's all the same.
-They are just sores.
-It's okay.
I’ve seen more than
a thousand penises. I’m okay.
I’ve only seen one penis. I’m not okay.
Sir, we are very busy here.
A lot of patients are waiting outside.
-I understand.
-Good.
Look. They look like these here.
You see them, right?
They are just like these.
I see.
What's okay, Doctor?
Fuck.
So this is what being raped feels like.
Did you get raped or something?
Shit. Can she hear my thoughts?
All done.
Come back next month for another checkup.
Next month?
My schedule is always changing.
I am quite busy.
I will prescribe you
some medicine for this month.
The pharmacist
will explain how to take it.
I need you to do four things for me.
Listen carefully.
First,
take all your medicine.
Second, stop eating seafood altogether.
Third, go to bed before 9 p.m.
Fourth, exercise for 30 minutes a day.
All that?
And do not scratch.
Can't you give me
a get-better-right-away pill?
I’m kind of in a hurry.
If you are in a rush,
then exercise for one hour.
There is no such pill.
That's not what I meant.
I just want some medicine to cure me.
Non-drowsy ones, please.
Mister, your damn body
is declaring war with you.
Shit.
The doctor just said damn.
She rocks.
I’m sorry I said damn.
Sorry. You see,
your body is trying
to let you know that it's not okay.
-It’s actually trying to kill me.
-Correct.
All right. See you again next month.
Ms. Toi, send in the next patient, please.
Take these home and read them.
SKIN ALLERGY
Here is your next appointment.
See you next month. I hope you get better.
If I’m not free next month,
-can I reschedule?
-Come on.
The date is set.
Don't reschedule.
I want to see you.
Okay.
-Goodbye.
Excuse me.
So, what’s wrong with me?
I don’t know yet.
I just know you have an allergy.
An allergy.
Thank you.
Stop staring. It's stressing me out.
I'm almost done.
You never finish work late.
I still have time.
You are almost out of it.
-Jae.
-What?
I’m curious about something.
What is it?
Have you ever had
a breast cancer exam?
Yes, why? Do you have breast cancer?
So, you’ve had them checked?
Yes.
Weren’t you embarrassed?
Why the hell are you asking? Just shut up
and work. Keep your hands busy.
No, I'm curious. Weren't you embarrassed
when you showed your boobs to the doctor?
Doctors see millions of boobs every day.
They wouldn't care about mine.
Not even if the doctor was a man?
No. The only time that I was embarrassed
was the first time
I showed my boobs to my boyfriend.
That is way too much information.
Well, you asked for it.
I asked about your doctor, not your boobs.
Why were you embarrassed?
Well,
because I like him.
We usually feel shy
around the people we like, right?
Why are you asking this?
Are you asking for someone else?
No, I was just curious.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Just tell me now.
What's going on?
I was just curious.
-Really?
-I'm done.
See? I told you it wouldn't be late.
Okay. Is it this one? I'll take it now.
Sure.
This is what they call late.
-How is it late?
-You are three minutes late.
Less than five minutes doesn't count.
Normally, you finish an hour early.
Is there anything to eat?
I waited for hours to get you this.
See how kind I am.
It's your favorite.
Send the rest to me later.
Okay.
Let's go, Suchart.
Shit. I’m conflicted.
What about the shrimp dumplings
you buy every day?
I don’t know either.
From what I heard,
if you are allergic to some kind of food,
you must eat more of that
to get over the allergy.
Like using snake venom
-to make snake serum, right?
-Yes.
-Have you ever heard of that?
-No. Never.
Fight fire with fire, man.
-You’re full of shit.
-I'm serious.
Damn it. What should I do?
-Kai.
-Yes.
Do you think we eat to live,
or live to eat?
Live to eat. Or else, why bother living?
I agree.
You should have said we eat to live,
so I would throw this away.
Don't you have any work?
-Well?
-I'm busy.
That's why I'm here to ask you.
Tell me now.
Okay. We eat to live.
Are you happy?
Right?
We eat to live.
But the soup is to die for.
What should I do?
You talk too much. How about this?
Trade your shrimp wontons
for my foot-long cheese sausage?
I’ll give you two.
Damn. Why am I not allergic
to macrobiotic food?
Everything that tastes good
is bad for our health.
But life without tasty food
is a sad one.
Such a waste of time. We've been talking
about wontons for ten minutes.
I’ve made my decision.
Fuck you, shrimps.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 23
I sent you the file.
See you at the meeting later.
Okay. But why did you send it late?
Bitch, it wasn't late.
Stop using the word "late". I hate it.
TAKE BEFORE BEDTIME MAY CAUSE DROWSINESS
Take before bedtime. May cause drowsiness.
I’ll have to skip this one, Doctor.
I feel so guilty.
What do I do?
Yes, Mister?
I want to become a member.
Monthly
-or lifetime?
-Lifetime.
Here.
All done.
Damn.
I feel healthier already just holding it.
I will be back.
Aren't you going to work out today?
Not yet. I have to go back to work.
I see.
Posting a picture of my new shoes
makes me breathe easier already.
NEW SHOES, NEW LIFE
This is where my healthy lifestyle starts.
What’s up, Jae?
“New shoes, new life.”
Someone like you,
jogging in the morning sunlight?
Why not? Even some rock stars
play ping pong. What is it?
Isn't a job better than a sunburn?
October 7, an early brief.
Sure.
This print job has five photos.
You have four days.
Do you know the way to Joe’s place?
DERMATOLOGY INSTITUTE APPOINTMENT FORM
Remember? You’ve been there.
Jae.
What?
What day is it again?
October 7.
WEDNESDAY OCTOBER 7
I can't go.
What? You just said you could.
I have another job. Sorry.
OCTOBER 7
Damn. Dark circles.
She will know just by looking at me.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 23
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 33
You’re not helping me at all.
I did what you told me.
New shoes?
Have you been jogging yet?
Judging from your rash,
you haven't done a thing.
No topical cream residue.
You’ve been scratching again, right?
It's itchy, Doctor.
Shouldn't I scratch when it itches?
-No.
-The itch goes away when I scratch.
It does not.
-What?
-Scratching makes it itchier.
You open up your wounds.
And the bedtime pills, you haven’t
been taking them either, have you?
Can you tell that I haven't?
No.
But based on your reply,
I know you haven’t.
And how is your penis?
Aren't you being too attentive, Doctor?
I’m really upset.
You're asking too much.
I feel like you're asking me to be a monk.
-This--
-Who sleeps at 9 p.m. anyway?
-It's not--
-My job doesn't allow that.
-What I asked you to do isn't hard.
-It is hard.
Doctor, do you go to bed at 9 p.m.?
Are you saying
that you work 24 hours a day?
Yes.
Don't you get weekends off?
-No.
-Sundays...
Wait. Shouldn't you get Sundays off?
Why should I?
Do you need the money?
No. It has nothing to do with money.
Let me explain.
The freelance industry is very tough.
Whatever work comes in, I have to take it.
Otherwise, someone else will take it.
And if I don’t take the job,
they won’t hire me next month.
Then I'll be in deep shit.
Why not get an assistant?
If I got an assistant, the company would
contact them directly and hire them.
Another thing is
since they called me for the job,
they want me to do the job.
I must do it myself.
Do you think you will only get
a rash and that's it?
This is just the beginning.
Fuck you, body.
Don't scratch.
What's your nickname?
-Yoon.
-Yoon, I'm Im.
Since we are around the same age,
let's be friends.
When I treat a patient,
I take it seriously.
I think that
you take things seriously too.
Because when I treat someone
and that patient doesn’t get better,
I feel like I'm not doing my job properly.
Do you know what I mean?
You may wonder
why I ask you so many personal questions
and they seem like none of my business.
But just trust me, I really do care.
Think of this as a partnership.
It's my pleasure to work with you.
Shit. You’re so screwed.
If you haven't improved
the next time you come,
you will see my dark side.
See you next month.
-Goodbye.
-You don't need to do that.
We are friends.
Don't scratch.
It’s perfect already.
Just check it and submit,
or you’ll miss your bedtime.
Hang on.
Fuck. Her nail is chipped.
Holy cow. It's almost 9 p.m.
You take long showers,
so you need extra time.
You also have to apply the cream.
Stop being paranoid.
No one will notice it.
It's tiny.
Enough. Done. Stop. Save. Send. Sleep.
Just hit Command-S.
Save.
Hello, I sent it.
What? Wasn't that too fast?
I'm just that good.
Sure.
You can't do any more. You sent it.
Turn off the computer.
Damn it. You only shook her hand once.
It's driving you crazy.
This is the bravest
you’ve been in seven years.
The last time you were in bed before nine
was in seventh grade.
Inhale.
Exhale.
Hold on.
I have another deadline
on Wednesday, right?
Damn it. Seven hours out the window.
I should have fixed the nail.
Shit! I’m lying down but I can’t sleep.
Her nail is still broken.
Forget it. No one will notice it.
But if you noticed it,
someone else might too.
How could you submit
such crappy work like that?
Shit. Her nail is broken.
Just sleep.
I won't be able to fall asleep
if I force it.
In order to fall asleep,
I have to stop thinking about it.
But her nail is broken.
Oh, my god. Just sleep.
Stop thinking already.
Shit. But her nail is broken.
Shit. Stop thinking. Her nail is broken.
Wake up, kid.
What's with this machine?
How can anyone lift it when it's so heavy?
Mister.
Do you need any help?
I am coming for you.
I’m going to get you. You damn rash.
Wait.
Shit. I forgot to turn on my phone.
Holy cow, 57 missed calls.
Did a client die, Jae?
What's up?
Didn’t you call me?
Never mind.
Just tell me why you called.
Nothing. The girl group's cover,
I saw one of the nails was chipped.
But I got Jerd to fix it. It's fine now.
What?
You sent my work to Jerd.
That was out of order.
Yoon, it's not a big deal.
-Not a big deal?
-It doesn't make a difference.
-Really.
-Fuck you. How can you say that?
-No difference?
-The job was simple.
-Be reasonable.
-Fuck you.
-You should have told me.
-You
turned your phone off for half a day.
I had to fix it. You weren’t here.
Is there a girl?
Hell, no.
Have you ever seen me with a girl?
No. I'm not saying you can't or anything.
But you can't just
turn your phone off like that.
Normally, you’re more professional
than this, you know?
Luckily, I spotted it first.
How could you miss that?
Even I noticed it.
"Normally, you’re more
professional than this."
Damn it. I'm not getting better.
I'm not getting better.
I'm tired.
I wasted my time.
What the hell am I doing?
Wait.
Shit.
NOVEMBER
There are fewer spots now.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 33
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 31
One or two spots fewer
doesn't count.
But there are fewer spots.
Thank you.
Did you do everything I told you to?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Where did it go wrong then?
Let me ask you more personal questions.
I need to find out more.
What is your favorite food?
I guess
shrimp dumplings from 7-Eleven.
Your favorite food is from 7-Eleven?
There's nothing else to eat at night.
And they taste good.
They also have rice balls.
Are you joking?
I’m not joking. They really have them.
What do you do when you are free?
Oh, that’s hard to answer.
No, it isn’t. How about
movies, music,
the mall,
or the beach?
-Nothing?
-Those are just a waste of time.
How are they entertaining?
What would I do at a mall?
Shop for clothes? I don't buy clothes.
You don't buy clothes?
My old clothes are still okay.
Why would I go shopping?
I'm can't be bothered.
You could go out just for the sake of it.
It's fun.
What do you mean,
"go out for the sake of it"?
You go out for the sake of going out.
I don't get it. What do you mean?
Sometimes, it seems like
you are trying to piss me off.
No. Why would want to I piss you off?
What entertains you the most then?
-To think of a new project.
-Stop. That's work.
No. Work is when someone hires me
to do a job. The one I'm talking about
is my very own project.
Okay. How about sports?
Sports?
I like to play badminton.
But I don't have anyone to play with.
Don't you meet up with friends
ever?
I meet them sometimes,
at funerals and weddings.
But I can’t make plans
since my schedule always changes.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Damn.
What does that have to do with my rash?
Seriously, some people think
they're not related
but a patient’s lifestyle
has an effect on their disease.
-Really.
-I see.
And if I don’t have a girlfriend,
what is your medical opinion
on having one?
It actually depends on the person.
Some people have a partner
and it benefits them.
But some people's lives
are ruined because of dating.
Like how it can make you fail an exam.
You are like a detective.
I’m close to finding the bad guy.
You already know half my life story.
My mom has never even asked
some of your questions.
Are you saying I’m nosy?
No. Why would I say that, Doctor?
You should get more sleep.
What makes you say that?
I'm an expert on this.
I can tell just by looking into your eyes.
Yes. It's my
exam period.
I recommend Red Bull
mixed with coffee.
It will keep you up until dawn.
And that’s good?
It’s okay.
Well, we are not
in our 20's anymore. Back then,
I could stay up for two days
with no problem.
Now that I'm in my 30's,
my body is starting to break down.
-How many days can you go without sleep?
-Five days.
I'm one of the X-Men, you know?
It's my superpower.
But I'm okay, it doesn't affect me.
It's...
necessary.
Then
I think you should quit.
It's my job. How can I quit?
If you can't quit, you should cut down.
I can't.
But other freelancers I see
don't work as hard as you.
That's the case for normal people.
It's their choice.
I know that I can do more. So, why would I
want to be a normal person like them?
I don't think your work
is the source of your rash.
Make sure you take the bedtime pills.
I have been taking them.
If you have, you would be complaining
how sleepy you are right now.
Fuck.
How is it?
See? His work is good.
It's as good as yours.
To be honest, Jerd is just like you
were five or six years ago.
Everyone is calling him
Yoon the second, you know?
So, why did you call me here?
-It's wasting my time.
-Look.
Adidas Japan.
I'll take it!
Fuck. I'm sorry, Doctor.
You agreed without thinking.
Good. You will finally work
with an international brand.
I know you’ve been dying to do this.
Do you know how hard it was to land this?
Do a good job this time.
What's wrong? Are you possessed?
No. I'm just thinking
if I have other projects.
You must clear those projects first.
Make this your main project.
If you do a good job,
you will definitely get more projects.
Don't worry, Doctor.
I won’t break my promise.
Hey.
You can't charge your computer here.
Sir,
I just need to download a file quickly.
-Make it quick.
-I will.
MAY CAUSE DROWSINESS
I'm taking it, Doctor.
Fuck!
I have half an hour left.
-Is it ready?
-Yes.
Yes.
Thank you.
That is half of it.
I'll send the other half tomorrow morning.
Did you not finish it?
This is a big project.
-What are you doing, Jae?
-I'm calling Jerd.
Why? I'll submit it tomorrow.
-Yoon. I need it now.
-Don't call him, Jae.
-You have another half to finish.
-It--
-I'll finish it.
-No.
-You couldn't finish it.
-I will.
-Hello, Jerd.
-Why--
Yes. This is Jae.
Yes. That's right.
Do you have some free time?
Yes.
Okay. I have an urgent job for you.
It's for Adidas.
You can? Good.
You are free? Okay. Great.
Okay. Where are you?
Okay, I'll send it to you right now.
Goodbye.
Yoon, put it on the thumb drive
for me now.
No.
-Yoon.
-No.
This isn’t the time to be selfish.
-Are you ten years old?
-That's not it.
That's not it?
What are you doing right now then?
I said I would submit it tomorrow morning.
You have another half to do.
You won't make it in time.
Didn't you tell me
that a freelancer must be responsible?
-"If you can't make it, don't take it."
-But I can make it.
Can you really?
Yes.
Seriously, do you think so?
It's impossible.
-You have another half to do.
-Jae, I have been waiting for this job.
I don't want it to go to someone else.
Do you want me to beg?
Jae, please. Just this one time.
I'll send it to you tomorrow.
What do you expect me to do?
Damn it.
Let's go, Suchart.
MAY CAUSE DROWSINESS
Bring it on, bedtime pill.
I’m not afraid of you.
Kai, badminton.
-What?
-Let's play badminton.
What?
-Hurry.
-All right.
Don't hit it to the left
then to the right. I'm tired.
What's with the fancy technique?
Damn. I'm now immune to this bedtime pill.
DERMATOLOGY INSTITUTE APPOINTMENT FORM
FRIDAY DECEMBER 11
Number 190.
Next, number 191.
Jae, I sent it.
EXAMINATION ROOM ONE
Sometimes I hate you,
but you pull through every time.
All right. Thank you so much.
I'll submit it for you.
Do you still have time to see me?
I’ve been standing here for a while now.
I feel like I’m making life hard for you.
Seriously,
why are you here?
I’m trying very hard, Doctor.
Do you call this trying hard?
Yes.
Do you even know it has spread
to your ear?
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 31
If your skin is this severe...
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 50
...just imagine how rotten
you must be inside.
I understand, but...
I got this job
that I have been dying to do.
And I finally got it.
Do you think I can turn it down?
An opportunity like this
comes once in a lifetime.
Don't you only live once too?
Exactly. You only live once.
That's why you must follow your heart
and do the best you can.
You don't seem afraid of death.
You said people only live once, right?
Shouldn't we be happy while we are alive?
My job is my happiness.
I never feel tired when I work, Doctor.
So, is it wrong for me to work hard?
Also, everyone dies.
You are a doctor. You should know.
You don't know anything about death.
I may know more than you.
-That's why I'm not scared.
-Hold on.
I used to know someone
who talked like you.
He never cared about anyone
his entire life.
Are you like that?
I think your diagnosis
has gone too far now.
Being told you are nosy
-is actually quite offensive.
-No, I...
I didn't mean it like that.
Okay. It’s a doctor’s duty
to never turn a patient away.
So I have to continue treating you.
Sorry for wasting your time.
Do you still have the pills?
Here.
Next time, if you want a different doctor,
you can have it.
Just inform them at the counter.
I'm never lonely
Because I have me
To care for myself
-The loser
-Damn.
Is this a music video?
Must take care of himself
Fuck you.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
No.
Are you sure? Do you want to see a doctor?
Damn it.
I have to wait a month
to apologize to her.
Yoon.
-Yoon.
The client said
the crack doesn't look natural.
You can tell it's been retouched.
It looks unrealistic.
I see.
Another thing,
I'm sorry that I have to point this out,
but you forgot to erase the finger
of the guy lifting the athlete's leg.
Shit.
Don't make excuses.
Accept that it's shitty.
The work is shitty because you suck.
Excuses don't exist.
Yoon.
Are you listening?
Yes.
The second part of the Adidas project,
the female set,
they put it on hold.
Who got the job?
No one. They just put it on hold.
That doesn't happen.
Who got the job, Jae?
Jerd.
-Peng. Hello.
-Hello.
How are you?
I heard you're having a hard time.
You heard about it?
Of course.
Even though I'm not in Jae's department,
I heard about her
getting severely reprimanded.
Accidents happen,
-I guess.
-Come on.
Some people become permanently disabled
after a car accident.
Freelancers need
to maintain their standards.
Or you'll be unemployed
before you know it.
I suck, Peng.
Come on.
Look on the bright side.
You'll get some time off,
just like other people,
for the first time.
Anyway, I have to go.
I have a briefing.
Goodbye.
Happy holidays.
Are you ready to be happy?
Starting today, many people
will be traveling back to their hometowns,
while others will be taking trips
to cities within Thailand and abroad.
We will ask...
I'm going insane on the first day.
Damn. I want a job right now.
...and where are you traveling to?
You've got mail, Sir.
"Happy New Year, Son. Stay healthy,
and take good care of yourself. Mom.
P.S. When will you retouch
the picture I sent you?"
That's not what I do, Mom.
Shoot, Jae.
Shoot what?
Nothing.
What's up?
I'm going to Japan. Do you want anything?
Japan? Why are you going there?
My boyfriend surprised me.
We will celebrate New Year's Day together.
Can't you do that at Central World?
It's just as boring.
Do you want to talk to my boyfriend?
Are you leaving now?
Yes.
I'm about to leave now.
So, do you want anything?
I don't know.
I don't want anything. You should go.
Enjoy your trip.
Okay.
Happy New Year in advance, Yoon.
Happy New Year.
JAE
Jerd Pantagan.
“Pulling an all-nighter on New Year’s Eve
is the highlight of my life.
My fifth day without sleep."
-Four,
-three, two, one.
-Happy New Year!
Shit.
How did I get to this point?
The point where my calendar is empty.
Wait. Maybe it's not empty after all.
DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT
MEDICAL EQUIPMENT
Excuse me.
Do you have anything
that is scientific, yet artsy?
What do you want it for?
A gift.
STONE INSCRIPTION 4,200 BAHT
SIR ISAAC NEWTON 2,900 BAHT
Let me take a look around first.
Sure.
A highlighter shaped like a needle
is the perfect gift.
Scientific, yet artsy.
Okay. The first step,
place the box on your wrapping paper.
Then wrap it.
-This activity is for a sixth grader.
-Estimate the length.
It's actually kind of fun though.
JANUARY
Number 133.
DERMATOLOGY INSTITUTE NUMBER 134
HAPPY NEW YEAR
Happy New Year.
I should say it in Thai.
Doctor, Happy New Year.
Well...
-Doctor. Last month, I'm sorry--
-Number 134.
Shit. My hands suddenly froze.
I feel like I'm on a roller coaster
that's about to flip upside down.
I'm Assanai.
Am I in the wrong room?
No, you aren't.
Welcome. Doctor Chonnikarn
is busy doing her rounds.
All right. Let me check
your progress.
Doctor. I...
can come back next month.
Why?
So Doctor Im can examine me.
She’s handling my case.
I have her treatment plan.
She wrote your medical records down.
It won't affect your treatment.
Come on.
What?
Sir, I studied the same textbooks
as Doctor Im.
You won't die.
Come on. Let me see your arms.
Here. There are
red spots.
How long have you been
receiving the treatment?
It's been half a year.
Wow. That's quite a long time.
Doctor Im.
None of her patients want to get better.
What the fuck are you saying, Chink?
Chink. Stop texting.
Pay attention to me first.
Here you go.
DOCTOR IM
TELL HIM IF HE HAS TO STAY AWAKE,
DON'T BE UP MORE THAN ONE DAY,
TAKE HIS BEDTIME PILLS AND REST
I feel the inside of my body is changing.
But I don’t know what it is.
OH, AND TELL HIM NOT TO SCRATCH
Hey, Mister.
You were only supposed to read it.
Please.
Let me answer her quickly.
DOCTOR, I'M SORRY ABOUT LAST MONTH
I'm sorry. Please let me read her reply.
HAPPY NEW YEAR, YOU
YOU SHOULD REST, TURN OFF
YOUR COMPUTER, GO TO THE BEACH
WATCH THE SUNSET OR SOMETHING
YOU TOO
This isn't an internet cafe.
Bye, computer.
I must rest. Doctor's orders.
I can't turn back.
Do you have other colors?
All of the rings float,
whatever color they have.
But these don't look nice.
How fun.
Yoon.
How entertaining.
What do I do next, Doctor?
I didn't bring my computer.
I'm sorry.
Next time, please...
Next time, please call me.
I'll do it for you right away.
Yes. Please call me.
Okay.
How can anyone just lie down
and do nothing?
This is so unproductive.
GODDESS TUBTIM
Goddess Tubtim.
Even though I've been
a bit picky with my work,
I still want some jobs to come my way.
Holy cow.
I haven't even finished yet.
What is it, Jae?
Hello, Yoon.
-Please come for the brief.
-Sure.
Yoon, these photos look cheap.
Shouldn't wedding photos
be a bit more elegant than this?
I want them to look
classier.
I won't take the job.
What?
Did the beach chill you out or something?
Why are you doing this?
I got pregnant, so my boyfriend proposed.
No. I meant, why do you have to quit?
I'm pregnant.
My boyfriend doesn't want me to work.
Can't you work when you're pregnant?
If I were pregnant, I would still work.
Why can't you understand?
I'm having a baby.
My job will affect the baby.
If you play that card,
there’s nothing more to say.
-Why are you getting upset?
-I'm not.
You told me
we would work together forever.
Yes, I said that.
I'm sorry.
But you understand, don't you?
I don't. You can't do this to me.
Are you really upset?
-You have no right.
-Why not?
No, listen to me. Don't worry.
Your work won't dry up.
I will find someone to replace me, okay?
Why are you upset?
Because no one can replace you.
I don't care if the new person
is better than you. She's not you.
For me, there will never be another Jae.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
It's my fault.
I knew that this day would come.
I prepared myself.
But now that it's really here,
I can't deal with it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I don't mean to leave you hanging.
But at some point, we have to choose.
I just didn't choose my job like you.
Can I ask you to do one thing?
Even if we don't work together anymore,
give me a call sometimes.
Sure.
I will call you.
Once my baby is born,
you will be the first one I call.
Oh, shit, no. I need to call my dad first.
You will be the second one I call, then.
Do whatever you want.
I have a lot of pimples there.
Please get rid of them for me.
No pressure.
The deadline is in two days.
Fuck you.
Please give me bigger boobs too.
Is this man the best for you?
Do I have time to find someone else?
I'm always with you.
SURPRISE PROPOSAL VIDEO OF JAE AND SHANE
Hold on.
You had a romantic moment like this?
How the fuck is this a surprise?
This is the most clichéd shit ever.
Jae.
We have been dating for many years.
Jae. If you cry,
I'll kick you in the face tomorrow.
Will you marry me?
Sure.
LET'S GET MARRIED
I'm sorry.
I'm not crying.
It's okay.
Wait.
I'm crying.
What the fuck?
FEBRUARY
Doctor.
How could you make a mistake?
People's lives are on the line.
We are not farm animals.
You should quit being a doctor.
Find a new job.
Please calm down, Sir.
Please calm down.
Doctor.
I have a gift for you.
You weren't here last time,
so I brought it with me today.
I see.
Thank you.
Let's have a look.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 50
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 24
It has improved.
All right. See you next month.
Tell the pharmacist
which medicine you have left.
Doctor. I want to tell you...
Doctor.
You don't feel well, do you?
I suck.
That guy's nephew
has been my patient for a long time,
but he never got better.
It turns out it was a misdiagnosis.
My patients are unlucky
to have me as their doctor.
Otherwise, you would be cured by now.
No one wants to waste their time
coming to the hospital, right?
I'm sorry.
And...
I
know that I'm not a good doctor,
but I'm trying.
I'm trying my best.
Fuck.
This is the time to come up
with a super cool encouragement.
What should I say?
What kind of a doctor am I?
I'm eating sausages that look like
puppies' penises. They contain saltpeter.
As a kid, I was hospitalized
after eating them.
But if eating them makes you feel better,
I think it's okay.
It’s not the standard medical practice but
the better you feel, the faster you heal.
Shit. It rhymes.
It sounds sweet like a poem.
Am I seeing a doctor right now?
Actually, I just realized
that being a doctor is tough.
You have to say things
that make patients feel better.
I feel like I’ve been a bad patient
all this time.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
Thanks a lot.
Aren't you busy today?
Am I keeping you from your work?
I lost my job.
I screwed up once
and word got out within the industry.
No one wants to hire me anymore.
So, I’m free every day.
I should say that’s great, right?
You can finally rest now.
Right?
You don't have dark rings
around your eyes.
I retouched my eyes for you.
I will erase the rash for you, too.
Actually, our jobs
have a lot in common.
I don’t know if you still want to die.
But don't die, okay?
You will get better.
Okay?
“The way you look at someone
says a lot more than words.
And feelings sometimes
cannot be explained.”
Shit!
How did he come up with that?
It's so warm and romantic.
MY WORK IN CENTRAL SHIBUYA
JERD, YOU MAKE THAI PEOPLE PROUD
WOW, YOU HAVE COME A LONG WAY
CONGRATULATIONS
Black and white
makes it look like a funeral.
Yoon, my boyfriend
wants it to look dreamier.
What do you mean by dreamier?
Dreamy, you know.
The fact that you took these
at the park is lame. Don’t tell me
-you want pink grass, too.
-Yes.
Just do it to make him happy.
-For real?
-Yes.
Do you want me to add
a hopping rabbit at the back too?
Sure. Anything that the customer wants.
Does a relationship
not waste your time?
It does.
But I made my choice.
To be honest, it is fun.
You get to do new things.
Such as?
I won't tell you.
I don't want to spoil it for you.
You are being coy.
You learn how to love.
Wasn't my answer so sweet?
But you fight and stuff, right?
It’s a lot of hard work,
but surprisingly, it feels good.
Weird, right?
Have you nailed her yet?
What the fuck?
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 9
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 0
Shit!
I'm better.
Shit. I'm better.
I don't need to see
the doctor anymore, then.
DERMATOLOGY INSTITUTE APPOINTMENT FORM
MARCH
I thought you weren’t coming.
Why are you late today?
-I couldn't sleep last night.
-Wait.
Didn't you take your bedtime pill?
I did.
But I couldn't sleep.
I see. How odd.
Do you feel better today?
Let me have a look.
Come on.
The other one.
They're...
They have dried up.
Wow.
Let me see your neck.
Wow. They are all gone.
Pull your shirt up.
You don't have them
anywhere else, right?
All gone.
So, you are cured.
Yes, I am.
Why do you sound like you already knew?
Oh. That’s why
you didn’t wear a jacket.
You know, if you’re all better,
you don’t have to come anymore.
All done.
Congratulations.
I guess
we won't see each other next month.
It's all good, Doctor.
Thank you very much.
Come on.
It's okay.
You are fine.
I understand. It's okay.
You knew that was going to happen,
didn't you?
So, why are you acting like this?
You won't
see her anymore.
Why does it feel like when you were
heartbroken in second year?
But are you heartbroken this time?
You're not, right?
Your relationship with her was
a few minutes together each month.
She was just doing her job.
There was nothing more.
How can you say you are heartbroken?
But you said the word heartbroken
three times already.
Shit.
You are not heartbroken.
You are heartbroken.
It isn't rocket science.
I’ve given you my diagnosis.
I can't be.
Why not? I'm sure.
You have all the symptoms.
You can’t eat or sleep.
I was like this too.
When I was a teenager.
But we are not even in a relationship.
From what you told me,
you have fallen for her quite hard.
Right?
You put your work aside to see her.
You invited me to play badminton
and work out with you.
-Right?
-I was sick, so I went to the doctor.
Sure.
Exercise made me better.
You did it because you wanted her
to praise you, right? You did it for her.
You wanted her to see
that you did well
and that you were
good enough for her, right?
This shouldn't be hard to understand.
Love is like a disease.
You can cure it.
I'll prescribe you some medicine.
Here. Shrimp dumplings.
Eat your favorite food.
It can help you.
Another thing is,
you must find something to do
so you don't think of her.
You should work.
When I was heartbroken
and almost flunked out of college,
all I did was work.
I forgot all about my broken heart.
I stopped being sad.
I had no time to be sad.
Don't stop working.
It works.
Yes. I'm free during Songkran.
Yes. I can finish it in two days.
Yes.
For sure.
Everyone.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 0
I am back.
NUMBER OF RED SPOTS: 1
I came back to life.
SHRIMP WONTONS
Hello.
Hello, Yoon.
It's Peng.
Are you free? I have a job for you.
-It's a--
-I'll take it.
This is why I like you.
You are hardcore.
Let's meet tonight at 9 p.m.
-Okay.
-It's very urgent, I have to tell you.
-See you later.
-See you.
This job is for my friend, Lisa.
She’s having a gallery exhibition
in New York.
It's extremely urgent.
And this is a part of her exhibition.
It’s an installation piece.
It needs some retouching.
Everything needs to be done quickly.
It’s so urgent
that I thought of you first.
You are the only person in the world
who could get this done in time.
DAY ONE
You have two weeks,
but you must update us every day.
-Lisa will give you feedback right away.
-Okay.
Kai.
But you must work alone
on this project
because Lisa is paranoid
about her work getting out.
But if you nail this project,
Jerd's Shibuya work
will be like a speck of dust
in comparison.
We will fly to New York together after.
DAY TWO
Yes, Peng.
I sent you the feedback
for the previous lot.
Are you done with the current lot?
Not yet.
What's taking you so long?
You must speed things up.
Understood.
DAY THREE
Do you have to work this hard?
Won't your body fall apart?
I'll be fine. My record is five days.
Kai.
I’m really thankful
that you told me to work.
It really works.
Shit.
My head feels so heavy.
DAY FOUR
Yoon. Did you take the job from Peng?
Yes.
That job is two months of work.
He gave you two weeks
yet you still took it?
Yes.
Yoon.
If the job didn't have my approval,
you should have known.
Why did you take it?
Peng always takes advantage of people.
You are the only one who looks up to him.
Do you know that he lied
when he said
you were the first one he thought of?
Do you know that?
At least somebody thought of me, Jae.
He doesn't care about you.
He just wants your work.
He flattered you
so you would accept his offer.
-Jae, I'm happy.
-The budget is small
-so he hired you alone.
-Jae.
-I'm fine. Okay?
-Others rejected it.
What the fuck--
Shit. This is day six.
I broke my record.
DAY SIX
DAY EIGHT
DAY NINE
Yes.
Why didn't you pick up?
Are you done? We are running out of time.
-Yes.
-Yes, my butt.
You must hurry.
Do you know how long you are taking?
Yes.
DAY 12
I've heard that the longest
someone stayed awake for was 11 days.
This is day 12 for me.
I broke the world record.
I'm at the next level.
This means more than a Cannes Lions award.
We only live once,
so we have to give it all we have.
I think...
I have reached the pinnacle of my career.
If Peng could see me now,
he would know I gave it my all.
My chest hurts.
It hurts a lot.
Body.
You are so unreasonable.
Can you let me do my work?
I only have two photos left.
Shit.
I can't breathe.
Hey, body.
You are getting back
at me now, aren't you?
Bring it on.
I’m not afraid.
Death is a natural thing for me.
I used to think that we should be able
to plan our own funeral.
I want my funeral
to not be at a temple.
It can be in this room.
Just a nice coffin and flowers.
I like the band TK a lot.
I have never seen them live.
I would want them to sing at my funeral.
I want them to sing
the song "Handkerchief".
It’s a hit song.
Everyone should be able to sing along.
The feelings
that I
Guest list.
Am overwhelmed with
-But don't understand
-Jae.
Where are we
Right now?
Kai.
Can somebody
Pongsathorn.
Tell me please?
-When everything
-Mom.
Passes
-Will there be
-Four people. That's it.
So few people.
Anyone here?
I'm not sure
if I would want the doctor to be here.
When the day comes
I'm sorry, Doctor.
I died.
I broke my promise.
But don't be sad.
It wasn't your fault.
Hey, everyone.
Don't be sad at my funeral.
Death is a natural process.
I just
regret the fact
that I won't get to see Jae's child.
Kai.
I won't get to play badminton
with you again.
That day was fun.
Shit.
I forgot to retouch that photo for my mom.
Doctor.
I haven't told you
about my trip to the beach.
To be honest, I want to go back in time
and apologize to you.
And...
I want to talk to you again,
as a friend.
Shit.
I'm actually missing out on many things.
That's why the doctor told me not to die.
Body.
I'm sorry.
I give up.
But you won't forgive me now, will you?
Bye, everyone.
Will this really be the last thing
I see before I die?
It's not a good view.
Hello, Peng.
Yoon.
Don't call me cruel or anything
but the work isn't done yet.
You have a bit more to do.
I asked Lisa to extend
the deadline for a day.
If you get up and do it right now,
I think you can do it in time.
You can work here.
I brought your computer.
There is Wi-Fi here, too.
That's why I said
don't call me cruel or anything.
But this is about finishing your work
and being responsible.
It's just a bit more. Two more photos.
Once you finish this job,
you can go home and rest.
You can sleep for as long as you like.
Then, we'll go to New York together, okay?
What did you tell him?
-I said I wanted to sleep.
-Damn.
Was Peng mad?
No.
He just told me to fuck myself
and find a new career.
Don't worry. I'll find you some work.
Can I ask you to do one thing?
Don't pull this shit again.
I'm begging you.
All right.
Jae.
You must have a baby, okay?
What?
I came back to life
just to see your child's face.
Are you free today?
Yes.
I came to see you.
I've got many things to do.
Number 116.
Mr. Assanai.
Why did you come back?
I thought you got better.
I missed you, so I came back to visit.
Really? Room number five, please.
Number 117.
If I only thought of you
as a patient that day,
I wouldn't have felt anything.
But since we became friends,
I was sad.
I hoped
for you to be healthy
so I wouldn't have to see you again.
I'm healthy and well, Doctor.
I just wanted to see you again.
I wanted to tell you a story,
but I never got the chance.
When you told me to go to the beach,
I actually went.
I never thought about
watching the sunset before,
but since you told me to,
I thought of giving it a go.
To be honest,
I felt that it was a waste of time
to watch the sunset.
But I don't know
what got into me that day.
I sat there for hours watching the sunset.
That day, I felt that
I could breathe so easily.
And I was happy.
Just like when I see you.
OUTPATIENT MEDICAL RECORD
DERMATOLOGY INSTITUTE
Thank you so much, Doctor.
I thought you said
you're healthy and well.
I hope I don't see you again next month.
Subtitle translation by
Pet-chompoo Sa-ngarmangkang