[narrator] For 6,000 years, man has
accepted the finality of physical death,
and when it comes,
he goes to a familiar grave.
But today, for those who see
the prospect of immortality,
there's a new
and less permanent resting place.
The start of a silent revolution
which could affect
the future of the world.
In those capsules,
people who determine to live twice,
who prefer the freezer to the grave.
The first of the
"die now, live later" group.
Men and women
frozen solid in their cylinders,
waiting for the future.
[metal scraping]
And, they believe, cheating death.
[announcer 1] Person placed in cryonic
suspension is probably...
without a doubt, it's the most sanitary,
and most scientific,
and perfect form of preservation
we can possibly imagine.
[announcer 2]
Each individual on this planet
has one big overriding problem,
his own death.
And it's a big problem
and no one has solved it yet.
[Sahatorn in Thai] It was morning when we
discovered the aquarium's oxygen pump,
which supplied air to the aquarium,
had broken overnight.
Our mother announced,
"No school today. Save the goldfish!"
So we scooped out the floating fish
and put them in an ice bath.
Lowering their temperature
slowed down the death process.
And we found we could revive them later.
We were very successful.
More than 50% were revived.
[Nareerat] Come on. Let's go!
-Beep, beep.
-[Nareerat] Beep, beep!
Daddy.
[both chuckle]
We named our daughter Einz.
In Japanese and Chinese,
"Einz" means "love."
-[Sahatorn] What kind of bed is this?
-My sister's crib.
[Sahatorn] Yeah.
Are you doing this for your sister?
Or are you just following my orders?
For my sister!
-Do you really love your sister?
-Yes, really.
-Do you really want a sister?
-I haven't even met her yet.
-Do you really want her?
-Yes, I do.
If she watches this video later,
what would you like to tell her?
I love you, little sister.
-Hmm?
-I love you, little sister.
[Sahatorn] Einz was born out of
Matrix's wish for a sibling.
[Matrix] Hello. Today is March 2nd, 2012.
I've brought my sister to the mall.
It's the first time she's left the house.
[Sahatorn] He was an only child then.
[Matrix in English] When she was born...
I drew a little house, and a door,
and a countdown...
saying that,
"29 days until Einz arrives." [chuckles]
And I changed the date every day,
30, 29...
until...
until, uh, the day she was born.
I think I cried.
I was so happy.
[Nareerat in Thai] Why are you sitting
on the chair by yourself?
Such a gifted child you are!
[Nareerat chuckles]
One, two, three!
[Sahatorn] Einz brought
the whole family together.
Everyone had been waiting for her.
[woman] Here she comes!
[Nareerat] Daddy! Daddy! You're 40 now!
Today is Daddy's birthday.
And you have your new daughter with you.
[Nareerat] Our family today
includes my husband,
Dr. Sahatorn, nicknamed "Top."
Then there's our eldest son, Matrix
and our daughter Matheryn, or Einz.
[Nareerat] Such a pretty dress.
[Sahatorn] My little Einz.
I think that for the bottom bit,
just drill a little and put this in there.
For the upper bit,
we'll clamp it until it's flush.
Just a little effort, and it should fuse.
In our family...
we place a lot of importance on science.
That means,
if we know something, we say we know.
If we do not know something,
we say we do not know.
Just because we don't know something,
it doesn't mean it's not true.
My family knows that I always used
the scientific way of thinking
to solve problems.
[Nareerat] We have
a good head of the family.
I was once Sahatorn's student.
He is still my teacher.
A teacher for our children.
[Matrix in English] What I like
about science is that
most of the thing can be explained.
Everything is natural and unnatural
at the same time.
[professor] Just grab a pair of goggles.
We're talking about thermal physics,
which is all about particles, of course.
So, if you were able to see
those particles,
what would be different about them
as I'm heating it?
It would be vibrating at a frequency
of a certain color of the light.
[professor] Okay. You're absolutely right.
The frequency of the light.
[in Thai] This.
Haven't used this in a while.
[Matrix in English] When people talk
about my sister, they'll be like...
"Oh, I'm so sorry. But it's okay
if you don't wanna talk about it."
But...
I...
I don't want to forget...
the pain we've been through together.
I don't want to...
leave out the bad memories.
They're all memories
and I feel like I wanna keep all of them.
I don't wanna...
I don't want to ever forget them.
[Sahatorn in Thai] What happened was...
We were working on a project
in another province.
Matrix, being in Bangkok,
was the one taking care of his sister.
I had this bad feeling. A nightmare.
So I phoned Matrix in the morning
and told him to go and wake Einz up.
But he couldn't wake her up.
[siren wailing]
[Nareerat] On that day, our daughter went
into a coma and was unable to wake up.
[Nareerat singing softly]
I wished I could take her place.
Take her pain away. Be the one who's sick.
I've always felt
nothing could happen to her
because her mother is here to protect her.
It's gonna be okay, honey. It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
[Sahatorn] The neurosurgeon said
it is probably ependymoblastoma.
No one had ever survived it.
[Nareerat] Einz has the deadliest
brain cancer in the world.
Since the day she fell into a coma,
Einz underwent ten surgeries,
twelve rounds of chemo,
and 20 rounds of radiation.
She was in and out of comas.
Always in and out of the ICU and PICU.
But through it all,
she always woke with a smile.
Everyone waited for Einz's smile.
-[woman] Here comes Ei-Ei!
-[Sahatorn] Here comes Ei-Ei!
[woman] Yay!
[kissing]
[Sahatorn] My heart was rebelling.
Maybe there was a chance.
So we had to keep fighting
until we were sure there was no chance.
I didn't have the right to decide.
She did. She had the right to decide
whether she would keep fighting.
[Nareerat] I discovered
that my husband had this powerful love.
Throughout 100 days of illness,
he never got a full night's sleep,
because he was researching
the latest technology and treatments.
[Sahatorn] I've started collecting
her cancer cells from surgery to culture.
But I'm not an expert in this field
so I've experienced many obstacles.
But what's important
is that I don't give up.
Even if the chances of success are low,
I have to keep working on it.
[Matrix in English] My dad spent
nearly every day,
when my sister was sick,
at Chula to, um, test medicines...
on her cancer cells.
I personally think he's
one of the mad scientists.
But many things in the world
that have been invented...
were invented by mad scientists
because they were crazy enough
to think of something new.
[Sahatorn in Thai] I experimented
with around five kinds of chemicals
as well as other treatments
that had the possibility
of curing my baby.
You mean...
you will place this camera here
to observe the cell culture.
Yes, to see if the cells are normal.
Then when we're done,
we prepare the tissues here.
After that, we bring the different cells
to the hypoxia closet.
[Sahatorn] There's so much
suffering in life.
We are under so much pressure
as we fight this.
As scientists, we know the chances
of finding the right medicine in time
are slim.
I began to think,
what if the doctors can't find a cure?
Can't find a way. What should we do?
That's when cryonics entered my mind.
[narrator in English] It's a possibility
that's existed
in science fiction for years.
Two American corporations
now claim to offer it as a reality...
[man] It sounds like science fiction
but it's not.
[woman 1] I wanna live until tomorrow.
I wanna live forever and ever.
I love life.
-[woman 2] I wanna see the future.
-Death is an option.
The idea of reanimating
is wishful thinking.
I don't care if it's robotic.
I don't care what my body is.
[Sahatorn in Thai] I've always loved
this area of science since I was a kid.
I've always known what cryonics was.
Cryonics is a process
that preserves bodies of living things.
This was the way to keep her.
We must keep her.
[Matrix in English] After my dad noticed
that the cancer was growing way faster
and Einz
wouldn't probably be able to fight back,
he said that she might need to be frozen,
and then we're all like, "What?"
My auntie, my mother,
everyone was against it.
[in Thai] When everyone learned
about cryonics,
her grandparents wondered,
"Why we would do this? What is it?
That death is death.
What was the point of doing this?"
Can we stop the process of dying? Yes.
Can you believe that we can stop it?
This is what I have to show my family.
[indistinct chatter]
They asked, "Even if we can preserve her,
has anyone been brought back to life?"
[Nareerat speaking indistinctly]
[Sahatorn] Growing up in
an Asian family...
I believe we have souls.
There was conflict within me about that.
I do believe that our souls can be reborn.
But we all still disagreed
with one another.
[Nareerat] He said he wanted to give her
a chance at a life in the future.
[Sahatorn] I know in my heart
that she can be preserved.
[Nareerat] The way my husband told me...
showed clearly
that he was doing this
out of love for his daughter.
[Sahatorn] I spent many months trying
to persuade my wife until she agreed.
She said we could do this,
not because it might or might not work...
but we'd do it because I asked to.
The one thing that helped
even those who have no knowledge
of the technology to understand us
is our love for her.
He knew well
from looking at the medical reports.
We knew in our hearts
that she would pass away.
She'd gone as far as humanly possible.
The doctors admitted
that she would not survive.
PEDIATRICS 2
[Sahatorn] We have reached the end.
The end of what's medically,
humanly possible.
There's no more.
We have reached the limit.
[Nareerat] You are in our hearts, always.
[Sahatorn] If one day,
you wake up and watch this video,
maybe many hundreds of years from now,
we want you to know we love you.
[Nareerat] On her last day,
we were with her.
Everyone in our family was with her.
We asked for Einz to die at home.
We prayed over her
and told her we loved her.
And prayed that we will see her again.
[woman 1] Dear all beings, our friends
in sin who are born, age, suffer and die.
May you find contentment.
May there be no bad fate.
May you find contentment,
have no pain in your body and your heart.
May you be content in body and mind.
Take care of your mind and soul.
Find contentment in both.
Forever and beyond.
[woman 2] May you find so much happiness.
-[woman 1] You can go now, little fighter.
-[woman 2 sniffles]
[Sahatorn] Matrix has described
that day as
being in slow motion.
Everything repeating itself,
creating a wound in his heart.
At the time that Einz passed,
the doctor examined her immediately...
and he pronounced her dead.
Then we began the cryonics process.
[Aaron Drake in English] As soon as
the heart stops beating,
we wanna start immediately.
Sixty seconds if possible.
Here we are with this family
and they're willing to be in the room.
To witness, to see, to help.
And this girl who just passed away
is being opened up, surgically.
I've just... I've never seen that before.
Okay, let's cut it.
To overcome that is true love,
in my opinion.
The fact that we were there in Thailand
and in place before she died
is very important.
The biggest fear is that we won't be there
when they die,
and will that prevent them
from being cryopreserved.
We're using cold,
profound hypothermia,
as a way to maintain cellular viability.
By doing that, as future sciences,
future technologies develop...
we may be able to come up with a cure
for what they died of.
[Sahatorn in Thai]
Einz's body temperature decreased...
until we closed the capsule
and sent her to America.
At that moment,
I was grieving beyond words.
I told her,
"Come back and be my daughter again.
Mommy loves you so much."
This is the dress my whole family loves,
especially her father.
When he saw it, he said right away
he wanted to buy it for Einz.
While awaiting her birth,
we named her Einz.
Einz was our beloved.
We bought this dress in two sizes.
A size for a one-year-old,
and a bigger one for a three-year-old.
Einz wore this white dress
even when it was too big for her.
She wore it nearly every day,
for every special occasion,
for her first and second birthdays.
But Einz didn't live long enough
to wear it on her third birthday.
On days we feel discouraged,
or exhausted and want to hug Einz...
we hug this white dress.
[voice breaking] Because it feels
like Einz is here.
[Sahatorn] In Buddhism, we believe
that when a body dies and disintegrates...
tangible elements will transform
into other things.
They are not permanent.
But there is the intangible.
It controls how things come to being.
Some call it the soul.
We cannot say Einz is truly dead,
but we now we have been parted...
and it will be very difficult
to meet again.
I told my son,
"Remember, your sister is there."
One day, technology will be able
to fix matter on a molecular level.
On that day,
Einz will have another chance.
[whimsical music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
-Did it hit the target yet?
-It has.
E and...
I haven't fixed it yet.
[Sahatorn] Go ahead and use one line
as the INT of the Y, okay?
And another line as the INT of motor X.
That way, you keep the code neat.
[Matrix in English] I have a passion
for science...
since I was the only child in my family.
Most of the things...
scientific things I've done
have been triggered by my dad.
He asked me whether I'm interested
in this and that.
Then I'll be like, "Yeah, sure."
And then I do it.
[in Thai] This is test number seven.
It's not igniting.
Test number 11.
Test number 44.
Test number 50.
Success! Success!
[in English] My biggest motivation
in science is...
Right now, it's my sister.
[in Thai] I don't need to adjust
the focus or anything, just look?
[woman] That's right.
[Matrix in English] So,
to have my sister frozen,
it's like keeping her in a capsule
where the clock is not ticking.
So, it stopped right there...
and wait for the technology in the future
to bring her back.
[Max More] The inevitable question is,
"When will we bring our patients back?"
Um, I really can't answer that question.
The exact details of the revival process
are unknown to us.
We're clear on that when people
make arrangements to be cryopreserved.
We're set up as a non-profit,
tax-exempt organization.
Now, if you want to go as a whole body,
that's a minimum of $200,000.
If you want to just cryopreserve
the brain, that's only $80,000.
It's hard to say
we're exploiting people's grief because...
almost all our members sign up
for this process well ahead of need.
[Aaron] In order for cryonics to work,
you have to really look at what would be
the mechanism to make it work.
Some people are hopeful
that regenerative medicine,
three-dimensional printing,
stem cell seeding,
we could maybe regrow a whole new body.
Some people are looking at nanotechnology,
where they're going
and doing repair at the cellular level.
Some people are looking
at the connectome theory in neuroscience,
where if we can just preserve the brain,
once we have the ability
to 3D scan that brain,
we may be able to create
a whole new person.
Or this may never work.
[Max] This is just my guess,
but I'm imagining that
you might first be brought back
to consciousness in virtual reality.
To prevent you getting into trouble
in the real world,
like walking in front of a flying car
or who knows what.
In Matheryn's case, I hope her family
will be there and she'll recognize them.
Hopefully, they'll be around the same age
or younger than when she last saw them
because we'll solve the aging problem.
[Matrix] The technology
which will be able to bring her back
is not gonna be like anything we see today
and I couldn't imagine
what it would be like yet.
[Sahatorn in Thai] Our body is
like hardware.
And the soul is software.
It's like we had manufactured
a defective computer.
So we have to put it on hold.
We believe that
the computer could work again.
We know how to assemble the human genome,
assemble DNA.
That means we are bringing life
to something that wasn't alive.
For sure, we are heading towards...
deathlessness.
That will be Einz's time.
Einz will wake up in a world
without disease.
[Nareerat] For our journey to visit Einz
at Alcor, in Arizona,
we've prepared CDs,
all the memories of her.
Like her first baby outfit,
shoes, bedding...
all her stories, her toys, clothes.
If she wakes up one day,
she will see the things
we've prepared for her.
It will be kept at Alcor.
[Sahatorn] I've already seen
a lot of images
of the cryonic facility interior.
So, I think that,
through these images I've seen,
I have a vague idea
of how their facilities will look.
It's not a grave or burial place.
More like a place to have a rest.
We plan to visit her regularly.
We are lucky.
It's like fate. Right?
Because the facility where Einz is
and our close friend's house
are located close to each other.
Only 30 minutes away.
Tomorrow, if all goes according to plan,
we'll go to Alcor along with our friends.
You're heavy.
[indistinct chatter]
FOREVER WITH US
EINZ, THE LITTLE FIGHTER
Let me see. What are you writing?
-Heart.
-[Sahatorn] One heart.
[Nareerat] A heart. Draw a heart.
Do you want to wash it? Do you?
-[man in English] Hello.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you, too.
So, what we'll show you today
is a little bit different
than what we did for Matheryn.
But this is more of
our standard sequence of procedures.
-Hello.
-Hello, there.
After we take the...
The patient's been legally pronounced,
the heart is stopped,
and the doctor has said
that they're clinically dead,
uh, we will move them off the hospital bed
and put them into this ice bath.
The next thing we wanna do
is we wanna
restore circulation of the blood.
In your case, we just did
compressions under the chest,
this would be way too big for her,
for an infant.
-But for an adult, this will compress...
-Yes.
...the heart between the sternum
and the spine.
And it will push the blood out
just as if the heart were contracting.
The next thing we wanna do
is we wanna get them into surgery.
So, we will fly the patient here
and we'll go into our surgery room
which is down the hall,
and I'll take you down there. Okay?
[in Thai] Matrix, did you take
photos of the parts
that interlock with each other yet?
Here.
These parts here. They're all important.
[Aaron in English] Some clients of ours
had decided to do a whole body.
This is our surgery table,
where we do our procedure.
Now, for those patients
who decide to do a neuro,
we've got a different container here,
where the head
will basically be surgically removed,
they'll be placed in here.
We'll put cannulas into the carotid artery
and we can flush basically in there.
So it's a little bit smaller container.
And, uh, this is, uh, how we--
[Sahatorn] Basically,
you separate the head
and put here, and connect the...
jugular veins.
-[Aaron] The carotid arteries.
-Uh-huh.
[Aaron] We push... The fluid goes in
and it comes out the jugular veins.
You're exactly right.
Just gets cooler and cooler
as we increase the concentration of fluid.
This is our patient care bay.
This is where
all 141 of our patients are stored.
So these are the dewars.
Uh, the dewars hold
any type of liquified gasses.
Liquid helium, liquid oxygen...
These hold liquid nitrogen.
Now, they don't require any power.
They're not plugged into the wall,
receiving electricity.
They're cold because
that's the temperature of liquid nitrogen.
Minus 196 degrees Celsius.
[in Thai] I still feel like a scientist.
I don't feel like the father yet.
I'm still the scientist.
[in English] So, follow me in here,
into our patient care bay.
Um...
Most people think
it's gonna be really cold in here.
They think, "Liquid nitrogen,
minus 196 degrees Celsius...
It's gonna be cold."
-Let's see where Matheryn is.
-[Sahatorn] Yes.
Where is my baby?
[Aaron] This is Bigfoot 17, right here.
It holds our most recent patients.
So we talked about
there were five neuropods.
There's one at the very bottom.
There's one above that. She's in that one.
[Sahatorn] That means she is...
The level she is at is around here?
-[Aaron] No, right here.
-Around here?
[Aaron] Mmm-hmm.
[in Thai] Okay, everyone, come hold this.
Here's Einz's dress.
[sniffles] Let's put her photo here.
[Sahatorn] We had thought that sending her
to America was the last of it.
We would return to school, return to work.
Alcor wanted us to tell this success story
of the cryonics process for a child
far away in Asia,
the first time in the world.
Our friends called us from abroad
to say our story had made headlines
in their country.
We were shocked
to see how quickly it spread.
Hundreds of outlets published the story.
It became global news.
For us,
we had no idea this would happen.
The program welcomes Dr. Sahatorn.
Welcome to our show.
Say hello to Dr. Sahatorn Naovaratpong.
Oh, dear, you froze her body?
And you sent her whole body overseas?
That can't be.
Please explain to us
what this is all about
and why you're doing this.
Cryonics is a process
that freezes you, right?
We don't usually freeze the human body.
[interviewer] Let me ask you
this straight. Forgive me.
Does she know
her father's done this for her?
She was the first in Asia?
She was the first in Asia
and the youngest in the world.
If Einz is revived, she'll have no one.
What will it be like?
Do you think about that?
[Nareerat] We just say,
please see from the point of view
of a scientific family
who loves their daughter
with all their heart.
Twelve!
Twelve operations on a two-year-old!
Freezing her corpse...
Freezing her brain, or whatever it is...
Can you please explain this a bit more?
There's a human that's frozen
and that person will be thawed
in the future.
Is this something that can happen now?
This was really big news
that there was this father
who chose to freeze his own daughter.
The head in particular.
[interviewer] Actually, you also work
with cancer, right?
And you've also given
to various foundations
or funds for genetic research.
Publicizing the research in this area
and how you can contribute to this fund
are why I'm happy to be interviewed today.
The reason behind all of this...
is to preserve the parts
of Einz's soulless body
that would help her in the future.
Then there's all the critics
in Thai society asking,
"Are you keeping her soul
from resting in peace?"
[Matrix in English] People that really
believe in the idea
of reincarnation would say that
we are trapping her soul.
[in Thai] Don't you feel like it's going
against fate, against destiny or karma?
Some might think,
and pardon me for saying this,
you are imprisoning her,
according to Buddhism.
Imprisoning her soul.
If they are just keeping her head
and don't cremate it with her body,
many will believe she left
to the next world incomplete.
She is still tied to this world.
Her parents haven't allowed her
to leave without worry.
So, I accept that
I have not been able to let go.
I don't care that people think
we cannot let go
and that we still hold on to her.
This is who I am. I can't let go.
She is in a refrigerator
where the temperature is -192 °C.
[interviewer] So she's still alive?
She's alive.
But without biological activity.
[interviewer] On the cellular level.
So you won't see her again?
If I only wanted to see her, it'd mean
I'm only doing this for selfish reasons.
But if you want
to give your child a chance,
to give life is to give opportunity.
Without life, you have no opportunity.
And that's why I'm giving her this.
[Sahatorn] What I return to is...
thinking about her body.
I refuse to believe that
I have the ability to trap her soul.
When I look at video clips
of Einz playing,
part of her soul is in there.
It's in the photons bouncing off her
into the camera through some process.
She's saved in there...
and in every atom
that has come into contact with Einz.
That's why I believe her soul is intact.
Her software is intact.
And she may come back
when those particles take a new form.
If she comes back to her old self,
is that reincarnation?
That's how science would explain it.
It would be her rebirth.
Actually, our minds must be unwell.
The minds of everyone
in our family are unwell.
But we willingly submerge
ourselves in our pain
so we can feel that
we still have her in our minds.
[Matrix in Thai] Today, I'm ordaining
as a novice monk.
When my sister was sick,
I promised her I would ordain for her.
I haven't decided for how long yet.
I'm thinking two weeks.
Please take care of Matrix.
[Phra Kitiwimonmaytee]
Let him go while he's here.
Matrix will cut out any longing.
He will share his problems with me only.
He can't call home and ask for things.
He will live like a novice monk.
[Matrix] I'm hoping that, by ordaining,
I will be able to send protection
to my sister in the afterlife.
So I can find some peace of mind.
On this day,
I give you my blessing, grandson,
that you will have luck,
be rid of sadness,
of disease and depression.
Okay?
My dear son,
I hope that you find happiness.
I'm so proud to be your mother.
[Phra] When we lose, we weep.
We weep because we have lost.
Because we haven't accepted the truth.
Our minds haven't opened wide enough
to accept the real truth.
All life experiences
aging, suffering, and death.
There's no way to calculate
when or where you will die.
When they accept this truth,
their sadness will wane.
They will be able to turn that sadness
into strength.
[indistinct chatter]
[man laughing]
[Matrix] I do miss my sister.
I'm sad because I miss her.
I miss...
the songs she sings.
I miss her crying.
I miss the sound of her
calling our names. Calling my name.
[monks chanting]
Ordaining these two weeks means
I can think less about the outside world.
It also gives my family some relief.
So...
it will help calm my mind down.
[chanting continues]
[Sahatorn] I've only dreamed of Einz once
since she died.
I'm at this place where
the scientists there told me...
Einz's repairs are about to be done.
I walked over to her.
And I asked the scientists,
"Will she hear me, if I speak?"
They told me,
"She can sense that you are here."
So I went over
and called her name, "My little Einz..."
She moved a little.
Then I had this feeling.
This isn't real.
I know very well
the technology is not here yet.
[Matrix in English] My parents,
especially my dad...
he thinks that he wouldn't
be able to live up
until the point where my sister
could be brought back.
So he passed on the dream
of bringing her back,
which was originally his dream,
but now I felt like
it's a part of my dream now
and I really want to bring her back.
Uh, right there,
there's my dad's liquid nitrogen tank,
which is used to store my sister's cells.
In the future, I might use those cells,
grow it, so I can have more of it,
and test medicines on it.
Well, I dreamt about it several times.
About her.
Two years old,
with an older version of me.
[chuckles] I don't even know,
50, 60 years old.
To have her back,
well, would be the greatest achievement
of my life.
The old "brain in a vat"
just got an upgrade.
In a first, California-based
research group 21st Century Medicine
successfully froze and then thawed
the brain of a mammal, a rabbit.
Researchers have thawed out a rabbit brain
from cryogenic stage
and done it completely successfully
without damaging the brain.
This is a huge breakthrough, Margaret,
and this has gotten them an award
from the Brain Preservation Foundation.
[Molly] The foundation said,
"It is the first demonstration
that near perfect long-term
structural preservation
of an intact mammalian brain
is achievable."
[Mark] Obviously, this is in research
towards the goal
of cryogenically freezing humans
and bringing them back.
The neuroscience community
is in love with the idea
that they can finally map out,
in three dimensions,
the precise neural circuitry of brains.
It's the first time you have
a brain-banking technique
that can preserve an entire connectome
in a brain, uh, for at least 100 years.
[Kenneth] All right, so let's review
what we've got here.
[Robert] The connectome at a real general
level is how is the brain wired together.
Um, what neurons are connected
to what other neurons.
[man] And I like this image the most.
[Kenneth] In the future, you would do
a full scan of that human brain,
uh, so that you can map out each
and every synaptic connection,
understand those connections,
and simulate them in a computer
to bring the person
back to life digitally.
So I think this is
a synaptic junction right there.
I would say, in my expert opinion,
that, uh, people can trace
the synaptic connectivity
of this preserved pig brain.
So, definitely, in the very near future,
I'm hoping to preserve
a whole human connectome
and demonstrate that all
of the connections are still there
the same way I did for the rabbit brain.
[Matrix] To hear that he could preserve
a rabbit's brain
and maintain the structure
of the connectome of the brain
makes me think that bringing
my sister back is not that far away,
and it might happen
in couple of decades, maybe.
My parents, especially my dad,
he asked me whether I'll be interested
in meeting the scientist.
Well, the answer was a definite yes.
The technology there, in the US,
would get me closer
to bringing my sister back.
[Sahatorn in Thai] He is sort of like...
in the category of a genius.
And his thinking is very different.
It looks like he's not that old.
[Matrix] That's right.
He's not even 30 yet.
Not even 30. Really?
This Robert McIntyre...
-Really?
-Yeah, I think he's only 28.
[Matrix in English] I think he just
asked me to, like...
to show me how one scientist
could make change
and that I might be able to be the one.
[in Thai] Matrix, sit up straight
and stretch your spine.
Otherwise, I can't cut properly.
So what do you want out of this?
When you go to America,
it is an investment.
And, in a sense,
it is... a trip
to develop yourself.
Okay?
In this self-development trip,
Robert is presenting you
with an opportunity.
Since he's giving you this opportunity,
you need to make some plans.
What will you ask him?
These questions...
When I read them,
I might say, "Oh, this question...
is it worth the journey all the way
over there to ask him?"
But Papa will not come up
with the questions for you.
Why? Because this is your duty.
[Matrix] Can you make the front
a bit shorter?
Maybe cut it all off.
-Really?
-[Matrix chuckles] Yes.
When I don't comb it...
it falls in my face.
Then I break out.
Well, if we cut it so short in front,
it will look a bit nerdy.
All right. Look in the mirror.
[Matrix in English] His method of doing it
is totally different.
He won the prize because
no one could do it before.
To be able to bring the same person
back from the dead,
you need her body,
her personalities, her memories.
And, uh, personalities and memories is...
what make that person that person.
[laptop chiming]
[Sahatorn in Thai] Can you see us, Matrix?
I see you but the video is frozen.
-[Sahatorn] Is the image quality bad?
-Yes. Very bad.
[laptop chimes]
-Hello, Dad.
-[Sahatorn] This works.
When you call, it works.
When I call, it doesn't.
Mmm.
[Sahatorn] Try not to make your face
so wide in front of the camera.
Maybe today is not good for this.
Why is your hair so messy?
Okay. Let's try tomorrow.
I love you, Mom and Dad.
[Sahatorn] Try and look
more handsome, okay?
We love you, Matrix.
Okay. Bye, Dad.
[in English] The biggest question
I would like to ask is...
how close are we to bringing her back?
[Robert] Well, welcome to my humble lab.
All right, so, anyways.
We're gonna make some washout solution,
and we're gonna make our osmium tetroxide
and, uh, it's gonna be awesome.
So this is a piece of brain tissue,
like, from the slices, tiny little bit.
[Matrix] The tiny, white...
That black thing.
Plus, see how thin it is?
Oh, the black thing on top?
Yeah. And then, you cut even more
insanely tiny little bits off,
with this ultramicrotome.
What do you think of that? [chuckles]
Whoa.
All right, you wanna
try your hand at cutting it?
So, uh, this knob moves this thing
forward a little bit.
So, twist it a tiny little bit forward,
like that much, okay?
And then you smoothly and slowly
go down like that.
Not bad.
But it's on the downstroke that... Yeah.
Uh, good luck. [chuckles]
And if you break it, that's okay.
That's fine.
I've always been interested
in how the brain works
and preserving memories.
All of the things that enable you
to be yourself,
not just knowledge
or previous experiences,
but also your particular approach
and your personality,
those are all ultimately memories.
And so, if you're not preserving
the connectome,
if your preservation technique just
destroys all the synapses, for example,
then almost certainly,
it's not preserving memory.
I think, ultimately,
our memories and our
individual perspectives on the world
are worth preserving.
Um, they're incredibly valuable.
So you gotta get the cryoprotectant in
as fast as possible, right?
Um, but...
To avoid toxicity, right?
Um, and you gotta do it
at lower temperatures
because that's also
gonna decrease toxicity.
But if you put the cryoprotectant in
too quickly, it dehydrates the brain.
Pulls all the water out of it
and it damages the structures.
I decided to stay in the, uh, room
where the procedure was being done
and, uh, I saw her face and her eyeballs
just got sucked in.
-Mmm-hmm.
-So I didn't understand what happened,
then my dad told me
that she's being dehydrated.
And so, her brain...
with the water being replaced with
cryoprotectant to prevent ice crystals,
now that she's dehydrated,
and her brain is dehydrated,
so her brain's shrunken?
Oh. So the structure of the neurons
wouldn't be the same.
There's no answers to that right now.
Um...
My estimate is 0.1% chance
that the current techniques
that we have actually work.
So bringing them back
would be really hard because
the structure would likely be destroyed?
I think that it's important to focus
on connectome preservation.
But you also can't say that, for sure,
all that data is gone.
The question is how much damage
can you do to that
for the search process
to find the original connectome.
Either can't find it,
or the search base is so huge
that it would take forever
to find it, right?
I kind of have to think about that.
'Cause being brought back
without memories is...
not actually being brought back.
[laptop chiming]
[Matrix in Thai] Hello, Dad and Mom.
Hi, Matrix. How are you?
I'm doing pretty well.
I went to meet Robert.
-Did you ask him any questions?
-Well, I had prepared questions for him.
But...
-But you didn't ask him any?
-I did.
But I didn't ask all the questions.
However, my perspective
has shifted a little.
-How did it change?
-It changed...
The question I prepared was...
"How close are we to bringing Einz back?"
But after talking to him,
I found out that he believed
in cryonics when he was younger.
He was sure it would work, 100%.
But now that he works in this field,
and tried using the standard methods,
he found out that, uh...
even though some cells are alive
and can function as cells...
Well, they've been dehydrated,
so the conditions of the synapses
and the connectome are broken.
Like a building...
that's been demolished.
Making the preservation of the memories
a very difficult thing.
For him, this means the probability
that we can bring a person back,
with all their memories intact,
is only 0.1%.
Well...
when he said that
the chance of bringing a person back
with their memories is only 0.1%,
I felt a bit disappointed.
[Sahatorn] There has to be
a reconnection process.
Yes.
[Sahatorn] We have to wait for better
technology to reconnect everything.
Right.
[Sahatorn] Better technology.
It's a step further from just freezing.
Yes, Robert told me that it won't be easy.
Just for her to be thawed
at the right pace
for detoxification, it isn't enough.
They have to rehydrate the brain,
since it has been dehydrated.
And they have to reconnect everything.
Then, they have to give her a body
and cure the cancer.
It is difficult. Especially difficult.
He said that it might not be accomplished
within our lifetime.
Don't think too hard about this.
If you believe humans
will one day travel the universe,
then this won't be a problem.
Right.
[Sahatorn] It won't be a problem.
It's okay. We can be patient.
We can wait a thousand years.
Hey, who knows,
maybe time machines will exist then.
[melancholy music playing]
[Sahatorn] You are that happy, huh?
Your face is full of tears.
Why are you crying?
Is it because you have a sister?
[woman] Come and see your grandchild.
[in English] I think...
I've never, ever loved...
anyone that much.
[Einz giggling]
[Nareerat in Thai] Peek-a-boo!
[Sahatorn] I'm filming
you and your mother.
So that when you grow up,
you will know that Mommy loves you.
When you do grow up,
you can't say, "Mommy doesn't love me!"
Remember this video.
Papa is filming this as evidence.
Auntie Joy loves you, too.
You can't say,
"Auntie Joy doesn't love me!"
Is that true?
-Brother Matrix.
-I love you, okay?
[Sahatorn] Can't say, "He doesn't love me!
Daddy doesn't love me!"
Is that true?
It's okay if you don't
understand now, my baby.
I'm recording this. Remember this.
[Nareerat] I'm going
to button up your shirt!
Perhaps reincarnation is real
and she is Einz reborn.
Whatever the truth is,
we love her the same
because she is our child.
[Sahatorn] She is healing our family.
But she is not a replacement.
I will always wait for Einz.
That hasn't changed.
[instrumental music playing]