Miss Sophie.
I've closed up the shop.
You should come too, Sophie.
I'll just finish this. Go have some fun.
All right, then. I'm off.
I'm going.
Look, it's Howl's castle.
What? Howl? Where?
Look how close it is.
Oh, no.
I wonder if Howl's in town.
It took off.
No, just hiding from all the soldiers.
Say, did you hear?
Remember Martha, from South Haven?
They say Howl tore her heart out.
How scary...
Don't worry, he's not going to want yours.
Hurry up.
Really?
Oh, cut it out...
Hey, you, little mouse. Lost your way?
Oh, no... I'm fine.
Then how about a cup of tea?
Care to join me?
No, thank you. I'm busy.
She sure is a cute little mouse.
Say, how old are you?
You live around here?
Let me pass!
See, it's those whiskers of yours.
She's even cuter when she's mad.
There you are. Sorry, I'm late.
Where've you been?
Who are you?
I'm with her.
Why don't you two take a little walk.
What the-- Hey, wha--
Don't hold it against them.
They're harmless.
Where to? I'll be your escort.
No, really, I'm only going to Cesari's.
Act normal. I'm being followed.
Just walk.
Sorry I got you involved.
This way.
Hold on.
Drop your legs and start walking.
Good. Don't be frightened.
You are a natural.
I'll draw them off.
Wait here until the coast is clear.
Yes.
That's my girl.
Any chocolate Letties?
Look this way, Lettie.
Here you go.
Let's go for a walk, Lettie.
My sister?
Come back soon, Lettie.
Sophie?
How did you land on the veranda like that?
Have you become an angel?
It feels like I'm in a dream...
Lettie, why not use the office?
Thanks, but I should really be working.
What? You sure he wasn't a wizard?
He was so kind...
He rescued me...
Don't tell me he's stolen your heart.
If that was the wizard Howl,
he'd have eaten it right up.
Don't worry, Howl's only after beauties.
There you go again.
Listen to me, we live in dangerous times.
They say even the Witch of the Waste
is back on the prowl.
Sophie?
Oh, you...
Lettie, the madeleines are done.
Okay, be right there.
All right.
I'm going home.
It's a relief to know you're doing well.
Hello, Lettie.
Nice to see you.
Listen, are you going to spend
your whole life in that shop?
It meant so much to Papa.
Besides, I'm the eldest.
That's not what I meant.
Are you sure you want to be a hatter?
Well, I...
Bye, Lettie.
Come by the shop next time.
Sure.
I'll be on my way.
Sophie, you've got
to look out for yourself.
Sorry, the shop's closed.
I thought I'd locked the door.
What a cheap shop,
full of cheap little hats.
And you're quite cheap-looking yourself.
This is just a simple hat shop.
I think you had better leave.
You're very brave,
taking on the Witch of the Waste.
The Witch of the Waste?
You won't be able to tell anyone
about that spell.
My regards to Howl.
Is this really me?
I've got to stay calm.
I've got to calm down.
It's no use panicking, Sophie.
I'll be fine, I'll be fine.
I've got to calm down.
I'm back!
Welcome home, Ma'am!
-Welcome home.
-How do you like it?
It's all the rage in Kingsbury.
Amazing.
It suits you.
Don't you think it's wonderful?
Sophie!
Mrs. Hatter,
Sophie hasn't come down to work yet.
I wonder what's the matter?
Sophie!
Don't come in.
I've got an awful cold.
I don't want you to catch it.
You sound just awful...
Like some 90-year-old woman.
I'll stay in bed today.
You sure? All right, then.
Here we go...
You'll be fine, old lady.
You're still healthy,
and these clothes finally suit you.
But I can't stay here.
Ouch, ouch.
It's not easy being old.
They're saying this war
is going to be terrible...
Like a hand, granny?
Such a gentleman, but I'll manage.
Sure, old lady, but where are you off to?
Just a bit farther
than where you're going.
I don't recommend it, granny.
Nothing but witches and wizards ahead.
Thank you.
Going to the Folding Valley, at this hour?
Says her youngest sister's there.
I've hardly made any progress at all.
Thank goodness I've still got my teeth.
That'll make a good cane.
Up we go.
Might be a bit too thick.
Ouch, ouch.
What a stubborn branch.
Never underestimate Grandma Sophie.
Heave.
A scarecrow, eh? I thought you were
working for the Witch.
But how do you stand by yourself?
Your head's a turnip.
I've always hated turnips.
At least you're not upside down anymore.
So long.
It's so cold.
The town's still so close.
Don't follow me.
You don't owe me a thing.
You must be a magical whatever-you-are.
I've had enough of witches and spells!
Just go stand wherever you like!
This is a perfect cane.
Thank you kindly.
While you're at it, could you bring me
a house to sleep in?
Seems you get more cunning with age.
What a huge battleship.
I never realized how weak you feel
when you get old.
I smell smoke. Maybe there's a cabin.
Turnip-head, isn't that Howl's Castle?
This is hardly what I meant
when I asked for shelter!
What is this?
You call this a castle?
Is that the way in?
Just wait up there.
Hey, there!
Are you going to let me on, or not!
My shawl!
It seems warm enough inside, Turnip.
I'm going in.
Thank you.
Even Howl wouldn't want
an ancient heart like mine.
This time, it's really goodbye.
You may be a turnip,
but you're a good turnip.
May you find happiness.
What is this place?
Just looks like a dilapidated heap.
Well, one nice thing about getting old
is that nothing surprises you anymore.
That's some spell you're under.
It won't be easy to break.
The fire talked.
And you can't even tell anyone about it.
You're Howl?
Wrong. I'm the fire demon, Calcifer!
Well, then, Calcifer,
can you break the spell I'm under?
Easy.
If you break the spell that chains me
to this place,
I'll break your spell in a flash.
In other words, bargain with a demon.
You sure you can keep that promise?
Demons don't make promises.
I suggest you look elsewhere.
But I'm an exploited demon.
I'm chained here by a contract with Howl,
who works me to death.
I'm the one who keeps this castle moving.
My, you've got it rough.
If you figure out the secret contract,
the spell will break.
If you do that,
I'll break your spell, too.
All right. A bargain, eh?
Granny.
Boy... I've got my doubts about her.
Hey, who's this?
Porthaven!
When did she get in?
Stand by.
Why, Mayor, sir.
The sun is already high.
Is Master Jenkins at home?
The Master is out.
I answer in his stead.
An invitation from His Majesty.
It has come to war.
His Majesty desires every wizard
and magician, even the witches,
to aid our homeland.
His presence is imperative. That is all.
War, how awful.
And who might you be?
Calcifer let me in.
Don't look at me.
She wandered in from the Wastes.
The Wastes?
That's strange.
You're not a witch, are you?
A witch could never get in.
Porthaven, again.
A customer?
Stand by.
State your purpose.
Mama sent me.
The usual spell?
Behave yourself, now.
It's not the Wastes.
Granny, are you a witch, too?
That's right,
I'm the scariest witch in the land.
Sprinkle this powder on your ship
and the winds will favor it.
Sure.
Many thanks.
I can't have you making up things.
You should give up that disguise.
It's not a disguise, it's magic.
The Kingsbury door.
Stand by.
Is this the residence of Wizard Pendragon?
It is, indeed.
I bear an invitation from His Majesty.
Please inform Master Pendragon
that he is required at the Palace.
Our thanks to you.
A city fit for a king.
Get back in or you'll lose your nose.
Stop wandering around.
That's enough!
I'm going to get really mad.
This is a magic house, isn't it?
Oh, boy!
Where does the black one lead?
Only Master Howl knows.
I'm having my breakfast.
But you've got bacon and eggs.
We can't use the fire
when Master Howl's away.
I'll cook for you.
But you can't.
Calcifer only obeys Master Howl.
That's right, I won't cook for you.
Oh, here's my hat.
All right, Calcifer. Be a good fire, now.
Forget it, I'm a demon.
I answer to no one.
You'll do as I say,
or I'll pour water on you.
Or would you rather I told Howl
about our bargain?
Hey! Hey!
I never should've let this old lady in.
So, what'll it be?
That's right, there's a good fire.
Hey! Hey! I'll burn the bacon.
Calcifer's doing what she says.
I'd like some tea, too.
Have you got a kettle?
Sure.
Welcome home, Master Howl.
You have letters from the king.
To Jenkins and to Pendragon.
Calcifer, you're so obedient.
She bullied me.
Not an easy thing to do.
Who exactly are you?
I'm Grandma Sophie.
You see, I'm your new cleaning lady.
Give me that.
Pass me two more bacon slices
and six more eggs.
Yummy.
And who hired you to clean?
Why, I hired myself.
I've never seen such a filthy house.
Markl, plates.
You're all ganging up on me.
Please join us, Sophie.
Sit over here.
Pick one.
Everything else is dirty.
I've got my work cut out for me.
Markl.
Yes.
Sophie.
Thank you.
Brethren, let us partake
of our daily bread.
Our daily bread.
Haven't had a real breakfast
in a long while.
So many manners to teach...
So, what's that in your pocket?
What?
I wonder what it is.
Let me.
It's scorched into the table.
Master Howl, this is...
Ancient sorcery.
And powerful, too.
The Witch of the Waste?
"He who catches a falling star,
oh heartless man.
Your heart shall be mine."
Well, so much for the table.
Wow, it's gone!
The scorch mark has vanished,
but not the spell.
Brethren, continue your meal.
Calcifer, move the castle 100 kilometers.
And send hot water to the bath.
Not that, too!
Do you work for the Witch of the Waste?
Don't be stupid! The witch--
Actually... the witch... I--
Confound it!
Damn that Witch of the Waste.
Wait 'til I get my hands on her!
Let me finish eating this.
Bugs, you'd better scurry away
or I'll sweep you out.
Every last one of you, mocking me.
There's a spell I need.
Later.
A witch rages within.
Sophie.
Sophie, I'm going out.
I'll die without some fresh wood.
What, what are you doing?
I'll fall, I'll fall I'm in peril.
I'm sweeping the ashes.
Won't be a minute.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
I'm in danger.
I'm in danger...
I'll go out.
Oh, no I'm slipping...
Hurry, Sophie.
Try not to torment my friend.
Master Howl, are you going out?
Markl, tell our cleaning lady
not to get too carried away.
What did you do, Sophie?
She abused me.
If I die, Howl goes with me.
I'm the cleaning lady.
It's my job to clean.
No, not the 2nd floor!
If I were you, I'd put your
precious things away in a hurry.
Save my room for later.
My little outburst gave me back
my strength.
What a strange house.
Amazing!
Calcifer, Calcifer!
Are you moving the castle?
What a lot of fuss! Of course I am.
You're incredible, Calcifer.
Your magic's first class.
I misjudged you completely.
You think so?
You really think so!
Oh, no, not yet!
How beautiful.
It's called Star Lake.
Something's stuck in there.
Oh, dear. Lend me a hand, Markl.
Sure.
And up!
A scarecrow.
He's called Turnip, the Turnip-head.
You sure like being upside down.
The odd creature seems to have
taken a liking to me.
He followed me here.
Are you sure you're not a witch, Sophie?
That's right, I'm the cleanest witch
in the land.
Turnip, don't pull it so tight.
Seems like he likes doing the laundry.
It'll dry in no time.
Turnip must belong to the demons.
Calcifer doesn't seem to mind him.
You're right,
maybe he's a demon.
But he led me to this wonderful place.
I've put away all the laundry, Sophie.
Why, thank you.
We'd better be getting back.
How mysterious.
I've never felt such peace.
Stinks.
You reek of burnt flesh and steel.
Keep flying and one day
you won't be able to change yourself back.
Isn't it great! Sophie did this for me.
The fighting is fierce.
The country's ablaze, from the south coast
to the northern border.
I hate the fire and gunpowder.
They have no manners.
My own kind attacked me.
The Witch of the Waste?
Hack wizards masquerading as monsters.
They'll cry plenty later on,
when they can't regain human form.
No, they'll just forget
they ever knew how to cry.
Aren't you supposed to report
to the king yourself?
Yes, well...
Hot water for my bath.
Oh, no, not again.
Is that Howl?
Yeah, wasting my hot water again.
I'm sure Howl won't eat any breakfast.
No matter.
Morning.
It's lovely shopping in the morning.
I've never seen the ocean.
Such beautiful, sparkling water.
Same as it always is.
I myself hate potatoes.
Pay up.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Fish, all fresh off the boat.
That one looks tasty.
I myself hate fish.
The fleet's come home.
Is that smoke?
There's been another battle.
Really? Sorry, lady. Later.
That ship's on fire!
Sophie, let's go get a closer look.
No, I've no stomach for such things.
Let's go home.
Our most advanced battleship,
reduced to this.
Markl, there are Blob Men nearby.
Don't move.
They work for the Witch of the Waste.
They're gone.
Don't people notice
those terrible monsters?
Look! Up there!
That's what dropped those bombs!
An enemy airship, Sophie.
Sophie, flyers.
Ignore the flyers.
They're enemy propaganda!
Are you okay, Sophie?
A glass of water, please.
Sure.
Sophie, what did you do
to the bathroom shelves? Look!
My hair's turned this weird color!
What... what beautiful hair.
Take a good look!
You mixed up everything
on the shelves and ruined the spells.
I didn't mix up anything,
I simply cleaned up.
Cleaning, always cleaning.
I told you not to get too carried away.
It's hopeless.
How humiliating.
It's not that bad.
This new shade's quite lovely.
I'm done for. What's the point
in living, if you aren't beautiful...
Stop, Howl! Cut it out!
He's calling on the spirits of Darkness.
He did this last time a girl dumped him.
Please, Howl, that's enough.
You can just dye your hair again.
I've had enough of you, Howl!
I've never once been beautiful!
I've had enough of this place!
Thank you, Turnip.
You're a kind scarecrow.
Please come back, Sophie.
Howl's in trouble!
Cut it out, Howl I'm going out.
Sophie!
Get over here.
My, he's dramatic.
Is he dead?
Don't worry.
A tantrum never killed anyone.
Help me, Markl.
Get that hot water running, Markl.
C'mon, you can still walk.
You look after him now, Markl.
Sure.
I'll have to clean up all over again.
I'm coming in.
Here's some hot milk. Drink up.
I'll leave it here.
Drink it while it's hot.
Don't leave me, Sophie.
Try a little milk?
The Witch of the Waste
is trying to find my castle.
You're right, I saw her henchmen
down at the port.
The truth is, I'm a coward.
All this junk is just sorcery
to keep her away.
I'm scared to death.
Tell me, why is
the Witch of the Waste after you?
She seemed quite interesting,
so I approached her.
But she terrified me and I ran away.
Now the king's ordered me
to report to him.
As Jenkins and as Pendragon...
How many names do you use, Howl?
Enough to guarantee my freedom.
Can't you refuse the king's invitation?
See that...
The oath I took at the Sorcery Academy.
Say, Howl... Why not visit the king?
What!
Just say it to his face.
"Stop this foolish war.
I refuse to help you."
Sophie, you don't know what they're like.
But he's the king, right? A king thinks
only of what's best for his people.
I know!
You'll go in my place, Sophie!
Pretend you're Pendragon's mother.
Just tell him your son
is an idle good-for-nothing.
Maybe Madam Suliman
will even give up on me.
Madam Suliman?
You're wearing that hat?
After all the magic I spent
making your dress pretty...
Off I go.
Sure.
See you later!
This charm assures your safe return.
Don't worry, I'll follow you in disguise.
There. Off you go!
I'm sure this will never work.
I don't suppose he's following me,
disguised as a crow.
I'm sure Howl would pick
a more dramatic disguise.
Not that...
The Palace is so far away.
Howl? Don't tell me you're Howl.
Disguising yourself as an old dog,
of all things.
Do you know how exhausting
it is to be old?
How nice to see you.
The little hatter, right?
The Witch of the Waste!
Thank you so much
for delivering my note to Howl.
How's Howl doing?
Quite terrified.
Thanks to him,
I've become a cleaning lady.
My, how delightful.
By the way, what brings you
to see the king?
Job hunting. I'm sick of working for Howl.
And yourself?
The king invited me.
It seems that idiot, Suliman,
finally needs my power.
Why don't you break the spell
you put on me?
That's impossible.
My gifts lie in casting spells,
not breaking them.
See you later, then.
Hey, wait a minute. Just wait!
If you weren't here,
I'd have hit her with my cane.
What's wrong with you?
Madam, vehicles are prohibited
beyond this point.
Please continue on foot.
That Suliman.
Using magic to force me
to climb these stairs.
We'll catch up. Pay her no mind.
Heavy, why are you so heavy?
You... Hey... Wait.
What is it?
Suddenly remembered...
how to break my spell?
I told you...
I don't know how.
Then, start studying up.
I don't get it.
Where does she get all that energy?
I have to put you down.
Why don't you call it a day?
You can't make it.
It's been 50 years now,
since they drove me out of here...
I've been longing for this day...
Ever since.
Good luck to you, then.
Still, I'm not nice enough
to help you out.
Come, Howl.
You heartless wench.
Next time I'll turn you feeble, too.
Hurry up!
Madam, follow me.
First, you should help her.
We are forbidden to assist anyone.
But the king himself invited her.
Hang in there!
Just a little farther.
And you call yourself a witch?
Who asked you?
You suddenly look older.
Madam Pendragon
and the Witch of the Waste!
Pull yourself together.
Isn't this what you've been waiting for?
Madam Pendragon
and the Witch of the Waste!
Pendragon... That name sounds familiar.
Of course it does.
That was the name of my hat shop.
It was?
Please wait here.
A chair!
It's mine!
Howl, get back here.
Madam, this way please.
I understand you're Howl's mother.
Yes. My name is Pendragon.
I'm sure you're weary. Please have a seat.
Yes.
I am Madam Suliman, His Majesty's witch.
Um, that dog is...
Ah, you mean Heen?
He does my errands.
I asked him to escort you.
Howl won't join us, then?
You see, he sends his mother
to make excuses.
I'm sure he'd be utterly useless
to His Majesty.
What a shame.
He was my last apprentice...
A student of such marvelous gifts.
I rejoiced in finally finding
a worthy heir.
But then, a demon stole his heart,
and he abandoned me.
He turned his magic
to purely selfish uses.
Mrs. Pendragon.
That boy is dangerous.
His power is too great
for one with no heart.
If he follows that path he'll wind up
like the Witch of the Waste.
Bring her.
What happened?
I just restored her to her real age.
All her powers are gone.
Once upon a time,
she was a magnificent witch.
She made a bargain with a demon
who consumed her,
body and soul, long, long ago.
Our kingdom can no longer afford
to turn a blind eye
to disreputable wizards and witches.
If Howl comes here to serve the kingdom,
I will teach him how to break free
from the demon.
If not, I'll strip him of his powers
as I have taken hers.
Now just a minute.
Now I understand why Howl
refused to come here.
Something's not right.
Forcing your aged guests to climb
stairs, dragging them into strange rooms.
It's like a trap.
You call Howl heartless!
Yes, he's selfish, cowardly
and unpredictable.
But he's straight as an arrow.
He only wants to be free.
Howl won't turn into an evil monster.
He'll battle the demon on his own.
I believe in him.
Mrs. Pendragon...
You're in love with Howl.
Howl... Howl's coming?
I want Howl's heart, I want it.
That's enough from you. Howl's not coming.
Howl will most certainly come.
Now, I've found his weakness.
Your Majesty.
As you are.
How are you feeling?
Thank you for asking.
Meetings bore me.
I flew out for a breather.
How lovely.
These are?
This is Wizard Howl's mother.
I see.
I appreciate it, but I don't intend
to win any war with magic.
It's true that Suliman's powers
shield our palace from bombs.
But they just fall on neighboring towns.
That's how magic works. Right, Suliman?
Such eloquence today, Your Majesty.
Suliman!
This is the final battle.
This time, we'll beat them to a pulp.
Suliman, you've outdone yourself
with that double. Await good news.
Thank you kindly.
Have my generals assembled?
It's been awhile, Howl.
Delighted to see you doing so well.
I saw right through you.
I've kept my oath.
I've no wish to fight you.
I'll take my mother.
I won't let you go.
Don't look down, you'll be dragged down.
It's time I showed your mother
what you really are.
Howl, don't! It's a trap.
Hold tight.
Sophie, sit up front.
Oh, no, Sophie,
you brought the whole gang along.
Nice doggie.
You're just Suliman's spy.
Oh, well, too late to toss you now.
Sophie, you steer.
What! I can't possibly do this!
They're after us.
I'll tackle them. Fly straight
to the castle in the Wastes.
What! That's impossible!
Don't worry, the ring will guide you.
Summon Calcifer with your heart.
Summon Calcifer?
It's glowing.
Follow the light.
You'll be there by nightfall.
Why send me to Suliman
if you were coming yourself?
Your presence gave me the courage for it.
She's too terrifying to face on my own.
You've saved me.
I was in grave danger back there.
Don't let go!
-You're good.
-Stop joking!
We've got a lead now.
I can give you five minutes
of invisibility. Now's your chance.
Howl!
No, thank you.
Thank you. That's the most fun
I've had in ages.
I supposed Howl thinks he's escaped...
His mother's awfully young.
We're not far. That's my hometown.
Don't try to be cute. I don't trust you.
The castle. They've come to meet us.
Sophie!
Markl, help!
I don't know how to stop this thing!
Sophie!
Doggie.
Markl.
I'm home.
Sophie, are you hurt?
You're home!
Thank you for coming to meet us.
Oh, no, you've gone too far.
I wonder if Howl's back.
Howl?
Howl? Is that you?
Are you hurt? In pain?
Stay away.
I want to help you.
I want to break the spell you're under.
You can't even break your own spell.
But I love you!
Too late.
Howl!
Howl must be back.
Sophie, you'd better figure out
how to break my spell quick.
We're both running out of time.
Meaning Howl will turn into
a monster? Is it true?
I can't tell you that. I'm a demon.
Calcifer, Suliman told me,
Howl has given you something
very precious.
What is it? Where is it?
That's confidential information.
And if I threaten to dump water over you?
How dare you! Howl will die with me.
Good morning, Turnip.
We've got to be brave.
Ready, Sophie!
Okay! Open wider, Calcifer.
Here goes! Push!
Heave!
I... said... move!
Come on!
They call it a castle,
but once you get inside, it's a junk heap.
It's time to eat!
Here, old girl.
But, Sophie she's the Witch of the Waste.
No need to worry.
Why's she staring at me?
Such a pretty fire.
Howl.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome home.
Master Howl, can we keep this dog?
An old Witch and Madam Suliman's dog.
Why'd you let them in, Calcifer?
Don't look at me!
They flew in with Sophie.
Sophie, always dramatic...
So you're Turnip.
You're under quite a spell, too.
Seems everyone in our little family
has problems...
He's so handsome.
This is a busy day. We're moving.
Moving?
Good. There aren't any shops here.
We're in the middle of nowhere.
Madam Suliman
can track us down in no time.
But you'll have to stay behind.
The magic in your spell's too risky.
All right, that's done.
Move it, Calcifer.
Excellent.
Stay right where you are.
Be gentle...
Here goes.
We've moved. You can get up now.
Amazing, Master. It's huge.
What a pretty fire.
This is--
I added a bathroom.
For our growing family.
Sophie, come here! Sophie!
I added a bedroom, too. Get in.
This is... Why?
I thought it would suit you.
Do you like it?
Yes, it's perfect for a housekeeper.
I got you some new clothes, too.
Open them later. Next.
Sophie! Come here! Quick!
A courtyard!
There's a shop, too.
Let's go, Heen!
See that new color on the dial?
There's a new exit.
My gift to you, Sophie. Step outside.
It's my secret garden.
Beautiful.
Did you make it with your magic?
Only a little, to help the flowers.
Thank you, Howl!
It's like I'm dreaming.
Sophie.
How mysterious.
I feel I've been here before.
I could cry with happiness.
Come.
Look.
A sweet little house.
My favorite hideaway.
When I was little I spent
my summers there alone.
Alone?
My uncle, a wizard,
left me this place as my private study.
Make yourself at home there, Sophie.
What's wrong?
I'm scared.
I'm afraid you'll go off and disappear
somewhere, once I'm inside.
Howl, tell me the truth.
I don't mind if you're a monster.
I want to make sure
that you can all live comfortably.
Why not open a flower shop,
with all these flowers?
You'd be good at it, Sophie.
And then, you'd go away?
I want to help you, Howl.
I'm not beautiful
and I'm only good at cleaning...
Sophie, you are beautiful.
The good thing about being old
is that you've got so little to lose...
Why is that thing flying out here?
A battleship?
On its way to burn cities and people.
The enemy's? Ours?
What difference does it make?
Murderers.
Look at all those bombs.
It stopped.
Did you do that?
I'm just tinkering with it.
It won't crash.
Howl!
Oops, looks like they're onto us.
Madam Suliman's henchmen. Let's go back.
Run! Move those legs.
Hurry on in!
No! Don't let go!
What happened, Sophie?
I've had it with this place!
Good night, Sophie.
Good night.
Don't worry about Master Howl, Sophie.
Sometimes, he's gone for days on end.
Thank you, Markl.
Need the toilet?
I'm fine.
Good night.
You're in love.
Sighing away like that.
I thought so.
Were you ever in love?
Of course I was. I'm still in love.
What?
Men, why ever should we want them...
But a young man's heart is so delicious!
Unbelievable.
And so adorable, too.
What is that?
Air raid siren.
Air raid?
It's not for here.
But best not go out tonight.
Suliman's creatures are searching
high and low for our house.
What a good fire, hiding us so well.
Sophie, a stranger got in!
Mother.
Sophie!
Where have you been!
I searched for you everywhere!
But, oh, look how you've aged!
It's all my fault.
I'm so sorry, Sophie!
Mother...
I barely recognize the house.
Who is that?
Oh, your landlady.
Sophie, I've got a new husband!
He's such a wonderful man.
And he's rich, too!
We can all live together again.
You'll never have to clean again.
But I'm happy here...
Really?
Oops, I forgot.
My car's waiting. I've got to run.
I'm so glad I found you again.
We'll really catch up next time.
In the meantime, you take care.
A peeping-bug, eh?
The oldest trick in the book, Suliman.
All yours, Cal.
May you find happiness, Mother.
Thank you. You too, Sophie.
I've done what I was told.
Take me back to my husband.
Yes, I'm sure Madam Suliman
will be pleased.
Forgive me, Sophie...
Look at all these people.
They're all running away.
The town will be empty.
Do you wish to run, too?
That's what that lady spoke of...
So, she did. I'm glad we made up.
Don't go, Sophie!
I love you, Sophie. Please stay.
I love you, too, Markl.
Don't worry, I'll stay.
Really!
Are we a family?
Yes, we're family.
Oh, good!
I'll never let Suliman get hold of Howl.
But the paper says we won.
Only fools swallow such lies.
How strange. I can't get Calcifer going.
Grandma, will you stop that?
Such an awful stink.
Why deny an old lady her pleasures.
Open the window, Markl.
I wouldn't open that now...
In Calcifer's present state,
he can't possibly keep them out.
Markl!
Close it quick!
Look after Grandma, Markl.
I'll check on the shop.
How dare you, now? If you have
energy to spare, put out the fires.
Howl!
Dramatic as usual...
I'm sorry.
I had too many enemies, tonight.
Howl, oh, Howl.
Master Howl! Sophie!
Calcifer, be strong.
Madam, was that a gift from Suliman?
That granny fed me something nasty.
Why, if it isn't Howl.
I feel we need a nice long chat.
Likewise, Madam.
But we have no time right now.
How unlike you. You're not running away.
Until later, then.
Stay here, Sophie.
Calcifer will protect you.
I'll see to things outside.
Wait, Howl!
Don't go! Please stay.
Another round of bombs is coming.
Even Calcifer can't stop those.
Let's run away. Don't fight.
I'm through running away.
I've finally found someone
I want to protect...
You.
Howl!
That's our town.
There's Howl.
Howl!
Sophie! Turnip...
Markl, come inside!
Move? You're nuts. There's nothing there.
No, as long as we stay here,
Howl will keep fighting.
He's better off a coward.
Grandma, get up.
Going for a stroll?
Suliman will find us right away.
She already has. At this rate,
Howl will never make it back alive.
Sophie!
The castle's falling apart.
That's all right Markl, take Grandma.
Sure.
You, too, hop on.
I can't! My contract says
I can't leave the fireplace.
If you two can't solve this,
I'll do it for you.
Watch it!
Cut it out! Cut it out!
If I leave, the house will collapse.
Fine!
We're out.
I'd better go last.
Even I don't know what'll happen...
I told you it would collapse.
Rain!
Is that heading for town?
Look after Grandma, Markl.
Turnip, find us a way in.
Don't worry, Grandma.
I'll take care of you.
Markl, we can get in here.
The roof's leaking. I'll go out.
Wait here.
It's wet, here...
Hurry.
Too damp.
Bring Grandma here, Markl.
The castle's empty.
I told you, if we'd stayed put,
Howl and I could've handled it.
Calcifer, please. You're my last hope.
I want to go to Howl. Move the castle.
I know you can do it. You're so strong.
But there's no chimney here...
And the wood's damp...
As the saying goes,
"The best blaze brightest in adversity".
I've heard that, but...
You really think so?
You're so pretty, Cal.
Sit here, Grandma.
Then, give me something of yours, Sophie.
Of mine?
I can't do it alone. How about your eyes?
My eyes?
This?
Amazing, Calcifer! You are the best!
Imagine what I could do
with your eyes and your heart.
Heart! You have a heart?
Oh, my!
There's Howl. He's trapped.
Hurry, Calcifer!
Don't!
Grandma!
Stop it!
Howl's heart.
Cut it out!
Grandma!
It's hot, hot!
Let go!
You'll die, Grandma.
No, it's mine!
Sophie!
She's so mean. That's mine.
Oh, no, Heen, look what I've done.
I poured water on Calcifer.
What if I've killed Howl, too...
It's moving... Is Howl alive?
Show me where he is.
The castle door...
Heen...
Howl...
This must be Howl's childhood...
Howl! Calcifer!
It's Sophie! Wait for me!
I promise I'll come back for you.
Wait for me in the future!
I'll walk there Heen. I'll walk.
I can't stop crying.
Howl.
I'm sorry I took so long.
You've been waiting all this time.
Take me to Calcifer.
Is he dead?
No, he's fine.
Grandma...
Don't look at me. I don't have anything.
Please.
Grandma.
You want it that badly?
Yes.
Oh, well, in that case...
You'd better take good care of it.
There.
Thank you, Grandma.
Calcifer.
Sophie... I'm all worn out.
If I give Howl's heart back,
will it kill you?
Probably not, if you do it, Sophie.
After all, we both survived
the water you dumped on me.
I'd better try, then.
It's all warm and fluttery
like a little bird.
It's still only a child's heart.
May Calcifer live a thousand years,
and may Howl recover his heart...
I'm alive!
I'm free!
He moved, he's alive!
You broke Calcifer's spell!
Turnip!
Turnip, are you okay?
I'll get you a new stick, right away.
Thank you, Turnip.
Thank you, Sophie.
I'm a prince from the next kingdom.
A cruel spell turned me into a scarecrow.
A spell that only a kiss
from your true love could break.
Exactly. And if Sophie hadn't saved me,
I would have died.
My, you're good-looking.
What a racket. What's the fuss?
I feel terrible.
Like I'm trapped under a rock.
Oh, yes, a heart's a heavy burden.
Oh, Sophie,
your hair is just like starlight.
It's so beautiful.
I love you, Howl! How wonderful.
Looks like your true love
is in love with someone else.
You'd best go home
and make them stop this war.
That's exactly what I shall do.
When the war is over, I shall return.
"A fickle heart is the only constant
in this world".
My, you have a way with words.
I'll wait for your return, then.
Why should you contact me now?
What on earth have you been up to?
A happy ending, I see.
You two-timer.
Well, there it is.
Bring the Prime Minister
and the Minister of Defense.
Let's put an end to this foolish war.
It's Calcifer!
You didn't have to come back.
I really missed you all.
Besides, it looks like rain...
Thank you, Calcifer.
THE END
Subtitle translation by
Linda HOAGLUND and Judith ALEY