I’m leaving now.
It was very fun flying with you.
Ms. Pleng.
Stop making me blush.
It's with me already.
You have good taste.
-I'll have one original mocha ice blended.
-Sure.
Gosh!
I’m sorry.
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
What are you looking at?
Do I look like your husband?
Are you Gym? Kaya’s boyfriend?
Kaya asked me to translate
this voice message for you.
It’s in this thumb drive.
I’m going to start, okay?
Are you mixed-race?
Hi, Gym.
I’m sorry about keeping my interview
at the factory a secret.
I love you.
But we hardly have anything in common.
For example,
our interests,
culture,
attitude,
religion,
and way of life.
I think
we won’t make it together.
We can’t really communicate
and understand each other.
Communicate, my ass!
We slept together every night!
I don’t know anything.
I’m just here to translate the file.
I’m going to continue, okay?
I hope you will meet
the right person one day.
You are the right one for me.
I'm done listening.
Okay. That’s fine
if you don’t want to listen anymore.
Wait.
You’re the one
who taught her English, right?
Yes.
This is your fault!
Damn it!
What the hell are you looking at?
Is that a bomb?
Excuse me. What is that?
I think it's chicken soup.
Chicken soup?
Here. Look, winter melon.
Winter melon!
What kind of person are you?
Are you talking to me?
I’m talking about that guy.
What kind of person are you?
Are you talking to me?
I’m talking about that guy.
A person like that shouldn't live long.
Oh. You must be talking about that guy.
I'm talking about you!
SPEAK ENGLISH LIKE A NATIVE
Oh gosh!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Don’t get any closer.
I will poke your eyes.
It’s not worth it.
Do you want to play rough?
I’m going to go for that interview
so I can get Kaya back.
And you have to teach me.
Ask your dad to teach you then.
Aren’t you mixed-race?
Hey!
My dad is French.
He fled back to his country
even before I could walk.
-You can study with some other teacher.
-No, I can’t.
You taught Kaya.
So you have to teach me too.
You saw your cut-out standee, right?
So will you teach me?
Sure.
One on one?
Okay.
Here. The fee.
If you ditch me,
I won’t ask for a refund.
I want something else in return.
Is this even worth it?
It’s four in the morning
and you're still awake?
You should have joined us for dinner.
Because you didn’t go, Aey and Chai
kept clinking glasses with me.
Hey.
They sent their regards to you too.
See?
There are a lot of them.
They wrote things on me
like I was a notebook.
DON'T BE SAD, MICRODICK! -AEY
THE END OF THE LEGENDARY
SEX MACHINE. -CHAI
Isn’t that the erotic chicken?
Wow. So sexy.
So erotic.
Hey.
Don’t be depressed.
You know when you get sad,
you don't look cool anymore.
-Dude, you’re drunk. Go to sleep.
-Hey, you don’t need her.
Kaya.
The Kaya kick.
It all came out...
my congee.
Why are you standing up?
I said understand, not stand up.
I know that.
I am going to get coffee.
Do you want one?
Sure.
Go ahead.
This is harder than trying
to move an elephant.
INTERNATIONAL SONG
The sound snakes make. Hisses.
Give it a try.
Head.
Not head. Pull your tongue back in.
Why are you making that sound?
It's like when you shoo away a dog.
Shoo shoo.
Yes, like that.
Combine them together.
Head shoo shoo.
Fail!
Do I have to exaggerate that much?
Z.
Excuse me?
X, Y and...
Z.
See!
Even sixth graders know this word.
That.
No.
Are you blind?
So what is it then?
Those are mangoes.
Mangoes?
What mangoes?
Ripe juicy mangoes.
Why are you walking up?
It’s already 10 p.m.
I had to teach you until late.
The building and the elevators are closed.
Do you need a ride to your car?
No.
My boyfriend gave me this.
You have a boyfriend?
Have the cap open and ready
so when you get jumped
you can use it right away.
I know you are talking shit about me.
I don’t understand though.
Do I just pick one?
Go ahead.
Everybody has to take a turn.
What do you want me to say about moles?
Anything you want.
Anything I want?
Ready?
Wow, that was fast.
Pleng, a student asked
for your number today.
Who?
Mr. Pruek, the student in your
conversation for business class.
And did you give it to him?
I did.
And why did you do that? That’s not right.
Try to keep a straight face then.
You're smiling from ear to ear.
This is me smiling from ear to ear.
My goodness. Life is good.
Bitch.
What is Mama?
Pork Mama, Tomyum Mama,
duck-flavored Mama. Never had any before?
But foreigners don’t know what Mama is.
They will think you want to
literally eat your mom.
Why do you keep smiling?
Have you lost your mind?
Or you can also say midnight.
If you use the word "mid"
in front of any word, it means half.
For example, midterm means
middle of your school term.
Then why if you get stabbed midway
between the ribs it goes all the way in?
Whatever.
You should say...
Or if you want to ask someone
a question back, you say...
What if I don’t care to know?
You will just look like someone
who has no manners.
Wow, she’s hot.
Damn it! Why did you use the flash!
Hey!
Her panties is showing.
Hey! What?
Where are you going?
Come here.
What are you doing to him?
He took a picture of your thing.
No, I didn’t.
-Really?
-No, I didn’t.
You like to look at underwear, right?
Hey. What are you doing?
-You like to look, right?
-I didn’t do anything.
-You didn’t do anything?
-I didn’t.
-Sure?
-Sure.
Give your phone to her.
Now!
That hurts.
It’s locked.
Password.
Eight, six, and double fours.
Hold on. Did you send it
to any of your friends?
No, I didn’t send anything.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Did you delete everything?
Are you sure?
Why are you only keeping quiet?
Did you say sorry to her?
I’m sorry.
Next time, if you want to have a peek,
go look at your mom’s.
Don’t let me see you
do anything like this again. Understand?
Hey! My phone!
Come on, man. Let me go! My phone!
Actually, it's pronounced as password.
Hey!
Shit! It’s shit!
Damn, he’s so scared he shit his pants.
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Get me some tissue.
There isn’t any.
Over there.
This is called a napkin not tissue.
Seriously!
What a punk-ass kid.
I wiped it off already.
Why does it still stink?
It must be some radioactive shit.
Damn it!
Are there any stains?
A little.
What the hell did you eat?
What's up with you?
What are you reading?
A Happy Door Plin.
A Happy what?
A Happy Doll Plin.
That says A Happy Dolphin.
Just put it down.
If you’re going to read this book,
it's better to read something else.
Cinderella has a lot of
easy words for kids.
That’s for sissies.
Let a daddy’s girl read it.
No way. I like this one.
A Happy Door Plin.
Talk to him.
You talk to him.
Tell him to go away.
You tell him to go away yourself.
Go away.
What? I don’t understand.
How is he supposed to understand you?
You just go far.
Oh, another one.
No. What?
I don’t know what it says.
I don’t want to.
Say hi to your dad.
Foreigners are not scary at all.
Just speak up.
Don’t worry about your grammar.
What are you doing?
Take it home to re-boil with noodles.
Are you done with that?
May I?
Who taught you this?
Kaya. Kaya taught me.
-You can understand each other?
-Sure, we can.
See. This is eat.
When it’s time to sleep, we do this.
And when you can’t sleep?
We do this.
And if the toilet is clogged?
A clogged toilet?
Stop messing with me.
And how did you ask her
to be your girlfriend?
We rode a motorcycle
and took her to the beach.
We were a couple the moment we woke up.
Oh. Then you can stop now.
Stop right here. Stop.
This is my car.
-This one?
-Yes.
IT'S ME, PRUEK.
Do you plan to sleep here?
Who is it?
None of your business.
I'm asking so you can teach me.
I’m not interested
in your personal affairs.
You don’t have a boyfriend.
I do.
If you really have a boyfriend,
he would have had his friends
beat me up since the first day.
Well he isn’t my boyfriend yet,
but he will be soon.
He is waiting for a romantic moment
to ask me.
I didn’t ask. So why are you telling me?
Later.
DO YOU WANT TO GO OUT OF TOWN TOGETHER?
So slutty.
SHALL WE GO ON A DATE?
Too flirty.
No!
My phone dropped and hit my chin.
It accidentally hit send.
So it accidentally typed
that sentence too?
Yes.
Then I will book a table.
What?
It’s late. I won’t bother you anymore.
Get some rest, Ms. Pleng.
Wow. He’s even got his own sticker.
Talk about a premium package.
Hey.
How the hell did she get a key?
I made a copy for my girl.
Someone sent you a bomb.
There is no sender’s name.
I will go wash this for you.
Don't you know how to wash it yourself?
Do you have no hands or feet?
You're always using my boyfriend.
I didn’t even say a word.
Gosh, are you his slave?
You’re lucky she sent it back.
Actually, throwing it away
would have been easier.
She probably sent it for you to resize it.
Being abroad she must have gained weight
eating all that milk and cheese.
Your friend isn’t a stupid cow
even though he looks like one.
Gosh, you didn’t even blink!
I didn’t even flinch.
I will get some pepper and
sprinkle it into your eyes.
I dare you.
You’re so going to get it.
Bring it on!
You picked the wrong path to cross.
Keep going.
Further.
What should I do now?
Whatever you want.
Don’t! Let it go babe.
This time I must.
Your wish is my command.
All that left is water.
I got to go wash my ass.
I got this...
for you!
You can wind it too.
I got it custom made
in Chinatown, you know?
They said Japanese people love it.
No. I asked Joke to buy
some grilled chicken. That’s all.
But...
Goodness.
Do you like it?
Can you send this back to Kaya?
She sent it to you?
You want me to send it back?
Yes.
Do you want anything?
No, thank you.
Thank you.
I want you to give her a message.
Can you both talk it out yourselves?
Facebook, FaceTime, Line, whatever.
I can’t contact her. She blocked me.
I don’t want to.
Why not?
You’re going to send the ring back anyway.
Come on. Just a little help.
I’m not doing this.
That’s one thick forest!
I won't break up with her.
She sent your ring back.
I think it’s game over.
Why are you so stubborn?
I HAVE BEEN AN ASSHOLE TO ALL MY EXES.
I REALLY WANT TO BE GOOD TO YOU.
Talk about being naughty. Really naughty.
I have a secret in my heart
It’s a secret hiding inside
-LOVE SONG
-but I don’t know how to tell you.
I have a secret in my heart
It’s a secret hiding inside
But I don’t know how to tell you
I love you.
You can’t contact her at all?
No.
What time did you Skype her?
Many hours ago. Many times.
Take out your notebook and jot this down.
-I have to take notes?
-Yes.
There are three tenses we use most often,
Present, Past and Future
Present Simple combined
with a subject and a main verb
becomes S+V1.
Present Simple,
you use when the action is happening.
No more!
Can we study conversation like before?
If you don’t want to study
or don’t take notes,
I can’t teach you anymore.
Why are you treating me like this?
Your test is in July. You’ve only got
two months. You won’t make it.
You are...
too dumb.
Am I that dumb?
Yes.
Just take your money back.
Yes, Mr. Pruek?
Where are you?
I’m on my way to work.
I want to invite you
to my mother’s birthday party.
Your mom’s birthday?
Yes.
When is it?
This Saturday.
Are you free?
I’m free.
Is that a hairdo or a banana bicycle seat?
You’ve got something on your lip.
Is there something there?
This is my grandfather’s car.
There are only three of them
in all of Thailand.
Do you want to try sitting in it?
Then I will get the key.
I’m back.
I think I should go now.
I am getting sleepy.
Is this Pleng’s?
Please stop the car.
You forgot your phone.
Thank you.
I’m sorry for making you run.
You are sweating all over.
If I didn’t run to give this back to you,
then who will I talk to tonight?
EVEN THOUGH YOU AREN'T A SINGER,
BUT CAN I ASK TO BE YOUR DEVOTED FAN?
SHALL WE CELEBRATE OUR ONE-DAY
ANNIVERSARY TOMORROW NIGHT?
It's just me.
Why does he seem so sad lately?
Hey. Don’t say that word.
Don’t use any Japanese words.
He'll be hurt when he thinks of Kaya.
We’re all going to be in trouble.
Joke, that sounds sensible.
But this means we need to say hi
to him more often.
No! Hi sounds just like Hai in Japanese.
If you want to say hi
then just say hey instead.
That makes a lot sense!
I have always looked up to you.
Hey.
I saw you working hard so I thought
I’d come over with this glass of water...
to say hi.
I’m sorry.
I’m just worried about you.
I didn’t mean to say hi.
What is your problem?
I’m dead.
My neck feels weird.
Dude, can you take a look for me?
It’s just a scratch.
Attention Mechanic Weerayut Kerdkaewngam.
Your teacher is waiting
in front of the statue.
Nice handwriting.
You missed.
Do you think this is funny?
Can I be your tutor again?
Do you want to get punched?
If you punch me, I will slap you back.
I really want to help.
Didn’t you say I was too dumb
and two months wasn’t enough?
That’s true.
If you want to speak fluently,
then there’s no time.
But if you just want to pass your test
there is another trick that tutors use.
What’s that?
Memorize the possible questions
and answers.
Translate.
Let’s go for it.
-Check.
-Hey!
What do you mean check? It’s my turn.
Then I'll check out what's over there.
I will kick your ass.
MAINTENANCE DEPARTMENT
Everyone. This is Ms. Pleng, my tutor.
The tutor said
I’m a cook and I use gas
to heat your fries.
American cheese is so extravagant.
Okay, let’s eat.
She wants some milk.
You sure learn fast.
How are we supposed to know
what the interviewers are going to ask?
I don’t know either. Help me think.
Come up with as much as you can.
Okay!
Why do you want to work in America?
I want to get my wife back.
Is that a problem?
Hey. If you answer like that
nobody will pass you.
You have to say
I want to gain new experiences
and come back to improve
our Thailand branch.
If the hydraulic pump is making sounds...
Stop that. Eed is my mom’s name.
So if the pump starts making
sounds like Kahlua's mom's name,
that means the problem is in
the forward pump. It is too narrow.
If this isn’t because the oil is dry
then the pump is starting to fail.
Why is your nickname Kahlua?
He made me drink milk spiked with alcohol.
What the heck?
Hey, tell me.
What is the optimum temperature
for our factory’s boiler?
What temperature?
Well, is your name Curl
because you like to curl your mustache?
He likes to curl his hair...
Down there.
When a machine breaks down,
do you replace it or repair it?
I’m a maintenance engineer,
not a repairman.
Replacing would be the last choice.
You’re through. I choose you.
Who would turn down
such a good employee like you?
There you go, kissing ass again.
He wants you to ask him questions
not kiss his ass.
Whoa!
Are those hips for real?
Hey, show me what you’ve got.
If the party isn’t big enough,
I don’t dance.
How about we let Ms. Pleng
come up with a game.
Everyone must say one letter
of the English alphabet A to Z.
You can’t go in order.
So little, only three alphabets?
A to Zed.
We’re all confused with your accent, see?
But hold on, whoever loses
must light a firecracker in the ass.
Women are no exception.
Let’s begin.
Are you withdrawing cash?
Are you going for some K-pop dance?
Come on now.
One, two...
Hey! K is mine.
I just said, "D".
It’s your turn.
-What?
-What alphabet?
-What is it?
One, two...
Hold on.
That’s taken.
Come on.
That was the first one.
I present to you, a butt crack.
Hey, that’s too deep.
Too deep?
Feels like a splinter.
I’m okay.
Are you ready, Kahlua?
Day, month, year.
Is it a dud?
Man. Let it go.
I did.
Not your hands, dummy. Relax your ass.
Shit.
Dude. It freaking smells like BBQ.
God, I probably won’t be able to shit now.
It burns all the way up into my asshole.
Are you okay? Are you going to make it?
My stomach hurts.
Are you going to die?
What do you mean by nozzle nipples?
You, pervert. I will break your shoulders.
Wow.
It’s not in here.
You were able to fix it still?
When I first saw it,
I thought it was unrepairable.
I'm a maintenance engineer
so whatever breaks, I can always fix.
You better keep your fingers crossed.
Some things are not as easy as you think.
If you are referring to Kaya
I never thought it would be easy.
If she couldn’t speak Thai
then I would learn English.
If English was too hard to learn
then I would learn Japanese.
-That went in my eyes.
-Are you okay?
My contacts fell out.
Hey. This way. I’m here.
I’m here.
You are extremely nearsighted?
Yes.
Do I look like a blind person?
Translate.
I think so means I agree.
Wait. Stop.
Let’s go.
Hey, slow down.
If we go any slower we won’t make it.
Hey, Pleng!
Gosh.
Hey!
You said you wouldn’t laugh.
I couldn’t help it.
Shit!
If Joke sees me now,
he will lose all respect.
Why are you doing that?
WHAT ARE YOUR STRENGTHS?
WHY SHOULD WE CHOOSE YOU?
AS A MAINTENANCE ENGINEER, I BELIEVE...
I'm a maintenance engineer
so whatever breaks, I can always fix.
EVERYTHING CAN BE FIXED
AND MADE TO WORK AGAIN.
If English was too hard to learn
then I would learn Japanese.
AND NO MATTER HOW HARD IT IS TO FIX
I WILL ALWAYS FIND A WAY.
YOU WILL REGRET IT IF YOU DON'T CHOOSE ME.
Before I came to study with you,
we ran into each other before.
Really?
Do you remember
the Ministry of Foreign Affairs party?
You were an interpreter.
I remember.
That’s when.
After that I asked my friend
to find out where you work.
and then I enrolled in your class.
So you had no intention
of actually studying?
That's right.
I didn't intend to study.
I just wanted to sweep you off your feet.
Are you okay?
Here. Let me help.
It’s okay.
I dreamed of doing this for a long time.
How romantic of you.
Close your eyes.
Close them.
Close my eyes?
COUNTRY SONG
A love this beautiful
All my life
I’ve been looking endlessly for
I want you to be by my side like this
Tell me you love me again
Let’s stay close together always
Pleng, are you happy?
Very happy.
So are you a fan of country music?
I would rather be
your devoted fan for life.
How lucky of me.
I didn’t know you were this funny.
I’m not trying to be funny.
He's for real.
Mr. Pruek, if you plan to go
to sail your yacht around this time
don’t forget to check the weather.
The weather forecast.
The weather forecast, for sure.
If you want to go to
-Maan-nok Island.
-Maan-nok Island?
-Maan-nai Island?
-Maan-nai Island.
Or Samed island.
Samed island, where everybody relaxes.
Yes, let me know.
All right?
Totally.
Pleng, you're just in time.
Come and try this on.
Why can’t it be me? Why?
I think this pair is a bit too small.
Then please try this one.
It’s a perfect fit.
Yes, perfect.
You could have called
and asked me for my size.
But then it wouldn’t be a surprise.
It’s a small price to make you happy.
There is so much more I can do for you.
Okay.
Will it be okay, if I don’t accept this?
Why not?
This pair is just like the one that broke.
Yes, it is.
But Pruek...
Yes?
Can we just go back
to being teacher and student?
Why?
My mom went to see a fortune-teller.
She said...
I shouldn’t date someone
who was born in the same month.
It’s really bad luck.
Remember?
Yes.
Sore feet?
Let me give you a massage.
Just relax. No need to be uptight.
It cracked too.
Didn’t I answer correctly?
Why did you punch me?
I didn’t get a chance to answer.
What’s wrong with you?
I can’t take it anymore!
Come on.
Hold on.
Do you feel better?
Much better.
What’s wrong?
I want to break up with my boyfriend.
Damn. She punches hard
like Manny Pacquiao.
Hey. Where are you going?
There is a crazy guy
who closed down the coffee shop.
Translate.
It means run!
Don’t tell me that he is...
Yes, that’s him!
Is that a bouquet of flowers
or a manhole cover?
You are not done yet.
You got to say one last thing.
You will regret it,
if you don’t choose me.
Isn't this sentence a bit over the top?
I will get kicked instead of picked.
It’s okay. It fits you.
Have some self-confidence.
It’s your selling point.
Let’s continue, okay?
Almost.
but that is number...
235.
I thought the key word is pressure?
Yes, but what I asked you just now
was pressure as in the force
not as in the stress you feel.
Talk about pressure, here he comes now.
Did he see me?
He didn’t even look over here yet.
Just be straight with him.
Breaking his heart would be like
running over a little puppy.
Come on. It won’t kill him.
I thought I would surprise you.
How are you, Pleng? Feeling better?
Ms. Tui said you were not feeling well.
I’m feeling better now.
That’s good. I bought some dinner for us.
Let’s go.
What a mess. My room is such a mess.
That’s good. I can help.
You are not feeling well.
It’s okay. I...
What’s going on?
Is this the guy?
Who are you?
What?
Come on. Let’s go up.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
I'm her husband.
I...
What is going on?
It hasn't been a month
since we started dating.
Come. Let’s go.
How could you say
that you were my husband?
I was trying to help.
I don’t know if I should thank you or not.
And what did you whisper in his ear?
He looked totally shocked.
I told him...
I knocked you up.
What!
You made me seem slutty!
What were you thinking?
Do you even care?
That’s slutty! So slutty!
I’m leaving.
Hey! Where are you going?
Why don’t you use the elevator?
If he is still freaking out down there
then our plan will be exposed.
Bye.
-Hello. What’s up?
-Hello. Where are you?
I’m here already, buying coffee.
Let’s just go. There is no time.
We will make it.
Taking my bike only takes a second.
What are you wearing?
I told you to dress up nice.
I did. Here.
Is this what you are planning to wear?
Yes.
You told me to wear something
I’d wear to a wedding party.
This is what I wear to every party.
Hey! Wait.
Don’t tell me you’ve never
bought a dress shirt.
The paper is still there.
Why didn’t you say something?
When you’re about to get into a fight,
you aren’t afraid.
I’m a player not a fighter.
Whatever you are,
if you don’t start talking,
you will never learn to speak.
No excuses. I got you here already.
Today you have to talk
to at least three foreigners.
Understand?
How could I?
They speak so fast like they are rapping.
Spot the key words.
See you.
Look at that. How lame.
We can speak Thai just fine.
What was up with that apology?
Seriously, he’s a maintenance engineer.
Dumbass!
Yes, I know.
Your mom has nice shoulders.
Are you sure you are excited?
Who are you?
Whose cute kid is that?
Wow. He really only dances at big parties.
I want to thank everyone who honored me
by coming here tonight.
And I want to also thank
our beautiful interpreter, Ms. Pleng.
Thank you.
-Okay. See you next time. Bye.
-See you
Do you want to take off first?
It’s okay. I can wait.
Why don’t you put them on?
It broke. It wasn’t fixed right.
Hold them for me please.
Thanks.
Did you understand what they said?
Or are you just clapping along?
I understood.
Good evening.
Wow.
I can translate the whole song.
Tonight...
Something about two.
Forget means we can’t remember.
Open your eyes means have a look.
That’s correct. Have some confidence.
Your...
dress is beautiful.
Thank you.
It sounded like “Do Do Look Look”.
I don’t know.
No. Listen carefully.
Do you want me to walk you home?
I have a mean dog at home.
Don’t help me on this one.
I think I need help.
I will always be yours. I promise.
Tonight, can I walk you home?
Morning.
Before we go back to reality...
where you go your own way.
Can you tell me
if you feel the same way too?
I fixed it.
Please tell me how you feel
’Cause deep inside I know it’s real
I promise I will forever be yours.
I got to go.
Darling open up to me.
Let me walk you home.
Even if you will never be mine.
I’m in love with you tonight.
Why are you home so late?
You have that test tomorrow.
Are you crazy? My test is next month.
Really?
Because I helped set up the room today.
Shit! June isn’t the seventh month?
Seventh month is correct.
The talking dictionary is wrong for sure.
You’re right.
What the hell!
Everyone on this planet uses one.
I’m just stupid!
Stop being such an ass kisser.
I’m always to blame.
Hello, Pleng.
Calm down.
Okay. You can come over.
I’m sorry.
It’s my fault for being dumb.
You remembered all of this?
Yes.
Nothing else to fix, right?
Pleng.
Go sit on the other side.
I don’t want Kaya to see you
and misunderstand.
What did she say?
She still wants you to go.
That’s all.
I heard she said...
Do you like me?
Do you still want to take your test?
I have my heart set on it.
I have to.
I know.
How can a tutor like me
get involved with a student?
She said she wants the ring back.
Today I will go first.
I admit I'm hurt...
but being straight forward
like this helps.
There is something I want to clear up.
I am not pregnant.
What made you think
that I think you are pregnant?
That day at my condo...
that guy whispered that to you.
He actually said...
Leave you alone.
You are his girl.
He always talks nonsense.
Do you remember my story
about the mole and destiny?
I do.
My mole
will have to set up
a new date with destiny.
Did that take a long time to come up with?
But I think you may
have found your destiny.
HEARTBREAK SONG
KAYA SAID TO MEMORIZE THE NAME
OF THE JAPANESE FOUNDER
Noda Toichi.
Shit. Is it something to do
with people or machinery?
You are not done yet.
You got to say one last thing.
You will regret it if you don’t choose me.
Wait!
What?
It's for you.
Miss.
Somebody left this for you.
Pleng, the interview result is out.
I didn’t make it.
I really wanted to pass my interview
to make you proud.
What is name of our company’s founder?
Doraemon.
You know I don’t know
how to talk nicely to anyone.
Well...
Just have a listen.
I don’t love her you know.
I just wanted to treat a girl right.
for once.
That’s all.
And she just happened to
walk into my life at that moment.
Damn! I am so freaking dumb.
That gear ring,
I flushed it down the toilet already.
I’m sorry for not telling you in person.
Anyway...
I am such an asshole.
I wanted to ask you...
if I want to tell Kaya that
I don’t want to go see her anymore,
how do I say that in English?
If that’s all you wanted to ask,
you could have just called.
Pleng.
I can
break up with a girl through a phone call.
But I cannot tell a girl
that I like her through the phone.
I want to see your face
when I tell you that I like you.
So...
Do you
feel
the same way?
Why are you crying? What does that mean?
Don’t cry.
How far have you listened to?
As a maintenance engineer,
I believe everything can be fixed
and made to work again.
No matter how hard it is to fix
I will always find a way.
I will be very sad if you don’t choose me.
Translate please.
Come here.
DANCE SONG
The State of O-ha-o.
I used to live in O-ha-o.
Okay. A new state.
They have their own anthem too.
Never heard of this O-ha-o state.
Have they got a state song too?
What does it sound like?
Just like that. Can you sing?
Yes, of course.
Never heard this type of accent before!
Okay, let’s eat. She wants some milk.