Ladies and Gentlemen,
We would like to welcome you onboard.
We are going to take off, shortly.
Please turn off all electronic devices.
Fasten your seat belts.
Put your seat back upright,
and return the table to its start position.
Captain, we are ready to take off.
Hello. Hello.
Hi. Good morning.
Hello.
Everyone, please put on the
oxygen mask and breathe normally.
What the f...???
Don't worry.
Everything is gonna be fine.
Just kidding, we are going to die!
- The plane is going down
- Oh My God!
Oh My God!
Oh My Gosh!
I don't want to die.
Everybody, brace for impact.
ABCDEFG
HIJKLMNOP
QRS
TUV
WX
Y AND Z
So you know your ABCs,
let's speak up and sing with me.
ABCDEFG
HIJKLMNOP
QRS
TUV
WX
Y and Z.
I'm leaving now.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye
- Tutor Pleng!
- Hey!
- Hi.
- Hi, Kaya
I passed my interview for a company!
I'm going to work in America!
That's so good to hear.
Congratulations!
Because of you!
Thank you. Thank you, Tutor Pleng.
Enough, enough.
Actually, I need your help.
I want to break up with my Thai boyfriend.
Okay, and then?
He can't speak English,
and I can't speak Thai.
You guys can't even talk to each
other. How did you get together?
You know, S-E-X
It's all about sex.
Because, sex is my life.
Ooohhh.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yes. Oh, yes. Ah... Ah...
Okay, okay. Enough. I got it.
Thank you, Tutor Pleng.
For what?
For helping me
break up with him.
Oh, no. I didn't say I would.
But...
I bought this Louis Vuitton bag for you.
Oh yeah, breaking up with
a guy is easy. Don't worry.
Thank you.
Hey...
I have it here.
Good choice.
- Oh, original mocha ice coffee please.
- Yes ma’am.
Oops, sorry.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
What are you looking at?
Do I look like your husband?
Are you Yim, Kaya's boyfriend?
Kaya recorded her voice
to translate for you..
Let's begin.
Are you mixed blood?
- Hi, Yim.
- Sorry I didn't tell you about...
- I'm sorry I didn't tell you about...
the very long interview.
- I love you. But we don't have a lot in common.
- The things we like.
Our cultures.
Our attitudes.
Our religions.
Our lifestyles.
I don't think it'll work out.
Because we don't understand each other.
Understand, your ass!
We fuck every day.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I'm just here to translate.
Ok, let's continue.
- Hopefully, you'll meet the right person.
- You are the right person!
I've heard enough!
If you don't want to listen,
it's ok.
Wait a minute.
Are you her tutor?
Yes.
It's your fault!
Fuck it.
What the fuck are you looking at, Sir?
Is that a bomb?
Hey...
Hey, what's that?
It's chicken soup.
Chicken soup?
This is fuck.
[Thai word for winter-melon]
Fuck.
[Winter-melon / language joke]
What kind of person is he?
You mean me?
No, I mean the other guy.
What kind of guy is that?
You mean me?
The other guy.
He won't live long with that attitude.
Oh, you mean the other guy.
No, it's you!
Goddammit!
Oy...
What's wrong with you?
Don't come close.
I'll blind you.
Not worth it.
You're into domination?
I'm interviewing at the factory,
so I can get back with Kaya.
You have to teach me.
Go study with your Dad!
I thought you were a half-blood?
Hey!
My Dad is French.
He went back before I
was old enough to walk.
Then go study with
another teacher.
No.
If you can teach others,
then you can teach me.
You see your big photo
in front of the school?
- Teach me?
- Yes, I will teach you.
- One on one?
- Yes, I will.
Here's the money.
It you trick me,
I won't take the money...
I'll take something else.
Is this worth it?
It's 4am already, you haven't
slept yet, Daddy?
Daddy should have gone out
with me this evening.
Since you didn't go...
Ko A and Ko Chai
kept forcing me to drink.
Meh.
They asked me to send
you some love.
Look at this.
They gave a lot.
This is human skin.
They wrote as if my skin is paper.
This is a thrilling chicken.
So thrilling.
Daddy.
Daddy's not sad.
Daddy knows...
if Daddy's sad...
Daddy's not cool.
- You're drunk. Go to sleep.
- Daddy doesn't want her!
Kaya, Kaya, Kaya, Kaya,
Kaya, Kaya, Kaya...
Kaya...  ka ka kicked.
Coming all out...
I was really craving Jok.
[Jok: rice soup and actor's name]
Okay, let's get started.
Now you're taking a conversation lesson.
So, you will have to speak
English as much as possible
I need your full attention
and participation.
If you have any questions, just ask.
Don't be shy. Do you understand?
Do you understand?
Why are you standing?
Stand up.
Yeah, I know.
I got up to buy coffee.
You want anything?
I'm set.
You go.
This is a huge project.
ABCDEFG
HIJKLMNOP
- E
- F
- Ep
F...
Like a snake hissing.
- You try it.  Fffff.  F.
- Ffff
F.
Fss.
G.
H.
Ep.
S.
Ssss... No, keep your tongue inside.
Sss too
"H" like when you tell a dog
to go away "shoo shoo".
- Shoo Shoo
- Like that
Shoo Shoo... Let's try again.
H... Ha shoo shoo
Wrong.
Is it too much?
- X
- Ek
- Y
Z.
Isn't it zed?
X, Y, Z!
Hey, waiter...
Yes?
X, Y, and then?
Zed.
Zed, you see?
What is this?
This is a glass.
And, what's this?
This is...
a lord.
[Thai for straw]
This is a straw.
Little school boys even know this.
What is that?
There.
That is... woman.
Wrong.
Ah, shoelace.
Wrong again.
- So, what is it?
- That is mango.
Mango? Where's mango?
Breast mango.
[Type of mango]
Why are you walking up?
It's already 10pm.
I finished teaching late,
they've already closed the
door and elevator.
Do you want a ride?
No.
My boyfriend gave me this.
You have a boyfriend?
Remove the lid and get it ready...
you might need it soon.
I wish you can make it.
Can't wait to see your damn face
when you find out the truth.
That you're just her sex toy.
I know that you're cursing me.
But I don't understand the words.
May I grab it?
Yes you may.
MOLE
It'll be your turn soon.
What should I say about moles?
Whatever you want.
Whatever I want...
You may begin.
Uh, mole.
A mole is...
destiny in action.
Moles are destiny's little miracles.
Because...
no person can predict where or when
a mole will actually appear.  Or...
Or even finally end up on their body.
Moles appear to be random.
But... But if moles are truly random, then
how can two persons, two total strangers...
have a mole in exactly the same spot?
Maybe it is destiny.
You see, moles, like destiny,
are no different.
If you wait to meet someone
with the exact same mole,
it is almost impossible.
That is why...
we need to write our own destiny.
Oh, that was fast.
A student asked for your
phone number today.
Who is it?
Pruek, your business conversation student.
Did you give it to him?
Yes, I did.
Why did you give it to him?
It's inappropriate.
Stop smiling so much.
Your smile is from here to
the elevator.
No, this is what you call smiling from
here to the elevator.
Oh, so boring, my life is awesome.
Dorks.
What do you like to eat?
I like to eat Mama.
What is "Mama"?
Oh, Mama is a brand
of Thai instant noodles.
Foreigners don't know what Mama is,
they're going to think you eat your mother.
Why are you smiling so much?
Are you nuts?
What time do you go to bed?
Uh...   Twelve.
Or you can say "midnight".
You can use the word "mid" when
you want to say "half"...
for example, "mid-term",
means half-term exam.
But when you stab someone
all the way it's called "mid"?
Ok, whatever.
What do you like to do in your free time?
Uh, I like to play Porkærm.
You should say
"I like to play cards".
Or, if you want to return
the question, you say...
What about you?
What if I don't want to know?
It's ok, but you will look like an idiot.
Wow, wow.
Idiot, why did you use the flash?
Hey hey hey...
Wow, it's like a pyramid triangle.
Wow, nice and white.
Hey!  What the???
Where are you going?
Come with me.
- Why did you hit him?
- He took your picture.
No, I didn't.
- You didn't
- No, I didn't
- So you like to look at underwear?
- What are you doing?
- You like it, right?
- I didn't do anything.
- You did not do anything?
- I did not do anything.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Give her your cell phone.
Give her your phone!
Oy!
It hurts, sir.
It's locked.
Pattword...
Did you send it to your friend?
- No, I didn't.
- Are you sure?
I'm sure!
Did you delete it?
Are you sure?
Say something!
Apologize to her.
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Next time you want to look,
go see your mom.
Don't do this again.
I will not let you off.
-Oh!!!
- Hey sir, that's my phone!
Let me go!
You're pronunciation is wrong. It should be
"password" instead of "pattword".
Hey.
Oh shit!
I scared the shit out of you.
Eww shit!!!
Get me some tissue.
- There's no tissue here.
- Over there!
- This is called a "napkin",
- not a tissue
- Hey
That damn kid.
Why is that shit smell lingering?
Is it eternal shit?
Holy Shit!!!
Oh damnit!
Any more?
Little bit.
What did you eat?
'Sup man?
What's up... what's that?
What are you reading?
Uh, Happy Dolpin.
Ah, Happy what?
Happy Dophlinth.
It's pronounced...
Happy Dolphin.
Hey, put it back.
Don't read this one,
read another book.
Cinderella...
easy vocabulary for children.
It's for little gay kids.
I prefer the dolpin.
Excuse me.
Do you speak English?
Can you?
Oh, perfect. Hey... Great
I'm looking for this restaurant here.
You know it? You've been there before?
I heard it's really good.
- Talk to him.
- Talk to him yourself.
If it's far? It's no problem.
I can take a cab no problem at all.
Tell him to go away.
Oh, tell him yourself.
Go far far.
Guy? I don't understand.
What? Guy?
Will he understand?
You, Go far far.
Far? How far? How far?
How far you think?
Hey, how's it going?
Eww, more friends.
I think he said it's far.
It's far? It's fine, I have a map.
- Would you mind here?
- He's got a map.
Would you mark here?
- Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah
- Right here
What do you want?
- Yes? Do you know?
- Just in the area didn't matter.
I don't know what you're saying.
Yeah, this, this one?
I don't know.
Hi, there...
I'd gotta run.
- Hey, wait.
- What's wrong?
Here.
Actually, foreigners aren't that scary.
You can just speak freely.
Why?
What are you doing?
I'll make Mama with this.
You've finished eating?
Can I take it?
Who taught you this?
I learned it from Kaya.
- You understand her?
- Yeah, I do.
This, eat.
This, sleep.
What if you cannot sleep?
This is "cannot sleep".
- What if the toilet is full?
- Toilet full?
Are you joking?
When you ask her to be your girlfriend,
what do you say?
I ride a bicycle, take her to the beach,
wake up and she's my girlfriend.
Okay, stop.
Stop right here.
Right here.
- Where? Right here?
- Yes.
This is Pruek.
Do you want to sleep here?
Who is it?
- Nosy.
- Oh...
I asked so you can teach me.
I don't mean to be nosy.
It's my boyfriend.
- You don't have a boyfriend.
- I do.
Hmmm...
If you had a boyfriend, he would come
check me out the first day of tutoring
He's not my boyfriend yet, but very close.
I'm waiting for him to ask.
I didn't ask you that.
Why did you tell me?
Going now.
Shall we visit the countryside together?
Slut.
Would you like to go on a date?
Bigger slut.
[Sending]
Oh
[Message Read]
No!
Oh...
Hello?
Hello, my phone fell over and I
accidentally pressed the button.
You accidentally typed an entire sentence?
Yes.
- Ok, I'll book a table.
- Ok.
It's already very late.  I'll let you go.
Get lots of rest, teacher.
Oh, he has his own sticker.
Fucking premium.
Daddy?
How'd you get the key?
I made a copy for my girlfriend.
Someone sent you a bomb.
Not even a sender name.
I'll clean up for you, Daddy.
He can't wash it himself?
He has no hands or feet?
Why are you using my boyfriend?
I didn't even say anything.
Are you his slave?
Luckily, they returned it.
It's easier to just throw it away.
Maybe they want a bigger one?
Living abroad, getting fatter,
eating cheese and stuff.
Your Daddy is not a buffalo.
Although, he looks like one.
Hey...
Why are you staring at me?
Cold staring at you.
I'll put chili flakes in your eyes.
- Go ahead!
- Coming right up!
Come on!
Very clever, you picked the right spot.
Ohh.
Go down, down, down...
More, more...
There you go, Daddy.
Do whatever you want.
Stop!
Let go of the lizard!
This time...
I must do it.
For Daddy...
I will take care of it.
It's like rice soup, now.
I'll go clean my ass.
This ring, Yim...
For you!
What?
Give me your hand.
It can spin.
I ordered it from Klong Thom.
[Discount store]
Japanese people like it.
Did you propose me?
Is it a joke?
No, no, I just asked Jok to buy me noodles.
He has nothing to do with it.
I... Don't know what to say.
You like it, right?
Can you return this to Kaya?
- She returned it?
- Yes.
Take it back to her?
Yes.
Would you like anything?
Thank you.
Leave her a message for me.
Can you talk to each other yourselves?
Facebook, Facetime, Line, whatever?
I can't because she blocked me everywhere.
I don't want to.
Why not?  You have to return
the ring anyway.
What is the big deal?
I don't want to.
Hairy.
I deny the breakup.
She returned it.
That means Game Over.
Why are you so stubborn?
"I've been an asshole to all my girlfriends,
but I want to be good to you."
- Hello, tutor Pleng!
- Hi, Kaya
Today I ran into Yim,
And he has a message for you.
Wanna hear it?
"I've been an asshole to all my girlfriends,
but I want to be good to you."
"Here is your ring back.
Even if you wanna break up with me,
I'm not breaking up with you."
What? Is he coming here?
Don't tell me, he's gonna
take the interview test to work here.
Yeah.
And you have been tutoring him, right?
No, you shouldn't have done that.
Ewww.
But he does study really hard you know.
Oh.. How cute.
You have a dog?
Is that a golden retriever?
Oh boy come here.
Hi. I'm Owen.
Hi, I'm Pleng.
Bye.
Oh... Hardcore.
Really Hardcore.
I hired you to break up with him,
But you're tutoring him to come see me.
How could you?
My love for you, in my heart.
It's a secret that I don't
know how to tell you.
I have a secret in my heart.
Deep inside my heart.
I don't know how to tell you, I love you.
I love you.
- You cannot contact her?
- No
What time did you Skype her?
I called her many times.
Grab your pen and paper.
- Do I have to write it down?
- Yes.
There are three kind of tenses
in a sentence.
Present, past and future tense.
The structure of present tense is simple,
and that is S + V...
No! Stop!
Can you teach like before?
If you don't want to write it down,
then I cannot teach you.
Why are you going to
leave me like this?
Because your exam is in July.
There's not enough time.
You are too stupid.
Am I really that stupid?
Here, take your money back.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, Hey, Hey .. No, don't!
Once, once, once, once...
Once upon a time.
There lived an unhappy young girl
named Cinderella.
Yes, Khun Pruek.
Where are you now?
I'm on the way to teach.
I want to invite you to my Mom's
birthday at my house.
- Oh, it's your Mom's birthday?
- Yes.
- Which day?
- This Saturday.
Are you available?
I'm available.
One day the palace arranged a ball
for the Prince to choose his Princess.
Cinderella stepped down from
the pumpkin carriage,
and found herself standing among
all the beautiful ladies in the kingdom.
Is that a hairstyle or a bicycle seat?
When the ball started...
the Prince gazed directly at Cinderella.
He walked straight to her
and ask her for a dance.
Would you like to wipe your mouth?
Is it dirty?
Cinderella danced with the Prince,
song after song.
This is my grandfather's car.
Both of them joyfully talked to each other.
Only 3 exist in Thailand.
Would you like to sit inside?
I'll go grab the key.
I'm back.
Then, at the first stroke of midnight,
before the spell would wear off,
Cinderella sadly said goodbye
to the Prince.
I think I'd better go, I'm sleepy.
In her haste, one of her
glass slippers fell off.
The Prince, now madly in love,
had every woman in the kingdom...
try on slipper in hope
of finding Cinderella.
Does this belong to Pleng?
Please wait!
Before long, the Prince warmly
unites with Cinderella again.
Pleng, you left your phone.
Thank you.
Sorry that you had to run.
If I didn't run to bring you your phone,
who would I talk to tonight?
"Can I be your boyfriend?"
YES
And they lived happily ever after.
The End
"Can we celebrate our
1 Day Anniversary tomorrow?"
Cuation.
Is it Caotion?
Cau... Cuation. Caotion, Caution.
Hey brother.
Why does Daddy look
so sad lately?
Idiot.  Don't say anything
that sounds Japanese.
If Daddy hears it, and thinks about Kaya,
we will be in big trouble.
Jok, you are right.
But, we must support him.
You cannot say the word "Hai",
because it sounds Japanese.
Use some other word instead.
Yeah, you are right.
I'm glad I respect you.
Daddy.
Daddy, I see you're working very hard.
So I brought an ice water...
for you.
Daddy, I'm sorry.
I'm just worried about you, Daddy.
I didn't mean to say "Hai".
What's wrong with you?
Very precise.
I can feel it in my neck.
It's not too deep.
Paging Mr. Yim.
Please meet your teacher at the statue.
Translate this for me.
You missed my finger.
What's so funny?
Can I teach you again?
You want a punch?
If you punch me,
I'll slap you.
What? I just want to help you.
You said I'm too stupid to learn.
Actually...
If you want to be fluent,
there's not enough time.
But, if you just want to pass the exam,
there is a way.
What way?
Practice exam.
Memorization.
Let's do it!
Translate, please.
It means "Let's do it!".
- Rook.
- Oy, what rook? It's my turn.
Get up and walk over there.
I'm gonna kick you until
your fat explodes.
Everyone, this is Pleng, my tutor.
Stand up, please.
Good evening, Teacher.
How are you?
I'm fine.  Thank you.  And you?
I'm good.
And I'm glad to meet you guys.
She said...
I'm a cook...
And I use gas...
to fry the fish!
Are these all in your department?
Can you take the head cheese...
out of the fridge?
Ok, haha.
Okay, let's start interview.
Okay, let's eat.
She's hungryyyyyyyyyy.
Hmm, you learn fast.
How do I know what the interviewer
will ask me?
I don't know either so we will brainstorm.
The more the better.
Ok!
Why do you want to relocate
to America?
To follow my wife.
Do you have a problem?
If you answer like this,
who will approve?
You must say, you want to gain experience
to improve your work in Thailand.
The hydraulic sound, eed, eed, eed, eed...
Can you stop?
"Eed" is my Mom's name.
If it goes eed, eed, eed,
like his Mom's name...
the problem is that
the piston is too narrow.
Perhaps the oil has dried
or the cylinder is broken.
Oh, hey...
Why is your name "Making Milk"?
Because my Dad made me
drink milk with whiskey.
- Your power hungry.
- Can you tell me...
what is the proper temperature
for the boiler room?
Oh, by the way... Your name is "Snap"
because you like to snap your mustache?
He likes to snap...
down there.
When the power breaks, will Daddy
fix it or replace it?
I'm the fix-master,
not the replace-master.
Ok! You're hired!
Who would turn down a great
employee like you?
Why are you praising him?
You're here to ask questions, not praise!
Woah.
He's a good dancer.
Hey, why don't you dance with them?
I only dance at big events.
This time, let her begin.
We will say the alphabet,  A to Z.
In random order.
Daddy, why so little?
Only 3 letters?
Since you said "A to Z",
no one understands.
Oh, wait a minute.
If you lose, you get this
in your ass.
The women get it too.
Begin.
- X
- A
- T
- M
You going to the ATM?
J
Y
- P
- Are you going to the Korean dance?
G!
W
Come on, come on, hurry up.
R
One...
- Two...
- Q!
K
K is mine!
What should I answer?
I just said D.
It's your turn.
What is your answer?
One...
Two...
Wait, wait, wait...
X!
- Already picked!
- Oh no Daddy!
First one.
Ladies and Man...
It is round 2!!!
- Oh, too deep.
-  Too deep?
To deep, bro!
Ok, Chong Nom.
1, 2, 3...
Is it working, Daddy?
- Let it go!
- I already did!
Let it go all the way!
Damnit.
It smells like grilled meat.
I cannot shit any more.
It's burning my hole.
Why did you keep flexing your hole?
Are you doing ok there?
My stomach hurts.
Are you gonna die?
Hey, what is breast mouse?
Pervert, pervert, I'll slap you.
Oh?
It's not here.
You've already fixed this thing?
It looked unrepairable.
I can't believe you fixed it.
What?
I'm the repair-master...
whatever is broken, I can fix.
Don't be so sure...
Not everything will be that easy.
If you're referring to Kaya...
I never thought it would be easy.
If she cannot speak Thai,
I will study English.
If studying English is too difficult,
I will study Japanese.
Hey!
- Ouch, it's in my eyes!
- What happened?
- My contact lens!
- Hey, be careful!
This way! Come here!
Here, here...
- Why me?
- Here, here...
You're extremely near-sighted.
Yeah.
- Do I look like a blind man?
- I think so.
- Translation, please?
- I think so means "I think so."
Hey, stop!
- Hurry up!
- Slow down please!
Why? We won't make it in time.
Hey! Teacher!
Oh...
You said you wouldn't laugh.
I can't help it.
Damnit...
If Jok saw me, he'd lose respect.
Why do you keep showing me?
"Nozzle"
"At idle speed, what size of nozzle
should we use?"
What are your strengths?
Why should we choose you?
I'm the repair-master.
Anything that is broken, I can fix.
I believe that I can repair
anything that is broken.
If English is too difficult,
I will study Japanese.
Even if the process is difficult,
I will find a way to repair it.
Before I came to study with you,
we had met before.
Really?
Do you remember the Ministry of
Foreign Affairs event,
where you were the interpreter?
I remember.
Yes, that one.
After that, I asked my friend
to find out where you worked.
So, I came to study with you.
So, you didn't really want
to learn English?
Yes.
I wasn't interested
in learning...
only to flirt.
Are you ok?
Let me help you.
Oh no!
I always dreamed of doing this.
So romantic.
Pleng, can you close your eyes?
Close your eyes.
Close my eyes?
SONG FOR LIFE
Love is so beautiful,
for my entire life.
I've always been looking for love...
I cannot get enough.
I want you by my side.
Shower me with your love.
Always close to me.
Are you happy?
Very much.
You love this type of song?
I'd sacrifice my life for this song.
I feel very lucky.
You have a good sense of humor.
I don't have one.
Is this guy for real?
Khun Pruek, If you want to take
your yacht out,
don't forget to check the
weather forecast.
Weather forecast!
[In foreign accent]
Oh, yeah, you mean
weather forecast.
If you want to go to...
Munnok Island.
- Mannok Island?
- Munnai -Monsnai?
Or Samet Island...
Samet Island?
[In foreign accent]
- Samet! Everyone has sex!
[pun]
Ask me any time.
- You ok with that?
- Yes, I'll let you know!
Ah, Pleng! There you are.
I have something for you.
Why not for me?
[foreign accent]
Why not me?
Why?
I think this one is a little
bit too small.
Ok.
Then let's try...
this pair.
Let's try it.
Hey...
it fits well.
Actually, you could just call me
and ask my size.
That would spoil the surprise...
for your happiness.
Anything I can do.
Ok.
Can I not accept it?
Why not?
This pair looks like the one you broke.
Okay.
- Excuse me?
- Yes?
Shall we go back to being Teacher
and Student, like before?
Why?
Because I went to see a fortune teller...
they said not to date someone who
was born in the same month.
It would be bad luck.
We need to write our own destiny.
Can you remember?
Yes.
Do your feet hurt?
I'll massage your feet.
Relax, relax...
Oh, nice sound.
What is your job position?
I am a maintenance engineer.
Hey, I answered correctly!
Why'd you punch me?
How do you feel about working
with foreigners?
I haven't answered yet.
What's wrong with you?
I'm stressed!
Come on!
Hold up.
Feel better?
Yes.
What wrong with you?
I want to break up
with my boyfriend.
She has a punch like Pacquiao.
[Filipino boxer]
Where are you going?
Some asshole requested they
close early.
What the heck!
Translation, please?
It means "we should run".
- Don't tell me that he is...
- Yeah, that's him.
Is that a flower or a shower lid?
As a maintenance engineer,
I believe everything can be fixed,
and made to work again.
No matter how hard it is to fix,
I will always find a way.
What?
Not finished yet.
There's one more left.
"You will regret it, if you
don't choose me."
You will regret it if you don't choose me.
Well, actually, I don't think this approach
will make them want to hire me.
No, I think it's good.
It's straight to the point.
It's perfect for you.
Ok, let's continue.
When the pressure in the cylinder
is abnormally high, how would you fix it?
Pressure, pressure...
Ah, for me working under pressure
is quite challenging.
Almost correct.
That's for another question.
- That's #235
- But pressure is the key word.
Yes, but this one is like the "pressure"
at work, not the "pressure" in a machine.
There's your pressure coming.
- Did he see me?
- He didn't look this way.
- You should just tell him.
- Breaking his heart is like killing a puppy.
It's not a big deal, he'll survive.
Hey...
I wanted to surprise you.
How are you doing?
Do you feel better?
Tui said you weren't feeling well.
Yeah, I feel better.
Here, I brought some dinner.
Oh, no no no, my room
is very messy right now.
That's fine, I'll help you.
- Ah...
- You are ill.
It's fine, don't worry about it.
What's going on?
Oh, it's this guy.
Who are you?
What?
Let's go the room.
Excuse me?
Who are you?
I'm her husband.
- Umm...
- What's this all about?
We started dating less than
a month ago.
Let's go.
Why did you tell him that?
What's he gonna think?
I'm helping you.
Should I thank you?
What did you tell him?
He seemed so shocked.
Oh, I said that...
I got you pregnant.
Oh my God!  That's so slutty!
How could you conceive of
such a thing?
Did you ever care about me?
You made me sound like a big slut.
Going now.
Hey, where are you going?
Why don't you use the elevator?
If he's still downstairs,
he will see me.
Going now.
Hello, what's up?
Hello, where are you?
I'm here, buying coffee.
- There's no time for coffee, we're late.
- I have my motorcycle, no problem.
What are you wearing?
I told you to dress nicely.
I have it, don't worry.
This is what you brought?
Yes.
What the hell do you want?
This is how I dress everyday for work.
Hey, hold up!
Have you never bought a shirt before?
The tag is still on it.
Oh, I beg your pardon!
I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
Ah. He is okay.
Don't worry about it.
I'm so sorry.
Why didn't you respond?
You're not afraid to fight people,
but you're afraid to speak English?
-  I'm a lover, not a fighter.
- Whatever "...er" you are.
If you don't start speaking first,
the conversation will never begin.
I don't know why I brought you here.
Today, you must speak with
at least 3 foreigners.
Understand?
How can I talk with them,
they speak so fast.
Listen for the key words.
How are you?  How are you?
How are you?
How are you... How are you...
Hey!
Who are yow?
Oy!
Who are you?
I am fine. Who am I?
- Is this guy okay?
- You think he has Alzheimer's?
Are you okay?
You okay?
- I am a Maintenance Engineer.
- Oh, Maintenance Engineer.
- That's good for you.
- Congratulations.
Yeah, congratulations.
I wish you are the best.
- Good luck.
- Ah, because...
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
- Oh, because sorry?
- Bye Bye!
- Okay, Bye Bye Yeah
- Bye Bye
- Good luck.
- Going now.
Oh!!! Such a weirdo.
I can speak Thai, why does he
have to speak English to me?
"Maintenance Engineer", you buffalo.
I agree.
You come one?
Pardon?
Ah, father, mother?
My parents are standing right over there.
- Standing?
- My mother is a lady in the blue dress.
Mother... Blue dress...
Nice white skin.
Woah!
Are you very excited?
You like to dance?
Oh yeah?
Who the fuck are you?
No.
Who's kid that?
So cute.
Oh, he only dances at big events.
Thank you for attending
the event tonight.
We must thank Pleng,
our lovely translator.
Thank you.
Thank you everyone for your presence
here tonight. Please enjoy the night.
- Ok I'll see you later, thank you.
- Ok thank you.
Hey...
Would you like to leave?
No it's ok, I can wait.
Why aren't you wearing them?
They're broken.  They guy didn't
repair them properly.
Can you hold it for me?
Thanks.
I'm very interested in your culture.
I'd love to know a bit more
about the elegant hand movement
- How did they do that?
- Like this.
I can not.
...and no shoes.
Oh, sorry...
my shoes are broken.
Please give a warm welcome to our guest.
Do you understand? Or are
you just clapping along?
Yeah, I understand.
- Good evening.
- Wow.
- I can translate the whole song.
Tonight...
Tonight.
It's just the two of us.
So, forget the world for a while.
Forget the world.
Yes.
Open your eyes...
Open your eyes?
That's correct. Be confident.
You.
- You're pretty.
- Thank you.
- Sounds like "do do, doo doo"?
- No it's not, listen carefully.
Can I ride home with you?
My dog's very vicious.
Don't help me with this line.
Ok, maybe I need your help.
I promise I will be forever yours.
Let me walk you home.
Before this morning,
before the sunrise.
Morning?
Before I go back to reality and you...
go back to your life.
Tell me that you feel the same way too.
I've already fixed them.
Going now, Thank you.
Daddy, why'd you come back so late?
Having an interview tomorrow?
Are you crazy?
It's next month.
I just went to help them
clean up the room.
June.
Oh crap!
June is not July.
Right, July is Karakada.
The talking Dict is incorrect.
Daddy is correct.
Correct your ass!
I'm wrong.
Everyone knows I'm wrong!
Stop praising me!
He scolded me again!
Hello Teacher.
Calm down.
Ok, come on over.
I'm sorry, I'm very stupid.
You can remember everything?
Yes.
There are no corrections needed.
Teacher...
Oy!
Go sit over there.
If she sees you with me,
she will misunderstand.
Hello tutor Pleng!
How are you?
Fine and you?
I'm doing great.
Today is the day of the interview.
Is he still going?
- I guess so.
- That's good.
Because I need all of the help from you.
Huh?
I know the important answer that
will help him to pass the interview test.
So he can come see me.
What? Say that again?
Tell Yim to remember the
name of the company's founder.
What is the intention of
your change of heart?
You've have been refusing
to encounter this fella all along.
I just changed my mind.
Why are you talking funny?
Oh...
Right now I'm in the middle of
translating some legal documents.
All the vocab must be rubbing off.
- I see.
- So, how about Mr. Golden Retriever?
He will be away for 3 months.
We have an open relationship.
So, I can see anybody I like.
So, when he returns
What will happen with Yim?
Why do you sound concerned?
I'm just curious.
- What?
- Oh, My God.
You love Yim.
Oh my God... Oh my God...
You guys had sex.
Hell no.
Stop it!
Tutor Pleng be careful
your going to get hurt.
Be ready to pick your broken heart...
What did she tell you?
She wants you to meet her.
That's it.
I heard her say...
"You love Yim."
I like you.
You still want to go for the exam?
I intend to go.
Anyway, I must go.
True.
How can a tutor like me...
fall in love with a student?
She told me she wants you back.
I believe I can fix it to work again.
Anything I need to fix,
I will always find a way.
Today, I will go first.
Fairy Tale.
Once upon a time a little
girl dream of being a Princess.
And meeting a charming Prince
that would sweep her off her feet.
In the real world, a Princess
may not want Prince charming.
But just an ordinary shoemaker.
And it is not Prince charming's fault.
You knows what's funny?
In the end who knows? The shoemaker
may not want the Princess either.
Therefore it is not necessary for the story
to end with "happily ever after".
I admit that it hurts.
It's easy to understand
once you admit it.
There's something I'd like clear up.
I'm not pregnant.
So what makes you think that..
I believe you're pregnant?
Umm...
That day at my condo...
that guy whispered in your ear.
He said...
Pleng is his woman.
Stay away from her.
He was just saying that.
Do you remember about
my destiny mole story?
Yes, I remember.
My mole...
needs to find destiny to erase it.
Did this take you long to think about?
But I think you might have
found your destiny mole.
Yes.
BROKEN HEART SONG
"You must remember the founder's
name of the Japanese company."
Nohada Toichi
Mr. Willay, have a seat.
Why do you want to work in the US?
Why US?
I want to learn new experience...
and come back to apply
here in Thailand.
Do you think you'll have any problems
working in a foreign country?
No problem.
I am a professional.
It is the nature of our work that we have
to deal with high pressure situations.
Do you think you can handle it?
Is it emotional pressure,
or machine pressure?
It takes a lot to work in
high-pressure machinery.
For me, working under pressure
is quite challenging.
Are you trying to
compare yourself to a machine?
What about you?
What do I think?
Yeah.
I think you're trying to illustrate
how you feel about things.
Uh, working on high pressure
machinery is dangerous,
but you're up to the
challenge right?
- "I think so" means you agree.
- I think so.
Why should we choose you?
What are you strong points?
As a Maintenance Engineer, I believe
everything can be fix and made to work again.
No matter how hard it is
to fix I will always find a way.
Not finished yet...
There's one more sentence...
You will regret it if
you don't choose me.
you don't choose me
Alright then, thank you
for your participation.
Thank you.
Wait!
I have one last question.
Yeah?
What is the name of our
company's founder?
Eh?
- For you.
- Huh?
Teacher, someone asked me
to give this to you.
Teacher, I received the interview results
I didn't pass.
Actually, I wanted to pass,
to make you proud.
What is the name of our
company's founder?
Doraemon
[Anime character]
It's difficult for me to say
sweet things.
However...
please listen to me.
I'm not in love with her.
I just want to be good...
with one woman.
That's it...
and then she comes along.
Damnit.  Stupid me.
I threw the ring in the toilet.
I'm sorry that I didn't come to
say all this in person.
That's it.
I'm an asshole.
Teacher, I want to ask you something.
If I want to tell Kaya, that I'm not
going to see her any more...
How do I say it?
Actually, you could have just asked me
this on the phone.
Oh.
I can break up with a woman
on the phone,
but I can't tell her I have feelings
for her on the phone.
I wanted to see the look on your face when
I said I like you.
Anyway...
Teacher...
do you still feel the same?
Why are you looking at me
like this?
Don't cry.
Which part are you listening to?
As a Maintenance Engineer, I believe
everything can be fixed and made to work again.
No matter how hard it is
to fix, I will always find a way.
I will find a way.
You will regret it if you don't choose me.
I will be very regretful.
If you don't choose me.
I think so.
Translation, please?
Come here.
Translated by DJPS and Namtaan
Once upon a time...
DANCE SONG
1, 2, 123
Ladies and Gentlemen.
Welcome to the classroom.
Let's sing along together.
ABCDEFG
HIJKLMNOP
QRS TU and V
WXY and Zed!
Yeah!
What about you?
I think so!
Are you ready?
What?!?!?
What's up man?
What's up girl?
Yeah.
Oh yeah!
Wow
Why? Why?
Okay...
Are you ready?
THE END
I used to live in Ohio.
[with bad foreign accent]
Ok, that's a new state.
- It has a song, too.
- I've never heard of "Ohao".
- They have a national theme song.
- How does it go?
Ohao, Ohao...
Ohao-ha-Ohaho...
- Can you sing the song?
- No, I cannot sing.
I've never seen a foreigner
with such an accent.
- Okay, let's start interview.
- Okay...
Let's eat, she's hungry.
Let's start interview!
Ok, let's eat, she's hungry!