Yes, I did it.
I don't want to talk about this anymore.
You're always like this, Nok.
I don't understand
how you can't feel anything.
I want to know how you feel.
We're getting married, Nok.
You can talk to me.
Okay. If that's what you want.
Thana! Watch out!
Hey, did you go jogging this morning?
I thought I saw you.
Yes.
I like to go running.
To prepare myself for the big test.
The big test.
You're going to meet that guy today.
Be careful.
All right.
I heard he was talented
but not so friendly.
It's getting worse, Doctor.
This doesn't help.
Blood pressure is not increasing.
BP is dropping to 80/40.
Doctor, shall we prepare blood
for a transfusion?
-Prepare for cautery.
-Yes, Doctor.
Blood pressure is decreasing.
The dosage we gave is not sustaining.
I'm aware of that. I'm trying.
Apply suction here, please.
The patient can't take it.
BP is dropping very quickly.
I know. Can you hold that for me?
Please step aside.
Stand over there.
Doctor, allow me to raise the table up.
Great.
Apply suction here.
How's the bleeding?
Still heavy.
Apply swab and sponge.
Cut here.
How's the BP?
BP is much better.
I think the bleeding is under control.
Check the BP again.
BP is great, 120/70.
Cut please.
You can take it from here.
Can you manage?
Cautery may not always
be a better option than sutures.
You have to check the bleeding.
Whether it's from the vein or the artery.
-Yes.
-These cases are rare but possible.
So you should be prepared.
Think and decide much faster.
Don't just stand around
and wait for a miracle to happen.
I wasn't waiting for a miracle.
I was trying to stop the bleeding,
I thought it was going to stop.
Don't stress yourself out.
You're still a resident.
I'm stressed
because you said
I was waiting for a miracle.
I don't want you to get the wrong idea.
Why?
What's so bad about a miracle?
Nothing.
But people who wait for miracles,
they have already lost
by believing in them.
You're hardworking.
I'm looking into the last patient's file.
I have to study it carefully,
so I can succeed in the future.
You've got an attitude.
That's why things
got tense with Dr. Thana.
How did you know about it so soon?
Well, Dr. Panthana
is on the most wanted list
of all the girls in this hospital.
How could I not know?
He's handsome, that's true.
But aren't the girls
afraid of his unfriendliness?
Bee, he's like that
because he's sad.
Sad?
You don't know?
Where have you been?
His case is very famous.
What happened?
Two years ago...
Dr. Thana's story is very famous
on the Internet.
HERE IT IS AGAIN,
A BOUQUET OF WHITE ROSES.
Everybody's been talking
about Dr. White Roses.
Mysterious white roses on the toll way.
I have seen them too for two months now.
They say...
The flowers are for the dead.
Really? That's scary.
What's the real story?
Can somebody tell us?
The tale of the roses
that went viral over the Internet.
There was an accident here,
a man and a woman, both are doctors.
They were going to get married
in just a week
before the accident happened.
They drove the car, then boom!
The woman died, but the guy survived.
He must have loved her very much.
He brings her flowers every Sunday night.
Can you give us an interview?
Hold on.
Just a second.
What's with him?
DR. KARN
DR. PANTHANA
You're interested in this story, right?
There's more to it.
Dr. Thana has remained single ever since.
If he's that handsome and that great,
how come nobody
has offered to heal his wound?
There were some,
but he wasn't really interested.
And some of them encountered some mishaps.
Mishaps?
The ghost of Dr. Nok.
They say that
those young nurses
who hit on Dr. Thana
met with some unfortunate events.
Tenth floor, door opening.
He's cute.
Door closing.
I've been here a long time.
I don't even dare to give him my number.
That's crazy.
Thirteenth floor, door opening.
Why don't you come out?
-Is that true?
-I don't know if it's true or not.
I've never tried to hit on Dr. Thana.
Or do you want to give it a go?
I'm going.
I'm scared.
-Iced cappuccino, not too sweet.
-Here.
Latte for Dr. Thana.
Americano for Dr. Nok.
I want to say sorry
and thank you for yesterday.
So do you want to apologize
or thank me first?
Sorry first,
for arguing with you.
And thank you for your help
with the surgery.
Please, sit down.
I guess someone must have told you things.
What's your opinion, then?
You like to have
two different kinds of coffee.
Nok and I...
We liked different things.
We would always argue...
about whose coffee tasted better.
Try my Americano.
No, Nok. I think it's bitter.
Come on, try it.
Bitterness is good.
The latte is not bad.
The level of sweetness is just right.
And your Americano is weirdly bitter.
We drank half of each other's cups.
So I've been drinking
two types of coffee ever since.
It's a clever way to solve an argument.
If it's a clever way,
then you're clever
for answering correctly.
You're the first.
Other people think I order it for Nok.
Somebody needs me.
The two kinds of coffee thing
is a secret I had never told anyone.
I've only told you.
Keep it to yourself.
Let people think whatever they want.
How are you doing?
-Hello.
-Hi.
I don't know, the pain comes and goes.
Let me look at your stomach.
Have you been passing wind?
Farting. She wants to know
if you've been farting.
Here and there. Why?
If you've been passing wind,
then your intestines work fine.
Nothing. Ple told me you were pretty.
I didn't believe her at first,
but now I see that it's true.
Thank you.
She's not just pretty,
she's a great surgeon, too.
Dr. Thana has been praising her.
The surgery was performed very well.
It definitely won't leave any scars.
Dr. Bee is pretty.
Dr. Thana is very good-looking.
Is this a hospital or a catwalk?
Hurry up and get well soon.
I'm getting jealous.
But Dr. Thana is not just handsome,
he's also romantic.
His girlfriend died two years ago.
He's still single.
I want to meet a nice guy like that.
Fine, when you die, I'll do that for you.
How come you know so much about this?
All the nurses
have been gossiping about it.
But his girlfriend must have been
so amazing.
Otherwise, he would be over her already.
Can you be as cool as her?
Asshole!
Dr. Bee.
Don't you want to have a boyfriend?
You're pretty
and Dr. Thana is good-looking.
You would be great together.
Get plenty of rest, okay?
Don't encourage that.
The ghost of Dr. Nok will come for you.
You bastard, don't joke like that!
I'm already scared.
Yes, June?
Don't forget about
the new residents party tonight.
I heard that person will be there too.
Who?
Well, the guy
you had coffee with last night.
Right.
Don't forget to come, all right?
-Uncomfortable in high heels?
-Yes.
But I think they look good on you.
Is that your ex?
What are you talking about?
That's your ex.
Not me, it's his ex.
Who is she?
That's Tree,
she's a pharmaceutical representative.
Her parents own a private hospital.
Her family is really rich.
It's good to be Dr. Thana.
The harder he is to get,
the more women want him.
What are you laughing at?
I want to thank that new doctor.
Thanks to her, you gave in to me.
This time, you even brought me back home.
What does she have to do with it?
Come on.
I saw you looking at her.
I was thinking about the time
when Nok and I were new residents.
I miss Nok.
It's so convenient to be a guy.
You miss you one woman,
but you bring another one home.
I'll be back.
So beautiful.
You can stay and watch if you like.
Thana!
Did you have a rough night?
Not really.
In the end, it wasn't like
how people think it was.
Only the beginning was unbelievable.
Why is that?
The beginning was very normal.
Women...
They come and go as they please.
And men...
They ask you to come when they want you.
If not, they tell you to go away.
She was okay about it and so was I,
so it was fine.
Or did you think...
What did I think?
Dr. Bee.
Do you need to love someone
to have sex with them?
Hi, Bee.
About before...
I want to apologize and thank you.
Apologize for what?
Sorry for...
being rude to you.
I was annoyed with myself.
And what are you thanking me for?
For forgiving me.
I never thought you'd be the type
to say things like this.
Get in, I'll take you home.
That's all right.
Then that means you haven't forgiven me.
How about this, I'll take you home
to make up for what I said.
I have to go with you, right?
Get in, we're blocking the road.
Are you hungry?
Let's go eat first.
I'd rather not.
I need to go to this place.
Could you accompany me there?
Please?
Thank you.
I thought we were going to eat.
You're only having coffee.
I only meant to come to this place.
Come to this place?
What do you mean?
For the last two years,
I visit this place once a year.
Two years?
Once a year?
This restaurant is very important to me.
You haven't eaten?
I told you not to wait for me.
Today was such a chaotic day.
My cell phone is totally dead.
So what you did was--
I left you a message, of course.
I know how meticulous you are.
There were some problems with the case.
I almost didn't make it out.
One of the nurses said that
we're lucky there's a miracle.
So you said--
So I had to lecture her for a bit.
We have knowledge and technology.
We have everything.
Do we have to rely on miracles?
People believe in such things.
I'm sorry, I've been complaining.
Let it all out.
It will then be my turn.
Is something wrong?
Nok.
It's fine if you don't believe me.
But you're my miracle.
This binds us together.
From now on,
wherever you go,
I'll follow you.
When you feel down,
I'll be next to you.
When you're happy,
I'll be in front of you.
But when you feel sad,
I'll be right behind you.
I will do my best to take care of you.
I promise.
Well, it looks like it's not just binding.
We're going to be stuck together.
If you let me go, I'll be so mad at you.
I'll never let you go.
I sat here waiting for Nok,
for three hours...
but I was so happy.
After that day,
I sit here alone at this table.
And this...
has tortured me.
I think...
this is a nice place.
But you might get bored
if you come too often.
It's like the love between you and Nok.
I'm not trying to be intrusive,
but from what I've been hearing
from you and other people,
I think Nok wouldn't
want you to stay like this.
You think Nok would want me to forget her?
We hold on to the moments
that made us happy, right?
If we only try to hold on
to the happy moments,
isn't it harder to let go of the pain?
Thank you for your advice.
Excuse me, sir.
Could you please move your car?
It seems that your car wasn't in neutral.
NOK
UNKNOWN NUMBER
Thana, look at it this way,
the later I am,
the more I'll be missing you.
Hold on...
I'll come to you soon.
Thank you for dropping me off at home.
I'm the one who should thank you.
I was holding on to the happy memories.
And that makes it harder to let go.
What if I try to be happy again?
Do I have to prepare myself
for another heartache?
Hello, Mom.
Who was that?
And you pretend like
you're watching some Korean series.
Spying on you is much more fun
than any Korean series.
He's a colleague.
He's just a colleague for now.
It seems like it's going to stay that way.
Why? Does he already have a girlfriend?
He did.
Are you sure it's in the past?
Either way, it has nothing to do with me.
In any case, just be careful.
I don't want you to be involved
with someone else's boyfriend.
Or you'll be miserable like me.
Oh, Mom.
His girlfriend might
come looking for you at home.
Sorry, I know it's late,
but I need this for tomorrow.
No problem. Come by in the morning.
-Thank you, sorry for the trouble.
-It's okay.
Thank you for accompanying me.
Thank you for your words of advice.
Thank you, too,
for dropping me off at home.
Sweet dreams.
You too.
Hey!
You look exhausted,
did you get enough sleep?
Or...
the ghost of Dr. Nok visited you?
Why did you...
I'm just kidding.
Yesterday, I saw you get in the car
with Dr. Thana, right?
If I were Dr. Nok, I'd be jealous.
That is nonsense, June.
I just accompanied him.
It's fine if you two
are going to be more than colleagues.
I'm going.
How are you today?
Not bad.
Where's your boyfriend?
He's not here, he's watching
a football match with friends.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Let me see your wound.
Even on my birthday!
Men are always like this.
He said the flirting part was his duty.
Now that we're together, it's my duty.
How did Dr. Thana's girlfriend do it?
She isn't with him anymore,
but he still loves her.
You're being too serious.
You're still young.
Dr. Bee.
If you and Dr. Thana were together,
what would you do
to make him love only you?
If Dr. Thana liked me
and we were together,
that would mean
he's no longer in love with his ex.
I thought you said
you wanted to meet decent guys.
Well, then, that doesn't count,
she's dead.
Get some rest.
Are you sure it's a good idea
for a doctor to smoke?
-Does the smell bother you?
-No, it's fine.
I like the smell of cigarettes.
The smell reminds me of my dad.
Nok didn't like it.
So I had to sneak up here a lot.
But you still brought her along.
What are you listening to?
What?
It's my favorite song
that I always listen to.
When I'm tired or discouraged
and I listen to this song,
I feel like...
I have some support.
I like her.
What about you?
Were you dreaming?
Sorry.
Dr. Nok, I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
What are you two doing?
What the hell are you doing?
You scared the shit outta me! So scary!
Happy birthday!
Love you, miss you.
What's wrong, Dr. Bee?
Nang.
Dr. Nok? Really?
That's very unlikely.
You think I'm seeing things?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
It's just that Dr. Nok
was a really nice person.
Even if she was a ghost,
she wouldn't be a mean one.
I've never seen her myself.
They said that...
she came to haunt those
who flirted with Dr. Thana.
I'm not saying that you flirted with him.
But he does flirt with you.
He flirts with me?
It's true.
Ever since you came to train here,
he seems to be in a better mood.
He smiles more often.
I doubt that.
A guy like Dr. Thana likes me?
But I hope he does.
If he really does like you,
will you like him back?
I'm not considering
anything more than that.
I just want to help him
get over his grief.
Really?
I saw you standing there awhile,
what have you been doing?
Dr. Nok? Really?
That's very unlikely.
You think I'm seeing things?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
It's just that Dr. Nok
was a really nice person.
Even if she was a ghost,
she wouldn't be a mean one.
They said that...
she came to haunt those
who flirted with Dr. Thana.
No. I'm not saying
that you flirt with him.
But he does flirt with you.
Earlier you said that...
Dr. Thana flirts with me.
It's true.
Ever since you came to train here,
he seems to be in a better mood.
He smiles more often.
But I hope he likes you.
If he really does like you,
will you like him back?
I've never thought about that.
Really?
Well, you should,
so he could get over his grief.
Dr. Thana.
The patient is a Thai woman aged 31.
She was in an accident,
her car crashed into a lamp post.
Her breathing is 30 per BP 70/30.
I think she has pneumothorax.
Give me number 32.
ICD number 32.
Scalpel number 10.
Thana!
Find Dr. Prapon.
I think we were lucky
that there wasn't any significant loss.
However, this mistake cannot be ignored.
So the committee and I,
we have agreed that you should refrain
from performing surgery temporarily.
About last night...
Seeing the patient last night
might have reminded him
of the night that Nok died.
The cases are very similar.
The patient was also a woman.
Is that all?
He probably felt guilty.
He felt guilty?
He probably felt guilty about Dr. Nok.
Can you wait for me on the 14th floor?
-I'll see you there.
-Yes, Doctor.
-Bee.
-Yes.
Did you hear that Thana resigned?
He resigned?
Yes. He submitted a resignation
letter, but Dr. Sanchai refused.
He told Thana to reconsider.
So where is he now?
I don't know.
If you can find him,
tell him to go talk to Dr. Sanchai
or Dr. Prapon.
-Okay.
-I have to go.
Sunday.
THANA
Why did you come here?
I just want you to change your mind
about your resignation.
You came to look for me...
but you might have been another person
to die because of me.
Another?
You think Nok died because of you?
Why?
Why do you blame yourself
when it was all an accident?
You know nothing.
You just don't know.
Calm down!
Help is here. Calm down.
Calm down.
Do you want to wait for Dr. Suthee?
No, I'm okay.
Still no pulse, defib 200 joules.
You're going to be okay, Nok.
Nok, I can help you.
Always together. You told me so, Nok.
-Out.
-Doctor.
That's enough.
The patient is no longer with us.
Hold the mask, hold it.
No, I can still help her.
No, Nok.
Nok, wake up.
What will I do without you?
Doctor, she's gone.
Come back, Nok, come back!
Damn it!
You can do it, Nok.
Why aren't you holding the mask?
It's not true. Again.
-Doctor.
-It's not true, don't do this.
Always together, Nok.
But in the end,
there was no miracle.
People die.
Even though you couldn't save her,
that doesn't mean
any other doctor could have.
You said it yourself.
People die.
Nok is gone.
I said she was dead,
but I didn't say she was gone.
She's still here.
Yes.
She's still here...
but only in your heart.
You don't understand.
She really is still here.
Nok donated her body.
If she'd lived,
she would be a lecturing doctor.
But even though she's not here,
her body is examined by students.
Thana.
I think...
I put that there.
I thought Nok wouldn't want me
to take it off.
At first...
I thought...
I could help you get over her.
So you can walk away from your past.
But this is more serious than I imagined.
Thank you
for trying to help.
You should stop trying, it's no use.
No one can help me.
Nobody can help you,
or you just don't want to be helped?
That's right.
Your forever love.
It's so great that you need no help.
As for me...
it doesn't matter.
I can't help myself either.
You know that I like you, right?
And you?
There is only you and me
in this room, Thana.
Help me, please.
You were sleeping,
so I didn't want to wake you.
The new clothes are for you.
And please lock the house.
Nok.
Nok, I know that you love me.
But please let me go.
I'm sorry, Nok.
I'm sorry.
You seem to be in a good mood today.
You think so?
You're the second female surgeon
who hums while operating.
Who is the first one?
Dr. Nok.
But Dr. Nok, she could only hum one song.
Which song?
I'll look for it.
Because she always listened to it.
Dr. Thana used to sing the song for her
in front of other people, too.
You think Nok wants me to forget her?
If we only try to hold on
to the happy moments,
isn't it harder to let go of the pain?
But Nok didn't like it.
So I had to sneak up here a lot.
But you still brought her along.
You don't understand.
She's still here.
She's still here,
but only in your heart.
You should stop trying, it's no use.
No one can help me.
Nobody can help you,
or you just don't want to be helped?
I have feelings for her.
But it's not the same thing
that I feel for you.
What should I do?
What should I tell her?
You already know.
I will never leave you.
The number you are calling
is not available.
Please try again later.
The number you have dialed
is not available at this time.
SEAMSTRESS FOR HIRE
The number you are calling
is not available.
Please try again later.
What is it, Mom?
A woman called.
She told me to warn you
to stop fooling around with her husband.
-Who--
-Why didn't you listen to me?
Did she tell you her name?
She said her name was Nok.
Thana.
Nok.
Is this you?
Yes, it's me.
That's all I wanted to know.
I didn't think she would do that.
It's not what she did.
Yes, I did it.
And do you want to know why I did it?
I don't want to talk about this.
You're always like this, Nok.
We have to talk about it.
We're about to get married.
You don't understand.
Yeah, I don't understand.
I don't understand
how you can't feel anything.
You think I'm tired of you.
Or I love you less?
All right, if you want to hear it.
Our love has never changed.
I believe that even
though you slept with her,
you still love me just the same.
But what's changing is...
Thana, watch out!
How are you?
How did I get here?
You passed out in the car.
Last night...
Dr. Nok, right?
I saw that photo.
What photo?
Yes.
I was wrong. I cheated on her.
She was still mad at me, so she did this.
Why do you think so?
At first, I thought
Nok would have accepted you.
Because you and her are alike somehow...
but she refused to give in.
She didn't want me to start over
with someone else.
That's all you cared about?
You slept with me...
because I'm similar to Nok, right?
You should go home.
Well, here we go again.
Please, come in.
You go first.
What is it?
You're so evil.
Did you know this picture
made them argue and led to the accident?
Let me tell you something.
Do you know why men cheat?
Because sometimes,
they get bored of good girls,
well-mannered like princesses.
So if there is a hero and a princess,
there must be a villain.
You should thank me, instead,
for helping to prove
the true love between Thana and Nok.
Just like you.
How?
You've already slept with him, right?
Normally, when people fight
over something,
they always bring out their good sides
to bluff other people.
Some are good at understanding.
Some are good at caring.
And some are good in bed.
If fighting over something is so bad,
then we three are bad people.
As for Nok,
when she knew that Thana cheated on her,
she took the easy way out and died.
So Thana's heart will forever be with her.
That was so bad.
Nok was not like that.
Oh, God!
You're so naive.
Or you're just pretending to be...
I know you're listening to us.
You're probably laughing at us
for fighting over something we can't have.
What?
You think I'm crazy?
Don't tell me you haven't seen
the ghost of Nok?
There. I told you.
She is so possessive.
One more thing...
ghosts can't make phone calls.
The person who called your mom
was me.
Consider it as my welcome present.
My mom has nothing to do with this.
THANA
The number you are calling
is not available.
You still remember where my place is.
I thought you had forgotten about it.
You're in such a rush.
Finally,
you've come back to your done deal.
A done deal is great.
There's no fuss.
There's no running away.
Nok!
You!
I didn't do it!
It was an accident.
Don't make me feel guilty!
It wasn't my fault!
Don't come any closer!
I didn't know! I didn't do it!
It was an accident!
It's not my fault!
I've always thought
that the love between you and Thana
is such a beautiful thing.
But in reality,
love is terrible, isn't it?
No matter how good we are...
in the end,
we have to be evil when someone tries
to take something that we love.
Then, go ahead...
I'm right here right now.
Do what you have to do.
If you think I'm taking Thana
away from you...
do it, Dr. Nok.
LABORATORY - ANATOMY
-Her BP is dropping.
-Give her adrenaline.
Her BP is dropping.
This binds us together.
Wherever you go,
I will follow you.
Her BP's not going up, load the IV.
Load the IV.
We need to give her a defib,
get the defib ready.
Where's Dr. Varaporn?
Calm down.
Everything is going to be okay.
Many things are not what they seem to be,
Doctor.
You're thinking about Nok, aren't you?
I'm thinking about you, too.
Nok.
I miss you.
I'm on my way to be with you.
Like I said...
Wherever you go,
I'll follow you.
I know.
-We're bound together.
Wherever you go,
-I'll follow you.
When you're happy,
I'll be in front of you.
When you're down,
I'll be next to you.
When you're sad,
I'll be right behind you.
Yes.
But you can't come with me.
I have to go.
But you have to live on.
I want you to live on with this woman.
Or anyone.
As long as you are happy.
But why...
Why are you still around me?
You're still close to me
all the time.
Think carefully about it, Thana.
Why...
Why I'm still around you.
Why I'm still lingering,
never leaving.
Nok, no.
Nok, don't go.
Come back, Nok.
Wherever you go, I'll follow.
We drank half of each other's cup.
So I've been drinking
two types of coffee ever since.
For the last two years,
I visit this place once a year.
Now this binds us together.
Wherever you go,
I'll follow.
It looks like it's not just binding.
We're going to be stuck together.
Because of me?
Because of you.
You miss me.
You won't let go.
I've been trying to tell you,
but you just can't see it.
You can't feel it.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be sorry,
you did your best.
You took the greatest care of me.
I never thought
that the love I have for you...
had caused you pain.
Love makes us happy.
But we suffer because we miss each other.
We love each other just the same.
But we won't miss each other just as much.
We'll care for each other less.
I love you.
We did everything we could.
It's up to him now
when he will regain consciousness.
Don't give up hope.
Thana.
I think...
You have to choose.
Which one of us do you want to make happy?
Nok?
Or me?
If you don't wake up...
then Nok will be very happy.
But...
I will miss you.
I can never let you go.
It's true that...
I once told you
that I would step aside...
if you were alive.
But right now,
I'll never give up.
Wake up, Thana.
Wake up and be with me.
You have to wake up.
Because I...
can never lose you to someone else.
I can no longer take it.
I'm not letting you go.
You have to stay with me for a long time.
-How is he, Doctor?
-The patient is not likely to make it.
So, please, be prepared for the worst.
You have to help our father!
Don't let him die.
You have to help him, Doctor.
We did our best.
Please, help.
You're going to be all right.
Please, stay with me.
I'll be with you always.
Subtitle translation by