NETFLIX PRESENTS
Do you…
Do you believe
in such things as blessings?
Say, for instance,
wishing on your birthday,
or wishing someone safe travels,
or maybe even,
wishing Merry Christmas, or the like.
It may be just a thought
or perhaps even a reminder.
The fact is, involuntarily
and quite unconsciously,
we believe our will
can bring about good outcomes.
But do you know that your will can
actually change the outcomes of events?
Let's do an experiment now.
Please use your mind to move the rotation
of the Ferris wheel to the right.
Now to the left.
To the left.
To the right.
The direction of this moving train
can also be either moving forward
or backward based on your will.
Now I want you to try to control it
only with your mind.
Did you see that?
Our will is quietly shaping this world.
This is how blessings work.
My name is Li Ronan.
Six years ago,
I violated a terrifying taboo.
Back then, anyone fortunate enough
to come close to this matter,
was befallen with misfortunes
I can't explain.
MOM AND DAD.MP4
What deity are you talking about?
Did you watch what's on that camera?
Didn't the master instruct us
-not to listen, look, and ask anything?
-Master, master, please.
-And you kept asking questions.
-You have to believe everything he says?
And with this curse,
the more you understand it,
the more you'd be affected by its power.
I am Li Kuo-sheng.
No!
I actually made this video because,
I'm hoping that everyone can help
resolve my daughter's misfortune.
If you're willing to keep watching,
just in case you'll be able to help,
please look at this symbol until,
until you've memorized it.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
And if you can,
please recite this with me.
Doing it in your mind is fine too.
HOU-HO-XIU-YI, SI-SEI-WU-MA
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
Hi, Dodo.
Hello, Dodo.
Hi-lo, Dodo.
Uh, hello,
this here is a new camera I bought
I…
Oh, this is not bad at all.
It's better than I expected.
Here, good job.
Hey, congratulations.
You can finally bring Dodo home next week.
Thanks so much.
What are you filming?
Oh, it's nothing.
I just want to record the time
that Dodo is here.
And maybe turn it into a sort of diary
documenting her new life.
Aah.
Listen, I hope you don't think
I'm being nosy.
I know that you're Dodo's mother.
But if you don't pass
the evaluation period,
it's unlikely that the court
will grant you custody.
And besides, you still have that record
from your past.
Don't worry, I'll cooperate.
You better do that.
Oh, wait. How do I turn this on?
Oh, uh… you didn't switch it off before,
so you can just keep filming.
Why aren't you smiling?
Come on over here.
Take a peek, come on, see. There.
Okay, I can film from here.
Why don't you go in and play with them?
Give that to me.
Okay, I'll go in first then.
Yes, go ahead.
-Hello.
-Oh, hi, hi. Hello there.
Ronan?
Yeah, that's right, I'm Ronan.
Come on. Why don't you stand up,
-Dodo and greet your mom?
-Hi.
I'm Ming, hello.
Have you heard
of the New Life Diary before?
"New Life Diary"?
You see, um…
I'm just filming this as a memento.
Um, hey Dodo, say hi to your mom. Come on.
It's… It's okay. This…
This is for you.
Wow! Go ahead and say thank you, Dodo.
-Thank you, thank you so much.
-No…
Let me go over there.
This lighting is good.
So, we're recording
a "New Life Diary" for Dodo.
Yes, as a memento.
Ah, right.
-Okay. All right.
-Okay.
Why do you want to run a foster home?
I never really thought about it.
Well, perhaps…
Perhaps it's to um…
Mm…
Perhaps it's because I've always wanted
to know what being a father feels like.
-I see.
-Mm.
-Do you want to bring me there?
-Yes, that's right. Come on, let's go.
-Okay.
-Come on, come on.
Ms. Hsia, how much of this
will you be filming?
-So, you…
-Until the battery runs out.
Is that your camera, Ronan?
Yes, I just bought it.
Aah.
Um, Dodo.
Is this your favorite toy, huh?
Mm-hm.
-Wow. And what's its name?
-Mm.
Woofy.
-Sit properly, Dodo. Mm.
-Dodo, sit up.
Mommy, is it okay if we take
Woofy home with us?
Mm…
-Sure, yes.
-Hey, Dodo.
Listen to me.
Let's keep Woofy here, is that okay?
Because we have to keep him here
for the other kids.
But this is daddy's promise.
I promise, that we will keep looking
for new Woofies.
Okay?
Do we have a deal? Hmm?
So, do we have a deal?
Let's see it.
She's different.
Dodo is special.
She would call me Daddy.
The other kids don't do that.
SIX YEARS AGO
Miss Li Ronan.
I'd like to inform you
that for follow-up purposes,
we will be recording this session.
Sure.
FOOTAGE FROM DR. WU
NEW-EAST MENTAL INSTITUTION
Okay.
So, you think that this um…
"tunnel that you must not enter"
has brought misfortune
to those around you.
Is that right?
Yes.
Then based on what you're saying,
did the baby you were carrying…
die?
I gave her away.
I'm just a little curious.
Can you explain
why nothing has happened
to you and your baby?
Because I remember you mentioned before
that knowing too much
would bring certain misfortune.
Yes.
And you'll die if you answer your name.
Even just watching the video
filmed inside this tunnel
would kill you.
All I know about…
about this deity…
…is that the more you understand about it,
the more likely
you'll encounter misfortune.
Huh?
Ooh…
Come…
I feel embarrassed because…
-…there's so many of you.
-It's fine.
-It's okay.
-Don't worry.
Is the watermelon sweet?
Yes!
Is this a photo or video?
-Oh, is that it?
-The setting is wrong?
-You're moving to a new home.
-Be careful, all right.
The… the key.
-Hey, what's wrong?
-Do you have it, Ms. Li?
-Do you have the key?
-Yes, but I didn't lock it.
Bye-bye.
-Let me take a look.
-No, there's no need.
Oh, you're unbelievable. Really.
It's okay, it's here. It's in the car.
You're so forgetful.
It's okay, don't worry.
Always listen
to your mom, okay?
-Okay, I will.
-Okay. Very good.
-Are you ready? Here we go!
-Behave, okay.
-Bye!
-Goodbye!
-Drive safely.
-Okay.
Oh, hold on.
Hey.
What?
Aren't you forgetting something important?
Ms. Hsia, thank you so much. Thank you.
There's a bread store right over there.
Is there a kind of bread
that you like eating, huh?
Um…
Dodo, do you like eating bread?
I like everything.
Yeah?
You like everything? That's great.
Hello there. Today is the first day
in our new home.
Let me.
You have to flip it around, like so.
Can you see me now?
Yeah?
And this here is your room.
Ta-da!
Do you like it?
Mommy, why are we filming all of this?
Oh…
Because, you know Mommy used to be sick
and I couldn't look after you.
But now that I'm fine and well,
we can finally be together.
That's why I want to record this
so we can watch it together
when you grow up.
Okay?
Okay.
All right.
How about I teach you
how to write your name?
-Mm.
-Let's write a very fat name.
-Okay!
-Okay.
Chen…
Le…
Tung.
Okay. Come on.
Let's show it to the camera.
See this right here,
that's Dodo's full name.
-Read it with me. Okay?
-Mm.
"Chen Le-tung."
Okay, good. Let's read it again
using a fat voice.
"Chen Le-tung."
-"Chen Le-tung."
Wait here, okay? Don't go anywhere.
Did I touch your eye?
Did I? Does it hurt?
Yes, that's right, look up.
What's this?
Today is the very first day of Dodo
staying in our new home.
She just fell asleep.
She smiled at me today.
So, I feel like
I must have done pretty well.
Well, at least I hope I did.
Hmm?
Is anybody there?
Dodo.
Dodo?
Dodo!
Chen Le-tung.
Dodo.
Do…
Chen Le-tung…
Chen Le-tung.
Dodo!
Dodo! Dodo.
Dodo, Dodo, what's the matter?
Dodo, Dodo, look at me.
Dodo. Look at me, Dodo!
Dodo!
Dodo, it's okay. I'm here, Dodo.
Mommy's here, you're safe.
It's all right, I'm here.
GHOST BUSTERS (SIX YEARS AGO)
What are you doing?
You look so ugly.
Up yours. Hmm.
45% COMPLETE
STRANGE MURMURS CHANNEL
Hi and welcome
to the Strange Murmurs Channel.
I'm Yuan.
Um… my name is Ronan.
He's Dom, an NTU student.
He's Dom.
And we are now driving
on a strange mountain.
And currently,
there is no phone signal at all.
How can the "tunnel you must
not enter" have a phone signal?
Are you serious?
Okay then.
In this episode, we, the Ghost Busters,
will take all of you to see,
the tunnel that has no phone signal
at all and must not be entered.
So, loyal viewers.
Are you ready
to bust this superstition with us?
-Go!
Aah!
-What's the matter?
-What happened?
Fuck!
Fuck, what the hell is this?
Huh?
Do you see it?
Oh, fuck.
What the hell is this?
What is this?
A Buddha statue?
Looks like it.
What did you say Granduncle
and the others worship?
Uh… I think they worship…
A Mother-Buddha or celestial being
or something. I don't really know.
Mother-Buddha? It's female?
What's wrong?
-Are you okay?
-She's possessed.
Has it started?
-Shut up.
-Has it started so soon?
-Are you okay?
-Hey viewers, take a look!
She's being possessed live on camera.
-Tell us how you feel.
-You're so annoying!
Fuck! That's a lot.
-Ooh.
-Careful, bro.
Don't worry, it's fine.
Is that Granduncle?
Yeah.
A-Dom, A-Yuan.
-Granduncle.
-Long time no see. You're both so big now.
-This isn't easy to find, right?
-Yeah, very difficult.
And this is?
She's not from our family, right?
No, she's not.
-A-Yuan.
-Hmm?
What are you filming?
Oh, no, nothing, it's a toy.
See, I just bought it.
I might not have been
clear with you on the phone.
This is a private family ritual.
We do not allow outsiders to participate.
But Granduncle, she's not an outsider.
She's his girlfriend.
-Yes, that's right.
-I'm his girlfriend.
Ah, miss. Do you know how to drive?
Maybe you can just come back
after we're finished.
-Huh?
-What do you mean?
I've never driven alone before.
You can work it out amongst yourselves.
You want her to drive down by herself,
Granduncle?
-Uh, hey, wait. Uh…
-Who's this old woman?
What is she doing?
Why does she keep staring at me?
-I don't know. Who is she?
-What's going on right now?
Who is she?
I told you to ask,
but you wouldn't. Now, look.
How would I know?
Granduncle.
Ah, miss, if you don't mind.
Can we take a look at your hand?
-Her hand?
-My hand?
-You must be tired after all that driving.
-I'm exhausted.
Go take a shower. It's your first time.
You can worship first.
So early?
Didn't you say we'll do it
in the middle of the night?
We have to pray again later.
-A-Dom, listen.
-Yeah?
The one who felt
your girlfriend's hand just now
is the Chen family's
most senior Great-aunt.
Aah…
-I'm sorry.
-She always going on
about Su-e's two sons.
-Great-aunt is over there.
-Okay.
Great-aunt.
These are Su-e's sons.
The most
handsome ones in the Chen family.
-How are you, Great-aunt?
-Greet your Great-aunt.
A-Yuan, what are you doing?
What is there to film at home?
Oh, it's nothing.
Granduncle,
isn't that a tunnel over there?
Ah, you. Listen to me.
We're here to worship, not play around.
-Hey, which brand is this, huh?
-Hmm?
It's so amazing.
What do you mean?
Even my nose looks sharper.
All done.
What's it like to have your daughter back?
Pretty good. It's all going well.
Hey. What are these?
Bugs?
Will you stop messing around?
Come here and get to work.
There are bugs here.
Look, they're all over.
What are you…
Hey. The bag!
They're inside the bag.
That's so gross.
Oh, gross.
-It's on your shirt!
-Where is it? Where is it!
Right there, do you see it?
Oh, no. You crushed it.
-Hello?
-That's dirty. How gross!
Yes, right, this is she.
Um…
Oh, hi. Hello, ma'am.
-Where? Where does it hurt?
-Dodo.
-Come on, tell me.
-Come out.
-Okay, Dodo? Come, apologize to him.
-Chang Che-wei, what's the matter?
-Apply some medicine for him, okay?
-It's okay. It's okay, it's fine now.
-Let's put medicine on it.
-Come on, Dodo.
Dodo.
Come on.
Oh dear, watch your head. Where's her mom?
-Hey, you're really leaving?
-Okay, sure. Don't worry.
-Thanks. Have you seen my keys?
-Did you tell Ms. Sung?
How would I know where your keys are?
-You should at least inform her.
-Help me out, okay? Cover for me, please.
-Thank you. Thanks.
-Help you with what?
-Thanks.
-Hey, Ronan!
Stop messing around!
It's all right, don't worry.
She's in the car with me.
We're heading home now.
Hey, drive safely, okay?
I know you're very busy.
And if Dodo needs anything,
make sure you let me know. Okay?
I hate going to kindergarten.
Why is that?
Because Chang Che-wei in my class
keeps teasing me.
Why does he keep teasing you?
He says that I'm crazy.
Crazy?
I heard Dodo
bit someone at school.
How could this happen?
She never did that
at the foster home or our center.
I find this rather strange.
Are you in some kind of trouble?
You're ridiculous.
How could you leave
without informing the client?
Did you know that Ms. Sung
had to do her own makeup today?
Listen, she's looking for you now.
You're on your own.
I've recovered. I'm not scared anymore.
One, two, three.
As long as I don't worry,
there's no need to worry.
Yes. Right.
I have long recovered.
Amitābha. Amitābha.
Please deliver me from evil.
-Ami…
-Start cleaning.
Please move the base
to a new location to start.
Come down!
Mommy!
-What is it, Dodo?
-There's a baddie.
-Who? You said…
-Up there.
Nothing's there.
Where's… where's the baddie?
It's right up there! Tell it to come down.
Okay.
All right, hang on, okay?
Baddie!
Come down. Hurry up, baddie.
You have to lead it out
by the hand.
Okay. Well…
Have I got its hand now?
Higher.
What about now?
Higher. A bit higher.
Oh, have I got its hand now, huh?
Have I?
Huh?
You got it.
Okay.
Then…
We're going now. Okay?
Baddie?
Let's go out and not stay in Dodo's room.
Okay?
We're going out now.
Come down!
Dodo, what are you doing?
CHIN CHIN KINDERGARTEN
Slow down.
Take care, don't fall. Careful.
Actually,
Dodo is very distracted in class.
-Ooh.
-She's not
really affecting the other students.
But she has this thing where she stares
at the ceiling and talks to herself.
Her classmate said,
that your daughter told them
that she saw a faceless baddie--
Principal, I'm sorry. You see…
Dodo told me something yesterday.
She said…
Kids, do you like the new toys we have?
-Yes.
-Right, listen.
Dodo's mom gave them to us.
We have to have manners.
So, what do we say to Dodo's mom?
Thank you!
Chen Dodo,
I promise that
I won't call you crazy anymore.
From now on,
I hope that we become good friends again
because your mom is very cool.
I hope that you stay
good friends with Dodo, okay?
Okay.
CHIN CHIN KINDERGARTEN
Come on. Come on.
Try and catch up with me.
Let's play hide and seek.
Ready?
Three, two, one. Run!
Dodo, where are you going to hide?
Where are you hiding?
Dodo?
Dodo.
What are you doing?
I'm playing with my toys.
Ooh.
Well, if you're playing with them,
then why are these dolls covered, huh?
Because they don't want to see the baddie.
Listen to Mommy, okay?
You know, I used to see baddies too.
-Really, you did?
-Mm-hm.
If you keep thinking about the monsters,
the monsters will surely go
and live inside your head.
Oh, no!
Doctor, what should I do then?
I'm so scared.
Okay then, let Dr. Bunny tell you how.
Listen, if you're feeling scared,
all you have to do is think about
your three favorite things
in the whole world.
Then, close your eyes
and then say them out loud.
And after that,
you won't be scared anymore.
I like three… pineapples.
Oh, is that so?
Pineapple is your favorite?
How about me, don't you like me anymore?
Don't you like me, Dodo?
I like you too, bunny.
What about me?
Huh?
-Pineapple, bunny.
Just think about these from now on
whenever you're scared.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay, this is the last time.
Then straight to bed after. Hmm?
If you don't go to sleep…
…the monster will come and find you!
Ooh, the monster will tickle…
…you like this!
-Mommy.
-Hmm?
Did you throw me away,
because you were also
scared of monsters, like me?
Mommy's…
Mommy's not scared anymore.
Mm.
Go to sleep.
LI RONAN
What is your name?
Give it to me.
HOU-HO-XIU-YI, SI-SEI-WU-MA
Come.
Bow.
You must return
to worship Mother-Buddha every ten years.
After offering up your real name,
remember, you cannot use it here anymore.
You mustn't even think it in your mind.
Mother-Buddha is happy.
Once the little girl growing in your tummy
has a name, you must offer it
to Mother-Buddha too.
Understand?
What?
Come on, viewers,
take a look at this.
This dinner was prepared
by the great Chen clan.
Let's try some now.
Fuck.
Come and eat.
-Why aren't you eating?
-Huh?
Have some.
I'm not hungry.
I think it's pretty good, come and try it.
Hey, Ronan. Want to come and eat?
I'm already eating.
What's this?
You got to be kidding me.
Come on, we're ghostbusters.
Don't tell me you actually believe
that little girl?
Why, who said anyone's believing it?
She believes it!
-She's just feeling unwell.
-She does! Look, she's so nervous, okay?
-Hey, bro, listen to me.
-Can you…
-She's not possessed.
-…please cut it out?
She's pregnant.
Mind your own business.
I knew it.
Dear viewers.
Take a good look.
This here is a playboy.
This is the face of a playboy.
-Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
I'm okay.
Fuck, stop being lovey-dovey.
Hurry up! What are you doing?
It's going to be over soon.
-Let's go.
-Oh.
-I'm sorry.
-Shh, shh. Go out, just go.
Slowly.
-Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
-What are they worshipping?
-Hou-ho-xiu-yi…
-si-sei-wu-ma.
-How strange.
Over there, the little girl.
She's over there.
Good, film her.
This is so weird.
-Fuck.
-What?
I don't know, wait. Just wait.
She knows. Shit!
Did you three sneak out to play?
Yes.
Over there?
Do you want to go somewhere fun?
-Where?
-Sure.
Little girl, listen.
It looks super fun over there.
Isn't there a tunnel?
You can't go in there.
-Why?
-Where are we going?
Hey. Hey, hey, wait! Little girl.
You can't come in.
She can, but why can't I?
I'm sorry, but you just can't.
Oh, that's fine, it's okay.
What are you doing?
Getting this. I can film with this.
Wait, for me here.
Huh?
Wait…
Where are you going, little girl?
What is this?
Come here.
Look.
Wait, what is that?
Feed it.
What, but…
This… this is hair.
Feed it.
Okay, hold on.
I'm throwing it in now.
GHOST BUSTERS WERE HERE
Hurry up, please. Come on.
Here, over here.
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
Hou-ho-xiu…
What happened to your ear, huh?
Mother-Buddha took it.
What does that mean?
You see, I was chosen by the gods,
so Mother-Buddha took my flesh
in order to bless everyone.
Hou-ho-xiu-yi,
si-sei-wu-ma.
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
What are you doing?
Don't you know that
you can't come in here?
-One, two, three!
Whoo!
Awesome!
Today is Dodo's birthday.
Wow, why do you keep getting shorter, huh?
Wow! Amazing!
-Mom, come here.
-Hmm?
Look at him.
You like him?
It's Woofy.
That's Woofy? Is he Woofy?
Woofy.
Woofy?
Look at Woofy.
Please tell me, Mommy,
when can we bring Woofy home?
Well…
We'll bring him home
when you're all grown up
and can look after him.
Otherwise, no one will take care of him.
Okay?
Come on, have some, okay?
Hmm? Aah.
Aah…
Is it delicious?
It's okay.
Hey little girl, what are you filming?
It's a birthday video.
-Thank you.
-Why don't we…
I have some questions about the house.
Okay, sure. Dodo, wait for me here.
I'll go inside and I'll be right back.
Okay? Hmm?
Well, the Buddha statues
on the top floor…
Do you still want them?
I think they're kind of scary.
Uh…
I'll get someone to take care of that.
Okay. I think some buyers would, you know…
Some would care about these things, yes.
Hmm?
Where should I go?
Huh? What is it?
Yes.
Is it down there?
And then what?
Okay.
Now, what do I do?
Where do I go?
Yes?
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
Dodo!
Chen Le-tung, what are you doing?
Didn't I tell you
to stay right there, Dodo?
I told you to wait.
Why didn't you listen to me? Why?
Do… Dodo!
Dodo, what's the matter? Dodo!
She was fine
when I saw her a few days ago.
What the doctor means is…
that Dodo's hemiparesis
might be brain-induced?
Oh, by the way…
Here. Take it.
You see, a few days ago,
Ms. Hsia got this for Dodo,
it's from the temple.
Dodo's name is inside it.
-And hopefully, it will keep her safe.
-I don't want it.
Why…
Why did you give me that?
I… I didn't say I wanted it.
Now, the teacher
is using a different tool,
so we can make changes
and adjustments to the shape.
And right now, as you can see him doing,
the teacher is using the digging
and kneading method.
Look at his technique carefully.
In order for him to change the shape,
the raw material must be very soft.
That means the temperature
must be very high.
So, what would happen
if the temperature drops?
Obviously, the work will be hard,
and there's no way
to shape the raw material.
In the process of creation,
you must also pay close attention to…
What? But we're already here.
It doesn't matter.
Go home tomorrow morning.
Granduncle, but it's so far from here.
Granduncle!
Shit, they locked the door.
-Fuck, seriously?
-I think they locked us in.
Hey!
-Let us out!
-Why did you lock the door?
Hey!
Do you have any tools?
-Oh, shit.
-Maybe there's something here we can use?
Got it?
I think so.
Try it.
It's open! Okay, come on, let's go.
-Hey, wait.
-I can't believe they locked us in.
-Shit.
-Hey, Yuan.
What?
Look at her.
How are you feeling? Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
-See, she's okay.
Are you sure?
I'm not sure where the little girl went.
Let's take a look.
Yes, let's check on her. Hurry, come on.
Okay. Dear viewers.
The Ghost Busters are heading
to the forbidden place.
The infamous place you must not go to.
Film the barrier talisman.
Film it quickly.
Yeah. Yeah, that's it.
Wow! Look at this barrier talisman.
It's terrifying.
Let's go.
Hey. What's wrong now?
Oh.
Dear viewers.
Up next,
the moment you've been waiting for.
We'll be heading into
the Chen clan's
"tunnel you must not enter."
Hey.
Are you really pregnant?
What's the matter? Are you scared?
No, I'm not scared.
What else could it be?
Let's name her Chen Le-tung.
-What?
-Fuck!
You're being lovey-dovey again.
-No, we're not.
-Then what are you doing?
She's not feeling well.
-You idiots, hurry up!
-Okay!
-Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
-What? What's wrong?
-What is it?
-Turn off the flashlight. Hurry!
-What?
-Turn it off first. Hurry.
Come on. Hurry this way. Follow me.
Turn off the flashlight.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
I'm turning it off. It's off.
-Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
-Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei--
I watched it.
What exactly are you afraid of?
Are you afraid of not being forgiven?
Or are you afraid that
even you can't forgive yourself?
One, two, three, go.
It's okay.
Are you afraid of this curse,
or that you're going crazy again?
Don't think.
Don't think about anything, then I'll win.
Yes, I just need to do it.
Don't think.
Don't think. Don't think.
Some people see a fallen chair
and say it's a ghost.
What the hell?
You told me you're not afraid
of monsters anymore.
You said so yourself!
But others would see
a fallen chair and say that it's…
a miracle from God.
Dodo.
Don't be scared, okay?
The world is
as you choose to see it.
I can't give you an answer.
Oh, gosh. This head looks so tasty.
How you view the world
can truly bring about tiny changes to it.
This is very important.
I have a document here for you to sign.
It mainly says that the court
has revoked your custody rights.
Go ahead. Just sign here.
-We need your cooperation here.
-No, I cannot sign it.
Please consider this carefully,
this is a notice from the court.
You have no choice on the matter.
You are just being notified.
I do not know
if ghosts or gods
really do exist.
But what I am certain of
is that you decide
how your world is shaped.
Dodo. Listen,
I'm going up to get something.
I'll be back real quick.
Where are we going, Mommy?
-Do you trust your Mommy?
-Mm.
Good.
Dodo?
Hi, Dodo.
Open this window for daddy.
Dodo.
Where's your mom?
My mom went upstairs.
Your mom is upstairs?
Did your mom…
Did your mom say where you're going?
Dodo.
Do you want to go back to my place?
Yes, dad.
Yes? Okay, then let's go back home.
What's the matter?
If we go, then what about Mom?
Open the door. Hurry, please.
Open up! Come on!
Please!
Open the door.
Open the door!
Get in. Get in!
She's over there.
That's her. That's her!
Stay there!
-Wait, miss!
-Stop the car.
-Pull over! Hurry to the front.
-Please stop!
-Miss, please!
-Stop the car!
Stop!
Stop the car! Hey!
Hey! Wait!
Hurry, hurry, hurry! Over here.
What, what is it?
-Fuck, it's that little girl.
-What's going on?
-Little girl?
-Let's take her down first.
Little girl.
-Little girl, wake up.
-Dear viewers.
This must be the Chen family's
"tunnel that you must not enter."
HOU-HO-XIU-YI
Yes, this must be it.
How is she?
A pig's head.
There's a goat.
Little girl,
can you hear my voice?
Okay, this is it. Let's go in.
-Yuan. Let's forget it.
-What?
-Huh?
-I have a bad feeling about this.
-How many times are you going to do this?
-Should we…
-take her down to see a doctor first.
-Shit! Are you insane?
Fuck, motherfucker!
-Hey.
-You do this every time.
-Ronan's not feeling well. Cut it out.
-Fuck!
-Are you stupid? Fucking asshole.
-Yuan.
Chen Chen-yuan!
Did you hear something?
What's that sound?
Is that a child crying?
Yuan.
Are you sure you want to go in?
But wait…
…what if there are
other children in there?
-Let's go.
-Hey.
What?
Stay here and look after her.
-I'm going in with Yuan.
-But, what if…
Let's go.
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
THE PLACE YOU MUST NOT ENTER
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
Hey!
What's going on?
Dom!
Where are you going? Yuan!
Yuan!
Where are you going?
Chen Chen-yuan!
Dom.
What should I do?
Huh?
Don't ask.
Don't ask!
Yuan.
Don't ask.
So, itchy. My teeth.
-My teeth.
-Yuan…
My teeth!
Yuan!
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
Don't ask!
How much further is the temple?
It should be close.
I haven't been there for a long time.
What is that?
Did you see it?
Is that a person?
How is this possible?
Hey.
What's going on?
How could this happen?
Something's wrong.
What is it?
What are you doing?
It's nothing.
A shocking gas explosion
happened at a psychiatric treatment clinic
in Yuexiang Road Section 3.
In the toilet…
…hanging corpse.
The victim is the person-in-charge,
Dr. Wu Yu-ching.
The cause of the fire remains unclear…
Come on, start!
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
Mommy, I'm scared.
-Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
It's okay. It's okay.
VANQUISH DEMONS, CATCH GHOSTS,
ELIMINATE EVIL SPIRITS
What should come will come.
Such as fate.
What exactly is in the camera?
You have to remember
and this is important.
Don't let the child eat anything
for seven days straight.
Seven days!
But how can a child not eat for so long?
The master and I are putting
our lives on the line here.
If you can't do that,
let's just end this right now
and stop this.
We have to set up the altar.
Remember you must not let her eat.
Come back in seven days.
Could you please tell me,
how does it feel
to raise a child into adulthood?
As you know, it's a foster home. So…
children, they tend to come and go.
I've never really raised a child
into an adult, so…
I want to know the answer to that too.
What it feels like
to raise a child into adulthood.
Dodo.
Tell me, you like your Mommy, huh?
Mm.
But don't you think
that she's very strange?
Yes, but she's still my Mommy.
Ming,
don't you have your own children?
Let's skip this question.
Okay.
Let's talk about Dodo.
I TOOK THE VIDEO CAMERA,
I'LL FIND OUT WHAT REALLY HAPPENED
I WANT TO KNOW
HOW IT FEELS LIKE TO BE A REAL DAD
Dodo.
Have you flown a kite before?
Not yet.
Sir.
How much is this kite at the front?
Oh, that's not for sale.
A customer ordered it.
The bubble blower is better, yeah.
She can blow on it while sitting down.
She's in a wheelchair anyway.
-Hmm, no, that's okay.
-The bubble blower is nice.
-No, it's fine.
-Okay.
Mommy,
it's bad to steal things, right?
We'll return it later
so we won't be bad. Hmm?
I hope she's happy
when she remembers our time together.
Dodo?
Huh?
Why are you all sweaty?
Do you feel really hot?
Let's go.
-Bunny.
-Come on, bunny.
We're almost at the hospital. Okay?
Hold on a little longer.
Hello, is anybody there?
LAI HSIEN-CHUNG'S CLINIC
Is there anybody there?
Come on…
Hang on. Hang on, hang on!
Please take a look at her.
It won't take long, it will be very quick.
Oh, dear! She needs an injection.
The antipyretic will have side effects
on an empty stomach.
Feed her then come back.
But doctor… must she really eat?
She can't be injected with it otherwise.
Don't you get it?
-Hurry up! Hurry!
-Okay.
I'll wait for you. Move.
Okay, okay.
HOW TO ADMINISTER A DRIP?
HOW TO ADMINISTER A DRIP AT HOME?
INTRAVENOUS METHOD
Today marks the third day.
Her legs have become wrinkly.
I think they're atrophying.
I wonder if I hadn't brought her home,
would she still turn out this way?
I'm so hungry.
Let's get rid of this, okay?
-Mm.
-I'll take it out.
On my birthday…
We had such a big cake.
Is this for Mommy?
Mm.
Then I'll eat it.
Don't cry.
All you need to do is
think of your three favorite things
and you won't be scared anymore.
Mm.
Keep the change.
Here.
Ah.
Mmm.
It's so sweet.
What do I do?
THE VIDEO CLIP OF THE TUNNEL
This video camera isn't broken,
the file was just destroyed.
Then I found a repairing software
on an international website.
But the repair progress
of the tunnel clip keeps failing.
This is strange
but the more of this video I watch…
…the more unwell I feel.
Could this be a curse?
So…
Okay, the hand gesture they do
is like a modified version
of Bafangtian in Tantric Buddhism.
The difference is
if Bafangtian gesture means
to "collect blessing."
This one's ending gesture
is completely in the opposite direction.
So, what does it mean?
To spread…
Spread it?
In this image
captured on the video,
there are similar temples all around it.
There's a goat on top of that temple.
So, I asked
a few of my theologian friends.
And they told me.
This kind of twisted text
looks like a Brahmic script
used to record Buddhist scriptures
in ancient India.
Then I researched online later on.
SHI KONG-YUN
There's a Tantric Buddhist monk in Yunnan
who lives in seclusion.
He's one of the last remaining people
who can translate
ancient Buddhist scriptures.
So…
I'm thinking that if I can go there
and find him,
maybe I'll get an answer.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you're arriving at
Xishuangbanna Gasa International Airport.
This should be the place.
I think he's telling me
to wait right here.
Listen carefully,
I've forwarded you the video
of the Yunnan monk.
It explains the origins of the disciples
and the meaning
of… of the incantation.
The…
The video clip of the tunnel
has finally been repaired.
But I won't send it to you anymore.
I'm sorry.
I was the one who reported your inadequacy
to the Social Affairs Bureau.
Because I didn't trust you.
I also thought it was unfair to me.
I'm sorry.
If something untoward happens to me,
I hope you can let Dodo know that,
that even though I can never have…
my very own children biologically…
I'm very happy that…
Dodo was willing to call me Dad.
Hsieh Chi-ming.
Hsieh…
FROM MING ATTACHMENT:
INSIDE THE TUNNEL
Ouch, it hurts…
What hurts?
My hand…
Your hand?
Let me see.
Come on.
Spit out the pineapple, okay?
Okay, here we go.
Okay, very good.
One more time. One more time, okay?
One more time, come on.
One, two, three.
Master Ching!
Master Ching.
Madam Ching!
Master Ching…
Did you let the child eat?
Madam Ching.
Listen, child.
Let me tell you.
When your mother was pregnant with you,
she was going to offer you to the gods.
Dodo.
Dodo!
Dodo…
Do you…
Do you believe in such things
as blessings?
My name is Li Ronan.
Six years ago,
I violated a terrifying taboo.
HOU-HO-XIU-YI, SI-SEI-WU-MA
Help me.
Please recite this with me.
Doing it in your mind is fine too.
HOU-HO-XIU-YI, SI-SEI-WU-MA
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma is--
The Yunnan monk says that,
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma
is actually an ancient religious blessing.
This religion spread
from Southeast Asia to Yunnan,
and to where Dom's family is.
The deity worshiped by their ancestors
is called Dahei Mother-Buddha.
It's a malicious deity.
So…
they've inherited bad karma
from generation to generation.
They must use this incantation
in order to receive blessings.
Therefore, if a lot of people chanted,
the power of blessing will be gathered
and it will protect
the person who chants it.
The child's breathing and pulse
have stabilized for now.
That's good news regarding her condition.
But we noticed that
she has severe dehydration
and she suffers from malnutrition.
Bacterial infection has already spread
across her entire body.
I am arranging for her
to be monitored further in the ICU.
-Thank you, doctor.
-But Ms. Li,
things are far from being good.
You need to be prepared for the worst.
INSIDE THE TUNNEL.MOV
PLAY
A naked girl around junior high age
was discovered lying naked
in an empty lot beside a hospital
shown to be wearing
only her undergarments.
What's strange is that runes
were written all over her body.
Dodo, Mommy's here.
Open your eyes and look at me, okay?
Dodo?
Right now, she's still unconscious.
So, now… now what? What do we do?
What now?
Please, calm down.
She's not in a good condition,
but we will continue monitoring her.
By the way, didn't she mention
something earlier?
Something like pineapple bun…
Pineapple bunny.
It's probably a doll.
-Mommy.
-Hmm?
Did you throw me away
because you were also
scared of monsters, like me?
Mommy's…
Mommy's not scared anymore.
I'm about to show you
the video when we violated
the taboo six years ago.
This way.
-Hey, Yuan. Yuan!
-Hmm?
Look at this.
Hey, don't touch it.
I'll just take a look.
MISFORTUNE AND BLESSING
DEPEND ON EACH OTHER
The sound is coming from there.
Hey, there's a mirror over there.
Hey, watch your step.
There are so many mirrors here too.
Let's keep going.
Is that a door?
I don't know.
What?
I'm looking.
Did you hear that?
Let's move it aside.
SI-SEI-WU-MA
Careful.
There's another mirror behind it.
Let's go.
Are we going in?
Look at this.
I filmed the same thing earlier.
Hair.
Hey.
Don't touch it.
There's another one.
Hey, come over here.
What the hell is this?
-Teeth.
-Huh?
Hey, listen.
You hear that?
That sound.
Take a look over there.
There.
Hey.
Forget about it. Let's go back.
It's okay.
Is anything there?
If not, let's go.
What are you doing?
-The sound.
-What are you doing?
I'll uncover it. Hold this for me.
Hurry up.
Dom.
What is it, Dom?
What's my name?
Dom.
Chen Li-tung!
Hey!
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Hey!
Chen Li-tung, that's enough!
What are you doing?
Don't scare me like this.
Don't scare me! What are you doing?
Hurry! Let's get out of here!
Don't scare me! Hurry, let's go!
Dom! Get up, hurry!
Let's go!
Dom, let's go!
Dom, come on. Let's go!
Let's go!
Dom. Dom!
Dom!
No!
Dom?
Dom.
Where are you, Dom?
Dom?
Huh?
Dom, what are you doing?
Dom?
Dom!
Dom.
Help!
They say that
the moment you set your eyes on your child
you will instantly feel like a mother.
But I didn't.
I was just so scared.
I'm still scared now.
I don't know if I'm very selfish.
CHEN LE-TUNG
I don't know if I only want
to be good to you
because of the guilt I'm feeling.
I don't even know how it was
that I fell in love with you.
Did I fall in love with you
while watching you sleep?
Or was it when you were crying?
Is that love?
You didn't have a choice, right?
You could have been in a better place.
You could've been fine.
Forgive me.
Dodo.
I'm sorry.
Mommy won't hurt you anymore.
Listen, if you wake up,
can you promise me…
to forget your name?
And forget me.
From now on,
if you're happy,
then laugh out loud.
And when you walk,
walk properly with big, big strides.
And if ever you see food that you like,
take big, big mouthfuls and grow plump.
Promise Mom.
When you open your eyes every day,
you have to be happier than others.
GHOST BUSTERS WERE HERE
Do you still remember the incantation?
And if you can, please,
recite it with me in your mind again.
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
Look.
This is the full translation
from the Yunnan monk.
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma.
Forgive me.
I lied to you.
If you're not willing to keep watching,
then do this. Please think
of your three favorite things.
From now on,
please close your eyes.
Actually, "Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma",
the incantation,
is not a blessing.
It's a Minnan dialect saying that
"misfortune and blessing
depend on one another,
death and life lies in the name."
Reciting it means,
"I wish to share in this curse
and offer up my name."
As for the symbol,
it's a spell for diffusing
Mother-Buddha's curse onto strangers.
The more people bearing the curse,
the more diluted it becomes.
The deeper you look,
the heavier the burden.
The Mother-Buddha's face
is the heart of the curse.
That's why they cover it up
and never look at it.
Ms. Li,
what the master means is that.
Hou-ho-xiu-yi, si-sei-wu-ma--
I'm sorry.
I'm aware that some things
should not be seen.
But this is really the only way
I can save my daughter.
If I can manipulate more people
to see this video and this symbol,
then perhaps her curse will be lessened.
If possible,
I really wish that you weren't my child.
Because I'm not a good mother.
Because…
I really…
really wish you can open
your eyes every day.
And be very happy.
What is your name?
Our beautiful home is so far away.
But it's okay. We can catch a bus.
But there are no buses heading
to our castle.
Our castle was blown away by bubbles.
Pretty bubbles!