[soft, eerie music]
[all audio in this movie
is spoken in Thai]
[drums and cymbals add to
continuing eerie music]
[distant animal screeches]
Jerd, it's getting dark.
We're almost there, Noi.
[distant animal screeches]
[chorus of birds chirping warning calls]
[eerie music continues]
[menacing music]
[hushed] Guys, have you heard
what people are saying?
There's a chest in this house
that holds... Nual's spirit.
She guards the forest
and refuses to go away.
Whoever comes here at night...
won't be able to leave.
[single drumbeat sounds,
audio is abruptly muted]
[laughs]
You chicken! It's just a story!
Noi, you look so pale!
If you're so scared, you can leave.
How about you two?
[encouraging murmuring]
[all]
Black one out!
[Jerd]
It's Ting!
[laughter]
Me again!
Poor you. Now close your eyes and count.
[eerie music]
One, two, three, four, five...
Noi, let's hide upstairs.
She won't find us there.
No.
Come on!
[Ting]
I'm coming to find you!
[menacing music]
[door creaks]
You go hide in that corner.
I'm going to be in that room.
If Ting comes for me,
you sneak behind and tag her.
Is it a good idea to split up?
My dad gave me this protective amulet.
You keep it.
Let's go.
[menacing music]
-[menacing music]
-[ghostly hissing]
[wood creaks]
[menacing music ends]
[ghostly hissing]
[menacing music]
[eerie music]
[eerie music fades]
[eerie theme plays on piano]
[violin joins piano playing eerie theme]
[birds chirp outside]
[man]
Sai!
Hi Jerd, Yam, Toh!
Leave the fish at my house.
Do you know when the school will reopen?
We'll have to wait
until the war in Bangkok ends.
But it's great not having to go to school!
People are being killed and hurt.
It's no joke.
Let's go to the field.
There won't be any patients today.
Please, Sai.
Here!
-Jerd!
-Let's go.
C'mon!
Jerd, stop!
Aren't you bored?
[shouting]
Doctor Metta!
Mon!
No one's here.
They must have been called up
for an emergency.
I heard Bangkok got bombed pretty bad
last night.
If it weren't for my dad,
I'd like to go there.
-Aren't you afraid of getting killed?
-No.
I'd get to be a soldier
and shoot at enemies.
Must be cool!
Nurse! Stop!
[mimics gunfire]
Go play with me now!
Jerd!
Sai, no one's coming. Let's go outside.
No. Someone might need help.
But if you don't go,
someone will get hurt for real.
Ouch!
Nurse, help me.
Jerd!
I'll cut your fingers off.
Please?
No.
[woman]
Doctor! Are you here?
See?
Coming!
[boy's mother]
Just a little bit more.
Sai...
I heard
a Krasue ate your neighbor Dang's hens.
I don't know.
Last night Mai and his friends
went out to hunt rats.
They saw a floating light.
[boy's mother]
I knew it!
You have to take precautions.
How?
Close all doors and windows at night.
Don't hang your laundry outside.
The Krasue like to wipe their mouths
on them.
If I really were a Krasue,
you'd be dead by now.
[boy's father] If you were a Krasue,
I'd blow your head off.
[boy's mother]
Tough talking, eh?
[eerie music]
-Sai!
-Hmm?
Don't you feel weird
seeing these things every day?
[Sai]
Are you scared?
A bit.
I can't believe you've become a scary-cat.
But it's gross.
I kind of miss Noi.
I don't know how he's doing now.
[sad theme plays on violin]
[boy]
Sai!
I'll be out on patrol tonight.
Because of the Krasue, right?
Who told you that?
Aunt Kamlai. I treated her son today.
She said Dang's hens
were eaten by a Krasue.
But no one has seen it in a long time.
I can't be certain...
You stay with Grandma.
Make sure to lock all doors and windows.
I'll get going.
Be careful.
Ouch! Let's go in.
Evening, Grandma.
-Hi.
-Yes, Grandma.
Here!
Jerd asked me to bring plum mangoes
for you.
Thanks.
I stopped by his house.
How are you, Dum?
[laughs gently]
You cutie.
Well, Jerd is kind of cute, too.
Good-looking and rich...
Don't you like him even a little?
He's head over heels in love with you.
I heard he's following you around
every day.
He just keeps me company.
[mms skeptically]
Why are you moving your legs? Huh?
You're blushing?
[laughs]
No.
All right.
[hushed] When you two finally do it,
let me be the first to know.
Ting!
-What?
-What are you saying?
All right, I'm leaving.
-Maybe I should eat the plum mango.
-Just leave already.
Make sure to eat some.
Go home safely.
[Ting]
See you.
[menacing music]
-[ghostly hissing]
-[flies buzzing]
[menacing music continues]
[inhuman rasping]
[gasps]
[eerie music]
[panicked gasp]
[eerie music continues]
Here. Pandan water.
Sai.
Sai. Let's go.
Sai!
Hmm?
You spaced out.
Jerd.
Come with me to the forest.
-[eerie music continues]
-[cicadas crying]
[flies buzzing]
Sai, wait.
We should turn back.
But we're nearly there.
It's dangerous.
If you're scared, you can go back first.
I'm not scared, I'm just worried.
[menacing music]
[menacing music continues]
[hushed]
Sai?
Noi!
[menacing music fades]
Sai!
Jerd!
Noi!
[approaching footsteps]
[menacing music]
We've come from Salaya,
where the Krasue have wreaked havoc.
In the beginning...
they ate all the chickens and ducks
until there were none left.
Then, the cows and buffaloes.
But the villagers were too slow
to take extreme measures.
So...
it began to spread.
That was when pandemonium struck.
Spread? How?
Once the Mother Krasue
spits in some water...
if a girl drinks it,
she'll turn into... another Krasue.
If it's a man,
he'll be in terrible pain from the poison.
When he can no longer endure it and dies,
the Krasue will devour his guts.
The folks were scared
and already abandoned the village.
Why should I believe any of this?
Pai. Plaew.
These are some of the Krasue
we have put down.
We don't want anything more
than a place to stay.
In exchange,
we'll hunt the demons down for you.
[man]
That sounds good, Chief.
[downbeat music plays]
Who told you there was a Krasue here?
I've brought a curry
and boiled vegetables.
I'll put it there.
You must be hungry from the journey.
Thank you.
Blankets and a mosquito net.
Hope it's good enough.
Of course. It was a lot worse in Bangkok.
Why are you here alone?
Where are your parents?
Bangkok got bombed terribly hard
that night.
My parents didn't make it.
I'm sorry, Noi.
And how are you doing?
Fine.
I come here every day.
There's not much to do at home,
so I come here to assist
the doctors and nurses.
They've just been called back to Bangkok.
You want to become a nurse?
I don't know. I guess.
And you?
I'd just got into medical school...
when war broke out.
When you graduate,
you can come back to work here.
Of course.
But I don't know what's going to happen
from now on.
Have you ever had to deal
with critical cases?
"Critical cases"?
Patients who are in really bad condition.
Well, I have. Remember Grandpa Samran?
Yes, the grumpy grandpa.
He died.
On this very bed.
Little Noi wouldn't have been able
to sleep here.
[laughs]
[soft, nostalgic music]
[footsteps approach]
Soap, toothbrush, and a bathing cloth.
We're about the same size,
so here's your shirt and pants.
They should fit.
Thanks, Jerd.
No problem.
Ting, didn't you bring anything
for your friend?
This lamp!
Wow.
[Ting laughs]
[Noi laughs]
So, is this hairstyle popular in the city?
[all laugh]
Jerd.
Take Sai home. I need to talk to Noi.
-[menacing music]
-[ghostly creaking]
Run along, I can go by myself.
No, let me walk you home.
I'm really fine.
It's late. Let me come with you.
No.
[menacing beat]
Are you sure those men aren't bandits?
Actually, I'm not.
Then why did you bring them here?
Because I have nowhere else to go.
So you told them there was a Krasue here?
[distant drumbeats]
-[chanting]
-[drumbeats continue]
[gasping]
[retches]
[menacing music]
[panicked gasp]
[hushed, panicked gasps]
[men speak indistinctly]
[flies buzzing]
-[men speaking inaudibly]
-[eerie music]
Sai.
A Krasue did that?
Or maybe wild animals.
Where's Jerd?
Krasue are fast,
but you have to be faster.
-Too slow! Again!
-Try again!
[gunshot]
Still too slow!
[man]
Hey.
So, you're going Krasue-hunting
with me now?
I'm here to talk to Jerd.
Right.
I forgot you two were friends.
Jerd, come see me
after you're finished with him.
What are you doing here?
Training, obviously.
You shouldn't.
We don't know what they're up to.
Don't hang out with them.
I've been with them to several villages,
and I've never seen even one Krasue.
And we don't know
what really happened in Salaya.
But you told them
there was a Krasue in our village.
I did.
But it was just an excuse
for me to come back here.
What if the Krasue
had nothing to do with any of this?
So how did it all happen?
I don't know either.
Knowing nothing won't save anyone.
I have to go.
[suspense music]
[suspense music fades]
POKING SOME MUCK FREQUENTLY
TO CREATE GAS
WHICH CAN CAUSE AN EXPLOSION OR FIRE
[sighs]
You don't believe in ghosts?
No, I don't.
Then what do you think it is?
I still don't know.
But I'm going to prove
that Krasue aren't real.
[man]
Sai!
Don't forget to lock your doors
and windows.
Yes.
[menacing music]
[pants heavily]
[wet, squelching sound]
[wet, squelching sound continues]
[hushed, pained gasps]
[menacing music]
-[flies buzzing]
-[continues gasping]
[wet, squelching sound continues]
[screams]
[menacing music]
[ghostly hissing]
[ghostly hiss]
Sang! Our child's gone!
[menacing drumbeats playing]
Help! Please help!
[Sang panting heavily]
[sobbing]
Dum!
Don't shoot! My son!
Calm down.
Dum.
[Ting screams]
[Ting]
Dum.
[Ting screams]
-[women scream]
-[Ting sobs]
-[gunshot]
-[women scream]
[Ting]
Enough!
[gunshot]
Dum!
[Ting sobs]
[Ting sobbing]
Dum!
[menacing music slowly fades]
[Ting]
Dum!
Dum...
-Are you OK?
-Dum!
-Is he hurt?
-Dum.
Thank you.
[Ting sobbing]
[Ting]
Dum.
[ghostly hissing]
[menacing music]
[grunting]
Sai!
[menacing music builds]
[wet squelching noise]
[inhuman hissing]
[gasps]
Krasue...
[menacing, eerie music]
[panting]
[menacing music fades]
[sobbing]
[downbeat piano music]
I am so thankful to Tad.
Otherwise, my son would've been devoured
by the demon.
Poor Dum.
My husband will join the hunting party
tonight.
They'll sweep the whole village.
-[sad violin music]
-[soft sobbing]
[monk]
Who're you?
I'm Noi, son of Teacher Sawai.
Krasue don't hurt people.
These demons have lived alongside us
for a long time.
They were once humans
who practiced black magic.
Their spells backfired
and turned them into hellish ghouls.
The female is called Krasue.
The male is called Krahang.
Usually people will hurry to find a hunter
when they see a Krasue.
Maybe this one isn't just any Krasue?
Sir...
She's someone I know.
Listen.
Believe what you see,
but do what your heart tells you.
[romantic piano music]
[downbeat orchestral music]
[takes steadying breath]
[menacing drumbeats playing]
[pained gasps]
[sad orchestral music]
[wet squelching noise]
[ghostly hissing]
THYROID CARTILAGE,
THYROID GLAND, TRACHEA
[tentative orchestral music]
[slow, hopeful orchestral music]
Let's go.
Jerd came by the hospital this morning.
We should act normal.
Do you remember...
I used to be really scared of toads.
They are ugly.
Disgusting.
No one wants to go near them.
Now I've become one myself...
I realize that monsters
do have feelings, too.
[sad violin music]
HER LEGS ARE DISTORTED
SHE WILL BE ALL RIGHT
[romantic music]
[downbeat music]
Aren't you tired of eating chicken?
Stop it!
I want you to lighten up.
No one has seen it for a month.
KRASUE HERB
Past karma forces them to drift around
to repay their debts
through many lifetimes.
They're condemned to hide like prey.
It is said that Krasue would eat
a plant called Krasue Herb
to halt the bodily transformation.
But I've never seen this plant myself.
HOSPITAL
Let's check your body temperature.
Hmm, looks like a fever.
-How long have you felt feverish?
-Two days.
Sore throat?
Yes.
Open your mouth please. "Ah".
Say, "Ah". Open your mouth.
"Ah."
It doesn't look too bad. Runny nose?
[girl]
A bit.
What color is it?
[girl]
Green...
I see...
Then I'll let our nurse sponge you.
And I'll prescribe some pills
to take home.
Yes.
Take a nap and you'll be fine.
Your turn, nurse!
Is the water cold?
Yes, it is.
Indeed!
C'mon, nurse!
You're so impatient, doctor.
[Noi]
Gently, you'll hurt her.
[Sai]
I'm being gentle!
[Noi]
Does it hurt?
[girl]
A little bit.
Sai.
I'll leave her to you.
[Noi]
Jerd!
Sai.
Bael fruit juice.
I'll be back.
Yes.
There'll be a full-scale hunt tonight.
Secure your doors and windows.
Be very careful.
Sure.
I'll get going.
[woman]
Kaew!
[man]
Kaew! What's wrong!
-Kaew!
-What's wrong!
[Kaew's mother]
Kaew!
-What's wrong!
-Kaew!
Kaew! Somebody help!
[Kaew's mother screams
and Kaew moans in pain]
-Help!
-Kaew! Help us please!
Kaew! What's wrong with you?
[pained gasps]
Kaew!
[screams]
[Kaew's mother]
Kaew! Help! Please.
Kaew!
[Kaew's mother sobbing]
Tad! Tad!
-Help!
-Tad.
[ghostly hissing]
[sighs]
Come out, little girl.
Come and eat this.
[Tad grunts]
[Tad screams]
[Tad groans]
[Kaew's mother screams]
[Tad grunts]
Pai, Plaew, now!
[Kaew's mother screams]
[both screaming and sobbing]
[wet squelch]
[wheezing laugh]
[Kaew's mother sobbing]
Kaew.
[Kaew's parents sob]
Where had your daughter been?
She was sick.
I just took her back from the hospital.
-[sad violin music]
-[Kaew's parents continue sobbing]
[glass shatters]
[sobs]
[sobbing]
Noi, what should I do?
Kaew died because of me.
One day the truth will come out.
I don't want to go on like this.
[sobs softly]
Pull yourself together.
I'm trying to fix this.
We have to go to the forest.
Whenever I'm in pain,
I have a vision of the forest.
And some other things, too.
There must be something there.
Noi...
Come with me.
We have to thank Noi for bringing us here.
But with this girl...
we have to tread carefully.
Tad, I think this is a misunderstanding!
[ghostly hissing]
[eerie violin music]
Sai.
[soft, wistful music]
[mystical piano music]
So?
It feels good.
Great! We'll collect lots of them.
I'll find a way to grow it
so you won't transform again.
See, there's finally a way out!
C'mon!
[hopeful orchestral music]
Ooh!
[sad violin music]
But you'll be in great pain.
[sad, romantic violin music]
[menacing music]
Tad!
Noi, you prick!
Sai, run!
Hurry up!
All Krasue are such sluts.
[ghostly hissing]
-[inhuman growling]
-[panting]
[strangled screams]
[panting]
[ghostly hissing]
-[wood creaks]
-[gasps]
-[ghostly hissing]
-[wet squelching]
[strangled gasp]
-[ghostly hissing]
-[grunting and yelling]
[wet squelching]
[both growling and grunting]
Jerd!
[frustrated screams]
[panting softly]
Jerd!
[calls repeatedly]
[wind rustles]
[inhuman growling and hissing]
[panting]
Sai.
[eerie, foreboding music]
[woman]
Sai.
Sai?
Yes, Grandma?
Found him?
[wailing and moaning]
[woman]
Have you seen Jerd?
[man]
Jerd!
[woman]
My son!
Get up! My son!
[woman]
Kill all Krasue!
-Bitch Krasue!
-Kill them all!
[woman screams shrilly]
Kill them!
[woman sobbing]
Jerd!
Chief, I couldn't find them anywhere.
-Bitch!
-Kill them!
[shouting and wailing continue]
Where's our son?
[man and woman scream repeatedly]
Jerd!
What the hell happened?
We three chased it
to the old house in the forest.
We thought we'd cornered it.
But this bitch isn't an ordinary Krasue.
It's vicious...
and killed two of my men.
Did you see its face?
Who is it?
[Tad laughs]
[ghostly rattling]
[menacing music]
[groans]
[strangled scream]
[angry yelling]
[mob]
Kill it!
Sai, what are you doing?
Did you see the bundle
I put on the cabinet?
Yes, I did.
But where did I put it? I can't remember.
[agonized screams]
You killed my child!
Grandma!
I'm trying to think!
You killed my child!
Stop!
Right, it's in the laundry basket outside.
Goodness, what's the hurry?
[mob]
Kill it!
[tense, menacing music]
Monster! Come out!
[mob, angrily]
Show your face!
Come out!
[mob continues shouting angrily]
[mob falls silent]
I'll call her myself.
If she's really a Krasue...
you can shoot her.
Sai!
[panting]
[loudly]
Sai!
Come out here!
[Sai's father]
Sai!
Sai! Come out now!
Monster! Come out!
[angry mob]
Show your face! Come out!
Pan, step aside.
She's your child, but she's a demon!
[mob]
Let's storm the house!
Let's storm them!
[Sai]
Dad.
[Pan] I've been calling you.
Where have you been?
I was taking a bath.
Look at her!
Where's your Krasue? Huh?
Jerd,
tell everyone what you saw last night.
Think of the poor girl
who lost her life...
because Sai infected her at the hospital.
Jerd.
Last night, Tad and his gang
kidnapped me to their camp.
They tried to rape me.
[menacing drumbeats playing]
Jerd rescued me and we ran away.
Tad's men got mad and beat him up.
Bullshit!
-What about the dead bodies at the camp?
-There's no proof that I did it.
Sai!
Just admit you're a Krasue.
Jerd and I saw it with our own eyes.
[menacing music continues]
Tad and his men were trying to rape Sai.
[all scream]
Dad!
Get out of my village.
Love her while you still can.
[Tad laughs]
[all scream]
Folks!
The show's over.
I'll go after the Krasue myself.
[sad violin music]
[in an inhuman hiss]
You had the nerve to betray me!
-[Jerd screams]
-[growls]
[eerie music]
[sad violin music]
[wet retching]
[eerie, foreboding music]
Can we do it next week?
Yes.
[Pan]
Gather all the villagers.
[foreboding music continues]
[sobbing]
-[flames crackling]
-[menacing music]
[inhuman hissing]
[Tad's voice echoes]
Kill Sai, and destroy her heart.
-Kill Sai, and destroy her heart.
-[screams]
-Rip her heart out!
[Jerd pants and screams]
Get out of my head!
[screams]
[sobbing]
[sad violin music]
[screams]
[sobs]
Noi!
We're finished. There's no herb left.
Let's run away to Bangkok.
What about my dad?
Just worry about yourself!
You're in danger!
That bloodthirsty Tad
is still snooping around.
In Bangkok there must be someone
who can help us.
Meet me in the forest tomorrow
after sunset.
We have to make a run for it.
[sad violin music]
Jerd.
I've known all along...
that you're a Krasue.
It's late, let me walk you home.
No.
[Jerd] That night at the cow pen,
I saw it for the first time.
[wistful piano music]
I joined the hunters
so I could misdirect them.
There'll be a full-scale hunt tonight.
Secure your doors and windows.
[sobbing]
It hurt every time...
that I saw you with Noi.
[sobbing]
Don't leave me.
Sai, please stay with me.
Please.
Don't leave me.
Please, Sai...
[Jerd sobs softly]
[emotional piano music]
[continues sobbing]
[knocking]
[Pan]
Sai, can I come in?
Yes, Dad.
How are you?
Still hurt?
Dad...
Hmm.
One day, if I'm no longer here...
will you be all right?
Why are you saying that?
I won't let anyone hurt you.
I promise.
[sad piano and violin music]
Venerable one...
I'm here to say goodbye.
I also have something to ask you.
About Krasue and Krahang,
there's more to the story, isn't there?
Have you seen it?
Well...
it began...
when the Krasue,
who was the wife of the first Krahang,
fell in love with a human.
She got pregnant...
and they ran away together.
But Krahang found them.
He killed the man.
Then he killed his wife
and ripped her heart out
to avenge his own heartbreak.
His wrath was passed down
through generations.
Since then, a Krahang has to destroy
every Krasue's heart.
[Pan]
Sai.
[panting]
So they can't spread another rumor.
Sai.
Hi.
Good evening, Chief.
What're they showing?
Have you seen Jerd lately?
[pained gasps]
[agonized screams]
[Tad's voice echoes]
Poor Jerd, as selfless as a saint.
Trying to protect the girl
who hasn't even looked at you.
[rattling hiss]
[wheezing laughter]
Stop!
Love is poison.
It turns you into a fool,
an irredeemable fool!
[laughs]
Go away!
Leave me alone!
Do you think Sai's going
to keep her promise?
She's running away with Noi to Bangkok!
She's going to leave you.
She's leaving you behind!
You're such a fool. A fool! A fool!
Sai!
Sai, what's wrong?
Sai...
Sai... Sai, what's wrong?
[Pan]
Sai...
-[Pan repeats] Sai...
-[Ting] Sai...
[screams]
[villagers scream]
[bones snapping]
[inhuman growl]
[in inhuman voice]
Kill Sai! Rip her heart out!
[laughs]
-She killed my child.
-Let's kill her.
Burn her body!
[chaotic screaming and shouting]
[dramatic orchestral music]
[villagers screaming and shouting]
Stop!
Jerd...
[growls]
That's Sai.
Don't hurt her.
I beg you.
[growls]
[inhuman growling and snarling]
Go away!
Go on, stay back!
I said stop!
Stop!
Stop it!
[inhuman snarling]
[menacing music]
[both growling and snarling]
[furious snarl]
[devastated sobbing]
Noi...
Take care of Sai.
Sai...
Sai, let's go!
[in inhuman voice]
Noi, why are you protecting her?
She's a whore, nothing but a whore!
You think she's going to love you forever?
-You really think so?
-Shut up!
[snarls]
[gunshot]
[menacing music fades]
[heavy splat]
Take that as my apology, Nual...
Someone saw it last night.
Reng's internal organs were gone.
Who do you think it was?
Nual...
[strangled moans]
[strangled screams]
[sad piano music]
[sobbing]
Release me.
No, please!
[Nual continues sobbing]
Noi.
Go through the forest
and you'll find a river.
On the other side is Bangkok.
Hurry!
[panting]
[menacing music]
[menacing music builds]
-[wet squelching]
-[ghostly hissing]
[menacing music fades]
[Noi groans]
Sai!
[ghostly hissing]
We're almost there.
Just across the river and we'll be safe.
Hang in there.
[voice trembling]
I'll find a way to treat you.
You'll be all right. I'll cure you.
Hang in there, just a little more.
Just a little more.
You'll be all right.
You'll be all right,
I'll treat you myself.
[haunting, sad choral music]
Everything's going to be all right.
You'll be fine. I'll treat you myself.
[sad piano music]
[softly sobbing]
[haunting, sad choral music]
[sobbing]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I can't keep my promise...
[sad violin music]
[gunshot]
[muted audio]
[muted screams]
[soft, sad music]
[haunting, sad choral music]
[sad violin music]
When the war's over,
let's go to Bangkok together.
I'll show you around.
Great, I want to go.
Promise?
Promise.
[laughs]