Mummy, look out!
No, no, no! No...
I love you.
I'm right behind you. Go, now!
Dad, would you like a...?
Do you mind turning it down?
It's a bit early.
Is everything OK?
You getting ready for work?
Yeah.
How is work? It's fine. Same old.
What is it?
I think I might sit tomorrow out.
It all just seems
a bit much at the moment.
You're kidding me.
It's just that...
Yeah, it's her, isn't it?
Alice has nothing to do with it.
Yeah, well, it's funny that
every year we go and now she's
here, you suddenly don't want to.
That's not it.
What is it, then?
It's been 11 years.
It has to be OK to move on.
And I know this may be hard to hear,
but you need to try to move on, too.
It's what she would have wanted.
Don't talk to me about
what Mum would have wanted!
She'd be really disappointed
in you, by the way.
Jess?
Jess. Hey.
Are you gonna help me or what?
Um, yeah. Give me a sec.
How is it you always
conveniently miss deliveries?
Shh! Ooh, yeah. Wow. Stunning.
They're hideous.
I know. Put it on.
Absolutely not. Do it.
Do it, do it!
OK...
Summer hon!
I swear, they're getting worse.
Uh, no, no! Delete it.
Why? You look stunning.
Don't post that, please.
Babe, I've already posted it.
No. No, no. Jess...
Give it here. Give it!
Give...
Oh, my God!
Get off me. Sorry.
I'm sorry!
Jess? Oh!
Oh, my God. What a weirdo!
He's actually quite fit, though.
Yeah, I suppose.
Oh, he is.
I dare you. Really? Yes. Go on.
OK. Go! Off you go.
Hey, hey!
Hey, I'm, I'm... I'm sorry.
I wasn't trying to...
I was just trying to see
if you guys were open. What?
You're interested
in novelty T-shirts?
Ha! No, no.
I'm looking for boat supplies.
You sure I couldn't tempt you
with a dream cat shirt?
Uh, maybe. Maybe.
Actually, though,
I'm... I am really sorry.
I didn't mean to see you like that.
Don't worry about it.
So, tourist guy, do you
want to come to a party later?
Potentially.
It will be nice.
Just drinks, bonfire, music.
OK. OK, yeah. Why not?
It's on the beachfront, 9pm.
I'm Ben.
Jess.
I'll see you tonight.
Boat supplies over there.
Thank you.
You were right!
I told you.
All right. Here you go.
It's way too early. Babe, it's
never too early to do a shot.
To catch a tourist, my
favourite time of the year.
American as well.
American? Very nice.
Look, it's
probably not that serious.
Yeah, but it's not just that.
He got fired again.
Jesus Christ!
What's she like, then?
I don't know.
I just avoid them, really.
All they do is drink.
Not the same! No.
Look, I mean, if he's happy,
it's not that big a deal, right?
Yeah, I know.
But it's meant to be our thing.
Flowers and everything.
I'll come with you.
If you want.
Honestly, I don't know
what I'd do without you.
Hm, probably be way
less hung over all the time.
Yeah, definitely that!
OK, I got beer or beer.
Beer. I'm gonna go for a beer.
A big beer!
You don't even like beer.
Why didn't you get anything else?
Yeah, why didn't you get
anything else? Thank you!
Cos they didn't have anything
else in the shop. Here you go.
Thank you! Here you go.
How you doing, Jess?
Yeah, I'm OK. Yeah.
Yeah, she's good.
Right? Yeah.
Hello. Hello.
Hello, boyfriend.
Where've you been?
Hmm. Building that.
Oh, did you make it?
Well, hello.
What's up? The sky?
Oh, that's a good one.
Why don't we have a dance? Tom...
You're not still
angry at me, are you?
Come on, we're good at this!
Come on.
OK. But just one dance.
Just one. Yup, just once. Yeah.
Oh, sorry! Sorry.
Jess. Look, I'm sorry.
I've got to go.
Huh? Hey. Why?
I said I've got to go.
My friend's here. Just stay.
Tom. Come on, wait a minute.
Tom! Come on. Just... Let go.
Just stay a bit. Tom, let go.
Off you go, then.
Hey, you came!
Hey, you OK?
Hey, mate. Yeah, it's
nothing I can't handle.
Who's this? He's my friend.
Let's go.
Where you going?
So she told you to leave her, man.
Oh, yeah...
What the fuck? Tom, what the fuck!
Get off him! Tom! Hey!
Fucking... Oh, my God!
Are you OK? Emi, get him some ice.
- Yeah. Are you OK?
- Yeah.
Shit, I'm so sorry. It's not
your fault that he's an asshole.
Yeah, but I... invited you here.
That was a really warm welcome.
What's his problem anyway?
It's just those guys don't
take out-of-towners very well.
Yeah, well, he made his point.
I'm gonna leave you guys to it.
Don't let this one get away!
For the pain?
Thank you.
Do you want to get out of here?
Yeah, yeah. Please.
You guys have been fighting, huh?
Small town boys.
Absolute arseholes...
Which one's yours?
It's just right up here.
All right, here we are.
I'm kidding, I'm kidding,
I'm kidding. Come on. Come on!
Fun neighbours? Yeah.
Yeah, they've been
partying since I got here.
This is your boat? Yeah.
It's a work in progress.
Wow!
Need a hand?
Welcome aboard!
This is kind of amazing.
Yeah, it's not bad.
Want the tour?
Yeah.
All right. Come on. Let's go.
Watch your step!
Turn around, turn around.
Like a ladder, yeah.
Oh, like a ladder?
What?
Welcome to my home.
It's... actually pretty nice.
Hey, don't sound so surprised.
Yeah, I'm not much of
a photographer, I know.
I'm impressed.
So, are you gonna offer me another
drink or... Oh, right, yeah!
Do you want more vodka?
I could make you a gin and tonic?
Sure. All right.
OK... How strong you want it?
However you're having it,
I'll have it.
What's this?
That is a comms sat.
Lets us know where we are
and lets us communicate
with the outside world. Yeah, this
is the dolphin translator, yeah.
You can talk
to them through this!
And this is my
tracking bracelet.
It shows me where
the boat is at all times.
Cool. Yeah, you don't wanna be
overboard without this.
You all right? Yeah.
Um, just a bit seasick, maybe.
Now, let me see if I have
something for that. Hold on.
You know, you're
surprisingly organised.
I try my best.
Mm.
What? Nothing.
You j... You look nice, is all.
What? Like, I look
like a nice person?
You know what I mean!
So, why do you live on a boat?
Oh, I guess I've always just
been obsessed with the ocean.
Yeah.
And what do you think
of our little town?
It's not bad. Not bad at all.
Were you born here? Mm.
Yeah, I've lived here my whole life.
Wow. Yup, but I'm getting out
as soon as I can.
What's stopping you?
It's just me and my dad.
Divorced parents?
Uh, no, my mum died.
A while back.
I'm sorry.
I lost my dad, too. To cancer.
I don't meant to take
away from you or anything.
I just... I wanted to say I get it.
How long have you
been away from home?
Oh, about two years.
That's a long time!
My, uh... mom kind of
lost it after my dad died.
After a while, I just realised
I couldn't be responsible
for her any more.
So, I got this boat and
I haven't looked back since.
You know, it's a beautiful night.
You want to take these up?
Uh, yeah, all right.
All right.
Here you go.
How are you feeling? Mm!
Kind of great, actually.
Good!
Mm.
It was quite a night.
Yeah, it was.
Thanks for inviting me.
Yeah, sure.
Mum!
Morning!
God, you scared the shit out of me!
I'm sorry.
Where are we?
On the ocean.
I can see that.
I, I just thought it'd be
fun to have breakfast up here.
And we're not that far out. OK, but
last night we were in the harbour
and now we're in
the middle of nowhere.
Shit, yeah, yeah. Uh, it
was meant to be a nice thing.
I didn't mean to freak you out.
You should have asked.
Yeah, you're right.
I... I messed up.
I'll take you back.
Wait.
I just... I need a minute.
No, no. I got it wrong.
I, I just got up early.
I thought it'd be nice
to have you up here. No, it's OK.
It's OK.
Just a bit of a shock.
I get it, yeah.
Uh, I'll take you back.
No, it's fine. Really.
Shit, I was meant to meet my dad!
Yeah, there's no service out here.
You know what?
He can just deal with it.
Sure? Yeah, I'm sure.
Forget it.
This... Well, this looks lovely.
Oh, come on.
You don't have to say that.
No, it is, really.
Gonna join me?
Yeah, yeah.
Freshly caught?
Of course.
It's from the fridge.
How you doing?
You OK?
Yeah, I'm all right.
I don't normally
come out on the water.
Why not? Not much of a swimmer.
Really?
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
Come on, help me.
All right, we're going to hoist it.
OK... Take this.
Pull on the slack, OK?
Yeah. All right, here we go.
Got it? Yeah!
There you go. Look at that.
All right, here we go!
All right, you got it?
Yeah. Hand me this. OK.
There, we're gonna tie it off
and you're gonna do this
two more times, OK?
OK, how do I do the...?
Two times around the top.
Got it? Got it.
All right, you got this!
OK. There you go.
Look at you go!
Where are we going?
You'll see soon enough.
- Gotta get a picture of you!
- You're beautiful.
Oh, come on! Having a good time.
There you go.
Amazing. One more, together.
Both of us?
All right, ready? Yeah.
Whoa...
Shit!
Oh!
That was really close.
Shit!
Is there a problem?
Um...
Uh, it's just my dad
wondering where I am.
Don't worry. I'll get
you back by this evening.
He just really worries.
Let him.
You need to learn to be a little
more selfish sometimes, OK?
Hey, come on.
I wanna show you something.
Come on!
Wow!
Where are we?
You can only get here by boat.
So, it's all ours.
Let's go!
Come on!
Come on, let's go.
The water's great.
You're gonna love it.
Come on!
Here you go, way to go.
Look, you got it. Go! OK...
Ah!
There you go!
What's wrong?
Hey, hey, hey. You OK? You OK? Hey!
Can you swim? Can you swim?
Can you swim? Are you OK?
Yeah, yeah. OK...
Better?
Yeah.
I know you said you're
not a fan of the sea,
but you swam from
all the way over there.
I can swim.
You OK?
It's... It's my mum.
She drowned.
Today is the anniversary.
It was an accident. A drunk driver
swerved and we went in the water.
We?
I got out, but...
Yeah.
I think she'd be
pretty proud of you today.
You know, you're actually
kind of all right.
Come on! Just all right?
Come on!
Come on. Faster, faster.
We should think about
heading back. Hmm.
I know.
I don't really want to.
Don't know what to do any more.
Spent my whole life
looking after my dad,
and now he's just
got this new girlfriend.
He's moved on from my mum and
he just expects me to do the same.
Come with me. For the summer.
We'll see how it goes.
I mean we'll go work when we
need the cash, live on the boat.
I know it sounds absolutely crazy,
but if you ever don't like it,
I can just bring you back.
You're mad. I'm not!
I'm absolutely serious.
Come with me.
What the fuck?
Oh, my God!
Oh, shit.
What do we, what do we do?
Hey! Hey.
She's unconscious. Get a rope.
She's bleeding. Here, come here.
OK, tie it off, tie it off.
You got it? Yeah.
OK, you're gonna help me.
Come on. All right?
You ready? OK, yeah, yeah.
You got her? Yeah.
There you go. Careful, careful.
OK. OK.
You got her.
Go get her some water.
OK...
All right, you OK? Hey!
You OK? Hey, OK, yeah...
- You're all right.
Don't try to talk. OK?
Here. You're all right. You're safe,
you're safe, you're safe.
OK. Relax, all right?
You're in shock.
Drink some water.
Snap!
Yeah, it's a great look, right?
Stings like a bitch.
Yeah, it will.
You still look good, though.
Coffee?
Yeah, thanks.
There you go.
Best fucking coffee I've ever had!
I'm Ben. This is Jess.
Lexi.
Welcome aboard.
Cheers.
Do you have any idea
what happened to you?
Um... No, I don't know, really.
I was supposed to meet
some friends for a boat party.
Uh, they weren't where
they said they were gonna be.
So, I started the engine.
But there must have been some
kind of blockage or something,
cos I got thrown
forward and hit my head.
Blacked out.
You're lucky you didn't fall in.
I know!
Thank God you guys found me.
Well, you're gonna be fine.
Uh, sorry. Sorry, I think maybe
I'm just a bit, um, jumpy still.
Sure, sure. Sorry.
Actually, you wouldn't happen to
have anything stronger, would you?
Yeah. Yeah, I could use one myself.
Jess? Um, maybe we should think
about getting back to shore?
I'm sure Lexi probably
needs to get checked out.
One can't hurt.
All right.
To Lexi. No, to you guys!
Agh!
Thanks. Another?
Uh, uh, no, actually, would it be
all right if I just took a shower?
Yeah, uh, it's just
right here on the left.
OK.
I'll leave a shirt in
the bedroom for you. Thanks.
Do you want me
to make anything to eat?
Uh, uh, sure. Sounds great.
I'll get the engine started.
Get us back to shore.
I've decided I'm gonna come with you.
I will.
That is awesome!
We're gonna have so much fun.
I just need to get my things
and break the news to my dad.
OK, we're doing this.
Hey.
Hey!
He's meticulous, isn't he?
Yeah, I suppose.
Uh, another drink?
Sure.
Thank you. Cheers.
Are you feeling all right?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Should we take this up?
Sure.
So, how long have
you and, uh...? Ben.
Ben, yep. Um, how long have
the two of you been together?
Uh, since yesterday.
What?
Yeah, it all happened really fast.
I went to a party and then,
we came back to the boat
and when I woke up,
we were out here.
What, he just... He sailed out
to sea whilst you were asleep?
Yeah, but it wasn't
like that, you know.
He made breakfast
and everything.
It was actually kind of cool.
Romantic. I think so.
How old are you?
22.
What?
You want the
good news or the bad news?
So, the engine won't start. But the
good news is, we still have beer.
What does that mean?
Well, we can still sail.
We're just gonna have to
wait until the wind picks up.
And the engine? I've been having
a problem with it overheating.
I think it just burnt out.
My dad's gonna kill me.
Look, why don't I
just raise the sails up?
And as soon as the wind comes back,
we'll be on our way in, OK?
Surely there must be
some kind of way
to call the coast guard
or something?
Nah, the comms sat's down, too.
What? So you're saying there's no way
of anyone contacting us at all?
It's kind of great, right?
I'm mean, how often do we
really get to be unreachable?
Yeah! Look, let's
just make the most of it.
I like this girl!
Look, why don't we just say,
this is like the first part
of our little adventure, OK?
OK. Give me one of them.
There we go.
Cheers. Cheers.
You see?
Wind!
I was just worried.
Ah, you're really
cute when you worry.
OK, more shots!
Shots, shots, shots...
OK. Here you go.
Ready? Cheers.
Cheers. Cheers.
Mm! Ugh!
You OK? Yeah.
OK, so explain this little
bond you guys have got going on.
I want to hear all the details.
Well, uh...
We're both members
of the dead parents club.
Oh. I'm... I'm really
sorry to hear that.
Mum or dad?
Dad. Mum.
How long ago?
About two years.
How did he die?
Heart attack.
I thought it was cancer.
Yeah, it was.
He had a heart attack when
he was going through chemo.
His body just kind of broke down.
Sounds kind of like
a blessing in disguise.
Yeah.
Well, we really lowered
the tone, didn't we?
Yeah, fuck that.
Uh, let's play a game.
I love a game.
Hm, bet you do.
Do you have a coin?
Oh, yeah.
OK, game on.
Flip, sip, strip.
Never heard of it.
I flip the coin,
you call heads or tails.
If you're right,
you're in the clear.
But if you're wrong,
you either have to
take a sip of your drink or
take off an item of clothing.
Who gets to decide?
The other two of us, I guess?
All right. Yeah?
Yeah, OK. Flip it.
Wait, who goes first?
Jess?
OK.
Heads.
Correct.
OK, Ben. Your turn.
Heads.
LEXI, JESS: Oh!
What are we gonna make him do?
Strip, obviously.
Oh, OK. All right.
This is fun.
For who?
OK. Uh, tails.
Nope.
You're lying.
I'm not.
Yes, you obviously are.
Strip.
OK...
OK, uh...
Tails.
Wrong again!
Fuck!
How about we change it
up a little bit?
OK, how so?
Instead of just sip and strip, kiss.
Fine.
Oh, no, no, no. Not me.
You two.
They're not the rules. What, am I
not hot enough for you or something?
Is that it?
You're hilarious!
You know, as long
as we're raising the stakes...
...how about we each
take one of these?
What are they?
Yeah, all right.
Jess? I don't know.
Come on. It's gonna be fun.
I'm already having fun!
Come on. Don't be so boring!
Yeah.
There you go.
Bottoms up.
Oh! It tastes horrible.
There you go. All right, go.
Ben?
Jess, I...
I've been looking for you.
What happened to you?
Um...
Ben! Oh, my God. Ben...
Just stay calm. I can explain.
Ben, can you hear me? He's fine,
I've already... Get off me.
Ben? Ben? Can you hear me?
Listen... Ben?
Get off me! Listen to me...
Thank you.
Look, he, he... he attacked me.
What? I, I came in
to check on the engine.
I just flipped that switch
there and it just turned on.
They're not broken, Jess.
He was lying to us.
Why, why,
why would he attack you?
I don't know. I mean, he
smashed my head into that thing.
Look, we, we need
to move him, OK?
We need to, we need to tie him up
or something, before he wakes up.
Why were you looking
at the engines anyway?
Because I didn't
trust they were broken.
He drugged you, Jess.
Ben wouldn't do something like that.
I saw it, Jess.
You were... You were passed out.
But we all took that stuff together.
I didn't.
What do you remember?
After taking it?
It doesn't, doesn't make any sense.
Why not? Hm?
You don't know him, Jess.
Neither do you.
I need your help.
To move him. No.
He threatened me, Jess!
He said he was gonna kill me.
He obviously wants us
out here alone.
Just help me move him. Please.
Come on, quickly!
Do it!
Before he wakes up.
Oh, my God!
Come on, you piece of shit.
Jess, his legs!
Ah!
Fuck!
What the fuck is going on?
Did you tie me up?
Are you OK? She said...
You attacked me.
What are you talking about?
You knew I'd caught you out!
Jess, listen to me.
You can't trust her, OK?
You can't trust her.
Shut... Don't. Don't!
Shut up!
He, he's bleeding.
He'll survive.
Something I need you to see.
Just watch him.
OK...
Jess, what the fuck is going on?
She says you attacked her.
She attacked me!
Ow! The last thing I remember,
I was working on the engine.
And the next thing, I come to,
and I'm tied up with my
fucking head bashed in.
OK...
There's an emergency panel inside
the cockpit on the starboard side.
Inside, there's a flare gun.
Get it, all right?
We have to get out of here.
OK. OK, you have to stop her. I will.
I thought you'd might
like to see these.
I've already seen these.
Look at the women in the pictures.
They're all young women, Jess.
OK. This is his thing.
He gets women onto this
boat and he drugs them!
Get off him! Don't you, huh?
I know what you did.
Don't! Stop.
Just come outside with me
for a minute, OK?
I know this is a lot.
But he's not a good guy, Jess.
You're just another
one of his conquests.
Look at this.
That's me.
I've been on this boat before.
I came back here, so I could try
and figure out what happened to me.
I can't tell if this is you.
He drugged me, Jess!
Just like he drugged
you last night.
You planned this?
Look, we can figure...
Whatever.
I'm gonna go get us moving.
Is this her?
What? No, that could
have been anyone.
Fuck.
Why else would she do this?
I don't know, cos
she's a fucking psychopath!
Some guy screwed with her head.
She's taking it out on me.
I don't fucking know, Jess.
That's not even fucking her
in that photograph.
For fuck's sake!
Take off my tracking bracelet.
Tell me what direction we're going.
Please, just do it. It's important.
Oh, shit!
Shore is to the east.
She's taking us the wrong way.
She's not taking you home, Jess.
Look at me. Look at me.
I've never touched her.
I have no idea who she is.
She's dangerous!
Why is the gag off?
Did he finally tell
you everything?
I told her that you're
a fucking psychopath.
And you believe him?
No.
You're right.
He's full of shit.
How long till we
get back to shore?
A couple of hours.
I need a drink. You want one?
All right.
Yeah, just make it quick.
Look what I found.
You said you love a game.
Fuck you!
Let's play yours now.
How about we start with two?
Open!
Fucking swallow it!
How many did you
make me take, Ben?
Swallow!
How about number fucking three?
Now! Quit fucking around!
Good. Open, show me.
Good boy!
Where's your fucking girlfriend?
What's taking you so long?
With that drink?
All right. Let's focus...
Ah!
She's out.
I hit her with a bottle.
I didn't know what else to do.
When she wakes up, she's
going to come after you.
So, just undo my tape and
I'll take care of this, OK?
I have to turn this boat around. So,
can you go lower the sail for me?
What's that for?
We have to tie her up if we're
gonna get you back to shore.
No, just... The sail.
Do you remember how to do that?
Yeah, I can do that.
Please.
What are you doing?
You're gonna kill her!
She was already dead.
No, she can't... She can't be.
You hit her too hard.
I don't know what
else I should do, Jess.
Look. No-one else knows
that she's on this boat.
And no-one has to. OK?
No. Hey, hey.
I care about you, Jess.
I don't wanna see your
life ruined over this.
So, just... Just think
about it, all right?
Ben, don't, don't.
Fuck!
Ah, fuck.
No!
You fucking hit me.
You weren't taking us back to shore.
You would have let him kill me!
You fucking bitch!
I love you...
You're my brave girl. Go, now!
Oh, hi.
Water.
What was that?
Sorry, my, um... My hearing
isn't quite what it used to be
after you smacked my head in.
Water.
Please?
Please.
Open...
Fucking deranged bitch!
Fuck you.
Where's Jess?
She...
Did you kill her?
It was an accident.
What do you want?
We both know this isn't the first
time I've been on this boat.
I didn't do anything!
I don't remember you.
Now, I have...
I've never drugged anyone!
You're lying.
You killed Jess! I told you,
it was a fucking accident.
OK, what do you want?
You want, uh... You want money?
Money? My dad's loaded.
I can get you as much as you want,
before you even get to shore.
See, I thought your dad was dead.
That's not the point.
What else have you lied about, Ben?
How much? Just name your price.
Do you think I want to
live off your guilt money?
All I want is for you to
tell me what you did to me.
I wanna hear you say it!
You still don't know.
Yes, I fucking do.
I was on this boat.
You fucking drugged me and raped me.
I know you fucking did.
Yeah, I cannot remember you.
I want to hear you say it.
Stop fucking laughing,
you're sick in the head!
I, I...
I told you already.
I don't even remember who you are.
How many other women
have you done this to?
I didn't do anything.
Shut the fuck up!
I need to drop anchor.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you fucking genius!
Come on, quickly.
Quickly!
Come on.
Who is it?
I don't know.
It's Lexi.
That's not her.
Look at her wrist.
Her tattoo.
Did you take any of me?
I, I can't believe you think
I would do something like that.
I would never hurt you, Jess.
I promise.
So, just let me out and we can...
We can what?
You drugged me!
It doesn't matter
what the fuck you think.
She's not going to let you off
this boat alive and you know that.
That depends.
I'll take you back, Jess.
But no-one can ever know what
happened here. Can I trust you?
You fucking what?!
You can't trust her! Look,
I never meant to hurt you, Jess.
I didn't even know you
were gonna be on the boat.
I had to know what he did to me
and he's gonna keep doing it
unless someone stops him.
You were right.
Oh, fuck!
You'll fucking regret this, Jess.
Jess, you need to go now..
We have to take him back to shore.
I can't do that.
You know I can't do that.
Lexi!
Stop! Let her, let her go!
Let, let go of her! Let her go!
She's gonna blow up this boat.
She's gonna kill us both.
Don't be fucking stupid!
Please, please, please.
Don't, don't! Don't.
Shut the fuck up.
Ben, Ben, Ben, you don't
want to do this, please.
Please!
Please! Please.
Jess.
Jess, Jess, I'm not
gonna hurt you, Jess.
OK? Because I, I need you
to help me here.
All right?
We can work this out, OK?
This could just be our little thing.
So, you just have to...
Just come here.
Promise me that
you're gonna help me.
Come here.
Fuck you!
Promise me!
Jess, open the door.
Open the fucking door!
That's what you fucking want to do?
I wouldn't do that.
Ugh!
Come on!
Lexi?
Oh, my God!
Lexi!
You OK?
Let's go.
AccessibleCustomerService@sky.uk