This national team is good.
Yes.
But our Iron Ladies is better.
Foul mouth! That's the national team
you're talking about.
You're a pain in the ass!
Mui, your feet!
What feet?
Crow's feet!
Shut up, you nutter.
Gotta brush it off.
Very good.
Is there any left?
It's still visible.
Okay, I'll take it.
Are you doing it yourself, Noina?
I didn't go to the medical school
but I can do it. Easy.
Don't worry.
-Really?
-Yes.
-What?
-Oh my...
-Noina!
-Shit!
-I didn't mean to.
Don't you see what I'm doing?
I didn't mean to.
Ouch.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
The medicine is kicking in now.
Good stuff.
It feels so tight.
Let go! Let go!
My head!
-How is my head!
-It's stuck.
The needle is gone.
All gone.
Ouch!
-Mui
-The needle!
Mui.
Do you remember when
you were a volleyball coach?
Of course.
It was exactly like this.
Prayuth!
Avoid the blockers.
Enough, enough.
Everybody goes over there.
Go receive the serves.
Work more on the basics,
attacking and digging.
Come on.
Let's go.
Push it. Don't dawdling.
Ready!
Ready?
In two rows.
First to receive the serves.
Second to attack.
Setters, do your job.
Okay?
Very good.
Focus on the first ball.
Focus on spiking.
-Shit!
-There he is.
On the line, not on my face!
Mui, sister!
Seriously, Coach Bee?
We're in competition!
-Really?
-Come to Lampang.
Yes, yes, yes.
When should I get to Lampang?
Immediately.
Yes.
Let me gather the team members.
Please prepare the application form.
-We'll see you there.
-See you.
See? We never fool you, Mui.
You go get your girls.
I'll go get mine. On the move!
Yes mama!
Mama my ass!
Just sister will do.
Yes, Sister Mama!
Move, out of the way, move.
Don't want to get hurt,
give me the way, let's move.
Trolley is hard, your feet hurt
when they get run over, man!
Khan Tok, you work hard, don't you?
No work, no food, aunty.
-Bro.
-Bro my ass, I'm a beauty!
Here.
You have such a foul mouth.
I just want to slap those lips of yours.
Why?
Do you know aunty Nok?
Sure, I see her everyday.
She talks shit about you.
That you're an old desperate tranny.
You'll die from AIDS.
What?
You slept with all boys in the market.
Even with the dustmen.
Nok!
Come on. Talk to yourself.
Calm... down
-Calm down.
-There, very good.
Shit! Which way?
This way.
Bastard! I am invincible.
All ten of you will be dead!
-Aunty Nok!
-What now?
-When will you die?
-What's up with that? Wanna be slapped?
That blond bitch said.
That grey-haired tranny? What did she say?
She said you...
You have diabetes, and hyper tension.
Plus, you'll die from cancer.
Damn, still following me?
Hey, stop there.
Must be his first.
Cucumber, bitter gourd, luffa, eggplant.
Do you know how I feel?
So enjoyable.
Should have tried that a long time ago.
It's awesome.
Can you come back?
Come back to me.
Ouch, it hurts like hell.
Si, you old queer.
How dare you say I'll die from cancer?
You know so well,
why don't you examine me?
You talk shit first.
You said I have HIV, I sleep with all men.
You are an attention seeker,
I never see you do any work.
What's the problem then?
Jealous of my beauty?
But you started this, right?
Khan Tok told me.
Same here.
You said I'll die from cancer, diabetes.
Khan Tok told me too.
Khan Tok again?
Khan Tok!
Yes, dear?
Move away, move away.
Hey! Wait!
Pak, Jung. What are you doing here?
We've come for you.
I don't get it, forget it. Come this way.
What? Sis, wait!
Wait up!
Here she comes.
Thidatep, hello.
Where did you learn English, so good!
I don't even understand
what I've just said.
But he can reply, I'm confused too.
He is a nutcase.
Okay!
What do you two want from me?
We want to...
Wait, let me finish this.
He is waiting on my cucumber.
Just five minutes.
What do you want?
We'd like to ask you to join
the volleyball team.
-Come together.
-Please, Please, please.
Like always. Just call me when.
Okay.
You bitch...
Hello?
Hello, Man?
Mui, what's up?
I'd like to tell you ...
the Iron Ladies will come back again.
You go gather our friends.
Okay, no problem.
I'm playing cards now. Later.
Man!
Nine-nine!
Yes! Come on!
Here for one game.
Here, here.
Come on, hurry up.
I told you I'm gambling, what now?
This is police speaking.
What? I'm not going to Poland.
I'm busy, later.
-I'm waiting, want another card?
-No.
Looking good.
Boat, did you order food?
That might be the delivery boy.
It's all looking good, damn it.
Now, now.
Fine.
Ugh, this is crap.
Hello.
Police!
We are very excited now.
From 11 contestants, there will
be only three left at the final.
Which number?
Which one?
Number... number...
Twenty!
Congratulations! 20 is going
through to the final.
Two more to go.
Well, now we are going to the questions.
We start with number 20.
And your question is...
Where is the first 7-Eleven's branch
in Thailand?
Answer it.
It's...
Where?
on the ground.
It's on the ground, is that correct?
Correct.
-Please, a round of applause.
-You are smart.
Next is number 32. Please step out.
Your question is easy.
The contest tonight...
What is the name of tonight's contest?
It's...
What's the name?
You can't chose who to be born as,
but you can be a good person. Thanks.
Well...
No need to answer to the right question,
thank you.
Number 100.
Why were you born... I'm sorry.
Who were you born as?
Thank you for your question.
When we see the silver linings,
Thai queers will rise.
Our land is so rich, Thai girls will rise.
What's the question again?
You haven't answered?
Pun Pun. Pun!
Man!
Mui wants you to join the team again.
-Really?
-Yes.
Pun!
What's wrong? We are all working here.
Why are you screaming?
Nothing, Mama.
Then tell me why.
Man asked me to join the volleyball team.
Man asked you to play volleyball?
Hello, Mama.
There is no man here.
How about your cabaret show?
I'll come back. I can do both.
-How could you do both?
-Please.
Who will perform then?
Mama, I'll take her place.
Say that again.
I'm leaving now. Bye.
Pun.
And the winner of 1996 is...
Number 100.
Please, a round of applause.
Congratulations.
Actually, this one is the runner-up.
Now, please welcome Lady Bygone.
She presents the prestigious crown
to our winner.
Please present the crown.
Don't freak out.
Sorry, just the crown, not with the tray.
Give her the crown,
give me back the container.
Give her the crown.
The judges must have bad eyes.
Say what?
Nothing.
Let's take photos.
Oh my God!
Why did you do this?
Are you alright?
Oh my god. What happened?
The beauty has become a frog now, look!
Nu, sis!
Don't be upset. The judges have no taste.
If you go to Miss Universe...
same year as Pornthip.
You'll beat her.
Really?
Sure, you are the prettiest.
I thought it was only me
that believe that.
You do, too.
How about...
you come play volleyball with us?
We will win this for sure.
You are a good player, and beautiful.
Please, please.
Fine.
Yes.
Tom! Tom!
Yes, Ma.
Your friend is here.
Man!
How are you? Haven't seen you a while.
Is everything okay?
Mui wants you to get back
to play volleyball.
Iron Ladies will compete again.
Iron Ladies! Jung and Dow are joining too?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Why do you have to hold his hands?
What's the matter?
I can hold his hands too, no problem.
-I better go.
-Good bye, good bye.
Ma, do you want me to have a heart attack?
Do you want me to die?
You are crazy.
Let's go back to your room.
Dig.
Come in.
Pun!
Man!
I have...
What?
-Where are you?
-They came after me in four rooms...
And you know what?
-Hey!
-You can't.
-This one.
-No, No, no.
Bitches!
Mama? I didn't really see you.
There you are.
You look like one of them Storm-Riders.
Mama, greetings.
Greetings to you too.
I have good news.
We will go to Lampang in two days.
Coach Bee invites our team...
to represent Lampang.
Hello, everyone.
Wait! Stop, stop, stop.
Chart, my dear Chart.
Still fit like always.
Chart!
Khan Tok, get away.
My dear Chart.
Muah!
I've missed you.
Chart.
Who is that, Chart?
My girlfriend.
-Your girlfriend?
-Yes.
-Really, Chart?
Bad taste.
-This is your girlfriend?
-Pathetic.
Skin is damn rough.
I am much prettier.
Yeah, seriously...
Are you a human or giant?
Who are you talking about?
You.
Oh, no!
Not true, not true, not true.
No.
Come on now. Stop it.
Pack up! Let's go to Lampang.
Lampang!
Lampang. Lampang. Lampang.
LAMPANG PROVINCE
Jung! Jung!
Kham.
Jung.
Come on, hurry up.
It's so cold.
And coach Bee?
Coach Bee?
Coach Bee asked us to welcome you.
-I see.
-Hello.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Let's get going.
-Go!
-Hurry
Lampang. Lampang. Lampang.
We are just friends.
Hey, you guys!
Are you not embarrassed?
Nothing is more embarrassing
than our outfits.
Whatever.
-And you're so damn pretty?
-She's jealous.
Lampang. Lampang. Lampang.
Stick with me, I'm embarrased.
To Boonyawas.
Follow me this way.
Jung, how do you know Coach Bee?
Since I was in high school.
I was her student.
She was a volleyball coach.
Then I went to university in Bangkok.
Lampang. Lampang. Lampang.
-Jung.
-Yes?
What is Coach Bee like?
Coach Bee...
She is kind. But she is a dyke.
Oh...
-Really?
-Yes.
Is she cute?
Not really. It's just that...
you never see
the same girl come to see her at school.
-Really?
-Yes.
And some days,
there were four or five girls.
And they fought over her at school.
Really?
Really.
Bro, can you get Coach Bee?
Alright. I'll tell her you guys are here.
Okay. Let's go.
Thanks.
Bitch, always getting horny.
I wanna see Coach Bee.
Here, they want to see you.
Eh...?
Thank you, kids.
-My pleasure.
-Thank you.
Coach Boo, who wants to see me?
I don't know. Your friend?
Hmm.
-This is refreshing.
-It's tasty.
Jung!
Coach Bee!
-Hello!
Hi!
These are the friends you told me about?
Yes, Coach Bee.
Whoa...
They look strong. Which one is Mui?
I'm here.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Hey, I have a class.
Okay, Coach Boo.
There are only dykes here.
-Don't call them dykes. It's bad.
-What should we call them?
Girls, go get change.
And show me what you've got, okay?
Yes!
Do your best!
Coach Bee.
The headmaster wants to see you.
I'll catch up.
-Who?
-Kham, Khai.
Take them to get changed
and go to the gym.
And see you there.
Yes, coach.
-Do your best!
-Yes!
Now, Coach Bee!
I have something to talk to you about.
Yes, sir.
What is it?
About the volleyball players
for our province.
I have them all, full team.
Don't you think that your players...
They are homosexuals.
What are you thinking?
Wait, sir.
What is wrong with them?
They just can't chose
who they are born to be.
And there is no gender limit
in volleyball.
They only need to be skillful, right?
You know, if they compete...
they will bring us bad names.
People would think that volleyball...
is the sport of the queers.
You should think about it.
I insist.
I will use this team.
And there won't be any changes.
You are stubborn,
you will bring us all down.
But I'm not surprised.
You are one of them too.
Sir, we'll see. This team of ladies...
or the queers as you say...
We'll see how well they perform.
I will make them the champion
of region five.
Wait and see.
If there is nothing else,
may I excuse myself?
Oh, there is no space there.
Thank you, Deung.
Whatever your skills are, show it...
So I'll know.
Show me the best in you.
Yes.
Wait.
This, I wanna have but I don't wanna see.
I mean, your skill. Show it.
Yes!
Do your best!
Then... let's begin!
Not this way, that way.
Help me!
Iron Ladies!
So good! You are so good!
Come on here.
There was no team as good as we are.
We will be the champion.
Let's get something to eat at my place.
My treat.
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Hey, bring me down!
Hey!
Are we there yet?
There is a giant sausage at this shop.
Sausage my ass, we'll get there in a bit.
Here is her shop. "Get Rich".
Come in.
Let's go in.
-Take a seat.
-Hurry up.
Where is food. I can't eat tables.
Take a seat, here.
Your balls. Don't flash them.
Come on.
It's damn far. My legs are short.
Nu, order the sausage.
Eat your own first. It's flashing.
Crap! I went past it.
Ugh!
Why didn't you wait for me?
I couldn't catch up.
You have short steps.
We are hungry.
Application form, miss.
Very well.
Everybody, check your photo and last name.
Let me know if there are mistakes.
Beautiful!
Pass it on.
I'm the prettiest.
So pretty! Look at my face.
Check!
Great! I look pretty.
-Angel!
-Pretty girl!
All correct?
-Keep it.
-Yes.
Hey, Sin, is it ready?
I think so.
You think so?
-I'm hungry!
-Me too!
-Hungry!
Calm down. Calm down.
Kham, Khai, bring out the food.
They could eat a buff.
Buffalo.
I mean buffalo.
-That one with the horns.
-Buffalo.
Here comes the food.
Put them down.
Over here, over here.
So many.
Give it to me.
Don't!
This food is divine.
You're eating all!
What's wrong?
-What is it?
-Nu?
Nothing is wrong?
You have bad breath.
Feed me.
Come on, guys.
-Awesome.
-So yummy.
You are not finished?
No, not yet. Just half full.
All your friends left.
Is your family that poor?
Take some more. Takeaway?
I'll bring some bags.
I'm full.
It tastes good, right?
Yeah, I get it.
We are finally here.
Jung.
They're booing us.
Screw them.
Faggot!
Everyone, stay calm. Fight!
Fight!
Coach, let me take the lead.
Boo!
Boys!
Give it to me.
Wait.
Why? There is nothing wrong.
They can apply, can't they?
Do what he said.
They told us to wait.
I want to slap her!
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Where are they all gone?
You guys, look!
Boys...
Boys!
Boys, if I get them...
Me too! Me too!
The winning team from Chiang Mai.
Don't give up.
Let's compete against these boys instead.
Nu!
I'll eat them all.
You're hungry out of nowhere.
You're cute.
You're crazy.
I also have a face, you can look at me.
Sign them up.
You're so cute.
What's wrong with you?
And why don't you look at me?
Do I have a face?
Nu. Come back here.
I can't contain myself.
Can we apply for the competition now?
Why do we have to wait?
-Approved.
-Approved?
We are in! We are in!
Where are you?
Mui!
Khan Tok!
Come on, sis.
Guys!
Mui, I'm tired.
Stop, stop.
Girls, I have a dream.
One day I will count down to
the New Year over there.
If you guys win this match,
We'll have a party on the hill.
Hey!
Hey, hey.Concentrate.
Hit it. Hit it.
Coach Bee.
Win this match.
Of course, we will.
We sure will. Piece of cake.
Hello.
Hi.
It's taking long.
Hurry up.
Bitch!
Iron Ladies! Alright. Fight!
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Alright, alright. Try again.
Dig it.
LAMPANG 8-8 CHIANG MAI
Watch out. Watch out.
LAMPANG 11-9 CHIANG MAI
Substitute. Substitute.
Fight!
Be careful.
-Here!
-There you go.
Focus. Focus.
Dao! Dao!
LAMPANG 15-11 CHIANG MAI
Be careful. Hurry up.
LAMPANG 15-14 CHIANG MAI
LAMPANG 16-14 CHIANG MAI
LAMPANG 13-13 CHIANG MAI
Focus. Focus.
Bring it on.
Iron Ladies!
We won!
We're gonna have a party on the hill.
And celebrate New Years.
To the hill! To the hill! To the hill!
Wait. Wait. Wait.
I can't go. I have something to do.
If you can’t, it'd be so much fun.
To the hill!
We're following our dreams.
We're celebrating the victory...
On the hill!
It's a pity Coach Bee can't come with us.
She is handling the match in Nakhonsawan.
And she's too old,
she can't walk this far.
Parn.
What the heck am I carrying? So heavy.
Hi.
Tonight, we're celebrating...
Our great endeavor that made us win
and become region five's winning team.
And we're gonna celebrate the New Year.
Tonight,
we're bringing you an entertainment.
Enjoy the show!
When will you reach the blocking? Huh?
You kicked me like I was a frog.
Just tell me nicely.
Don't look right here
You're making a big deal
Don't look at me like that
If you wanna love me, make it real
Don't look right here
You're making a big deal
Don't look at me like that
If you wanna love me, make it real
Don't look right here
You're making a big deal
Don't look at me like that
If you wanna love me, make it real
May our team...
win the next match in Nakhonsawan.
Sap peh sat ta...
That's a prayer for the dead.
Was I so wrong that you gotta slap me?
Please bless us
with victory for this game.
Good night.
-Let's go.
-Bye bye.
Can I sleep with you?
Dear God Guan Yu,
please bless us with happiness.
Please bless us with good health.
Please bless us with fortune.
Most of all, I wish for my son
to be grateful of his family.
May he be good and well-behaved.
Most importantly, God Guan Yu.
I'd like to make a wish.
Stop him from hanging out with queers.
Prevent him from being a homosexual.
Mhuay, why did you say that?
Why?
Mama, I'm making a wish.
It's nothing to do with you.
You're upsetting me.
You spoke so loud. I heard that.
Tom is sitting right here.
So? Are you gay?
No, I'm not.
Tom, pot the incense sticks.
We finished now.
Pot them.
JUNGKOCHIKA RESTAURANT
Are you sure that this is Jung's house?
Yes, Coach Bee.
There it is. Jungkochika Restaurant.
If you think it is, call him out.
Jung!
Is anybody home?
Who is it? Why are you yelling?
Who are you here for?
Hello, I...
Hey! Are you trying
to sell me a water filter?
No. I already have one.
No, I'm not. I'm here to...
Ask me for some money?
Old trick.
You missed your bus and need money.
No. I won’t give you any.
Hello, I'm Coach Bee.
I came from Lampang to meet Jung.
Coach Eew!
Oh it's you. Hello, Coach Eew.
No, Mom. This is Coach Bee.
She's Coach Eew. I know.
Jung talks a lot about you, Coach Eew.
Come in. Get inside the house.
Come on, come in. Come in.
Wait, Mom.
It's locked.
I forgot.
I've got it. Here.
Here you are.
I don't remember which key is which.
Try it.
Come in, coach.
Coach Bee, take it easy.
Jung went out practicing. She'll be back.
She goes out everyday.
That's alright.
Aren't you from the North?
I was born in Udonthani,
but now teaching in Lampang.
An Udonian. Where do you live?
Wang Sam Mor.
We're neighbors!
I'm from Pattani.
I was born in Pattani
but I grew up in Maha Sarakham.
Which district were you in?
Bor Krabue
Bor Krabue?
I go there often.
I go there to sell my buff.
Everyone wanna buy my buff?
You don't need to go
to Bor Karbue to get one.
We have ones around here.
Yes, we have one around here.
Jung, Dao. Coach Eew is waiting for you.
Coach Bee! Hello.
Hello.
I need to go to the loo.
That explains a lot.
We all miss you, Coach Bee.
I thought you'd come earlier.
What took you so long?
I've just got the time.
-Kam!
-Jung!
What are you doing here?
To find something to eat in the toilet?
So cute. You're here to meet me.
Do you miss me?
A bit.
What's wrong with you?
I'm going to pee.
Hey!
Dao, tell the girls to meet me here.
Okay.
Coach Eew, are you spending a night here?
Yes, ma'am.
You must have traveled a long way.
To our happiness.
Same here, Coach Eew.
-It's Coach Bee.
-Alright.
Madame Jang.
Yes?
How many people live in this house?
Just the two of us.
-My son and..
-You.
Mother and son. Alright, alright.
How long have you two lived here?
A long time. Since...
Since Jung was young, right?
If I wanna ask you about your love life,
Would you mind?
No. You can ask me.
Well... Umm...
What's your type?
My type?
I like short and bulky guy.
And he's working in...
Lampang?
Lampang!
I live in Lampang.
Cheers! Cheers.
My pleasure.
-Madame Jang.
-Yes?
Do you remember what I told you?
About my buff.
I wanna tell you that my buff is strong.
Big. Tough. Rough.
Do you have a lot of buffs?
I have a pen full of them.
They're all over my field.
-A lot of buffs.
-A lot.
You can't sell them out. No.
You can't sell them out, huh?
No, I can't. Cheers. Cheers.
-Cheers! Cheers! one, two, three!
-A lot of them.
-Madame Jang.
-Yes?
I...
I think...
-Will you be my...
-Mom
There are more orders.
You don't need to ask me anything.
Customers are calling. Excuse me.
Mom, hurry up.
Madame Jang.
Madame Jang!
Just a second longer
and I would have gotten her.
Coach Bee.
I'll take you to your room.
Madame Jang...
Madame Jang, can I touch your boob?
I'm not Madame Jang.
Can I touch you?
That's my cabbage, coach!
I want you to see my buff.
My buff is huge.
As huge as a rocket.
It can shoot up to the sky.
Ball two. Ball two.
Nu!
Set!
Attack!
Good. Good. Good.
Tom.
Yes, Mui?
Why didn't you come to practice?
I was busy with school.
Busy with school?
You can come here after school.
Mui, I have a problem with my mother.
Tom.
You can tell me anything.
Thank you, Mui.
Go practicing.
Dig it.
Ball!
Let go!
Khan Tok!
Yes?
Dig it well.
Come here.
Hurry up.
Keep practicing.
-Come, come.
-Come on.
What's the matter, Mui?
Can I ask you something?
Where's Noina?
I don't know.
I don't sleep and eat with him.
Yeah?
Are you having a problem with Noina?
I swear.
I don't have any problem with him.
Up to you. Go practice.
-Noina!
-What's the matter?
Sure you're not having a fight with him?
There's nothing.
Why are you asking me so much?
Bitch!
Totally no suspicion!
Parn.
Mui.
Coach Bee got here from Lampang.
She's now staying with Jung.
She told me she wanted to meet our team.
Tonight, Mui.
Alright. But...
Put your bags in the lockers
and go practice.
No privilege. Go!
Alright.
Parn, attack!
Let go!
Dig it!
Anyone wanna take a break?
Jung.
-Go on.
-Okay.
-Parn.
-Six people here!
Three back, three front.
I'd like to make a wish.
Stop him from hanging out with queers.
Prevent him from being a homosexual.
Welcome Coach Bee to Bangkok. Cheers!
Cheers!
Yay for Coach Bee. Cheers!
So happy Coach Bee is here. Cheers!
-Hi.
-Chart, Joy. Come sit here.
Chart is here.
He is fucking here.
Parn, you cheeky bitch. Get out!
Now!
-Joy, Come sit here.
-Here.
So cheeky. Sit.
Here.
When are you getting married?
Where did you pick her up?
Since we are all here...
Let's drink.
Cheers!
I have come here for two reasons.
First, let me say...
Jung, you are pretty like your mother.
Thank you, Coach Bee.
Next, it's serious.
I know the schedule
of "Paknampho Games"
There are four regions.
First is region nine, Pattalung.
Don't worry.
Second is region six, Nakornsawan.
Third is region ten, Bangkok. Average.
The next is tough, they are very good.
It's region seven, Supanburi.
It's all up to us. Don't be afraid.
We have to train hard and stay strong.
The most important is,
we hold on together.
Hold on together!
Agreed!
Cheers!
Nu, music.
Yes, coach.
Faster.
Chart, try this.
Make yourself at home.
Music!
Nu. Stop it! Now!
Bitch!
Are there any other songs?
Coach Bee, I am taking off.
Where are you going?
I don't feel well.
Why don't you stay with us?
What's wrong with her?
She is not well.
Mui.
Don't you worry about me.
You guys have fun.
Where are you going, Mui?
Must be a PMS thing.
Like your mother.
You talk shit about my mother?
Bitch!
Quiet now. Eat up.
Come on.
I don't think so...
Who is that?
It's Chart.
Come in.
What is it?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Where's Joy?
I took her home already.
I'm just worried about you.
ROMANTIC BLUE
You like that movie?
Don't you?
I do. We went together, didn't we?
Mui, where are you going?
I’m going home.
Let's go out for dinner and a movie.
Really?
Yes, "Romantic Blue" is a big hit.
You like Nook?
No, I like Tao.
And do you like me?
Of course, that's why I invited you.
Let's go.
Wait, wait, Chart.
Uh...
Chart.
What do you think about me?
I care about you.
And love you...
as a friend.
Get some rest.
I'll get going.
Four hundred fifty, 451...
Coach Bee, what are you doing?
I like to exercise.
I do four to five thousands a day,
you know.
So strong.
Don't look,
you'll be frightened of my face.
-Coach?
-Almost 6000 now.
Coach?
Coach Bee?
-How are you?
-Stop talking. Lift me up.
Why is it so hard to win over a girl?
Take a seat.
Seriously, am I good looking?
The best.
My mom and grandma are not home.
Mama.
Why isn't Tom home?
He said he has a meeting
at the university.
It's just an excuse to stay out late.
He said he has a meeting.
He goes to study.
Stop complaining, alright?
Tom?
What, Mama?
Tom!
What are you doing?
Who the hell is he?
Get out of my house! Get out!
Mama, please. Don't!
Mama, don't hurt me.
Why?! Why?!
Don't. Mama, stop!
Muay, calm down.
Muay!
Our family name is ruined.
We are all in shame.
Muay, calm down.
Think about it.
Mama, please!
You never listen to me.
What do you want?
You ungrateful child,
I'll beat you to death.
Enough.
Enough! Enough! Enough!
Muay?
Mama.
Enough, he is still your son.
Gay or queer, he is still your son.
Mama, stop.
-Go pack up.
-It hurts.
Go pack up, and leave now.
Get out, get out!
Go, go, go.
Go.
Tom.
Tom, sweetie.
No.
Tom, come here.
Are you hurt?
It hurts.
Muay.
What have I done wrong?
Jung?
-Dow?
-Yes, yes, I'm coming.
What happened?
Come in.
Come on, don't cry.
I'm worried for him.
What a pity.
It must be difficult if it was me.
I don’t know what to do.
His family doesn't understand him.
Hello. Jung, where are you?
Hello. I'm at the ground level.
Here. I'm at the sign "Jung Kochika".
Come on in.
Hey.
Open the door, Jim.
-Miss you.
Come in here.
Let's go.
Come on.
With the up coming match,
I don’t want us to get the hopes up.
Winning or losing, it doesn't matter.
What matters is,
will we be ready to fight?
We have to train hard to get ready.
No absence, no days off.
Because the competition is getting closer.
Hey.
Leg...
At my face.
Sorry.
Every matches we will be in from now.
We do our best.
Yes!
Noina. Where have you been?
I haven't seen you around.
You'll know soon.
Let me talk to this bitch first.
Come here.
Alright, let's warm up.
Let's go practise.
Do you remember that night?
On the mountain, in the tent.
Let's try it without the glasses.
So ugly, I better put them back on.
Why the hell do you stop?
Lift both legs, that's how it's done.
Alright.
Shit. The pants are still on.
So torturing.
So agonising.
So pleasurable.
So magnificent.
Super satisfying!
Well...
I was drunk. I didn't mean to.
Didn't mean to?
You were up all night.
You screwed me, Khan Tok.
So...
You have to take responsibility.
Are you pregnant?
Pregnant my ass, I haven't pooped
for weeks. I only ate fried pork.
I am in so much pain because of you.
You have to take responsibility.
Enough. Let's go practice.
I said practice first and talk later.
You want to practice?
Yes.
I'll do it too.
But with you here, bitch!
Khan Tok! Noina!
You can't. My hair's all lubed up.
Stop now!
Khan Tok, Noina!
Hurry up.
Stop it!
Noina! Khan Tok!
Noina, No!
Stop! Stop!
Khan Tok, stop!
Don't!
Stop fighting.
I said stop.
I said stop, stop!
Stop now!
No? You won't? Then I will!
Noina, stop! Stop!
Let go.
Let go of me!
Hey!
Don't do that to her!
Where is Mui?
I'm leaving. You take care of them.
Come on!
No! Stop! Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Coach Bee!
-What happened to her?
-I was hit on my face, bitch!
Coach Bee?
-Jung.
-Yes.
I'm going back to Lampang.
Yes.
Tell Mui and everyone,
let's meet in Nakornsawan.
I'll have everything prepared there.
Yes, I will.
Let's go.
And your mother?
Mom? Mommy?
Yes, sweetie?
Coach Bee is leaving.
I'll go back to Lampang.
I miss my buff.
Nobody is taking care of it.
If I have a chance, I'll show it to you.
Don't forget to wash it.
-Yes.
-And brush it sometimes.
I have to tell you.
I'll look much better next time.
Good bye, Coach Eew.
-Bye, Jung.
-Bye bye.
Bye, Jung.
Jung, give Coach Eew a ride.
Coach Bee, I'll drive you there.
Is it all you have now?
Let's give a try, so you can see.
Let's give a try...
Who is it?
One moment.
Stop knocking, bitch!
Ouch!
Let me help.
How are you? Just be patient, okay?
Be careful.
How's your leg? Are you good?
My legs are okay.
I haven't performed for many nights.
Mama keeps calling me.
If I don't go this time, I'll be fired.
Parn, someone wants to see you.
Who?
Come in...
Some fruits.
Thank you, Khan Tok.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
If I had been more reasonable,
you wouldn't have got hurt.
It's okay, Khan Tok.
I understand very well.
If I were you,
I would be ashamed to have Noina.
You bitch!
Oops, sorry again.
Parn, I have an idea.
So Mama won't fire you.
How?
Don't worry, Dow and I will handle it.
Right, Khan Tok?
Me?
-Bye, Jung.
-You go girl.
So beautiful.
You are talented.
Yes.
Even better than Parn.
Not really.
Interested in working here?
No, I'm not available.
Very well then. Gotta go.
Yes, good luck.
-Khan Tok!
-What?
You are so good.
You're sweet talking, Jung.
You are good at everything.
Even better than all my dogs.
Bitch!
I'll slap that mouth of yours.
-Khan Tok.
-Yes.
Thank you for replacing me.
My pleasure. It's Jung's idea.
Thank you, Jung.
It's okay. Friends help each other.
What's going on?
Parn!
Is it bad?
It's much better, Mama.
Lucky that your friends are here.
Otherwise, what would we do?
But I have something to tell you.
I found your replacement.
She has a title with her too.
And she is here now.
Sang-harn.
Here is your replacement, Sang-harn.
It's okay, Mama.
If you want to go bankrupt, hire her.
I have to go.
Man, let's go.
Come on. Yes, let's go.
Parn! Parn!
I was joking, come back.
Don't be upset.
Sang-harn.
Yes, Mama.
I fired you.
What?
But I haven't performed.
With this look, no need.
Go back to your farm.
Go hug your title.
Come on now, just stay.
Good bye, Mama.
When we see the silver linings.
Thai queers will rise.
-Sang-harn.
-Yes, Mama?
Did you steal anything from me?
No.
Very well then. Go, go, go.
Good luck with farming.
Amen.
Sang-harn!
Yes, Mama?
Got money for the bus?
I am richer than you.
I'll wire the money to you.
My family knows about us.
They don't want us to see each other.
They want me to marry
the woman they picked.
You are telling me...
We won't see each other again?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
Tom.
Why are you crying?
Jet broke up with me.
Tom, don't cry. It's okay.
Come on, don't cry.
Tom.
Men are like gums.
Tasteless at first.
No.
Juicy at first.
Yes.
But finally, tasteless in the end.
Dow, you can say this.
You haven't experienced it,
you don't understand.
Don't cry, Tom. It's okay.
Tom.
Tom, don't be sad.
At least, you have us with you.
Yes.
Stop crying now.
Don't cry.
Grandma!
-Tom!
-Grandma!
Tom!
How are you?
I'm good, Grandma.
I miss you everyday.
Is it difficult out there?
No.
How do you eat? Who cooks for you?
Jung takes a good care of me, Grandma.
I miss you everyday.
I miss you too.
Come back home, Son.
Tom, come home. Grandma.
Tom, hurry up. You'll be late.
Grandma, hello.
Hello, Mama.
Hey...
The whole time you have been away.
You've been with these freaks?
Is that right?
Alright then!
Mama, please!
Don't hurt us.
Mama, no!
Get out! Get out!
He came back for you.
Why are you doing this?
Get out!
-Grandma! Grandma!
-Get out!
Let's leave.
Get out!
Tom!
Mama...
We are not freaks!
Go.
Jung, you think the man I love come to me?
I don't think so.
I can see the stupidity on his face!
Jung!
Dow, I have come for you.
Dow, please come out.
Dow, I heard someone calling your name.
If there are a million stars.
I just hope one would listen to me.
It's him!
See? The guy I miss
is not stupid like someone around here.
Dow, you call me stupid?
-Who is it?
-That guy from Chiang Mai team.
Tonight we all see starlight.
As long as the sky is bright.
Enough, I'm here.
Dow.
How did you get here?
I took a bus to Mo Chit station.
And take another bus here.
You have come so far...
I didn't think I would find you.
Now I'm here. Still miss me?
I still miss you, but can I go inside?
Oh, sorry I forgot.
Everybody.
This is Fandee-Fanden.
This is Jung, and Tom.
Hello.
Oh, that Chinese boy.
Absurd!
His name is Piak.
Or call him Fandee-Fanden.
My head is not bald yet.
So... what are you doing here?
I was looking for my girlfriend.
Her name is Dow.
I love her so much. She's hot.
Again?
Let's go, Tom. Let's sleep somewhere else.
I don’t want to be the third wheel here.
Dow.
Dow, give yourself to me.
It won't hurt.
Wait, wait.
I'm not ready.
Just a little.
Dow! Dow!
-Wait.
-Dow.
I have never... Will I get pregnant?
No.
Don't!
Wait.
Dow!
Ouch.
Dow! Dow!
And yet you said you never.
Mama.
Come in, it's not locked.
What's up Noina?
I come to tell you, that everything...
it's my fault.
If I'm not in the team,
all of this wouldn’t have happened.
And if I didn't let myself
go with Khan Tok
it wouldn't happen.
What do you want to do?
You were both drunk, weren’t you?
Yes,
I was so wasted.
And I lost my conscious.
Had no strength to protect myself.
What do you want?
I want to resign.
What?
Mama, do you know...
my part...
is not ready to play volleyball.
Think about it.
Khan Tok...
screwed me hard.
Can you imagine...
Corn,
durian,
cheese...
falling down the floor?
Enough, I'm going to throw up.
It's up to you.
I'm not talking to you.
Mui, I...
Don't tell me,
You come to resign too.
Yes, I'm the cause of this.
I'm leaving now.
-Mui.
Do you know Khan Tok
and Noina is resigning...
I know.
And what did you say?
What do you think?
Not enough players, we can't play.
Mui!
Why did you say that?
I thought it through, Nu.
Now go.
Yes.
Think about it, Mui.
What are we going to do?
I think we just have to lay low.
Give Mui some times to think...
and then go back to her again.
I really don't get it.
Why she gives up easily?
Chart.
Why don't you try to talk to Mui?
She might change her mind.
Nu, she won't.
But Mui listens to you.
Chart, don't you know Mui loves you?
I know it for a long time.
-Yes?
-Yes.
I have been so stupid!
I told her that I like her as a friend.
What?
Really?
You both deserve each other!
Piss me off!
Nu!
What?
-What?
-Stop.
Nu!
It... it's leaking.
Put down your money. Fingers crossed.
Mod, you dealt me such bad cards.
Selling a lot, Papa?
-Mama, did you?
-I did.
You're really lovely.
Jung. I love you all.
Take care of the team.
It's my fault.
The team is broken up because of me.
I'm bad.
Goodbye.
Mui!
Jung, what's wrong with Mui?
Something happened. He said goodbye.
Goodbye?
What?
Mui!
Mui! Mui!
-Mui! Mui!
-Don't die.
Mui! Mui!
-Mui!
-Guys!
He drank shampoo to commit suicide!
What?
Mui! Mui!
I'll give him CPR.
Mui!
Nu, stop it. You're killing him.
Mui! Mui!
Mui!
What do we do now?
Bitch! You can tell me
if you wanna play cards.
Noina! Mui...
Mui drank shampoo to kill himself.
Huh? Mama killed himself?
Stand back.
Mama! Mama! Mama!
Don't just watch.
Anyone gave him a mouth-to-mouth?
No.
I'll do it.
Go on.
I'm not dead.
Wow!
Mui's alive.
He's alive.
Thank you for caring about me.
Mui.
Why did you have to kill yourself?
I didn't.
I just wanna see what you'd do.
Huh?
Too expensive.
Thank you for loving one another.
Jung.
Yes?
Do you love Dow and Parn?
I do.
What about you?
Khan Tok.
Do you love Noina?
I do.
Noina, do you love Khan Tok?
Of course. He's my hubby.
-Bitch!
-I munched his nose.
Thank you, once again.
Do you love me?
We do!
Do you still love playing volleyball?
The most!
Very good! So...
Tomorrow, be punctual. Don't be late.
Don't skip the practice.
Don't dawdle. Got it?
Why didn't you just call me?
You wasted the shampoo.
-We're leaving.
-Go.Go.
Take it, you plan master.
Don't dawdle.
Mui, don't do anything crazy again.
Alright.
Chart cares about me!
I killed two birds with one stone.
Boy up. Boy down.
Iron Ladies!
Alright, everyone.
I'm glad to see you all as a team again.
No matter what will happen today.
Keep on walking.
We'll reach our dream together.
We gotta fight.
We gotta fight. Gotta fight to win!
Go!
Welcome to the 28th
National Sports Competition.
Paknam Po Games.
Next, we'll have
the volleyball men's match.
The final match of region seven Suphanburi
And region five Lampang...
Or the Iron Ladies!
LAMPANG - SUPHANBURI
Yay!
Down!
Damn it!
Teamwork, alright?
Chart! Chart! Chart!
-Hurry up, Chart!
-Catch!
LAMPANG 5-0 SUPHANBURI
Suphanburi. Fight!
LAMPANG 7-3 SUPHANBURI
Grandma is cheering for you.
Tom!
My nephew. Cheer for him!
Tom! There he is.
Mama is cheering for you, Tom.
-Do you Miss him?
-Climb down there.
Come on. Climb?
Tom!
Aunty, you're blocking my view. Get out.
Ma, let's go.
Get out!
Tom, Grandma is cheering for you!
Tom!
He's pretty good.
Mama...
Why is he staring at me?
What's the big deal. Move. Go.
You can stare at me.
Hello.
He's my nephew.
-Tom, Mama is here.
-Where are you going?
I'm going to dance.
Mama!
Mhuay, come here.
Another one.
Hurry up.
Parn!
Parn, keep it up!
Mommy's here. Keep it up!
Keep it up! Mommy's here.
Parn! Parn! I'm bringing you fresh milk.
-Noina, fight!
-Noina!
Noina!
Are you ok?
Your hubby's here.
Fight!
Iron Ladies!
Jung!
Mommy's here!
Daddy's here!
Dad!
I'm so glad!
I flew from Saudi Arabia.
Win the game. Get the cup.
May the team win. Girls, make some noise!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
-Coach Eew, Hello.
-Hi.
-Your hubby?
-Yes, he is.
He's from..
-He's from...
-Saudi Arabia.
He's from Saudi Arabia.
Yes.
-Coach Eew is fainting!
-Coach Bee!
Coach Bee!
It might be too hot.
-Too hot.
-Will The team win?
-Is That Your dad?
-Yes.
He's damn ugly.
-Your father?
-I'm heartbroken.
I'm heartbroken.
LAMPANG 10-9 SUPHANBURI
Damn it!
LAMPANG 10-11 SUPHANBURI
Coach, they're beating us.
Hey! hey!
Eyes on the ball! Eyes on the ball!
Address one another by names!
LAMPANG 4-1 SUPHANBURI
LAMPANG 2-0 SUPHANBURI
Dow!
I'm cheering for you.
I've got custard apple and longan for you.
I love you!
Come here, everyone.
Remember, this match is about dignity.
We can't be defeated by queers.
Dig.
Dow!
Dow! Get up!
Fandee-Fanden.
Dow!
Dow! Get up!
They can ruin the reputation
of volleyball.
Remember, to be defeated by queers...
-Isn't an option.
-Yes, sir.
Dow, catch! Dow, catch!
Dow!
Are you calling for your dad?
I know that you love me.
I'm in a game. Sit down! Sit!
Sit! Sit!
Sit down.
-Hey!
-Yes.
Are you in?
Suphanburi. Fight!
LAMPANG 5-10 SUPHANBURI
Queer!
-Queer!
-Buff!
Bang-rachan queer!
Are you insulting me?
-Are you insulting me?
-Calm down!
Fight, Noina.
Noina. Fight.
Noina!
Noina.
Come here!
Noina!
LAMPANG 4-6 SUPHANBURI
LAMPANG 12-13 SUPHANBURI
Come here!
Everyone, listen to me.
I know that you're all tired.
But we have to put a good fight.
Because we've come so far.
LAMPANG 13-13 SUPHANBURI
Although we aren't strong like them,
But I believe...
Our spirits can beat them.
Ready.
All the way. Iron...
Iron Ladies!
The winner of today is region five.
From Lampang. Iron Ladies!
After we won the Paknam Po Games,
We're famous.
We're featured in interviews
and television programs.
Our story was made into movie.
After the dream was accomplished,
We returned to our normal lives.
But we still dream that one day
We'll reunite as a team.
It's good stuff, Mui.
You bitch! You're even better than me.
Turn on the fan!
-Dao.
-No!
Don't be too rough.
I told you not to be aggressive.
-Hey!
-What was that?
Shit. Who smacked my balls?
I take all the blame.
I can't take care of my team.
I love you all.
My whole world is for you, Chart.
Oh, I shouldn't make it funny?
Tom, can I have a shot?
Your jaw is so undefined. Come on.
-Jung, Parn, she's so snatched!
-Damn, she's on point.
I want Angelina Jolie's lips.
Please give it up for the Iron Ladies!
Make way!
Madame Jang, allow me to touch you.
This is my junk!
I want you to see my dick...
Wait, that wasn't in the script!
They're so awesome.
They play so well.