Your Holiness!
Two handsome temple boys are here!
Are you up?
-Monk Jazz!
-Your Holiness!
-You'll be late for almsgiving.
Kor, moor the boat.
-Careful.
-This rock here.
Your Holiness! Monk Jazz!
He's rigorous.
He even meditates!
Enough about me. What about you two?
Since our return from Bangkok,
you two have really been dressing up.
Your Holiness, this isn't much.
When will you stop your pilgrimage?
We're tired of taking a boat
to pick you up here.
-Your Holiness.
-We want to go back to Bangkok.
We want to go to Bangkok.
It's nice here.
No fuss. Calm.
It's also beautiful.
Let's go. It's late.
Careful.
Please, Your Holiness.
-Will you be all right?
-Take him.
Come, Your Holiness.
Get in. Get in.
Hold tight.
No need to hurry. Just go leisurely.
I like it here. It makes us feel calm.
The place is serene.
I want to stay here for a year.
-Isn't it too long, a year?
-What time is it?
It's 6:00 a.m.
Calm down. Paddle carefully.
Your Holiness, it's 9:00 a.m.
No hurry.
If we don't hurry, when will we arrive?
Humans.
We're born with a hot temper.
We want to arrive to destination quickly.
We want to do things quickly.
And it turns into temper.
It will end badly.
When the water runs still,
we feel calm.
When you see that water
move up towards you,
you feel scared.
It's just water all the same.
Go calmly.
Let your mind be at ease.
Be conscious.
It's 10:00 a.m., Your Holiness.
It's 10:00 a.m., so what?
I told you to stay calm.
Like the old proverb says,
"Slow and steady wins the race."
-No hurry.
No hurry, Kor.
We've arrived. No need to say anything.
-You need a hand?
-I can do it.
-Careful, Your Holiness.
-Careful!
Will you be all right?
-We'll help.
-I'll do it myself.
Thank you all so much
for making me miss the alms.
You said not to hurry.
You said we're not late.
I wanted you all to be calm.
Are you sure you won't be hungry?
I've been here for a long time.
Once, I starved for ten days.
I was fine with it.
Are you sure you won't be hungry?
You paddled too slowly!
Monk Jazz!
Here we come!
Monk Jazz, here we come!
On a long-tailed boat, too!
You're sitting still.
Get up! Hurry!
Hurry! Hurry!
Your Holiness! Hurry! Hurry!
Monk Jazz!
Hurry! Your Holiness!
Your Holiness! Hurry! Hurry!
Saisin.
Do you remember when we went
to receive alms in Bangkok?
Of course, I do.
That time when we got lost, right?
But we finally found our way
back to the temple.
Let me ask you frankly.
What's with you and Bangkok?
Why do you really want to go back there?
Bangkok is chaotic,
unlike the countryside.
Everywhere is good and beautiful.
Even the mountain has a heart attack.
-It's heart-shaped, Your Holiness.
-That's right. I was wrong.
Your Holiness, I'll tell you what.
The reason why I want to go to Bangkok
is because I want to be...
Saisin, you tell him.
Why me? You tell him.
I don't know what you want to be.
A celebrity maybe?
How do you know?
You say that everyday.
You two can't be celebrities.
We can, Your Holiness.
We've come up with the title of a movie.
What is it?
Blow Till You Groan.
"Glow" not "Groan"!
Yeah, yeah.
I think you'll be better in this one.
What is it?
So Brutal, So Fucking Duck.
Action!
Ducks are small.
So Brutal, So Fucking Duck.
This is fine too.
-Not good when you stoop.
-Again then.
-Time for alms. Quickly!
-Watch us first!
-What?
-Namo, you didn't do it well.
-You do it.
-Your Holiness.
So Brutal, So Fucking Duck.
Lower! Ducks are small.
-Your waist, it won't do.
-How?
So Brutal, So Fucking Duck.
May you live long and...
...fucking duck.
I mean, prosper.
You're in time for breakfast!
You can have breakfast today!
Are you happy?
Your Holiness?
How do you feel, Your Holiness?
Say what's on your mind.
Next time, can we use a paddle boat?
This is faster!
This is quick, Your Holiness.
Was that Kor or Vin Diesel?
He was going too fast!
Your Holiness, can I ask you something?
When will you stop your meditation?
I've been meditating here.
It feels so good.
When the place is good,
you don't leave that place, right?
How long will you stay here?
Three months.
-Eight months.
-Eight?
-Ten months.
-Ten months?
You stay alone then?
I've been waiting for you to say that.
-You say it yourself.
-Maybe a year and a half.
A year and a half!
-Goodbye.
-I'll leave.
-I haven't eaten yet.
Sorry.
I'm going, Your Holiness!
What you're taking now is worse.
-Quickly.
-Quickly, Kor.
Quickly!
What is this?
You said you would stay for ten months.
Well, you're done after just one day.
Quickly! Quick!
It took us so long.
Are you all right, Your Holiness?
Heard you didn't get any sleep last night.
Did someone come to stay with you?
I heard there were three of them.
How did you know?
Well...
Your Holiness, are you sure
Monk Chongruai is here?
Yes.
Before coming here,
I called him.
Where are you going?
You don't wait for us.
Quickly.
-It's heavy.
-Quick.
-This stuff is heavy.
BUDDHA VADI
Oh, God!
Can't take it anymore!
Your Holiness.
Monk Chongruai.
Your Holiness!
Monk Jazz.
Why didn't you call my name?
Why did you all come so quietly?
How was that quiet?
I plan to go back
to the temple in the country.
I heard that you became the monk
here at this temple.
So I came to visit you.
How have you been?
Do you want a password?
There's no WiFi here.
And the WiFi...
WiFi? Did you ask?
I did not!
Let's do this.
Let's go sit somewhere and talk.
Here.
Your Holiness,
why did you choose to stay here?
People often redeem their vows
to Buddha here.
Around 10,000 firecrackers
go off every day.
Bang! Bang! Bang! Always so loud.
1,000 FIRECRACKERS
FOR SUCCESS IN WORK, WEALTH, AND LOVE
It's giddy, dull, and deafening.
That's why.
There's so many things here.
Since you're here,
I would like to ask you for help.
Many years ago, there was a woman
who left her son at this temple.
He was ordained as a novice monk
and stayed for years.
I want your help
taking this kid to Bangkok
so that he can go find his father.
It'd be inconvenient.
I must return to the temple.
Well, if you agreed, I'd feel at ease.
I'll leave it to you then.
No, I can't do it.
Good. Good.
I feel at ease now.
After taking him to Bangkok,
if you want to go on a pilgrimage,
then it's up to you.
Good. Good.
All right then.
You said yes earlier, and now you tell me
you can't? What do you want then?
Don't confuse me.
No, no. I can't.
Good, good.
Well, then I'll give you this now.
Here.
Go find him.
He's Abbot Chaiya.
A preacher.
Accumulation of merit for yourself
can be done simply by
making a donation to the temple.
Your face will be wrinkle free.
-Do you like that?
-Yes!
People say merit
can help with everything.
It helps people be normal.
You'll stand out and be dignified
because you've made merit.
He knows everyone in Bangkok.
All right.
I'll leave it to you.
Kid.
Yes.
Come here.
Wait. Pay respect to Monk Jazz.
And then Monk Jazz will...
Not here. That way.
That way, son. All right.
Very endearing.
Please take care of him.
Be safe, son.
Your Holiness, can I ask you something?
Is he well-behaved?
Around 5:00 a.m.
Thanks a lot.
What is there around 5:00 a.m.?
It's 6:00 a.m. after 5:00 a.m.
That's even worse.
Behave. Don't get carried away in Bangkok.
Don't go outside the temple.
There's a lot of traffic in Bangkok.
You might get hit by a car.
Monk Jazz, please take care of him.
He can be stubborn.
Your Holiness.
Please don't worry.
I'll take care of him.
I heard it too. She will come perform
near the temple.
I saw the signboard.
I said I will take care of him.
I got it. You mean the singer,
Lamyai Haithongkham, right?
Goodbye then.
Your Holiness.
The outfit for Bangkok is ready.
-Handsome, cool, and awesome?
-Awesome?
You're wearing this in Bangkok?
-Why?
-For the producer, Poj Arnon.
That's right.
-What if you meet other producers?
-What?
Yes. Good luck, everyone.
Bangkok!
This.
A society where everyone
plays with their phones.
Look.
All with their phones.
You.
You. Why are you lowering your head?
I don't have a phone. I'm just sleepy.
Monks can fall down.
So can novice monks.
You.
Monk Eakachai! Still a monk?
Your Holiness.
Yes.
You said you'd leave monkhood a while ago.
Your Holiness.
I thought I would do that,
but I changed my mind.
Since I got ordained and studied,
I decided to stay.
My parents said it's better for me
to stay, which is true.
I wanted to study more dharma.
I studied in Surat Thani for three months.
Told my folks I'd be a monk
the rest of my life.
And he is...
This is Monk Ple.
I'm from Lamphun.
I moved to Chiang Mai.
I came to Bangkok to study dharma.
At first, I didn't know anyone.
I met Monk Eak. He's so nice.
Monk Ple is nice. He's a good monk.
So good, Your Holiness. It's true.
Well...
What are you doing here in Bangkok?
I'm here to take him to meet Abbot Chaiya.
Hello, Monk Sun.
Hey, Ekachai. Who have you brought here?
This is Monk Jazz.
He's here to meet Abbot Chaiya.
I accompanied this kid
to meet His Holiness.
Today's not good.
His Holiness is very sick.
Please come back another time.
We came from the province.
That's all right.
Please stay the night here.
Wait for His Holiness to get better
so you can talk.
It's not expensive. 500 baht a night.
I'll go sleep at Phuwing Hotel.
It's only 350 baht a night.
The soap is so tiny there.
You're funny like me. I like that.
Well, then please. Hope you find a place
to sleep with trouble.
With no trouble?
Many mosquitoes here. No AC.
It's not comfortable.
We'll be fine.
We'll stay at the temple again?
But it's fine too.
We can enjoy the nightlife.
Hell of a beat, you two.
Please, make yourselves at home.
Your Holiness.
Your Holiness, it's all right.
Your Holiness, calm down!
Your Holiness!
Your Holiness! Doctor!
What? Your Holiness?
I'm gonna die because of you.
Oh, sorry.
I thought you were having a heart attack,
so I performed CPR.
Change the caretaker.
Your Holiness, please give me
another chance.
Ble, how did you end up at this temple?
Actually, I plan to be ordained here.
But it's not time yet.
So I stay here to prepare myself.
Nakhee.
Do you have a husband?
No, I don't.
Nakhee,
all this time,
though you've had no feelings for me,
please remember this.
In our other lives,
I will still love you.
Nakhee,
though we are not meant to be together,
I...
will keep my legs open.
Will keep waiting for you.
Ble!
What's wrong?
I don't know.
-I'm really going.
-Going where?
Anywhere! I'm a grown-up.
-I'm going.
-For God's sake.
Was I dreaming?
-What's up?
-They're here.
Your Holiness.
Please take them here.
Please.
This way please.
You're Monk Jazz, right? You were on TV.
Yes.
You're famous.
Will you be a dealer for Heaven Mic?
Your Holiness.
Should we stop talking about Mic?
All right.
Do you keep water lizards as pets?
Your Holiness, you're a monk.
I will knock you all out.
Knock us all out? You're picking a fight.
Monk Sun, call all temple boys.
Gather everyone. Assemble! Quick!
Wait. Wait.
Your Holiness.
We've come in peace.
All right.
So you don't dare!
This is me again. Please come now!
Anything to add?
No, Your Holiness.
If not, then what has brought you here?
I came to visit Monk Chongruai
in the province.
And he asked me
to take to this novice to meet
Abbot Chaiya.
What's your name?
My name is Pleum. I'm four years old.
My mom's name is...
Hormone.
But I don't know my father
because my mother has many husbands.
My special talent is,
I can chant homage to Buddha.
Namo Tassa, Bhagavato--
No need, Novice. It's ok.
Here's your tea, Your Holiness.
Please pass it on.
Are you Ble?
Jazz?
-You should fight him solo.
-As Thai teens, we should pummel him.
You start. I follow.
If he falls, I'll strike again.
I'll take care of it. Do everything
like movie theater staff.
-Iced coffee?
-Damn, iced coffee?
Really?
I'm not drinking this!
Can I stab you with a straw?
You're new. Don't act up.
Don't stay still. Don't be a coward.
Look at me when you talk to me!
Why are you looking at me?
-You told me to.
-I'm not eating pork.
I mean, looking at your face.
Fermented sausage on my face?
I mean, staring at your face.
Looking at the face then?
Wanna pack your stuff and go home?
Don't be nosy, or you'll get hurt.
You'll get blood on your shirt.
-You, just go home!
-You asshole!
Okay, I'm leaving then.
You bastards.
You called me an asshole?
Oh, God...
Step away.
There are so many of them.
Kneel at my feet.
-What?
-Kneel at my feet.
-Last year, someone said that to me.
-Said what?
"Kneel at my feet."
Hope I don't have to say
what I did to him.
I don't have to say it!
I don't have to say much.
He's bold.
Hit here, here, and here.
And then, bam!
-Why are you shaking?
-I'm cold 'cause of AC.
Don't shake.
Do you have a problem with my bro?
We'll have a long conversation.
Enough. I got excited.
Are you afraid of me?
I think I am.
Yes.
I heard you were ordained as a monk.
I almost got to be ordained,
but something happened.
What thing?
That day...
Stop!
You can't be ordained yet.
You must be curious who I am.
It's me, Lovesick.
-You can't be ordained yet.
-Why?
You got my friend pregnant.
-Who?
-You!
Who got pregnant?
Hormone!
Hormone?
Jazz, I'm pregnant.
Three months, four days, five hours,
twenty minutes
-pregnant.
-Yes.
I can be a witness.
Jazz, are you all right?
Should the baby die?
You don't have a father. Should you?
Don't worry.
Jazz!
What's wrong, Your Holiness?
Did you really do it?
I was drunk. Can't recall.
God helps those who help themselves.
I'm happy for you.
You get to meet your son today.
Oh, God!
This is not my son.
How can he not be?
Tell him your mother's name.
My mother's name is Hormone.
Not true.
My son doesn't look like this.
I'm leaving then.
I'll take my leave too.
Monk Jazz.
Don't hurry back.
Please stay with Novice
for a few more days.
That's right. I don't want to go back.
Haven't met Poj Arnon yet.
You want to meet Poj Arnon?
Poj Arnon comes to this temple often.
Does he come to make merit?
To get rid of misfortune.
-Why?
-Too much criticism on the Net.
-Hello, Song.
-What's up, Ble?
You know who I met today?
How would I know? Who did you meet?
-I met Nakhee.
-Nakhee?
-And Jazz.
-Jazz?
-Monk Jazz.
-He's a monk now?
He brought me something.
What is it?
-A child.
-A child?
He said Hormone and I are the parents.
You and Hormone are the kid's parents?
You should get a DNA test.
What is DNA?
You're so stupid!
I don't know either.
I only know you need
that child's hair for the test
to find out who the father is.
-Where is this test?
-At the hospital, stupid!
Since I became friends with you guys,
-I've become smarter.
-That's for sure.
Nam, right?
-Yes.
-Rain water.
Pus.
Pus leaks everywhere she goes.
From her wounds.
It just leaks.
What's up?
There's a ghost at my house,
Your Holiness.
Everywhere in your house?
Yes, everywhere.
At the dressing table too?
Yes, there too.
And your bedroom?
Yes, bedroom too.
You see a ghost wherever
there's a mirror, right?
Yes, Your Holiness.
Evidently.
I'm a monk.
It's not my business to deal with ghosts.
Please help me, Your Holiness.
-Please sympathize with me.
-People come and ask for help.
We shouldn't ignore that.
What's up, Monk Jazz?
I'm here to say goodbye.
Wait.
The province will always be there.
You can go back anytime.
Can you please stay and help me?
If you want my help, then I'm glad.
Promise me?
Yes.
Please help deal with the ghost
at Nam's house.
Ghost!
Clearly!
Take care of it! Quick, Your Holiness!
Haunted right at the front door!
You!
Why are you scared?
This is Nam
the owner of this house, not a ghost.
Please.
Are we really going in there?
Come on in.
No...
No, Your Holiness.
I'm scared.
It's dark.
-Oh, God!
-Clearly, Your Holiness.
Tie it with holy thread.
You don't have to be scared.
This is my little sister.
Her name is Noona.
She's living, right?
Yes, 100%. Give them your hand.
Both of them.
A monk can't touch women.
Oh, gosh.
Please come in.
Gosh.
Come on in.
Your Holiness, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
Gosh!
Put away the holy thread.
Time to use this.
Go ahead, Your Holiness.
Don't be afraid.
This is my son.
His name is Chaonai.
Say hi to Your Holiness.
Hello, Your Holiness.
Come on, the ghost is upstairs.
Help!
Help! Please help!
It's so scary.
Go away from this house!
Still here?
Damn! I'm not a ghost!
Stop throwing rice at me! It hurts!
You're not a ghost?
A ghost could be this beautiful?
Nam, Noona, please help me.
It's so scary. Please help.
The ghost is upstairs.
Your Holiness,
you're really going up there?
Stop pushing me.
God, I can't take it anymore.
I'm scared.
Scared me.
Which room?
This one.
Okay.
Your Holiness! I said the other room.
Why didn't you go in the other room?
Your Holiness! Ghost!
Your Holiness!
I see nothing.
Where did it go?
It was just right here!
Where?
Loud and clear, Namo.
-You were in the picture in that room?
-Yes.
-So you're a ghost?
-Your Holiness!
-I'm going.
Go! Quick!
Go. Go.
You.
It's wrong, what you're doing.
Why are you haunting
this scary-looking family?
Please go haunt some other place.
I'm not haunting them.
Give me a talisman.
-It's not with me.
-Give me a talisman.
Are you gonna kick me out?
You're being defiant.
Defiant.
That's the wrong side. The other side.
Put it away. It doesn't work.
If you want to get out alive,
have these two come in this room.
Why?
You want to be dead?
Of course not.
A living human shouldn't be this stupid.
So your skirt got stuck in the door.
Your Holiness! Run!
Thanks!
A ghost shouldn't be this stupid!
Why are you stepping on it?
Go.
You must die first.
Go! Quickly!
I'm going. Bye.
This damn skirt!
Should have taken it off when I was dead.
Wait for me! I'm gonna get you,
Your Holiness!
How were things at Nam's?
Look at my face.
It was so scary there.
A ghost?
The people in that house.
Everyone looks so creepy there.
Don't blame her. It's nobody's fault,
what they're born with.
They have a face like that because they
did many bad things in their past lives.
They killed many toads.
Face?
Monk Jazz, what are you doing here?
I'm here to see Novice Pleum.
He's around here somewhere.
Don't force yourself.
You want me to help?
Please do.
Novice.
I want you all to be quiet.
Novice. Don't fight.
Calm down. Sit down first.
Novice! Sit down first.
Sit down! Don't fight!
-Novice!
-Don't fight.
Sit down! Here's a snake!
Khob!
What's wrong?
I'm practicing my dance skills.
-Am I doing okay?
-Look at me.
A nice waist you've got there.
-Where are you going?
-I'm going to see His Holiness.
-Where are all the novices?
-They're in class.
Take me there.
Why don't you go there yourself?
-Will you take me or see His Lameness?
-"Holiness."
Okay.
-Are you going or what?
-Okay then.
You're easy to persuade.
How are my dance steps?
Enough, do it just like me.
-Here, here.
-Twist.
Yeah, twist.
Twist some more?
Like this?
Enough, you.
-When will we arrive?
-Here we are.
Where are all the kids?
Just turn left and here there are.
Oh, no!
I forgot my appointment with His Holiness.
Just go in there yourself.
Gosh, I forgot.
Who is it?
Don't cry.
-What are you doing?
-Don't cry.
Stay still!
Let me have a look.
What are you doing?
You have no hair?
I'm being ordained.
What can I use for a DNA test?
You have no armpit hair.
-How about your nuts?
-I don't know.
What are you doing?
I'll tell His Holiness.
Shut up.
How can you wear boxers?
I keep it a secret.
Damn, yours is bigger than mine.
-Can you dance?
-Not very well.
I bought love online. My heart is for you.
You said "not very well."
Turn around.
-Can you sing?
-Yes.
-A song by Ble Patumrach.
-Okay.
To me,
you're precious...
-Facebook...
-has no response...
-Hug you,
-for the last time.
-I'm not a coward,
-and I can't win her heart.
It's not Ble Patumrach's.
It's by Zack Chumphae.
You're like me when I was young.
Or are you my son?
-You want to have a father?
-Yes.
Try hugging me.
Wait! I forgot.
What's up, Ble?
Hello, Song. Novice has no hair.
You idiot!
Do you have some cotton swabs?
Open his mouth.
Swab the bulge of his cheeks
with cotton swabs.
Stay still!
Open your mouth.
When you're done,
you keep these cotton swabs safe.
That's the DNA.
Bring them to the hospital for a test.
See if the DNA matches with yours, okay?
Okay, I got it.
Whose car is that?
His Holiness is in there too.
Yeah, Your Holiness.
No, no need.
It's fine. Go, go.
I would have been back a long time ago,
but Sun...
Until the next morning.
I enjoyed that.
Yeah, Your Holiness.
Where have you been, Your Holiness?
Oh, well, I was invited out.
You got up early.
I was out since yesterday.
I was invited out to chant prayers
called Yavikarajanang.
What is it called?
Yavikarajanang.
It's the prayers chanted at night.
They exist, these prayers?
Yes, they do.
You haven't mastered them yet.
Where are you going?
It's to receive alms.
Why do you have to do that?
Why is that?
People will come giving alms
at the temple.
Yes, yes. He doesn't know.
Your Holiness.
Let Monk Jazz go receive alms.
We should go back to our rooms,
or we will be hungover.
What hangover?
Arahang Samma Sammasabuddho Bhagava
-Let's go, Your Holiness.
-Yeah, yeah.
Your Holiness!
Your Holiness, you're always like this.
Stay focused, Your Holiness.
Go straight. Be still.
-Be still.
-They were drinking.
Your Holiness, they stink of liquor.
Arahang Samma
-Holy--
-Don't say it.
I know.
Your Holiness.
That Yavikarajanang prayer.
Does it really exist?
Can a monk leave his temple late at night?
He said he was being invited out.
So that's that.
What kind of invitation at that hour?
Your Holiness, please.
Today's my son's birthday.
May you live long and prosper.
Were you in that viral video
where you swore at a policeman?
DO NOT IMITATE.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
Why did you do that?
I just recalled, so I asked.
What do you want?
Hey, you!
I'm ordained. I'm a monk.
Good for you. Otherwise, you'd be dead.
I cursed at a policeman.
Why not at a monk?
-Did you bring a razor?
-Why do you need it?
-To shave my head so I can fight a monk.
-People can get angry.
It's normal to be mad.
But you have to be conscious.
I understand what you did.
But you have to know this.
If you've done 100 good things,
and you do one bad thing,
nobody will think about
all the good things you've done.
You do one bad thing,
it will destroy all the good things
that you've done.
Think carefully before doing anything.
Be conscious.
Be rational, not emotional.
After listening to me,
I hope you understand this better.
-Any question?
-Take off your robe and fight me.
Go! Go!
Please, Your Holiness.
Please, Your Holiness. Please, get in.
Where is he going again?
Your Holiness!
I saw the same car picking up His Holiness
and his crew again.
They were probably invited out.
What invitation at this hour?
Don't you want to know
where they're going?
I do, but it's none of my business.
Let's do this. You don't have to butt in.
We'll find out for you.
Is that good?
It's all good, except when you said
I didn't have to butt in.
Your Holiness,
you don't have to believe in our talent.
Just trust us.
This is not a thing anymore.
What's in now?
What is this?
We're going.
Please, Your Holiness.
Walk carefully.
Your Holiness.
I think we need an escalator here.
Be patient.
Wait for the sales of Heaven Mic to go up.
I'm waiting for that.
Hurry, Your Holiness. You'll be late.
You took a bath or what?
Frankly, I forgot.
Please get some rest...
or you'll have a hangover.
What hangover?
Arahang Samma Sambuddho Bhagava
The morning comes, and you've just arrived
You denied that you were not drinking
But, damn, you reek of alcohol.
Amen.
Oh, Your Holiness.
He got the whole prayer.
I'm leaving then.
Monk Jazz,
that prayer,
when you have time, write it down for me.
Please.
Yes.
Smelly, very smelly.
It's gastroesophageal reflux disease.
Go, go.
Here's the target.
-Hello, Your Holiness.
Do you remember us?
Sang and Kang.
Exactly.
How can I forget you?
Bastards like you two,
I remember them well.
Thank you for the honor.
Have you been well?
Yes, Your Holiness.
I heard Monk Jazz
has come to Bangkok, right?
Yes, I met him last week.
That's right. He was with a novice monk.
A very cute little boy.
But Monk Jazz is not here.
Where is he then?
He's at
the Dharmathikarn Benchamarachasit...
Vivekvikaramon Praditmongkol Temple.
Yes.
Right.
You all...
you have to pay attention in class today.
Wait.
You should join the Army
with all your walking.
You told us to watch all novice monks.
No need to do it that seriously,
like a military parade.
Just go stand like
some soldiers over there.
Do you know
why your parents sent you to study here?
Because they want you
to learn about dharma
and religion.
When you grow up,
you'll have moral codes in your heart.
And, in the future,
you'll be good citizens in our society.
-Understood?
-Yes.
We have Heaven Mask and Hell Mask.
You do bad things,
you get Hell Mask.
-Good deeds for Heaven Mask.
-3,500 baht.
-Masks are very in now.
-Your Holiness.
Where are you going?
I'll check the offerings made for lunch.
What are you doing?
I'm feeding Pleum.
Say hello to His Holiness.
Hello.
Go the result of the DNA test?
Not yet.
I must take care of him for now.
I feel sorry for him.
He doesn't have a father.
And his mother
is only interested in her lovers.
I'll tell you something.
Have you heard of this poem?
"Oh, a raven left its egg
for a crow to hatch.
A crow loved the baby,
believed it was its own,
feeding the baby,
taking very good care of it."
Just a verse is enough.
You cited almost the whole thing.
"Put another's kid on your elbow,
he'll creep on it."
No. "Put another's child in your bosom,
he'll creep out at your elbow."
-Didn't sleep. Meniere's disease.
-You're rambling.
Any of you remembers how long
you've been ordained?
How long have you been ordained?
Twenty years.
Twenty? How old are you?
One year old.
Ordained for 20 years, and you're one.
Up to you then.
I want to go back and see my mom.
-Why are you crying?
-I want to see Mommy.
Do you want rice in iced water?
Who wants to go home?
I want to go home.
Sing the national anthem.
Okay. Go. That's great, everyone.
You're good, Monk Jazz.
You can deal with them well.
I'm not good.
I'm just very good.
-What's up, Ble?
-Your Holiness,
I've brought friends
who want to be ordained.
You two, get up here.
Here they are.
What's your name?
Songkran Laiproi.
I can't let you be ordained.
Your Holiness!
Why?
You can't keep your face
and your body clean.
I'm afraid it will damage Buddhism.
Even Buddha was ordained for Angulimala.
But Angulimala didn't have any tattoo.
See this, Your Holiness?
See? Here?
-Your mother?
-Your Holiness!
It's a woman's face. I just assumed.
You're right! I just called to you.
I won't ordain you.
-You know in what field I finished school?
-What field?
You don't have to know that.
But will you finish this thing between us?
Yes, let's finish it.
But I don't want to!
Why do you judge on appearances?
Why not judge the inner self?
-How's the inner self?
-This is how it is!
Even more tattoos.
You want to finish this?
I finished a while ago.
I'm going.
Your Holiness!
You won't ordain us?
I can't do that. I'm done.
Your Holiness! Your Holiness!
Come back and ordain me!
He won't ordain us.
People nowadays are very bad.
They even steal money
from the donation box.
When these people die,
they will go to hell and turn
into hungry ghosts.
They even steal Buddha,
not just money from the donation box.
Then you must be careful.
If you sleep soundly,
someone might kidnap you.
Buddha's image.
I'm kidding.
Thank you, both policemen and soldiers,
for looking after our temple.
All right.
-Sun.
-Yes.
Bring me four Heaven Mics.
Thank you, Your Holiness.
It's 3,500 baht each.
I'm just teasing you.
Right.
Now, police and military cooperate well.
They always work alongside each other.
Right.
Is there any problem?
No, all goes smoothly.
Do you have any idea
if that person escaped via
Poipet or a natural border path?
I don't know.
-Are you scared? Boonchoo.
-Yes, Your Holiness.
Go find a new donation box.
This time, pick a big one
so those thieves can't carry it.
All right, Your Holiness.
This scripture contains 12 days...
What are you doing?
I'm tutoring him
for the Buddhist missionaries' exams.
This year, our temple has been
chosen to be an examination hall.
Would you like to take the test?
I'm afraid I'm not smart enough for that.
All this time,
when you solved problems,
how could you do that?
I guess that's my inner talent.
Come to think of it, this is good.
If I pass the exams
and get to be a missionary,
I can promote Buddhism worldwide.
People will get to know
about the religion,
its core, and how good it is.
Your Holiness!
Your Holiness.
Something bad happened.
Many policemen and soldiers are here.
Because the donation box
in the Vihara is missing.
Does Father know about this?
Yes, he does.
He was the one
who called the officials here.
These people are weird.
They steal even from the temple.
Your Holiness,
stop speaking in English.
It gives me a headache.
Well, then...
we have to keep our eyes and ears open.
Don't let those evil bastards
harm our temple and steal from us.
The signal is very bad.
No connection.
-What?
-Connection lost.
Why don't you use TrueMove H 5G like me?
The signal is great and no fuss.
Here, here. I'll let you see a live video.
Wait, Your Holiness.
Isn't there only 4.5G?
5G is not yet available.
It's 4.5G,
plus 0.5G from the goodness
of His Holiness.
So it's 5G, right?
Yeah.
Very advanced. What is it again?
TrueMove H 5G.
Perfect for good people
from the new generation, just like me.
Are you good in English?
I'm quite fine, just for a bit.
That's too easy.
What are you two cocking about?
No. No.
It's not "cock." It's "talk."
"Talk," Your Holiness.
"Talk."
You hair--
Two people. Not the right tone. Hair.
Oh, so that's "hair."
"People."
You two... cocking about what?
"Talk." "Talk."
"Talk." What are you two talking about?
-Sit down.
-Sorry.
Hey, Namo.
-Where are they going?
-Let's go take a look.
Yeah.
Now it's time for Rama and Sita
to enter the mediums' bodies.
Excuse me.
For people to live well and prosper.
Great!
That's why so many people have come here.
Why is it so crowded?
It's your turn to ask questions.
Here are my offerings.
What is it? Tell me.
Well, I--
You have power.
-You have power.
-No.
I've got cramps.
I'm all better.
She's very sacred. Look!
I... A spirit
was sucking your toe.
So I chased it away from my pavilion.
That's sacred.
I'm gonna ask you a question.
Your mother is an elephant?
Poor you.
But you look sad.
I'm asking you now.
I want to release my own song.
I want to be a singer.
Sing! Sing!
Change your career ambition.
Goodbye.
Why is she so sad?
It's your turn.
I want to ask Rama.
Husband.
Can you stay out of this?
Husband, please feel for me.
I will ask you then, Madam Pimp.
My name is Sita.
Yes, Sita.
I would like to know whether
my ex-lover, whom I was parted with,
and I can be together again.
Between my husband
and your lover, who's more handsome?
Rama.
Bitch.
Bitch...
Bi? Bit?
You will have a crush on a monk.
A crush on a monk?
Sita,
I would like know
if Rama can really float in the air.
Your Greatness, open up her world.
I can take a look?
Go now.
He can float thanks to these two balls.
Go to hell!
Ravana.
Did you see what I saw?
Clear as day.
Excuse me.
That was close.
-Yeah, sacred.
-That's true.
-Sacred.
-Excuse me.
Let's see if it's gonna work.
Your Holiness.
Saisin and I went for a walk
at the back of the temple.
You know what I came across?
-What?
-The pavilion of Sita and Rama.
What's that?
It's a pavilion of mediums.
So what?
"So what"?
If you do nothing, more and more people
will believe in mediums.
Then no one will believe in Buddhism.
This is for the good of Buddhism.
Namo, Saisin, listen.
There's a thin line separating
being well-intentioned and being nosy.
We may be well-intentioned,
but they might think
we are just being nosy.
Whatever they believe in,
it's their choice.
It's their happiness.
If we butt in,
then we are just nosy.
Let me go.
Let me go! Help!
Wait up!
Your Holiness!
You've got something urgent to tell me?
You know us, but, this time,
it's really big.
Saisin and I went to
the pavilion of Sita and Rama.
-I met Song.
-What about him?
He lured a woman to rape her.
Yes, it's true.
What goes around comes around.
Song will pay for what he's done.
PAVILION OF SITA AND RAMA
Please make way for His Holiness.
This is what I told you.
See? So many people here.
I can't find it.
Please make way for His Holiness.
-Please.
-Excuse me.
Please. Excuse us.
Your Holiness.
Why are you here?
You have to queue up.
Your Holiness, you have to do something.
They've gained popularity.
Yours might drop. Have you heard of...
Why?
Husband.
How dare you?
How can you disrespect me?
Can't you see?
I'm floating in the air.
I want you to come down so people know
how you can float.
Don't make me come down there,
or you'll be dead!
-Have you practiced long for this show?
-Jazz!
You disrespect me!
I'm Ravana.
Song.
You're a medium?
Ravana doesn't know me.
Calm down, Song.
Ravana.
-Song.
-What's up?
Ravana.
-Song.
-What's up?
What's up, Jazz?
You got all mixed up, huh?
Everyone, please listen to me.
Humans have brains,
but they have to be conscious too.
You can believe in anything,
but you have to be wise.
Don't be ignorant.
-Because belief--
-Is the song by Hin-Lek-Fai.
-Ignorance--
-Bodyslam song.
You have to remember that.
Click "Like."
And go download the songs.
This is so messed up.
Go, go, go.
Yes.
-Jazz.
-A one-minute talk enlightened me.
Monk Jazz!
Wait up! Monk Jazz!
Wait.
Whoever wants to go, just go.
And I will...
go!
It's because of Jazz.
Three of us can't handle him.
Yeah!
How is it three?
I'm a god.
I am...
Rama.
He's lost it.
Be conscious! Be a little more like that!
I don't care about Rama.
-You wanna come with me?
-Yes.
-Let's go then.
-You don't remember me?
Why are you here? Go!
Bring me down!
Who are you here for?
-I'm here to ask Rama to the station.
-Rama is not here.
There's just Pu.
I don't know. He's floating away.
He can float in the air?
Let's go.
You don't have to float in the air.
I'll bring you there.
Let's go.
Let go.
Lucky you were there to help.
People are able to realize the truth.
Next time, don't get me involved.
All right.
Jazz!
What is it, Nakhee?
I miss you,
even when you have no hair.
You're as handsome as--
As who?
Vin Diesel.
Why do temple boys say
I'm more like Si Quey?
In what way are you similar to Si Quey?
You...
Your talking about this in the temple,
I think
it's not okay.
All right.
I still remember it well.
The day you broke up with me.
-Wait. Let me aim for it.
-It's not going down.
Aim.
Next turn.
I don't play to win.
Really? You don't play to win.
Nakhee.
Let me interrupt you for a bit.
I have something to tell you.
Jazz, are you sure?
I'm here today--
You're gonna regret it.
I've come to tell you that...
we should break up!
That's harsh.
What?
Let's break up.
Let's break up!
What?
Let's break up
Serves her right. Hope her throat cracks.
Why?
Why do we have to break up?
We really can't get along.
Can't get along?
You come in every time.
How could you say that?
What you said is right.
I understand.
-How could he understand that?
-I know.
I know. Enough.
Enough.
Enough, you bitch!
You want to cry or talk? Pick one!
I'm sorry.
That's all right. I'll take care of you.
Yeah. You do it.
Zack!
No matter how much time has passed,
I always miss you. I never forget you.
Now I'm ordained.
I've left everything behind.
Love, greed,
anger, and lust.
Please get over it.
But if you miss me so much
that you can't take it,
how about we meet
at the back of the temple?
I walk past there every morning.
Don't forget to give alms.
All right.
Tomorrow, I'll get up early
to take a shower
and scrub every part of my body
to make sure I smell nice.
So I can take you--
So I can take the offerings to you.
Please excuse me.
Don't cry.
You shouldn't have said that.
Your Holiness, she's crying.
No matter how much time has passed,
I can't forget you.
Your Holiness!
What is it?
It's the DNA test results.
Where are the results?
Here.
DNA DOES NOT MATCH
The DNA results are not a match.
So Pleum is not your son?
Right?
Right.
Why do you look so sad?
Well...
I...
Does this mean that you've gotten
to love and care for that kid already?
I love that kid.
I want to take care of him,
be close to him.
I want to clean his butt.
I want to feed him,
clean up when he pees or poops.
-Play with him--
-That's enough.
Ble, I'll teach you one thing.
Sometimes,
when it's not right, then it's not,
no matter what you do.
But if it's right,
no matter what, it's still right.
If it's right, then it's right.
If it's not right, then it's not.
This is not right.
If it's not right, but we think it is,
we're disappointed.
It's more than right or not right.
Do you understand?
Sun.
Explain it to him.
I think it was right at first.
Ble thought so too. Turns out it's not.
You know that it's not right,
but Ble still thinks it's right.
At first, Ble thought it wasn't right.
Since the beginning. Then they met,
and he thought it was right.
He thinks it's right, so a bond's created,
but it's not right.
That's not right. Ble thought it was right
but said it wasn't right,
but you thought it wasn't right.
-Ble still thinks it's right.
-Right!
-I think it is right!
-You can't do that.
It's what I thought at first.
We have to think if it's right!
How can it be right?
Look at the result. It's not.
Here, take a look! Look!
I saw it at the start.
It says that it's not right.
It's right or wrong, right?
Ble, is that right?
You don't seem to be right.
-He's gone.
-He also isn't right.
That's true.
I would like to consult with you.
About the abbot, right?
Yes.
You knew about this?
About Heaven Mics
and the fact
he goes out partying at night?
Your Holiness,
this is not monks' business.
Now that it has come to this,
how does it not concern us?
Can I be the one to warn him
before people know about this?
Everyone knows about this.
Why don't they say anything?
He has many followers.
People believe in whatever he says.
But it's not a good thing.
Yes, that's right.
We can't let this happen to our temple.
This harms Buddhism.
I'll take care of it.
Should we do it today?
We can't today. He's sick.
He's sick again?
Please.
Your Holiness.
Hello.
What is it, Jazz?
Your Holiness,
I have an important business
to discuss with you.
Can't you see that I'm sick.
I can't talk today.
I'm a young and well-known monk.
I'm also pretty myself.
Say it.
I would like to ask
how you became ill so quickly.
Are you accusing me of lying?
Sickness
appears unexpectedly
without warning
or agenda.
How would I know if I'm going to be sick
on the 18th or the 19th?
But today is the 14th. Are you sick now?
It was just a metaphor.
Your Holiness,
please stop what you're doing.
You're going to destroy
my beloved and respectful religion.
Jazz.
Do you know what you just said?
You're teaching fish how to swim.
But if you keep doing this,
you'll become the smallest fish.
Are you criticizing me?
There are many good monks,
but a monk like you destroys Buddhism.
Your Heaven Mics
and your going out late at night,
we all know about it.
Please come clean,
so we can fix it in time.
I'm being blamed.
Your Holiness...
I'm being framed.
I'm being censored.
I didn't go anywhere.
I'm always at the temple.
Where can I go
when my leg is like this?
What is wrong with your leg?
I have Can-Dia-Hype disease.
-What is it again?
-Can-Dia-Hype disease.
-Slowly.
-Thok...
It's cancer, diabetes, and hypertension.
Please let me touch.
Don't.
He's been hurt enough.
Please leave him alone.
Let him leave us freely.
Oh. Yes.
Then I'll Ta-M-Le.
What?
Ta-M-Le.
Slowly and clearly.
I'll take my leave.
It's the same.
-Can I touch it?
-Don't!
Your Holiness,
I hope you leave us comfortably.
You've been hurt enough.
Enough!
They've gone.
Thank you.
I've some, some, some money
Please give me 200, 300, 400
Abbot, get out!
Abbot, don't go!
-Abbot, get out!
-Abbot, don't go!
ABBOT, DON'T GO
ABBOT, GET OUT
Your Holiness, please calm down.
You always say there's a solution
to every problem.
I don't think it's a big deal.
Wait!
Please calm down and be gentle.
-We can talk it over.
-We can't.
Do you know the abbot is a fraud?
He steals from the temple
and parties with women at night.
You know that?
Where is the abbot?
Yes! Right!
It's not true!
-Wait!
-What?
More importantly, this stings the most.
This! See? Heaven Mic.
We never reach heaven with this.
Wait. You'll go to hell for this.
The abbot never goes partying.
He's always here.
You don't know how to use Heaven Mic.
If you know, you'll go to heaven for sure.
Wait! Wait!
Wait!
You! Yeah, you!
Go find the abbot!
Go!
What's going on?
Go find the abbot!
All of you, please calm down.
Please don't shout.
-Your Holiness--
-Your Holiness!
It's out of control. They won't back off.
They want to see you.
You're the only one who can stop this.
What should we do?
Please lead the way.
You.
You're here today because of who?
I asked, you're here today because of who?
Because of you, Your Holiness.
You know what to do, right?
Yes.
Thok.
Yes, Your Holiness.
He can't come out.
Calm down. Don't fight.
Go find the other one.
Abbot Chaiya. Not the right one.
Go check if he's ready.
Yes.
All of you from two sides,
those who support and
those who are against,
we're all Buddhists.
Please be conscious.
Be rational, not emotional.
Please let me take care of it.
Please go ahead.
Hello, everyone.
Bring Abbot Chaiya.
Calm down.
Don't get angry. Be conscious.
Don't get emotional.
Calm down! Calm down, you all.
Your Holiness,
Thok told me to bring you this.
Where is he now?
I saw him leave in a hurry.
Thok, you just saved yourself.
Can you stay and help me?
Yes, Your Holiness.
Please do as I say.
-Yes.
-Very good.
Don't. Calm down.
I told you all to calm down.
-What's going on?
-As you can see,
They want to see Abbot Chaiya.
You all.
You all!
Stop!
Back off! He told us to stop.
Can't you hear?
Damn!
Serves you right!
Listen to me.
Those who support the Abbot,
you're Buddhists, right?
Those who are against him,
you're also Buddhists, right?
You believe in the same religion.
Your hearts are the same.
Why don't you work together
and create good things for Buddhism?
You have fought against each other,
divided into groups.
You're all Buddhists.
Please think about it well.
Here he is.
Here he comes.
Are you all well?
We're fine.
-And this side?
-We're not fine!
You guys,
if you are not well,
why not take some medicine?
How can we afford medicine?
You ripped us all off.
Right!
-How can we afford medicine?
-What did I do wrong?
Framing a monk for being a fraud is wrong.
You'll go to hell.
It's not framing. It's true.
The Heaven Mics you sold us--
All right. Calm down.
Heaven Mics bring you to heaven.
Say it together.
Heaven Mics can't bring you to heaven!
All right. Enough.
Can we take them out?
No, we can't.
Please calm down.
The reason I came out here late
is because I'm really sick.
Liar! Liar!
If you don't believe me, look at my leg.
It's rotten.
Is it true? What did he do?
I don't think it's true.
Does he need to be amputated?
Your Holiness.
The other day, when I saw you,
it wasn't this leg.
It's this one.
See it clearly.
What is wrong with you? Are you confused?
-Isn't it the other side?
-Do you have bipolar disorder?
Do you want to shoot nine bullets
into the sky?
-This side.
-It's true.
Last time, it was the left side.
Kra.
Please tell Jazz which leg it is.
The left one.
The right one.
Liar!
Stop!
Monk Jazz.
This one?
That's Pleum.
That's Pleum. Let's go, Your Holiness.
Novice monk! Your Holiness! Follow us.
Novice!
You! Where are you taking him?
Novice! Damn it!
You! You!
Monk Jazz is telling us numbers for
the lottery. It's 0-0. Write them down.
It must be winning numbers.
Back off!
-Don't move.
-We're holding him hostage.
Anybody play tricks or moves,
the whole train will blow up!
No, no!
Your Holiness! Talk to him first.
Quickly.
Talk to him first.
Why do you keep following us?
Sang, Kang.
Calm down.
I know that you two are still mad at me.
The whole thing happened
because of you.
I had nothing to do with it.
To forget a wrong is the best revenge.
Be conscious.
Anger will only make you crazy.
Think carefully.
Put down the bomb.
What? We're dead.
Idiot!
Monk and normal people,
the bomb is not armed. How can it explode?
That's right.
You...
The person you're holding hostage,
he's just a kid.
If you want a hostage,
take me instead of him.
Next station is Ploenchit.
-No, Your Holiness.
-You can't!
No, you can't!
The poles, guys!
Go! Let's go! Quick!
If you're still playing tricks,
everyone here will die.
Quick! Go!
-What do we do?
-Take him and run!
Quick! Your Holiness! Back off!
Here, let's kill him here.
I kill him. You pour cement on his body.
And you bury him
so that nobody can find him.
Very clever.
Let's do this.
I'll shoot him,
and you pour cement on his body.
-Shoot him!
-Wait.
Can I tell you two something
for once before I die?
I can honor that request.
Say it then.
Think about it.
We're ordained as a way
to thank our parents.
-Why do you have to talk about parents?
-A mother exhaust herself
in order to give birth to her child.
If you go to jail,
how sad will your parents be?
I can't say much.
That's all I can tell you before I die.
Enough!
Just go, Your Holiness. Go!
I'll be here.
He won't leave.
I want both of you to go back
and wash your faces with clean water.
-I'll leave.
-So you know,
if that makes you feel happy,
anger and hatred
are like lighting up
the fire in your heart.
Your Holiness!
-Go!
-Your Holiness!
Where are they? Your Holiness!
Stop asking me!
Now, just take me anywhere!
But not here!
ABBOT HAVING SEX AND PARTYING!
Hello! It's me, Lovesick.
I want to confirm that
there were three of them.
They were partying with us women.
Their hands were all over us!
So scary! They gave us a big tip,
especially the one in the middle.
His wig fell off.
That scared me!
I can confirm that three of them
are very likely monks.
Your Holiness.
Have you read the news
on social media lately?
No, I have not. What's up?
People on social media are talking about
Dharmathikarn Benchamarachasit
Vivekvikaramon Praditmongkol Temple.
That's our temple.
Many people have asked,
where is the remaining money
to build the temple?
-Sun.
-Yes.
Was it you who asked me this question?
For both of us.
I just want to know
how you will handle it.
Don't worry. I have a plan.
Your Holiness.
I have good news.
See?
There's a solution to every problem.
-What is the good news?
-A letter from DSI.
Your Holiness! Your Holiness!
You read it.
The DSI makes you illiterate?
No, I don't feel strong enough to read it.
It's a letter. There is no vibration mode.
It's the AC.
There's no AC out here.
Are we hit?
Bull's-eye.
Your Holiness!
Please.
Please, Your Holiness.
Don't block the way. Move!
Excuse me. Please go to the station.
I'm very sleepy. Can I sleep first?
Do you want to stay in jail?
Lieutenant, the abbot isn't in
his dwelling. He's run away.
What goes around comes around.
Did you bring money?
Thief!
That's a kid's voice.
Stop, or you'll die.
Stop, or you'll die!
Song! What are you doing?
You stay out of this!
Are you taking a novice monk away?
Go! Why are you still here?
Let him go!
I can't.
I said let him go.
I can't! He'll go tell!
Let him go!
Damn you!
Don't!
-Damn it!
-Why did you shoot?
That's my brother!
-And then why--
-Bastard!
You bastard!
-Damn you.
-I don't care!
Do you have all the evidence?
-Yes.
-Sure?
Yeah, sure.
Ble!
Damn it!
Song!
Ble!
What's going on? You're bleeding.
He's still bleeding. He was shot.
-Who shot him?
-I don't know.
He got away.
That's fine.
Help him first. He was shot.
Take him to the hospital!
Ble.
Hello, Monk Jazz.
Please.
How are you?
I'm worried about you.
I'm all right now.
How is the wound?
It's better. There's nothing serious now.
By the way,
how is Song?
He was arrested.
Song...
Is His Holiness here too?
Yes.
Here he comes.
Hello, Your Holiness.
Here.
Your Holiness.
He would like to ask to be ordained.
Your Holiness,
for any physical, mental,
and verbal act I did,
whether intentionally or unintentionally,
to your face or behind your back,
I would like to ask for your forgiveness.
From here on out till the end.
Amen.
I'm happy for you, and I forgive you.
I wish you well.
Hope you get better soon.
Thank you, Your Holiness.
Ble.
I'm leaving then.
Thank you, Your Holiness.
Let's go.
Monk Jazz.
I don't want to go just yet.
I want to be with Ble.
How do you like that, Ble?
He wants to be with his father.
All right, Your Holiness.
Let him stay with me.
Thank you, Your Holiness.
Get well soon.
-Get well soon.
-I love you.
I'll take care of you.
Yes.
I love you too.
I'm here to say goodbye.
Where are you going?
I think I'm going to promote Buddhism
to help people understand Buddhism better.
Most people think religion
is something serious and difficult.
When they think religion is out of reach,
we'll bring it to them.
That's great.
If we have 100 or 1,000 monks
just like you,
Buddhism can prosper better.
Your Holiness.
I'm here to say goodbye.
Where are you going?
To the temple in the countryside.
I'll promote Buddhism
to more people there.
Many of them consider religion
as something stressful
and difficult to understand.
If they think religion is out of reach,
we'll bring it to them.
Do you think it's a good idea?
I think it's great.
If we have 100 or 1,000 monks
just like you,
Buddhism will surely prosper.
Your Holiness, we've talked about this.
We have?
I'm going then.
Where are you going?
I just said it to you.
What's with you? Why do you keep
saying the same thing?
I have a Meniere's disease.
You're funny.
We're not stressed when we're around you.
Before I go,
I have some words of wisdom for you.
They say a swift horse
can lose to a donkey.
-Why is that?
-A donkey says goodbye and leaves first.
Is it funny?
Before I go,
I also have some words of wisdom for you.
A swift horse can lose to a donkey.
Why is that?
A donkey says goodbye and leaves first.
-Am I funny, too?
-You're a copycat,
since you were talking about
promoting religion earlier.
Quickly. You remember
which bus number to take?
I don't.
Hey, Peun.
When were you ordained here?
I've just been.
Why were you ordained?
Since I was in trouble with the law,
there's no place in society
for me and my mother.
Anything I do is wrong.
So I've turned to religion.
-For how long?
-For the rest of my life.
There'll be a special pardon.
I'm at the temple, not in jail.
I'm kidding.
Please, Your Holiness.
Monk Jazz, I'm here to give alms.
It's good the see you. I won the lottery
with the "00" you gave.
I got 30 million baht.
I won the lottery and also a husband.
You do bring us luck like water lizards.
Just say I'm a good luck charm.
A good luck charm.
Aren't you afraid
your winnings will go missing?
No, I won't lose them.
I keep them safe and even lick them.
Why do you lick them?
Just in case a DNA test is needed.
You're very careful.
Wit.
Let me show off my husband.
He looks a lot like Poj Arnon.
Is he Poj Arnon?
I'm Wit.
-He's not.
-From the way he salutes,
he will be very rich.
The ring is his mother's,
and the watch is his dead friend's.
-Peun.
-Your Holiness.
A policeman is here to give alms.
Don't get in trouble with him.
Or you both will be in the news.
It will be difficult to clear things up.
I don't want to imagine that.
I'm going then.
-Goodbye.
-Please.
THAMMAPATHIP TEMPLE
It's unbelievable you passed
the exams and got to come to France.
Even a monk from nowhere
like you can come here.
After this, any monk can come here too.
Listen to me carefully.
I'm a limited-edition monk.
Any copycat is not like me, the original.
Your Holiness,
why didn't we go visiting Paris first?
I wanted to go take some pictures.
Look, I'm all dressed up.
You dress like pillow cases.
Hello.
Hello. Monk Jazz, right?
Yes.
Congratulations on completing
your training to become a missionary
and on promoting Buddhism
here at Thammapathip Temple in France.
Here is Lapin,
the assistant monk here.
Oh, Your Holiness!
-Beautiful, right?
-Why are you shouting?
It's beautiful.
-One... Smile.
-Smile.
Your Holiness,
here is Avenue des Champs-lyses
Shopping places for everyone.
You know,
what is this called?
It's called Arch of Victory
or Arc de Triomphe in French.
Smile.
Smile, Your Holiness. Don't look serious.
-Your Holiness.
-People here look rich.
If they know me,
they will come pay respect.
Yes.
Your Holiness!
Jazz.
How have you been?
I'm a missionary here.
Good. Good.
Why are you dressed like this?
It's a new cult.
You're no longer a monk?
No, I'm a goat.
-What goat?
-I'm a scapegoat.
How can you be here?
How were you not arrested?
I'm here as a normal tourist.
Nobody arrested me.
Your Holiness,
there is an extradition law here.
Aren't you scared?
-There really is an extradition law here?
-Yes, Sir.
Can I go to Montenegro?
A powerful person like you
going to a small country,
I don't think it's right.
How about Dubai?
Dubai might be too difficult.
Where can I go? Please advise me.
For someone powerful like you,
you should go with VIP services.
Just go casually by sea.
-How?
-Like Rohingya people.
Thanks a lot.
Please excuse me.
Wait, Jazz.
-Can you lend me 200?
-A picture with that door would be nice.
-Let's go.
-So beautiful.
Please sympathize with me.
Your Holiness.
You won't say anything to the abbot
for what he did?
It's true, Your Holiness.
Do you love Buddhism?
I do.
Then just believe in yourself.
Let other people do what they want.
What goes around comes around.
We just do our duties,
promoting Buddhism so it can prosper.
Look at Karaked.
She's a good person,
so she ends up with a good husband.
Got it? Okay?
That's a TV series.
I like this show too.
You're very trendy.
If Ble wins, you have to promise me
you won't bother him again.
But if you win,
-we'll all crush you.
-That's fair.
Are you crazy?
Go! Go!
Fight him!
Get up!
Jazz! Get up!
I'm so tired. I did it many times.
What's wrong?
My eyesight.
I think I need a new pair of glasses.
Ouch!
This time.
Cut!
Shut up!
What should we do?
I've been wanting to ask.
This date you ate,
when will you swallow it down?
That's very sharp.
Cut!
Nakhee will be yours.
Can't you do it gently? You hit me hard.
They both did it.
-Mom isn't back yet.
-Mom isn't back?
-Go.
-Who wants to go home? Smile!
I'm going.
Keep that in mind!
Are your fathers dead? Bastards!
Bastard!
Follow him!
You're motorcycle punks.
No!
You're not happy. How about a fog prince?
So outdated!
No!
Two-wheel angel.
Just name whatever you like
on your Facebook.
Motorbikes can be driven at high speed
only on a race track.
Your Holiness,
how about a race in the field?
Eakachai.
I'm in the mafia.
But there're just so many of you.
I want you to think of your parents,
of your wife and kids.
If something happens to you,
how sad will your families be?
Subtitle translation by Lalawan