Are you certain, doctor?
Where is Kinn?
Porsche.
Kinn is...
Mr. Tankhun.
Shit.
How?
Kinn...
Mr. Tankhun, please lower your voice.
Kinn is out of the woods.
Just not up yet.
What?
Why the hell are you teasing now?
Hey!
Porsche!
This is Mr. Tankhun.
Right.
Why can't I play?
Why is he being so moody?
And where is Kinn now?
There.
Which room?
Over there.
Where are you going?
He's not up yet.
Isn't he overreacting?
I'm Kinn's brother and I'm not overreacting.
How's Mr. Kinn doing?
Everything seems to be fine.
There's nothing to worry about.
Oh.
Oh, hello, Porsche.
Kinn's not up yet?
Not yet.
And these flowers are for Kinn?
Nope.
These are for you.
Yellow roses mean friendship and care.
And there's also another meaning.
Love.
That doesn't expect anything in return.
Well, I'm off now.
Oh, you're leaving?
If I stay,
I might make Kinn uncomfortble.
So I'd better get going, Porsche.
Wait.
Take your flowers back too.
I'm allergic to those.
It might land on my bodyguard's skin.
Well, I’m outta here. I don't want to disturb you.
Where are you going?
Are you gonna let you boss sleep alone?
Why, can you not sleep alone?
I'm on my work leave now.
Are you really gonna go back alone?
This is one of the most haunted hospitals.
You think I'm afraid of that?
I'm not scared...
The A/C in my room is just too cold.
What made you come back then?
Have you ever done anything without a reason?
Yes.
Papa gave you 7 days to think...
So...
Are you coming back to be my bodyguard?
Well, I'm lying here.
Do you still need to ask that?
You wanna call your brother?
Of course.
Can I?
Hello, Chay.
Hello, bro.
Where are you?
I came back and I missed you.
Are you doing alright?
I have an urgent matter to attend to.
I miss you, bro, how are you?
I miss you so damn much.
Got to see you just a bit, hasn't eased me at all.
If you're free, come over to see me again, alright?
Sure.
I love you, Chay.
Take a good care of yourself.
I love you the most in the whole world, bro.
Thank you.
Are you still hurt?
The wound is quite far from the heart.
What a mouth!
That means you're still alright.