Some of this story is adapted
from the legend of Ayothaya.
A long time ago...
beyond all imagination...
in the center of the earth
was Mount Meru,
which was as tall as the clouds.
At the time, all the land was one.
It was divided
into small and big kingdoms.
One of them was called Ayothaya.
It was located on a rich and abundant land
surrounded by converging rivers.
It appeared as if an island
had risen up from underneath.
Ayothaya was originally a small city
that was established by powerful demigods.
Later,
the Kinnara, or male human-birds,
took over
and nurtured and developed it
to become a huge kingdom.
But after a series of wars,
the Kinnara army was defeated
by the mighty Garuda army.
The Kinnara became slaves to the Garuda
for thousands of years.
Then, 200 years ago,
a young slave rose up
to lead the Kinnara
across the Great Sidantara Ocean
and establish a new kingdom
in the faraway Himmaphan Forest...
well known for being home
to remarkable legendary animals
that no one had ever seen.
North of Ayothaya
stretched the Singkonkiri Mountains.
Beyond the mountains
was an inhospitable land
as hot as the fires of hell.
The horrifying land...
was occupied by savage, ruthless monsters
called the Rakshasa.
These monsters were vicious, savage,
and skilled in every form of combat.
They attacked and routed
the other kingdoms
until they finally crossed
the Singkonkiri Mountains,
heading straight
for the last kingdom standing,
which was...
Ayothaya, the Garuda's kingdom.
Vayu, Varee, heed my commands.
-Yes, sir.
-Both of you shall
fly ahead to the Singkonkiri Mountains.
If you see anything suspicious,
report back immediately.
Yes, sir.
The rest of you will be on guard duty.
We're spending the night here.
THE SINGKONKIRI MOUNTAINS
It's cold. Are you cold, Vayu?
It would be nice to have a campfire
in such cold weather.
Hey, Varee. No!
-Do not start a fire.
-I know, I know. I didn't mean it.
I'm not stupid like you, bro.
By the way,
a hundred years ago,
if King Subunpon hadn't abdicated
and become a monk,
this wouldn't have happened...
Sir, I can smell the Rakshasa army.
Vayu, we can't defeat them.
Your big wings make you
the fastest flier in the army.
Go tell the master.
-But what about you?
-No buts.
Hurry, come on. Go!
Bring it on, assholes.
I have a blade for each of you.
Get back. He's mine.
Get back.
Dumbass!
Sir, the Rakshasa have crossed the border.
I know. Hurry, show me the way.
Pichai. Bawon.
Form a two-pronged attack.
-Left and right.
-Yes, sir!
Varee! Varee!
Where are you, my brother?
Men, retreat! Let's go!
AYOTHAYA'S INNER COURT
KING SURIYAINTRA
AYOTHAYA'S KING
It was hot and sweaty, but worth it!
Such beautiful diamonds
for such little effort.
Look at this!
I told you.
King Suriya-indra knows next to nothing.
There are no Kinnari
in Ayothaya these days.
The Minister.
Hand them over.
Get out of here!
You vagrant Garuda!
Finally!
Varee? You're not dead?
Damn you!
Sorry to disappoint.
No! I was worried sick.
Despite your foul mouth,
you're still my dear younger brother.
Isn't that right, bro?
This is to show my love.
Stop! No need to love me that much.
Varee! How did you survive?
What happened?
Sir, I gave it my all
but I still couldn't defeat them.
When they breathed fire at me,
I jumped into the water to hide.
To my surprise, they didn't come after me.
They just stood there watching.
So, I escaped through a crevice...
and found my way out to this river.
All right. I'm glad that you're okay.
Get up.
I think
they were just scouts.
If so, the main army of the Rakshasa
will be here soon.
A lot of our soldiers
are injured right now.
We need to stop and rest.
I think we should do two things.
First we must notify Ayothaya
to get ready.
Our second task
is to search for King Subunpon,
who has abdicated
and become a monk in the forest.
We'll ask him to come back
and lead the army
to protect Ayothaya.
Sir, I would like to volunteer
to go to Ayothaya.
Great, Pichai.
Once the soldiers have recovered,
I'll return immediately.
So, Bawon, it is up to you
to seek out King Subunpon
and convince him to return to Ayothaya.
Yes, sir. Right away.
FOREST ON AYOTHAYA'S BORDER
Garuda bones?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Is that you, Bawon?
AYOTHAYA'S OUTER WALLS
Stop!
No one is allowed to fly in here.
Please open the gate. I have urgent news.
Who are you?
Don't you know the Garuda's laws?
My name is Pichai.
I'm the right-hand soldier
of Phya Watchara,
reconnaissance commander.
I have urgent news for Ayothaya.
Please hurry and open the gate.
No! The Defense Minister has ordered
not to open the gate at night.
Come back again in the morning.
It would be too late.
I have to notify King Suriya-indra
right now. Open the gate!
Or I'll have no choice but attack.
You can try!
Isn't that Phya Watchara?
I am Phya Watchara,
-reconnaissance commander of Ayothaya.
-Move, move.
Open the gate
so my army can enter.
Wait!
Commander, what's the hurry?
Why aren't you guarding the border?
You could be severely punished
for abandoning your post.
Don't you realize?
Let me explain, Minister.
I have not abandoned my post.
The Rakshasa army has crossed the border.
Haven't you received news?
Nonsense. Nobody came to notify me.
What? Impossible.
I sent Pichai here a while ago.
-Why--
-All right.
I'll notify the King myself.
Phya Watchara,
bring your soldiers in to rest.
You, open the gate!
The enemy is at the doorstep,
why are the people of Ayothaya
still not preparing anything?
What happened to you, Pichai?
Your Majesty,
it's time to drink your medicine.
No. I don't want to. I'm not sick.
You must drink it in order to get well.
No. I said no. Get out!
Very good, Your Majesty.
Now, press your finger here.
Just like that. Beautiful.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Over my dead body!
During this war,
the King has seen fit to appoint
the Defense Minister
as the commander-in-chief
of Ayothaya's army.
He shall have
absolute power to make any command.
Signed and stamped with the Royal Crest,
King Suriya-indra, this 110th year
of the King's reign.
Long live the King!
Now it is time
to hear my plan to protect Ayothaya.
CITY WALL ON THE SOUTH
Damn, I'm bored.
Hey, stop fooling around!
If the master sees you,
you'll be punished severely.
Come on. Relax, Vayu.
You know that the Rakshasa
would never come through this way.
Yeah, you're right.
That Defense Minister must be
out of his mind
to assign formidable soldiers like us
to guard the south fort
and place incompetent soldiers
at the front line.
We will be defeated for sure.
Yeah. Our master disagreed
with the Defense Minister so many times,
but he refused to listen
and even threatened to put us in jail.
I'm very curious
why King Suriya-indra entrusted
that stupid Minister to take charge.
Speaking of His Majesty,
since we've been back,
we have yet to see him.
Something strange is going on.
We've been told not to use cannons,
since King Suriya-indra is sick
and doesn't want to be disturbed.
We have to ask for permission beforehand.
There'd be no time during an attack.
I agree with you, sir.
Even a naive child can see
that this plan is poorly conceived.
I suspect that the Defense Minister
is a spy for the Rakshasa.
Impossible!
He's a Garuda, after all.
Why would he spy for an enemy
that wants to eradicate his own species?
Greed, sir.
Greed can motivate someone to do anything.
If that's true,
Ayothaya could cease to exist.
The Rakshasa are here!
What should I do?
I'm afraid to fire the cannon.
Soldier, fire the cannon!
-Hurry!
-But the Minister said we're not allowed--
Fuck! Give it to me. I'll take the blame.
Everyone stationed at the cannons,
fire!
Yes, sir!
Come on, assholes.
I'm gonna blow your asses away!
Phya Watchara, you disobeyed royal orders.
I didn't mean to, sir.
It was an emergency,
I didn't have time to ask for permission.
-Or--
-The arrogance!
See what this is?
This is the King's sword
of absolute power, given to me
to harshly punish
whoever disobeys my command.
But I didn't--
Soldiers, escort him
to the underground jail.
Sir.
-As for all of you...
-Yes, sir.
Return to your stations
on the south fort now,
or I'll throw you in jail with him!
-Sir!
-Pichai? What happened?
Why are you here?
Sir, I was trying to deliver
a message about the war
just as you had ordered.
But once I crossed the city walls,
I was attacked by a shadowy figure
and knocked out.
When I regained consciousness,
I found myself locked in here.
A shadowy figure?
Yes, sir. I couldn't see it clearly.
But it was too big and tall
to be a Garuda.
After drinking this special medicine,
you'll be resting peacefully.
Who do you think you are?
Intruding in the King's sleeping chamber
-is punishable by death!
-Minister.
We parted ways only recently,
yet you don't recognize me?
King Subunpon! Your Majesty.
I failed to recognize you.
Please forgive me.
Planning to kill the King
deserves the death penalty.
-Bawon, grab him.
-Yes, Your Majesty.
-Your Majesty. Please let me explain.
-Let's go, Minister.
-Your Majesty.
-This way to jail. Move!
Put him in jail for now.
I'll come back for him later.
Your Majesty, it's not what it looks like!
Please!
My little brother, are you okay?
I brought you the antidote
that will save you.
Over my dead body.
Over my dead body!
Don't, Suriya-indra! Run!
I'll help you, brother!
No!
Your Majesty.
Arise, Watchara and Pichai.
You are both free from punishment.
Let's go protect Ayothaya
from the Rakshasa.
I'll protect it with my life.
-Soldier.
-Yes, Your Majesty.
Bring the Defense Minister here
and secure him tightly.
-Don't let him out.
-Yes, Your Majesty.
Come on, Watchara.
Let's plan this battle.
-Come!
-No!
Let me go! Let me go this instant!
How dare you do this to me?
You dirty little mutts.
When I get out--
Brother.
Suriya-indra.
I would like to fight alongside you
and all our soldiers to protect Ayothaya.
You're doing the right thing,
Suriya-indra.
The King has a duty
to protect the land and people
with his life.
How touching!
Your Majesty,
the Rakshasa army approaches.
The Dark Monster.
Capture Ayothaya
and kill every last Garuda!
Die! You damned Garuda!
Die!
Your Majesty, don't you remember me?
You must be the mole.
Yes! I am Noir, a Rakshasa,
and the top soldier under
our great commander Dark Monster.
I've been possessing
this brown-nosed Garuda
for quite a while.
What fools!
I had you tricked this whole time.
You bastard!
Die!
What? Two against one?
Gotta go. Bye.
Brother!
Finally, we meet again.
This time, Ayothaya will be mine.
Men, take him!
Men, retreat to the south fort. Quick!
Sir, what should we do next?
We should reserve our small force
for the time being.
We'll figure out a way to get past them
to find some allies
and recruit more soldiers,
then come back for Ayothaya.
But they surround all of the walls.
We're going to fly across
the Great Sidantara Ocean.
It is immensely vast,
and who knows where the end is?
They say even the greatest Garuda
couldn't make the journey.
No Garuda has ever flown across.
We will fly across!
Soldiers,
gather all your strength
and prepare
for the toughest flight of your life.
They'd been flying for quite some time,
but still couldn't cross
the Great Sidantara Ocean.
Some of the Garuda soldiers
were so exhausted
that they fell into the ocean.
The rest couldn't afford
to help those that fell.
Below them were hundreds of Naga...
and Anantanagaraj,
the seven-headed King of the Naga,
that looked to the fallen Garuda
for their next meal.
Finally, after a long, tough flight
of seven days and seven nights,
their perseverance bore fruit,
as nine of them survived
the crossing of the vast
Great Sidantara Ocean
and arrived at a mysterious remote land.
What the hell is this?
What the hell?
Hurry, Vayu.
Fly away!
I have no more strength.
I can't even lift my wings.
Just run!
-See you.
-Wait for me!
-Get on that tree! Hurry!
-Yes, sir.
What are they angry about?
Hey, my head!
-My head!
-Come on.
It's better than falling down there
and being crushed.
What the hell?
Watch out.
Hey, Vayu,
the trees are consoling each other.
What? Whoa!
They're making very weird sounds.
What are they saying, Pirun?
They're wondering what we are.
Sir, I'll try to converse with them.
Those weird trees told them
that the place was Himmaphan Forest.
The place where they landed
was home to the Kochasri.
To the east dwelled the Norasingha.
As for the south, it was the kingdom
of the intellectual Kinnara.
So the Kinnara moved out here.
Yes, sir. The trees said
the Kinnara's king is Kinnarajan.
Kinnarajan?
I have an idea.
If we can get all these Himmaphan
creatures to be our allies,
then we'll have a strong army.
We'll be able to go get Ayothaya
back from the Rakshasa.
What do you guys think?
If I may speak freely, sir,
they are wild creatures, free and fierce.
I don't think they would agree
to be our allies
unless we force them.
But there are only nine of us.
We can't defeat them.
You're right, Pichai.
We have a small force,
so we must use our intelligence
to defeat them.
However, right now, we're exhausted
from flying across the ocean.
We need to rest and revitalize ourselves.
I agree, sir.
My stomach is rumbling
louder than a battle drum.
Well, in this wild forest,
where can we get food?
Sir, look!
This magic fruit is called Makalee Pon.
We'll survive! Hurray!
TERRITORY OF HALF-ELEPHANT-HALF-LION
Pirun, tell the King of the Kochasri
that we mean no harm.
Attack!
King of the Norasingha,
I came here to ask for your help.
I came here--
Please, King of the Norasingha...
King of the Norasingha!
Let go of my hand.
Never!
We'll go down together.
Commander Watchara.
King of the Norasingha.
What's on your mind?
I'm worried about Ayothaya.
I don't know what's happening there.
Then we should move against
the Kinnara as soon as possible.
The exit to the labyrinth is closing.
Hurry up, men!
What?
What the hell?
Hurry! The mountain pass is closing.
Get them!
Everyone, cut off your wings.
Do it!
What? Sir, what do you mean?
We're nothing without our wings.
A wingless Garuda has no honor.
We don't have a choice.
It's the only way to survive.
Sir!
Move! Come on! Find the gold.
You slaves!
Chain them securely.
When the time comes,
I'll send them to be our slaves.
Enough. That's enough for now.
Your Majesty, why must you be so stubborn?
Tell me the location
of Ayothaya's hidden treasure.
Then I'll let you fly freely once more.
Otherwise,
I'll make you a cripple for life.
My life may be coming to an end,
but Ayothaya will stand for a long time.
I will never tell you
the location of the hidden treasure.
Go fuck yourself, you monstrous Rakshasa!
The arrogance! Hey.
Cut his wings off!
Gold? Where is all the gold?
It's been over 200 years
since we fled slavery
and came here to establish a new kingdom.
A free and peaceful kingdom
without killing or corruption.
Now, our peace is threatened
by our old enemy, the Garuda.
We have to go to war
to protect our land from the invaders.
Wait, Father!
-Kanoknaree.
-I heard that Phya Watchara, their leader,
wishes to arrange a summit to discuss
the fight against the Rakshasa.
Father, I think we can avoid this war.
A summit?
The Garuda once killed us brutally
and took Ayothaya from us.
They enslaved us for thousands of years.
I will never meet with them--
-But, Father, listen--
-Enough!
Even though you're my daughter,
you don't have the right to speak freely
in this meeting. Soldier!
Put her in a cell.
Father, please, listen to me.
Let go of me. Let go.
It's so delicious.
Who lit that bonfire?
Kanoknaree, why are you crying?
Sakunnee? How did you know I was here?
-I know, I know.
-Yeah, that's right.
You're so tiny
that you can easily
move through the labyrinth.
Sakunnee, please help me.
Take this
and find the Garuda army.
Once you find them, give this message
to Phya Watchara, their leader.
Can you do that for me, my friend?
Of course!
How do I know which one is Phya Watchara?
Yes, I forgot to tell you.
You will recognize
Phya Watchara of Ayothaya
by the scar across his face.
Scar, scar.
Go away, Rakshasa assholes.
What are you?
Phya Watchara,
my mistress wanted me
to deliver this to you.
The entrance map. Who is your mistress?
Kanoknaree.
Kanoknaree? It's really her.
Wait.
I have something for your mistress.
Gift, gift.
Were you successful?
Did you find him?
Gift, gift.
It's really you.
According to the map,
this waterfall
is the entrance to the Kinnara kingdom.
We're all going in at the same time.
Hold hands so we don't get separated.
Hold my hand, not my mouth!
Come on, same thing.
Invaders!
Men, take control of the tower!
Yikes! My wings aren't spreading.
Cover me! I'll deactivate this.
Sir!
They're relentless in their attack
We're going to fall.
A little longer.
I've almost deactivated this.
Almost there.
I did it!
Phya Watchara is here, sir.
I can't believe
that after we moved out here,
a bloodthirsty species like yours
would still come attack us.
Go ahead,
I've lost.
Have your way with us.
Please accept my respect, Your Majesty,
King of all Kinnara.
We come here in peace.
And yes, our ancestors used to
attack you and your people.
But I never thought
it was the right thing to do.
Ayothaya was attacked by the Rakshasa
and we fled here.
I humbly request your strong Kinnara army
to be our allies
in taking back Ayothaya.
It wasn't my intention
to invade your kingdom.
All right, I accept your goodwill.
As for being your allies,
I can't make that decision on my own.
This is a serious matter
that concerns the life and death
of our species,
so it must be discussed
with my military commanders.
I can't give you an answer right now,
not until we have met
and come to a decision.
I really appreciate it, Your Majesty.
I await your decision.
No matter what the decision is,
we'll gladly accept it
and treat you with the respect
you deserve as King.
Kanoknaree, I came here to help you.
You.
That girl looks good enough
to be a royal dancer.
Catch her and bring her
to the royal palace. Hurry.
-Come be a royal dancer.
-No!
-No! Let go of me!
-Come!
Help! Somebody help me!
Kanoknaree?
My dear!
Hey, you think you can escape?
Help! Let go of me!
Stop! Let go!
Let her go!
Kid, move! Move out of the way!
No!
-You're asking for trouble.
-Let's show him.
Buddhaisawan sword pose!
No!
Kanoknaree, I'm here.
-Father!
-Catch that impudent slave!
No! Let go of me!
Father! Help!
No!
I've been holding on to this for 200 years
with the hope of returning it
back to its owner.
I've been dreaming of you every night
since that day.
I never thought
that we'd ever have the chance
to meet again.
What an amazing invention!
If my father decides to join forces,
I'll ask him to create one
for each of you. Okay?
That would be amazing.
As wingless Garuda,
we are like tigers without claws.
Can your father really create
mechanical wings for all of us?
He's been an excellent craftsman
since the time he was a slave.
The Great Sanphet Royal Palace in Ayothaya
was entirely made by my father.
I remember as a child,
before the major Kinnara evacuation,
I snuck into the secret evacuation tunnel
one night.
I saw my father making
a huge and complex invention.
He said
it was a deadly weapon.
I hope we'll never need it,
because it's unimaginably powerful.
What is the invention?
It is...
Look! A smoke signal!
Look at the smoke carefully.
If it resembles a Kinnari,
it means they don't agree
to be your allies.
But if it looks like a Garuda,
then they agree.
No!
Wait.
There's another one.
-What does that mean?
-I don't know, either.
Well, then we should go ask
for clarification. Let's go.
Your Majesty, what do those
smoke signals mean?
The council didn't come
to a unanimous decision.
So...
I accept your offer and agree to join you
as a favor
for helping my daughter in the past.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
But listen,
I have two conditions.
First,
only Kinnara will be involved
in this battle.
No Kinnari are allowed.
-Especially you, Kanoknaree.
-But, Father--
I agree.
And the other condition?
After we take back Ayothaya,
you and your Garuda
will never set foot on
or invade Himmaphan Forest!
Kanoknaree, we'll probably never see
each other again in this life.
Payuha, take the wheel.
Lower all sails.
Sir, we're stuck on a rock
and can't go any further.
Some of our boats have sunk.
Tell the oarsmen
to get the boats out of here
-before they sink.
-Yes, sir.
The oars are stuck.
We can't move.
I'd like to volunteer
to investigate underwater.
Please be careful, Varee.
King of the Naga!
Anantanagaraj!
Hello and goodbye!
Come on, Varee. Grab my hand!
Pull me up! Hurry!
Oh, shit. What's he doing?
How is this possible?
It's incredible.
Anantanagaraj said
the Rakshasa army
has taken control of every land.
They are pouring poison
into the Great Sidantara Ocean
hoping to destroy
all sea-living creatures.
Once the ocean dries up and turns to land,
they will bring their army across
to attack the Himmaphan Forest,
the last territory to conquer,
and take over the whole world.
Anantanagaraj, we're evacuating
your Naga to a safe place
and shall deliver this dire news
to the Himmaphan Forest.
My soldiers and I will stop this disaster.
At the cost of your lives,
we will go on to attack
and crush the Rakshasa.
We will take back Ayothaya!
These Garuda are so weak.
Since you're no longer useful...
Attack!
Split into three groups.
We'll attack simultaneously!
Fire wall!
Watch out for the fire wall. Go around!
Men, spread out and find the Dark Monster.
Yes, sir.
The bastard took ordinary Garuda
as hostages.
Ayothaya's gold taste really good.
Dark Monster!
You shall die!
Put down your weapons,
or I'll pour this oil
and kill these Garuda.
Varee!
Help! It's hot!
Hang in there, Varee.
You can't die.
You must take back Ayothaya.
Vayu.
No! No!
Varee!
You. Who are you?
How are you holding up?
Kanoknaree? How did you get here?
I left the Himmaphan Forest
disguised as a Garuda.
You didn't notice
there was one extra soldier in your army.
How stupid of me.
I'm impressed you found a way
into this secret tunnel.
Remember, my father, Kinnarajan,
built the Sanphet Palace,
we made our escape
through this very tunnel 200 years ago.
Kanoknaree, I'm so glad
to see you once again.
If you hadn't come to my aid,
I would have been killed
by the Dark Monster.
The tunnel is collapsing.
Let's get out of here!
Wait. I remember something.
In this tunnel,
my father left an invention
from before our evacuation.
I came here to find it.
There's no time. Let's go.
Hot!
Help! Help!
What?
The Naga are here to help us!
Attack!
To my surprise, they didn't come after me.
They just stood there watching.
Varee sacrificed himself for us.
We must take back Ayothaya!
Hang in there.
Our mission is not yet accomplished.
It's still alive?
Wait here. I'll take him.
Aim!
Nothing seems to hurt him.
Sir, let me try again.
Don't you test me,
Anantanagaraj.
Pirun!
You.
Kanoknaree!
Kanoknaree. Kanoknaree! No!
I don't think I'm gonna make it.
No! Kanoknaree! You'll be fine.
There.
-Our hope.
-What is it?
Do you remember
I told you about my father's invention
that I saw when I was a child?
I built this killing machine just in case.
If the Garuda catch us
during the evacuation,
they'll have to kill us all.
Whenever a Kinnara's blood
flows into its mechanism,
this weapon will appear
and destroy all of Ayothaya.
Luckily, at that time,
there was no need to use it.
The evacuation was successful.
The time has come, Watchara.
Aim this arrow towards the target
through the eye of the killing machine.
This arrow will control the direction
of its destructive power.
Remember, you only have one chance.
I... I...
Kanoknaree! No!
No!
Don't leave me!
Aim this arrow towards the target
through the eye of the killing machine.
This arrow will control the direction
of its destructive power.
Remember, you only have one chance.
You missed, Phya Watchara!
Buddhaisawan sword pose!
Finally, the Dark Monster is killed.
The Garuda can take back their kingdom.
Once the war ends,
all are saddened
to see the once-exquisite Ayothaya
reduced to rubble
with mountains of corpses.
Even more depressing
is the news that King Subunpon
was among the prisoners
driven to the kingdom of the Rakshasa.
No one news has been heard of him since.
One day,
I'll lead our army to attack the Rakshasa
and rescue King Subunpon.
Good luck. Bye-bye.
Bye.
-See you.
-Bye.
I feel sad
that we lost so many
brave Himmaphan soldiers
who fought alongside us.
All wars,
even the ones waged for a just cause,
are cruel.
When will all living beings
learn how to live together peacefully?
Eventually,
Ayothaya is restored
to her former exquisite glory.
Statues of the Himmaphan creatures
that fought to regain Ayothaya
are placed at the city's gates,
the palace steps, temples
and other buildings.
That's why you see
sculptures of Kochasri...
Norasingha...
Naga...
Kinnara...
Kinnari...
and Garuda adorning Ayothaya.
It is to commemorate their bravery
during that Great War
even until today.
After Phya Watchara
was enthroned as King,
he waged countless wars
against the Rakshasa
until he was killed on the battlefield.
He couldn't help the former King,
once his master, who remains in prison
even until today,
over a thousand years later.
"SUBUNPON"