[exclaiming, grunting]
Skadoosh.
[suspenseful music plays]
[rumbling]
-[dramatic music plays]
-[grunting]
[chuckles]
[muttering, grunting]
[yelps]
[exclaiming, yelling]
[grunts]
-[whimpers]
-[dramatic music plays]
[cackling]
-[grunting]
-[cackling]
[laughing]
[exclaiming]
[cackling]
-[distorted laughing]
-[whirring]
[yells]
[music intensifies]
[whirring]
Dragon Master!
[emperor] Please help!
[music intensifies]
[suspenseful music plays]
[somber music plays]
[Blade] Po?
Po!
[sighs]
They're gone.
Down the hill.
You should get going. [coughs]
Now, hold still, Po. You're hurt.
What happened?
My son was left to clean up your mess.
I even defended you,
but look what's happened!
Po… I--
Don't talk to him!
If you want to talk to him,
you gotta talk to me first,
and then maybe I'll relay the message.
I, I didn't mean for this to happen.
-[sighs]
-[chuckling] Oh…
She says, "This is all my fault,
and now it's your turn
to punch me in the arm
with a magical punchy glove thing."
The Knight's Code… Being your page…
All of it was a lie.
Why?
-[sighs]
-[soft music plays]
Alfie.
It's my fault that he died.
[Blade] He told me to stay home
that night, but I followed him.
[male voice] Sir Alfie, the mages have
attacked. The Queen calls for your aid.
[gasps]
[Alfie] Go, I'll meet you there. Go!
[atmospheric music plays]
[young Blade] Alfie!
Huh?
Are you going on a mission?
I want to help!
Lulu!
Not tonight. It's too dangerous.
What about you?
[sighs]
Do you know what I named it?
Luthera's Shield.
But it's a sword!
Yes. But its purpose is to protect you.
I'll always protect you.
And your mission is to stay here
and protect her until I get back.
-[stirring music plays]
-[kisses]
[suspenseful music plays]
[panting]
-Uh…
-[insects chirp]
[growling]
[rustling]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[swords clanging]
[grunting]
-[dramatic music plays]
-[grunting]
[grunts, chuckles]
-[shrieks]
-[grunting]
[exclaims]
-[whooping]
-[grunting]
-[grunts] Ah! Woohoo!
-[mystical music plays]
[Veruca laughs]
[whooping]
-[dramatic music plays]
-[grunting]
[exhales]
[chuckling]
[yells]
[young Blade] Leave my brother alone!
-Lulu!
-[grunts]
-[yelps]
-[Alfie] Get back!
I told you not to follow me.
[young Blade] But Alfie,
I knew you needed my help.
-[thudding]
-[echoing groan]
[chuckles softly]
-Alfie?
-[groans]
[both grunt]
No! [breathing heavily]
[kisses]
[whirring]
[yelps]
[crying]
If it wasn't for me,
my brother would still be alive.
-[soft music plays]
-[sniffles]
I have to fix this.
I have to avenge my brother's death.
[Po] Come on, you were just a kid.
You're more than your mission, Blade.
And you never have to lie to me.
So what if you're not a knight?
I'm not a Dragon Master.
Now, come on.
We got some weasels to catch.
[stirring music plays]
You're… still going to help me?
[wind whistles]
Of course I am.
[emotional music plays]
[fast-paced music plays]
[laughs]
[Veruca laughs]
[exclaims]
[whimpering]
-[whirring]
-[laughs]
[yells]
[dramatic music plays]
[yelling]
[screaming, whimpering]
[suspenseful music plays]
[whirring]
[cackles]
[grunts]
-[Veruca cackles]
-[Blade] Oh, we have to catch up.
[Mr. Ping] Not so fast!
Wherever he goes, I go.
This is a new rule I have,
ever since I met you.
I might have an idea.
[snoring]
[Blade] Zhen?
-Zhen is your idea?
-[grunts]
Trust me.
[sighs]
[grunts]
-[clanking]
-Huh?
[Weimin chuckles]
Nice try, Po,
but you're not escaping on my watch.
Oh, Weimin, buddy.
You're gonna regret that.
Hm?
-[Po] Woohoohoo! Yeah! [whooping]
-[yelling]
-[Po] Yeah! Oh, boy! Yeah!
-[dramatic music plays]
[grunting]
So long, suckers.
Yeah, baby! [whoops]
-[whirring]
-[Po] Ursa Major!
-[fireworks exploding]
-[Weimin screaming]
-[whirring]
-[groans]
[Weimin screaming]
-[whirring]
-[grunts]
[yells]
-Whoa!
-Hold on!
[yelling, grunting]
[squawks]
-[whip cracking]
-[whimpers]
-[groaning]
-[Po] Alright, push!
Hand me the reins.
Dad, do you even know how to drive a sled?
I won the North Chinese Sled Racing
Championship three years in a row.
[soft music plays]
Now get in, and hold on to your tenders.
[groaning]
[fast-paced music plays]
-Woohoohoo!
-Whoa!
[chuckling]
[whirring]
[Po] Come on!
[groaning]
[creaking]
[yelling]
-[whirring]
-[gasps]
[Weimin] Yeah!
We'll use the chicane to close the gap.
I'm sorry, the chi-- What now?
Now, we'll get into their slipstream
and make my move. [chuckles]
[yelling]
[distorted screaming]
Got you!
Dad! You're… [high-pitched] awesome!
[dramatic music plays]
[gasps] Dragon Master!
You came to save me!
Oh, now I'm the Dragon Master, huh?
Hand over the whip, Rukhmini.
We had a deal! I leave with the whip!
The whole world is doomed
if they get that whip.
That sounds like
the world's problem, not mine!
[exclaiming]
[yelling]
-Sorry about this, Weimin.
-Huh?
-[grunts]
-[yells]
[groans]
-[yelps]
-[groans]
[grunting]
Wait, what?
[yelling]
-Hey! You… c-can't.
-[grunting]
I'm the Emperor!
Well, that's something
you don't see every day!
-Hm… Or every night.
-[dramatic music plays]
-[emperor] Hey, you…
-[groaning, yelping]
[fast-paced music plays]
[grunting]
[laughs] Outsmarted again! Boop-de-boop--
[groaning]
-Doop.
-[Veruca cackles]
Huh?
[fast-paced music plays]
[whirring]
[gasps, grunts]
[dramatic music plays]
[cackles]
Ugh. Mages.
[exclaiming]
[exclaims]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[groaning]
-Right on the arm.
-[groaning]
-[tense music plays]
-Oh.
[Klaus] Such a nice boat.
Give our thanks
to the Emperor for the loan.
Now then, we'll just be taking
the whip off your hands.
Where's it at, eh?
[dramatic music plays]
-[exclaims, gasps]
-[yelling]
Ha ha!
Hand over the whip, bears.
No, you hand over the gauntlet, weasels.
No sense making this harder on yourselves.
[scoffs] You're both delusional.
The other mages are gone.
You two are all alone.
Even if you got all four, you couldn't
defeat all the knights of England.
[laughing]
Oh, but we can.
[somber music plays]
It's all right here in this scroll
that we took from the Lotus Village.
-[Klaus] A gauntlet to move the Earth…
-[whirring]
-[Klaus] A whip of endless flame…
-[growling]
-[Klaus] Wheels to ride the storm…
-[thunder crashing, electric crackling]
-[Klaus] And a helmet to master the wind.
-[air rushing]
[atmospheric music plays]
[Klaus] The ancient warriors
created these weapons for one purpose,
to trap the souls of their enemies.
[Veruca] But once
you bring all four together,
the souls inside
come out to play, play, play! [laughs]
[growling]
Did you know about this whole
evil army of resurrected monsters thingy
with the weapons?
You don't think I would have mentioned it?
Communication isn't exactly
your strong suit.
-[groans]
-I'm giving you one chance, Pandy.
Join me.
[somber music plays]
What? Wait, what?
No. No way.
[Po splutters] Not in a hundred
thousand million years would I ever,
you know,
even consider possibly thinking--
Yeah, yeah, got it.
-Your loss! I'm a catch!
-[whirring]
[yells]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[groans]
-[Blade grunting]
-[gasps]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[yells]
-[whip cracks]
-[Po exclaims]
Whoa! Did you see that?
-Po!
-[grunts]
[grunting]
I've been waiting for this for 15 years.
I should be thanking you.
If you hadn't shown up that night,
we'd be deady, dead, dead!
[grunting]
Our hero. [chuckles]
[exclaims, groans]
[groaning]
[grunting]
Ow!
[grunts]
[somber music plays]
[chuckles, yelps]
Take that!
-Whoo!
-[music chimes]
[music chimes]
-[dramatic music plays]
-[grunting]
[exclaims] Huh?
-[chuckles]
-Do you know what you're doing?
Oh, I'm getting the hang of it.
Isn't it peachy to see
you two back together again?
[yells]
-[laughs]
-[grunts]
[Po yells]
-[crackling]
-[grunting]
[yells]
[groaning]
-Blade, are you okay?
-[groans]
[Veruca] It's over, bears.
Not so--
Not so fa--
-Where is it?
-[Klaus] Looking for this?
Blade, we gotta go.
No.
Uh… Two magical weapons.
No magical weapons.
Maybe I'm not more than my mission.
[atmospheric music plays]
[grunting]
[yelling]
-[yells]
-Blade!
[groaning]
[sighs] Okay, think, Po.
What do we do? What do we do?
-[dramatic music plays]
-[Po] Okay.
I'll come with you, Veruca.
My…
l-love…
[gasps]
But you gotta leave Blade alone.
-[groans]
-[dramatic music plays]
Ah, offer's off the table, got it.
[yelling]
[groaning]
-Hm.
-[dramatic music plays]
[grunting]
That's my whip.
Not anymore.
[dramatic music plays]
No!
[groaning]
[grunting]
[suspenseful music plays]
No!
[grunting]
-[thudding]
-[gasps]
-[Blade grunting]
-[pants]
[straining]
[gasps]
You can't be serious.
Blade!
[grunting]
-[grunting]
-[creaking]
[squeals]
Let go!
I can't!
Black Steel of the Equinox! [exclaims]
[grunts]
[gasps]
-[suspenseful music plays]
-[Klaus sighs]
[Blade] You let them get away.
[sighs]
-I had to. I couldn't let them--
-[grunts]
-[Po] Oh…
-[sighs contentedly]
[gasps, sighs contentedly]
[soft music plays]
Thank you.
You would have done the same for me.
No. For being my friend.
My first friend.
And I shouldn't have lied to you.
You're making water come out of my eyes.
[sighs]
We don't know where they're headed,
and we have no weapon that can match them.
[Rukhmini] Uh, not quite true!
[stirring music plays]
[chuckles]
How did you--
If you have the whip, what do they have?
Always good to have a fake.
-[gasps]
-You switched it out?
[laughs] So what, you want to help us now?
I didn't say that.
But, we are after the same things.
The whip was supposed to be the first
on my hunt for all four Tianshang Weapons.
-But now--
-Uh, no, no, no.
If you wanna say something to my son,
you say it to me first,
and then maybe I'll tell him.
Same goes for you, still.
We aren't done.
Dad, it's okay.
You know how to find the other weapons?
It may cost more
than you're willing to pay.
Hm, sounds promising.
Uh, too bad we're heading home.
We're late for the dinner rush.
[Po] I have to go, Dad.
You heard Klaus and Veruca.
If we don't stop them,
they're gonna resurrect the evil army
and take over the world.
[soft music plays]
So if that means
I have to trust a fake knight…
Seems a bit harsh.
-And a con artist slash thief…
-Master con artist slash thief.
Then that's what I have to do.
Then I'm coming with you.
I'm sorry, what?
Stay out of this, Meandering Knife.
I'm not gonna let you do this alone,
with the two of them. [laughs]
You clearly need someone to protect you,
and that's always been my job.
[stirring music plays]
Then we're off on a treasure hunt.
[dramatic music plays]
And that means we're leaving China.
Wait, what?
[rhythmic music plays]