[exclaiming, grunting]
Skadoosh.
[owl hoots]
[mystical music plays]
[music crescendos]
Oh, Lady Veruca. [clears throat]
Your Majesty.
You grace me at quite the late hour.
Yes, um, you see,
I enjoyed a generous helping
of royal cheese at supper.
[whispering] And it seems
I'm in need of a royal flush, if you will.
Oh. Right away, ma'am.
[mystical music plays]
-[music intensifies]
-[whirring]
A bit of mugwort. A pinch of bladderwrack.
Thank you, ladies.
Whilst I have you,
I was thinking of appointing Sir Alfred
as my new Master of War.
Hm. Interesting.
Do you not think it wise?
As your loyal advisor…
I only ever want
what's best for you, my Queen.
[straining]
Come on, you little blighter.
[Veruca strains]
-[Klaus groans]
-[snarls]
[sighs] What are you doing?
-[insects chirp]
-Nothing.
[groans] No map, no leads.
I'm bleeding out
and you're lagging behind!
Prison made you useless.
-[grunts]
-[groans]
Keep moving. Or do I need to carry you…
[grunts]
[Veruca grunts]
Useless, eh?
[atmospheric music plays]
[music intensifies]
[owl hoots]
[grunting]
[panting]
[sighs]
[takes deep breath]
[rustling]
[scats] Stealth.
[scats] Camouflage.
Sneak attack!
-[grunts]
-[groans]
A good strategy for a sneak attack
is to not yell "sneak attack."
Yeah, no, totally. I know.
Just, like, practicing.
[whispers] Sneak attack.
When we use that thumb,
Klaus and Veruca
will be pulled right to us.
Oh, I got a plan.
And its name is Operation Ursa Major.
-[lively music plays]
-[grunting]
[grunts]
The gauntlet would mash you
before you even got to the Ursa part.
We need to take that gauntlet
out of the equation.
[sighs] And we need
a lot more than a belly bump.
Hey, you okay? You hungry?
I always get that faraway look
when I'm looking for food.
Far away.
I just…
I've never been this close
to capturing Klaus and Veruca before.
[groans] We have to get this
absolutely right.
Do you understand?
I do. I won't let you down, Blade.
Then, Page,
it's time you have
your next lesson in knighthood.
-[majestic music plays]
-[gasps, giggles]
[gasps]
Oh, is it weird to bow?
That's more of a kung fu thing.
What's the knight thing? Curtsy?
No, it's gotta be something tough.
Plan B is still Operation Ursa Major.
[exclaims]
[Veruca] Klaus! Klaus.
Wake up! Wake up.
-Klaus! You hit your head again. Wake up!
-[yelps] What are you-- Ow! [yells]
[groans] What's the matter with you?
You were once the Queen's archmage,
and now you're just
nothing but a crazy animal.
-[atmospheric music plays]
-[groans]
[footsteps recede]
[intriguing music plays]
[mystical music plays]
[music intensifies]
[strains]
[groans, sighs]
[emotional music plays]
[groans]
[rattling]
♪ I am Changpu, la la la ♪
[hums]
♪ I love mushrooms, la la la ♪
♪ Changpu mushrooms
Changpu mushrooms, la la ♪
-Shadow, stranger! [shrieks]
-[dramatic music plays]
Hello, love.
Oh, my. Hello. Happy harvest to you.
Quite the harvest, indeed.
Looks like enough for a whole village, eh?
I am forbidden from telling strangers
about our secret village. I, uh--
Oh, dang it! [groans] Changpu. [groans]
And this village that you
didn't tell me about, it's got a doctor?
[tense music plays]
Listen up, Po.
This training will be grueling, painful,
and may push you to your absolute limit.
And should you excel,
I will advance you to the level of squire.
Squire? Squire!
That's just one step below knight!
[gasps] Okay, so like, what am I learning?
-How to disarm the enemy.
-[soft music plays]
[gasps]
[Blade] It's a simple maneuver.
The enemy charges at you.
Okay. [chuckles]
Alright, here I come. [chuckles] Whoo!
[yells, grunts]
[grunting]
-[cracking]
-Uncle? Auntie? Grandma?
[yelping] Second cousin twice removed?
-And then, you simply remove the--
-[laughs]
[grunts] Ha! Nailed it.
Now, what's the move to get the glove off?
[inhales] That was the move.
[sighs] You ruined it.
Well, you said
to give it all I've got, so I…
[grunts] Let's reverse roles.
Remember, do exactly as I did. Ready?
[suspenseful music plays]
[sighs]
[grunting]
[groans] Not bad. For a page.
But you see, I can still--
Ursa Major! [exclaims]
[groaning]
Was that right?
[groans] No! No, that was not right.
What's with the gut check?
That's not how the move works.
Well, your move didn't totally work,
so I threw some mustard on it.
And a little belly bump,
a little catchphrase, kapow!
[scoffs] Is that even a kung fu move?
If a kung fu master does it,
then it's a kung fu move.
Will you please just do as I've asked?
Okay, okay. Whatever you say.
[sighs] Give me the glove.
Let's go again, Page.
[Champu straining]
How much further? I'm getting tired.
[chuckles] Maybe i-if we both pulled--
[spluttering] A-Actually, this is great.
I-I've been meaning to do more upper body.
If you don't get my brother fixed up soon,
you won't have an upper body.
[grunting, panting]
So very pretty and quaint.
-[rhythmic music plays]
-[Veruca] I hate it.
The harvest arrives soon, sisters.
Just as the Yaojing foretold.
[rattling]
[groaning]
-Changpu has returned.
-Happy harvest.
-Happy harvest, Changpu.
-Yay!
[chow chow 1] Harvest! Woohoo!
I'm back, sisters. And with traveler--
Hello, ladies and gentle-- Mm…
Huh. No gentlemen. No matter. [chuckles]
Who's in charge here?
Why, we all are.
But I speak for the Yaojing,
and she flows through me.
Like a gorgeous fresh mountain stream.
Ooh, the Yaojing demands
you write that down, Changpu.
"Like a gorgeous fresh mountain stream."
Perfect for this week's newsletter.
"Flows through me, like a stream."
-Mountain stream.
-Fresh.
[high priestess] Fresh mountain stream.
Uh, the Yaojing?
She is our great, unseen spirit.
This humble forest village maintains
the mystic purity of all of her daughters,
and I am her high priestess.
-Our lady!
-She cares for us all.
-Our lady. We love her.
Look here.
I need someone to patch my brother up.
So take us to your doctor, now.
-Did you say "brother"?
-[chow chow 2] He's here.
-He's here.
-At last.
Ooh!
[shushes] Shut it, everyone.
Happy to help.
Do you really need the knife?
It's my lucky cleaver.
Oh, lucky.
Hm, fair enough. Follow me.
Hey, you. Don't forget my brother.
[groans]
[grunting]
[atmospheric music plays]
[groans softly] What?
Where am I?
[Klaus] What are you?
Am I dead?
You wish, you wish.
[slurps, smacks lips]
[sniffs] Mm, smoky.
Like sipping a campfire.
[slurps]
[groans] You call that tea?
Tastes like sock juice.
What are you doing?
Enjoying the fruits of my labor.
It's been months
since the Yaojing sent a traveler.
We were starting to worry
we'd angered her.
I mean, Changpu angers her so often.
Oh, it's true, I'm a lot. [chuckles]
Well… [slurps]
I cannot thank the Yaojing enough.
Feels better already.
[Klaus, echoing] In fact,
I don't feel much of anything.
[Klaus laughs, echoing]
[chow chows laugh, echoing]
[gasps]
Wait, what's in this stuff?
[echoing] Well, you see,
usually we do not allow men
into our secret village.
-No. Never.
-They can't be trusted.
But you happen to have arrived
just in time for…
the harvest.
Harvest? Oh, that sounds great.
Will there be any food?
Oi, what are you… [groans]
-[grunts]
-[somber music plays]
Say, I'll… [grunts]
[grunts]
We don't usually care for a lady,
but, who are we to refuse
[echoing] the Yaojing's abundant harvest.
Everything I foretold. [grunts]
Mm?
Where did they go?
When are we eating?
You idiot.
We're the harvest.
[music crescendos]
[Po and Blade grunt]
-[Blade groans]
-[Po laughs]
-[crashing]
-[groans] Po.
-[gasps]
-[groans]
Okay. Lesson over. Lesson over. [grunts]
What? No, no, no, I'm sorry.
I'll take the mustard off
and do it exactly like you showed me.
-[groans]
-[soft music plays]
It's not you, Po.
I've imagined this moment
every day for 15 years.
[dramatic music plays]
[Blade] The day they realize
that there's no more running…
I have to be perfect
in every swing of my sword.
Because if I am,
I may look them in the eyes
and finally say,
"In the name of
Her Majesty the Queen of England,
I place you under arrest
for the murder of Sir Alfred of Landreth,
Son of the Saxon Guard,
Knight of England."
[Blade sighs]
What if I can't do it?
[soft music plays]
[inhales, exhales]
Let's go again.
[emotional music plays]
[rhythmic music plays]
Pretty.
[grunting]
[groaning]
I will not be locked up again.
I can't breathe. I can't think.
The room is spinning.
Spinny-spin the room…
Veruca, the moon's out.
You could use those powers of yours.
-Don't you understand?
-[mystical music plays]
I used to feel connected to the Earth,
like a thread in my hand.
But that thread's been cut.
I can reach out and feel for it
all I want, but it's never there.
[Veruca] Not there…
[thumping]
Take him.
-Are we eating now? Oh! [exclaims] Ouch!
-Klaus. Klaus. No, Klaus.
-[groans] Wait!
-If anyone's gonna kill him, it's me.
-Wait, where are we going? Veruca!
-[Veruca] No! Klausy!
Oh, fear not, sister.
He goes to the Yaojing.
And you?
[high priestess laughs]
You will join us for dessert.
-[door slams]
-[Klaus] Veruca!
[Klaus, echoing] Veruca!
-[intriguing music plays]
-[frogs croak]
Seize the fugitive!
For the murder of Sir Alfred.
You can't arrest me, you dolt.
I'm the Queen's mage.
We're here on her orders.
You've been plotting to betray her.
[laughs]
Betrayal? Ha!
I did what I had to do,
and I'd do it again.
Now, let me go! Lemme! [grunts]
This isn't over. [grunts]
Just you wait until nightfall.
[yelps, pants]
[grunting] Lemme out!
-[Veruca pants]
-[mystical music plays]
[exhales softly] The moon…
[straining]
[rattling]
-[dramatic music plays]
-[Veruca gasps]
No!
[tense music plays]
[clanging]
[clattering]
[scratching]
-[tense music fades]
-[breathes shakily]
[Klaus] Veruca!
[clanging]
-I found you.
-[soft music plays]
After 15 years, I found you.
Klaus? Klausy?
Klaus. Klaus! [gasping]
[Veruca] Where is everyone?
The other mages?
Gone.
[Klaus] It's up to us now.
Klaus.
The moon.
-[tinkling]
-[mystical music plays]
[exclaiming] Wait, wait, wait.
You can't eat me.
I'm very lean. And-And gamey.
Plus, I hear weasel's meat
is very high in cholesterol.
Stop, please. [exclaims] Hot. Hot!
Be comforted knowing that the Yaojing
has brought you for the harvest.
And besides, you're not my first weasel.
[dramatic music plays]
-[chow chow 3 screams]
-[chow chow 4] Oh no!
-[chow chows exclaiming, gasping]
-[dramatic music plays]
[chow chow 5] It's the Yaojing. Yaojing!
-Veruca! She found it.
-[chow chows exclaim]
Oh, you're in for it now.
-[whirring, humming]
-[grunts]
-[creaking]
-[screaming]
[suspenseful music plays]
[screams]
[grunting, yelping]
I-I don't understand. She's real?
[scoffs]
Oh, she's real.
Just, uh, just as I foretold.
[screams]
And you, all of you angered her.
One more than the others.
[dramatic music plays]
[screaming]
[yelling]
You can't be the Yaojing,
because I made her up.
You're right.
[dramatic music plays]
I'm far worse.
[chuckles nervously] Oh.
-[yells]
-[screams]
[yelping, screaming]
-[dramatic music plays]
-[screaming]
-[owl hoots]
-[soft music plays]
[Po exclaims]
[grunts]
[gasps] How… How did you…
Threw my voice.
[high-pitched]
Ventriloquism lessons as a boy.
[groans] It's useless.
Hey.
Maybe you're just
too in your head about it.
You've been planning it for 15 years,
but nothing ever goes the way you plan it.
Sometimes you've just gotta
bust a move and find a new way.
[takes deep breath]
[groans] You might as well
just catch them yourself.
[stirring music plays]
The Archmage of England has returned.
You, you found the thread.
Thanks to you, brother. And the moon.
[Veruca] England will be ours.
And from there, we will build
the empire we've always deserved!
Blade, we'll only bring them to us
when you're ready.
[Veruca] But this village
will have no place in it.
[whirring]
Or maybe now's good.
-[music intensifies]
-[yelps]
-[whirring intensifies]
-[grunts]
[echoing]
[suspenseful music plays]
[dramatic music plays]
[grunting]
[coughing]
[growling]
Um…
Hi?
[growls]
[grunting]
[gasps]
-[whirring]
-[exclaims, laughs]
[grunts]
-Veruca!
-[gasps]
[grunts]
[suspenseful music plays]
[grunting]
[echoing] Ursa Major!
[yelps]
[groaning]
[sighs]
[stirring music plays]
[gasps]
[whirring]
[atmospheric music plays]
[whirring stops]
[gasps]
-[Veruca] The moon's gone.
-[birdsong]
-[Veruca gasps]
-[stirring music plays]
[grunts]
In the name of
Her Majesty the Queen of England,
I place you under arrest
for the murder of Sir Alfred of Landreth,
Son of the Saxon Guard, Knight of England,
and my brother.
[growls]
Good work.
[Blade] Squire.
Squire? [gasps] Squire? For real?
But you got the gauntlet.
Thanks to your lesson in kung fu.
[emotional music plays]
[grunts]
[grunting]
Patience, little brother.
I was 15 years in darkness.
We need only wait for moonrise.
[dramatic music plays]
[rhythmic music plays]