WHEN HONG KONG'S TRIADS WERE IN POWER
Ma Si-feng, the head of Golden Dragon.
He controlled the market
and made a living by extorting people.
Shen Zhi-lang,
the head of the Ghost's Gate Gang.
He controlled bars and brothels
and made a living by collecting rent.
Yi Tsun-pak, the head of Rong Jae Alley.
He had mahjong and fantan casinos.
After Ma Si-feng died,
Ma Zhen-li took over the gang.
He then fell ill with gout
and couldn't walk.
He passed away soon after.
Ma Zhen-li had three sons.
Ma Yong-chong, the eldest,
died after his father's death.
He said he wanted to follow his father
and take care of him.
Ma Yong-hai, the second eldest, took over.
Ma Yong-tai, the youngest son,
left the mafia world
because he loved beauty.
After Shen Zhi-lang died,
Shen-piao, his only son,
took control of the gang.
He only had daughters.
So, he stole a child from an orphanage,
named him Shen-po,
and raised him to be the next leader.
Yi Tsun-pak died from unknown causes.
I'll tell you when I find out.
His son, Long-ye,
took control of the Rong Jae Alley Gang.
Finally, Fei, his son, took over from him.
These three gangs didn't want to
be friendly with one another.
They all wanted to be
the only one in control.
Even if you don't remember
anything from this, it's okay.
Because the movie hasn't started yet.
GTH presents
an Ar Ti Film production...
Kung Fu Tootsie
A toast to Tao, who will be
the next leader of the Golden Dragon Gang!
My man, one larb and one Pedigree, please.
Did you bring your dog here?
No. I ordered it for myself.
Tao! Something happened!
Tao.
The next in line to lead Golden Dragon.
Let's go!
Some of the characters are
dubbed in Thai by Panthamitr.
Follow him.
Go!
Help! I think they got my ear!
Where are they? Stop following them.
They're all bleeding already.
They were foolishly outnumbered.
You didn't know
how many of them would show up?
I did, but I didn't know Tao and you guys
would be ready to fight.
Nobody listened to me
after Tao said, "Let's go."
Wait, Nokroo. Why aren't you hurt at all?
I didn't follow you.
Hey.
Where's Tao?
The Golden Dragon Den.
How pathetic.
You've hurt so many people.
It seems like he won't last long.
Ma Yong-hai, the leader of Golden Dragon.
You would've been the next leader.
What are we going to do?
Hai is very sick already.
He's old and his brain is damaged.
Have you eaten?
Out.
I ask if you've eaten yet.
What do you mean "out"?
Stuck.
What do you mean "stuck"?
If Ghost's Gate
and Rong Jae Alley knew about this,
they would laugh their asses off.
You still have me, Kun!
You?
Hai. Look at your son.
How could he say that?
Out.
I'll lead Golden Dragon myself!
You? You can't even wipe your own butt!
Out.
What do you mean?
What?
Out.
You have gout too?
How did it get in there?
Why are you whimpering?
-Why didn't you tell me that?
-I did tell you.
Where are you going?
To the market.
Why?
To get my arm.
A dog must have eaten it already.
Tao.
What are you looking for?
The heirloom ring.
How did it get lost?
Let me. I'll look for it myself.
It's not in here.
Is it in your pocket?
Let me see.
Oh, no.
Yes.
-He's doing the lion dance? How can he?
-I know.
Look at him.
-Look at him.
-This is atrocious.
-He can do this all day.
-How nasty.
-This will ruin our reputation.
-Yes.
Tien is Tao's twin brother.
He already knew he was gay
from a young age.
Ma Yong-hai couldn't accept him,
so his mother raised him on her own.
You look so old for a queer,
do you know that?
Yes.
And your arms are not feminine at all.
They're hairy, too.
Yes.
The lion dance is for men.
You shouldn't do it.
Shame on you!
Wait.
What do I have to do
to be feminine like you?
Please help me.
I really want to be feminine.
I can see your dedication.
The three angels will help you.
We'll turn you from a gorilla to an angel,
like us.
Can I change my mind right now?
Shut up!
This is my signature move.
All the boys fall for me because of this.
It's important for gay people
to be foul-mouthed.
I'll teach you how to use words
as your weapons.
Bitch. Dummy.
You filthy cow.
Dickhead. Bastard.
-Fuck you, bitch!
-Good.
-What the hell are you looking at?
-Great.
-Shut the fuck up, whore!
-Awesome.
Say that again and I'll mess you up.
You talked so much about Lady's Kung Fu.
Let's see it.
-Yes. Show it to us.
-Yes.
No. I don't want to make a scene.
You think it'll cause a scene?
Are you going to show it to us or not?
-Show it.
-Yes.
Tien!
What are you doing?
Tien, what are you doing?
This is the Lady's Kung Fu
that my mom taught me.
What did you do?
Do you want to buy
some illegal lottery tickets?
Aren't you afraid of getting caught?
The police just bought two.
Good. Go ahead and sell them.
Mom, why do I have to carry this?
You have so many servants.
The Lady's Kung Fu relies on your wrists.
But what are these bags for?
-Are they heavy?
-Yes.
There. That's the wrist workout for you.
Then why don't you carry them too?
No.
I'm good enough. Wait here.
Where are you going?
Don't worry. I'm not looking for
a new husband, not right now.
They're fighting now?
They're not animals, you know.
Hey, don't hurt the helpless woman!
Kun?
Hai, how are you?
Let me see my son first.
Mom.
No. You lost your arm?
-It's okay.
-What about the rest of your body?
Dad!
Dad.
Tao.
Tien.
No one in the house knows about
what happened to Tao.
Why didn't you tell them?
If you had stopped being gay,
I would have told them.
What does that have to do with me?
You have to be the next head
of Golden Dragon.
What about me and Dad?
I'll take them to Jew Jow Gow
for treatment.
Tien,
I believe you can do it.
And you can do it well...
if you stop...
being gay.
Please, it's for your dad
and your brother.
Dad.
Hai.
-Dad.
-Hai.
Hey!
Hey.
What's up with that hand?
-Hey!
-Good!
What the hell was that?
Chin up. Chest out. Tuck your butt in.
Stand straight!
Your hands go like this.
The men in these photos.
You have to remember their names.
Do you understand?
This is Shen-po of the Ghost's Gate Gang.
They have control over the nightclubs.
Fei of the Rong Jae Alley Gang.
They control the casinos.
This is Three.
She takes care of the place.
This is our gang.
They are Ler, Nokroo, Jer, and Sing.
And this is Pei-pei, your girlfriend.
You failed from the start, bitch.
Who says you can touch me?
You think I was going to fall?
-Oh, Tao.
-Let me stop you right there.
You messed up, Nokroo.
I'm Jer.
Why didn't you tell us, Nokroo?
I'm Sing.
Why didn't you check
if we were outnumbered or not?
If I wasn't Tao,
the head of the Golden Dragon Gang,
I wouldn't be standing right here.
It's a good thing he's safe.
Tao.
What is it, Six?
That's not my name.
What is it, Three?
Miss Pei-pei is here.
Tao.
Pei-pei!
Pei-pei.
The Ghost's Gate Bar.
We're foreigners.
Show some hospitality here.
Yes, you're foreigners.
But you're not the owners.
So, pay up.
Damn it.
That hurts.
Go ask Shen-po
if he's going to sell this bar to my boss.
Shen-po.
Do you see that I'm hurt?
Shen-po, the head of
the Ghost's Gate Gang.
Hey, I asked you to look after the bar.
Why are you sleeping here?
I was beaten up.
Krapa. Meow-sao. Go in there.
Don't take too long. I'm hungry.
I'm having dinner with my kid.
He came out, Krapa. Get him, Meow-sao.
Oh, are you okay?
-Are you okay?
-Okay.
Come on.
Now that's a knockout.
Is anyone in there?
Come out already.
That's enough! I can't take it anymore!
Tell your boss
that my boss won't sell this place.
There!
Who was that? He almost hit my toe.
Rong Jae Alley Casino.
Fei, the head of Rong Jae Alley.
Steady, boss. Steady.
A little to the left and then...
Go ahead. Good.
Fei.
You can't even catch the watermelon.
You think you can beat me?
I've got a full house.
I'm so sorry, Fei.
I've got a straight flush.
Hey.
No!
No! Fei, please, don't!
-Fei, please spare my life!
-Go!
Come here!
-Fei. No!
-Stay still.
-No, Fei! Let me go!
-I said stay still.
Fei, please. I beg you!
Fei, don't!
I'll give you seven days
to find the money.
Thank you so much, Fei.
Thank you.
You've got it.
Now I've got it.
Remember, Tien.
Our gang relies on extortion.
Come on, Kun-kun.
Some vendors aren't selling well.
Where will they get the money to pay?
Think.
I'm already ashamed that you're gay.
Now you're calling me by that silly name.
My name is Kun, not Kun-kun.
If people hear this,
they will lose respect for us.
Act like a man, for God's sake.
You keep saying that every day.
I'm trying so hard,
I think I look a couple of years older.
What more do you want from me?
Tao.
If they say things like that again,
I'll beat them up.
-Don't be afraid of them.
-I know.
This is your soup. Be careful. It's hot.
Thank you, Three.
Both Shen-po and Fei...
Do you want some congee?
-They want to take over the market.
-I think I'll make you some noodles.
-Don't trust them.
-Which one would you like?
If you can't stand them, just shoot them!
-Who?
-I'm going to shoot you. Damn it!
Fine. No soup for you, then.
Ghost's Gate Gang.
Pei-pei.
Do you want me to die of grief?
You know Tao is my enemy!
How could you be in love with him?
Why are you so upset?
You're not the one who's marrying him.
But he's the son of Ma Yong-hai!
You need to know the difference
between love and revenge.
When your sister married Fei's son, Kung,
it almost drove me crazy.
What is this for?
I'm talking to my daughter.
-Are you done?
-Yes, honey.
-Good. Let's change the subject.
Someone is bugging us.
What kind of bugs are they?
There are foreigners disturbing the
casino.
Jeez.
Please, boss.
Damn it.
He cheated.
He started acting like this
when we found out.
They're not bugs.
What are they, then?
They're dead.
What do you mean they're dead?
I mean, they're going to be dead soon
if they don't stop that.
Are you messing with me?
I told you not to use old cards, didn't I?
How did you know we used old cards?
You didn't even look.
-It was salty, dummy!
-Yes, sir.
You've been here a lot lately,
haven't you?
It's good that you're here.
My boss told me to ask you
whether you want to
sell this place or not.
Tell your boss I won't sell it!
I mean, my boss won't sell it.
People say your kung fu is the best.
If you don't mind, please show it to us.
He took his jacket off. What's next?
-He clapped and snapped.
-Clean up.
Wow, that's some talent.
This must be your first time.
Let me show you what's next.
Please, be my guest.
Things are about to get real.
Be careful.
Will their moms know
that they gave birth to punching bags?
-He got him.
-Yes.
He's so kind.
What now, boss?
Can you find it? No, you won't find it.
What are you looking for?
A weiner?
I can't find it.
Come on!
Hang on a little longer.
You almost got him.
-Are you okay, Fei?
-He doesn't look so good.
-Yes.
-Oh, no. He's going to fall.
Oh, the big guy fell instead.
You're the greatest, Fei.
Please use this chair.
He doesn't need a chair.
I thought you didn't need it.
Shit.
-What did he say?
-I don't know. I'm not a foreigner.
If he's not a foreigner,
-then what the hell is he?
-I don't know.
Tao.
Do you remember what happened last month?
Yes. I remember. Last month,
we went out somewhere, right?
No, we didn't.
Last month,
you were tackled
by a bunch of foreign men.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Every single one of them was ripped.
It took you all night to take them down.
Do you remember?
Wow, we were at it all night?
Yes. And when you were in there,
you used your entire body against them.
Your face was pressed against them.
You could feel them breathe behind you.
You were so cool when you were fighting.
That really turned me on, damn it.
I might decide to crash
your side of the car.
Then I might hit your face.
I might kick you.
I might slash your throat.
This is love, we're in love
It's like you swept me off my feet
You and I, we'll be together forever
-How much is this stinky tofu?
-Four dollars a plate
-I'll take one, please
-Okay
Ler, do you have any money?
I have some
-Keep the change
-You don't have to
Take it
That's so kind of you
Try this, Pei-pei
Oh, your pinky is out
We're so in love
We're creating our own happiness
You smile gave me meaning and hope
The world seems pure and sweet
With you in it
Do you notice something weird?
That was odd
He has never paid for the food
But today, he did
Stop being nosy, let's go get ice cream
Did that hurt? How about this?
Do you know that Fei is going to
take over this market?
Pay me right now.
I already paid.
There.
That hurts.
-What's up with the noise?
-It hurts.
That hurts.
Tao, I already paid you.
Why is this happening?
Stop talking.
Oh, he's alone.
Hey.
Let's make Fei proud.
Sure.
Tao, be careful!
Tao.
Here. Take that. Damn it.
Oh, what is this? I can't see.
What is going on?
That hurts.
There.
Again?
Oh, my.
I've got you.
Hey, what's this?
Hey.
Hey!
-What happened?
-I was beaten.
Left. Right.
Oh, I'm stuck.
Help me, I'm being assaulted!
What is this?
-Gosh.
-Hey.
What do we do?
Let's go.
Going home already?
Look at these goons.
You're rolling him like a burrito.
To compensate for that,
you won't have to pay me for three months.
Let's make it a year. I was so shaken.
Six months.
I've never given anyone this much.
Eight months. Do we have a deal?
Why didn't you take it off?
Oh, right.
From now on,
if anyone goes against my orders,
I'll kill them.
That's too much.
Jer! Sing!
Why did our income
for this month decrease?
You told us not to take money
from those who didn't have it.
Yes.
And you gave some money
to our wives and children.
-Yes.
-That was awesome.
To keep my men happy,
I must keep their families happy.
-Right?
-Yes.
-That's right.
-My wife just got some money from him.
I was fortunate
to meet the saint of the mafia world.
No way.
Tao, one of Fei's men
wants to talk to you.
Hey.
What is it?
Would you like to join forces
with Rong Jae Alley
and destroy Ghost's Gate?
-Show me the Lady's Kung Fu.
-Fei is asking you.
-Make it brutal.
-If you don't want to, we'll destroy you.
Oh, sure.
"Pew!"
That "pew" part was gross.
That was the most brutal thing I've seen.
Deadly striking.
Fei, eat some more.
Open your mouth.
Fei.
-What?
-He said that
he's going to take over
Rong Jae Alley soon.
How dare he say that!
-Fei, don't waste food.
-Yes.
-Tao.
-Yes, honey.
One of Shen-po's men wants to talk to you.
My job here is done.
You don't have to say anything.
Tell Shen-po that the bars and nightclubs
are going to be mine soon!
Oh, take that.
Tell him I punched you in the gut
and I don't care!
That was cool.
I asked you. What did he do to you?
Why can't you say it?
If you can't say it, just act it out!
Do you want to die? Do you?
Then he said, "I punched you in the gut
and I don't care!"
But they are the enemy of Ghost's Gate.
What does that have to do with me?
Please, listen to what I'm saying here.
What the hell did she say?
What did you say?
Oh, she heard me.
What do you want me to do?
Stop being part of the mafia.
What are we going to eat, then?
You can be a stinky tofu vendor.
That's what you want me to do?
-How about this?
-Yes?
You can...
merge your gang with Golden Dragon.
To hell with that.
I'm sorry.
You know that's impossible.
Do you even think of me at all?
You're just like your mother.
Please listen to me.
Stop it, Three!
Don't say anything.
Wait until we leave before you say it.
See? Everyone is hot-blooded.
And then what happened? You all swallowed.
You mean you all suck?
-Well, you more than just suck.
-Yes.
-Kun--
-Stop it, Three!
And now, we're getting less money.
You need to take care of this.
Now you can say it.
You forgot to wear your pants.
We want to have
braised pork intestines tonight.
I don't think that's going to be
a problem, Mr. Chang.
I don't think that's possible.
My restaurant is quite small.
It's not suited for Golden Dragon.
We will expand the restaurant
to match the gang's greatness.
But I don't think
you'll like the food here.
Oh, the best chef in Asia
just arrived here.
But if you're going to fight in here,
I'm afraid things might get damaged.
Well, we can fix them.
The honor of the gang must come first.
The head of Golden Dragon invited you
to an event to introduce their new leader.
Tao said the casinos we own
and the nightclubs that Ghost's Gate runs
are going to be his.
Get me another one of this.
The vendor said they ran out of noodles.
Take this gun and shoot them.
-Easy there, Fei.
-Why?
You can order one tomorrow.
No! I want it today!
If they don't have it,
just shoot up their shop.
It's my father's.
Shall we shoot them up now?
-Who are you going to shoot?
-Your dad.
Go ahead. I'm not telling anyone.
They'll make fun of me too.
The celebration for the new leader.
Let's toast to Tao.
-Cheers!
To greatness.
You get to eat. And you get to eat.
And you get to eat. You get to eat, too.
There.
That was stupid!
How dare you disrespect Tao,
the leader of Golden Dragon!
Apologize to him.
-We're sorry.
This is a happy event.
Please don't ruin it.
Are you the leader here, Kun?
Shut up!
Now, Fei, if you're here
with good intentions, sit.
Thank you.
May you be blessed with greatness.
Hey! Say,
"May you be blessed with greatness."
-May you be blessed with greatness.
The rule here is "no weapons."
How is it going?
Oh, Shen-po. I thought you weren't coming.
We're pals. How could I not be here?
Oh, Fei is here.
Hey, guys. Look, Fei is here.
-Hi, Fei.
I don't know you!
Po, please don't bring weapons in here.
-Excuse me, Shen-po.
-It's fine.
I've got it.
Is it a gun?
It's a fish.
A fish?
Why does he have a fish?
General Jia is here.
Stand up, Po. The police are here.
It's nothing, Jia.
Nothing?
Hey, what's going on?
That hurt.
Have you been glassed before?
No, but I've had a glazed donut.
Oh, they're discussing the menu.
Let's go.
Who discusses the menu
with broken bottles?
Don't. We can't fight them.
This is my territory.
Please show some respect!
Here we go.
The rule is "no weapons."
Why don't you people listen?
They must have hidden them
between their butt cheeks.
I hope the guns go off and blow up
your butts if you do this again.
-That would be nasty.
-Put them away.
I'll sell them later.
Dang it. I thought I would
get to shoot people.
Sit down.
Now that that's over, please have a drink.
Since you're going to be
the new leader of Golden Dragon,
why don't you show us some moves?
It's up to you.
I can't even take care of myself
these days.
If you and Po assist,
I can certainly do that.
Okay.
Then, we split the area in half.
That side will be for Po's men.
This side will be for Krapa and Meow-sao.
If you're still standing
after ten minutes,
then you're fit to be the new leader.
Begin.
Give me back my belt. My pants are loose.
Oh, no.
Look at that white butt.
Let me do this.
Watch out.
I can't do it anymore.
I heard someone calling you.
Me too.
-His leg.
-Don't share this.
I can see it now.
That must hurt.
Are you okay?
Is your back turning red?
-He's been defeated.
-How is his back?
Oh, that's a good one.
-Hey, you.
-There.
-Did you call me?
-Hang in there.
There.
Wait!
Does it hurt?
If I said it doesn't,
would you believe me?
No. I have to try it myself.
Yes, it does hurt.
Serves you right. You wanted it.
-You just knew it hurts?
-Hey.
Hey.
I think my spine just got crooked.
-Stop!
-He doesn't care who he hits.
-Let me do this.
-Sure. You're going to get hurt.
You think you're so good?
Why did you hit me? You...
Hey, wait.
This isn't about you anymore.
Let me finish this first.
Why did you hit me?
-Hey, stop.
-Don't stop us!
-A knockout.
-What do we do now?
He still has five minutes left.
Look at him. He's mad.
Hey.
Get out of the way, losers.
I'm not seeing you out, Fei.
Hey! I already surrendered!
What more do you want?
What?
Who tripped me?
That thing.
Oh, I didn't see that.
Get out of the way!
Everything looks normal.
Don't fight in here.
You really don't know
that they're fighting?
They're all sweaty.
I've got cataracts.
I've been meaning to get eye surgery.
-Hello, Tao.
Hello, Tao.
-Hello.
-Tao.
Hello, Tao.
Kun, can you not walk this close to me?
I want to be with Pei-pei.
Now, before I lose my patience.
I'll be like Tien if you don't.
Hey, go wait in the market!
But this is the market.
I'm coming with you.
-Where are you going?
-Just tell us where in the market.
Yes.
You're right.
Pei-pei, are we going to stand here
and get darker and darker?
Let's go over there. There's some shade.
Oh, my!
Why are these roses so fabulously red?
-Why are they so red?
-I painted them.
-Let's go over there.
-Why?
To look at some hairpins.
For you, of course.
-Tien!
-Crap!
Gorilla!
You lion-dancing bitch!
Who's Tien? Why are we running away?
Wait for me, you unfeminine gay.
A fortune-teller told me
I killed a eunuch in my past life.
-What does that have to do with this?
-They're taking revenge.
Can we slow down?
Those three gays over there.
Distract them, but don't hurt them.
-Hurry.
-Where are we going?
We've got them.
And this is what we'll do.
We're so proud.
-Shit! Who was that?
-Right.
Damn it! I think it was Shen-po!
But it's more likely to be Fei.
There were ducks over there.
Give me the gun.
You already have one.
I can't use this one.
Why?
It's been gunned down.
Do you want me to kick you in the face
or are you going to laugh at my puns?
Good.
That was cool, Fei. You shot a duck.
I'm getting old.
So, I just shoot ducks now.
When I was younger, I never shot them.
So what did you do?
Duck.
My baby.
Fei is crazy.
Back in the day,
when your dad was the leader,
Fei barged into our house
and shot your dad multiple times.
Over there. On that chair.
He fired until he ran out of bullets.
Then he reloaded and started firing again.
Why didn't he die?
Dad was at the market.
I'm right here.
That's enough. Alcohol isn't good for you.
I have some soup for you. It's really hot.
You're so nosy.
Three, do you remember
when Fei came in here and shot Hai?
Of course.
That crazy man was just shooting
at the same chair over and over.
Kun, do you want some braised intestines
for breakfast tomorrow?
Nobody respects me in this house.
Those people in the mafia are perverts.
-Yes, I'm very mad at them.
-They like seeing us naked.
It's embarrassing.
Hey, give it back. That's mine.
It's lipstick.
This is not sold in Hong Kong.
You have to buy it in Thailand.
So what can you get in Hong Kong?
The better kind.
Why didn't you buy one there, then?
I wanted something cheap.
You got a problem with that?
Bitch.
Hey, why did you say that?
I want lipstick now that I've seen one.
I want to wear makeup to be feminine.
I'm so repressed.
I want to act gay again!
Oh, shut up, Tien.
Don't act like you don't want this.
You're living in paradise now.
You're surrounded
by handsome, muscular men.
We're thinking of applying to your gang.
Yes.
Don't you get hot and bothered
whenever you see the hair
on their broad chests?
That sounds amazing.
-That's right.
-Hey.
Don't say it like that.
I might not be able to stop myself.
Are you sure you can take them all?
Let me take some off your plate.
Hey, I think Tao is acting weird.
How so?
The other day, he asked me
to practice using a lance with him.
But I didn't do it.
Why? There's nothing odd about that.
Nothing odd?
We don't have a lance in the house.
You're reading too much into things.
Let's go pee.
How could he not ask me to come with him?
Stop right there.
Let the seniors pee first.
-I'm waiting at the bus station.
-I'm waiting at the airport.
-I'm waiting at the intersection.
-I'm waiting at the police station.
It's all done, Ler. We beat them up.
Whose men were they?
They were ours.
So why did they beat us up?
The other day, we got information
that Fei's men were going to pee there,
so our men waited there.
Then, you got here and went to pee there.
So, you three got beat up there.
And you walked back here.
And then you laid here.
-We're going over there.
It hurts here and there.
Tao is a cruel man.
He bullies the people in the village.
They come to me
and complain about it every day.
So you're running a crisis center now?
I didn't mean that. What I meant was,
he's an immoral man,
so why are you sleeping with him?
Wait. Why are you still with him?
Seriously, who are you going to choose?
Me or him?
-Do you want the drumstick?
-Yes, thank you, honey.
You need to stop contacting him
from now on. He's my enemy.
-The chicken is a bit salty.
-Yes, I think so too.
I think I need to tell that to the butler.
If you keep seeing him, I'll disown you!
Ming called from Singapore.
His gang and our gang
never got along, anyway.
She said she's coming back to see you.
Let's just say that
you need to stop seeing him.
-Piow is coming too.
-Like, never ever see him again.
What? Ming and Piow are coming?
Eight years ago...
Don't let Kung come near my daughter.
-Why?
-Your son is bad.
Your daughter is fat.
Just like her mother.
I'll find other women for you.
Eight of them, all right?
The only woman I want is Ming!
If he wasn't Fei's son,
I would let you see him.
-Will you let me see him?
-No!
-You need to break up with him!
-No way!
What does that mean?
What are you going to do?
It's okay. We'll get Song to help.
Kung and Ming are like
my nephew and niece.
I have to ask you two
not to stand between them.
Po. Fei.
What can I say? You asked.
If that's what you want,
then I won't do anything.
Good! It looks like
no one wants to disobey me.
So, making money is now a little easier.
Dad, you have a grandson.
Grandpa!
Piow!
-Grandpa.
-Piow.
Piow.
-Grandpa, I miss you.
-Piow, my beloved grandson.
-Grandpa.
-Piow.
-Dad.
-Kung!
Kung...
Piow.
How is living with Song?
-It was great at first, but last month...
-What?
He took a lot of money to gamble in Macao.
His opponent was Master Kao.
What? Master Kao?
In the end, he lost.
So, Master Kao killed him?
He didn't kill him.
But Song lost all of his money.
He didn't have any food.
So, he died of starvation.
Oh, Song.
Even if you have a child together,
I won't let him come to my house.
Why?
Because he's Fei's son.
Oh, you're a good boy.
You should break up with him.
That's nice, Piow.
Then, come back and live with me.
Good.
We have a deal, right?
Jeez.
Piow, you little piece of shit!
FEI GUILD HALL
Please come in.
If you've run out of money, please leave.
Come back when you have the money.
Please come in.
Please come in. Bet on anything you want.
We'll call the police at 10:00 p.m.
Come and catch me.
-I finished my meal. I'm going to play.
-Piow, don't run around.
He didn't eat his vegetables.
Go play outside, all right?
Yes, Grandpa.
Good.
Piow, what's in the bag?
It's Wong Fei-hung.
What is Wong Fei-hung?
You're not giving me that?
This is funny.
What was that? Synchronized dancing?
Kung, get your child away from me. Go!
Grandpa is scolding you. Do you hear that?
Wong Fei-hung is a snake.
I know!
Ming, Tao has been acting weird lately.
He's not as bad as he used to be.
Pei-pei, you are a grown-up now.
You know the right thing to do.
What do you mean by that?
Go to his house and find
the right moment to have sex with him.
EXTRA-STRONG APHRODISIAC
I'm going to get laid tonight.
Tao.
I've got some soup for you.
Thank you.
I don't have any.
What are you doing here?
Go get me some men!
Get me some men!
Where are all the men? Go get me some men!
Whip me!
Bring out the candles!
Candles!
What is going on? Hey!
What is this?
Don't do this to me!
Thank you, Pei-pei.
If you hadn't been here,
I would have become his wife.
It's nothing.
I think he passed out.
But the drug is still in his system.
So, like I said...
My Tao lost an arm.
My beloved amputee.
Do you miss him?
Don't say that.
You need to keep quiet about this.
I know that.
Hey, come to think of it,
what did you put in the soup?
An aphrodisiac.
An aphrodisiac?
Kung, how is Piow doing in the casino?
Don't worry.
There's only one thing he hasn't done.
What is that?
He hasn't burned the place down yet.
Hey, that's Fei's son.
He must be here to mess up our market.
Hey, step back. Let me handle this.
-Kung.
-What?
-Are you here to mess up our market?
-No.
Hey!
Kung.
What? You've got a problem?
You can hurt him back.
So there's no need to hold grudges.
Are you sure?
I think we can just look past this.
It was a misunderstanding. Believe me.
Let's be friends.
Jer, are you okay?
You keep talking
like you're being nice to me.
Ming, let's go before he wakes up.
The gangsters are here.
Normal people, please make way!
How dare you ask me out for tea?
Stay calm, Shen-po.
-I'll order some good food for you.
-Hey.
-Fei. Shen-po.
-Hi.
Mr. Chang, how are you doing?
I'm doing great.
Bring out the shark fins for Po.
-We're out.
-Give me your ear, then!
Yes, sir! Please wait.
How hungry must he be to eat my ear?
We should gang up
and take over Golden Dragon.
Fine. But Piow stays with me.
He must stay with me!
General Jia is here.
Hi, Po and Fei.
To keep the peace in this town,
can I show some IDs?
Yes, give me yours.
Everything looks good. You can go.
Thank you.
-General.
-Stop talking.
You saw what happened.
Don't tell that to anyone.
Ma Yong-hai is still alive.
I don't feel good about this.
People say he plays with
his own poop when he wakes up.
-What do you mean?
-He's retarded now.
In English, they say "antarctic."
It's "autistic."
Fei.
What are you doing?
Stay still.
Yes, Fei.
What is coming out of my stomach?
Fei, you stabbed me!
You tricked me.
Remember, Po.
Skepticism is what makes
good gang leaders.
Or else you'll get this.
Like this?
Ma Yong-hai?
Does it hurt?
I'm glad you're here.
Please give this to Tao.
That hurts.
No.
Daddy!
He even put a knife in my dad's head.
I don't want to be in this anymore.
Don't worry about it, Tien.
It's just a dream.
But what if it becomes a reality?
I'm sorry.
We must not let that happen.
We should wait here
to see your father, my husband.
He'll come see us.
Why did you bring me here to see him?
It's because you're the one
he loves the most,
and you're the one I love the most.
Yes, you are the one they love the most.
That must be a sign from the gods.
The one they love the most is Piow.
What about him?
Think about it.
Think.
I know what to do now.
Take Piow to the market.
And then what?
Next, Nokroo will take Piow
and fake his kidnapping.
Then, you go back and tell your father.
I'll be a man and bring Piow back.
Then Shen-po and Fei will be grateful
for what I've done.
Our three gangs can finally be united.
How does that sound?
Do as he says
and everything will get better.
This is a waste of my time. If you don't
have anything else to say, leave.
Do as I say. Now you have to leave.
Fortunately, he doesn't understand
what we're saying.
He must think that
I don't understand what he's saying.
I think he understands.
-Tien, I have--
-Try this mung bean soup.
It's very good.
-I want to--
-Does it taste good?
-I--
-I think it's really good.
Open your mouth.
Do you think it's too sweet?
No. It's good.
What were you going to say?
I forgot.
Your plan isn't working.
When will their businesses be mine?
Soon.
I cut off Tao's arm. I shot them.
Who do I have to kill...
"Kill this time."
Yes, who do I have to kill this time?
You don't have to kill anyone.
We must take the thing they love the most.
Oh, Piow. It's nothing.
Oh, candy.
Can I have one bag of these?
Where are they?
-These ones too.
-Why aren't they here?
-Who are those people?
-Farmworkers, maybe.
You've got the wrong person. He's there.
It's that one, not me! There!
-Hey. It's not me!
-Let me go!
You've got the wrong person!
Dad, Piow is missing!
What? He's missing?
Piow is missing?
He really is missing!
-Pei-pei too.
-Pei-pei?
Who took him? When did he go missing?
This morning. Kung called.
Three people in ski masks took him.
It was my fault. Please forgive me.
Forgive you?
You can't even
take care of your own child.
You're so stupid!
Tao must have done this.
Why did you take Pei-pei?
I didn't order you to do that!
We didn't take them.
What do you mean?
If you didn't take them, then who did?
I don't know.
They took them before we got there.
Our lives depend on your mercy now.
You couldn't do what I said
so you ask for mercy?
Form a circle!
-Form a circle, hey!
Knock in a circle!
-Knock in a circle, hey!
He said "knock," Jer.
Good.
Come here.
I found out that he's gay.
He was peeping while I was pooping.
Now I know
why he looked at me in a weird way.
-What about you--
-Kick in a circle!
-No!
There are so many vegetables.
Can you please eat it?
I want chicken drumsticks!
Shit, I didn't know
that he doesn't eat vegetables.
Chicken drumsticks, bacon, steaks, bread,
butter, and jam.
Did we get them all? No vegetables.
You don't eat vegetables?
He just said he doesn't eat them.
-Just like Piow.
-What?
Who's that?
That fat kid who is Po and Fei's grandson.
Are you buying those for him?
Don't talk about that!
People might hear us!
Where did you hide Piow?
I'll count to three.
If you don't tell me, I'll shoot.
One, two, three.
I'll count three more.
Four, five, six.
Dad. Tao didn't do it.
And he said he's going to find him.
You're going too far, Po and Fei.
-How about I shoot you instead?
-Yes.
-We found Pei-pei and Piow.
-And Piow.
How about that?
People in Golden Dragon get things done,
unlike other gangs.
They do nothing
but put guns to people's heads.
We followed them.
-Where are they?
-Yes.
At an abandoned Changzhou rice mill.
General Jia, why are you here?
I'm not the general for nothing.
-What are you waiting for? Let's go in.
-Yes.
Wait.
If we all go in there,
I'm afraid it might endanger the hostages.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Dad! Tao!
-Pei-pei.
-Hey.
Dad! Tao! Help!
Don't come any closer!
Or I might let go of the rope.
Dad! Tao! Help!
Do you want to know what happens
if they fall into the pan?
What are you doing?
Hey, what do you want?
I want what I want. It's up to me.
You don't get a say in it.
-We must do as he says.
-What?
Or they might end up like that duck.
I want 50 percent of your businesses.
Hey, if we go in right now,
even if they burn the ropes,
we might still have time
to save Piow and Pei-pei.
-Are you sure?
-What if things don't go well?
Get them!
No, Dad!
If they want to risk it, let them.
Sure.
Don't!
Help!
Dad!
You...
son of a bitch!
Why are you just standing there?
Come and help us!
How could I?
Even you people got beat up like that.
I wouldn't stand a chance!
Tao, put out the fire!
What is this?
Put out the fire!
Help!
Pei-pei!
Tao!
You got here just in time, Tao.
Take out these four and put out the fire.
I'll take out this one, okay?
"Okay"? You got one and I got four.
Go put out the fire.
-I'm gay!
-I have one arm!
Gay? I can take him down.
You're fast. Are you sure you're human?
Oh, I thought I dodged it.
-Tao!
-Put out the fire!
Tao!
Tien!
Why did you just stand there?
Remember, Tien.
Women like us have
a higher pain tolerance than men.
The feminine power
will unleash its full potential
only when we've reached our limit.
The Lady's Kung Fu has ten moves.
The first one is the Lady Butterfly.
The second one is the Hiding Lady.
The Lady Opening the Gateway.
My butthole!
It's coming out!
My mom taught me. This is the Lady's Feet.
This is the Lady Picking a Carrot.
What are you doing?
I haven't seen anything like it!
This is the Lady Weaving Silk!
That's enough!
That's the Lady's Bite.
This is called the Lady's Butt.
This is called the Lady Monkey.
The last move of the Lady's Kung Fu
is one you must come up with yourself.
You're living in paradise now.
You're surrounded
by handsome, muscular men.
If I were you, I would eat them all up.
Think.
That was the Lady Having a Meal.
I came up with it.
You're under arrest, Mr. Jonas.
General Jia was the one who ordered me
to do all this.
He ordered me to cut off Tao's arm
and fire guns at you.
The rope is breaking!
Do something!
Hurry!
Yes, that's good!
How are you feeling?
Warm.
-How warm?
-Yes.
I pooped my pants.
That must be warm.
How are you feeling, Pei-pei?
Pei-pei!
ETERNAL HARMONY IN MARRIAGE
Are you ready?
Come a little closer.
I'm very happy today.
Why?
Our three gangs will become
one big family.
Why are you here?
What was that?
Why are you in my house?
We are a family now.
Tao is getting married to Pei-pei.
This is a lucky day.
Golden Dragon wants to present
its new leader.
Kun-kun, tell the men to bring out
the gang's new sign.
He forced me to do this.
Nokroo! Jer! Sing!
Nokroo. Jer. Sing.
-Ler!
-Ler.
He's a natural.
He was born to do this.
Let's open it.
GOLDEN DRAGON
Are those balloons?
We're sorry.
But we are not accepting
new members right now.
Didn't you hear?
We don't want new members.
Go!
Wait.
Go home and come back tomorrow.
And change your outfits.
Damn it. This is all my fault.
I made a gay the head of the gang.
Kun-kun, come join us.
No, thank you.
Have fun.
Look at what he did to his dad.
Subtitle translation by Janamon Moonjanta