[exclaiming, grunting]
Skadoosh.
[Po] Lou-ee-ooh!
Loojee?
Luigi?
Looney?
Lunu?
[burbling]
Lou-ee-lai! Lalailoo!
[Po] Lukulululu? Lu?
I know it's an L word. Um…
-Lorelai? [groans]
-[creaking]
[exclaims, grunts]
[weakly] Leela?
Ow.
Lila… What was her name?
[Veruca grunts, chuckles]
[Klaus] Will you stop it, Veruca?
-[Veruca grunts, chuckles]
-[ominous music plays]
[whirring]
Careful with that. Our work's not done.
Just having a bit of fun. [laughs]
-Hm… Quite a river.
-[Veruca sings indistinctly]
[gasps]
Oh, pretty.
[chuckles]
-[gasps] Ah…
-[ominous music plays]
-[growling]
-[grunts]
[growls]
[grunts]
Oh, scary.
Scaly and scary!
-[Veruca cackles]
-[menacing music plays]
You look lost.
Wouldn't be,
if you could point us toward the Lotus?
-[crocodile lizards mutter]
-[crocodile lizard 1] Lotus? What is that?
This is our river, that's our bridge,
and this is our mountain pass.
And nobody crosses it
without paying a fee.
-[crocodile lizards chuckle]
-[giggles]
-[gasps]
-[atmospheric music plays]
How about that pretty glove?
[gasps, laughs]
You want the glove, do you?
-Do you?
-[dramatic music plays]
You've got it.
-[whirring]
-[growling]
[gasping, exclaiming]
[wind blows]
[atmospheric music plays]
[dramatic music plays]
[sighs] That silly bear
probably wandered into a ditch.
Broke her legs. Needs my help.
That's why she should've waited for…
[grunting]
The Dragon Master!
[soft music plays]
I mean, you know,
former Dragon Master. Whatever.
[gasps] Lisa Longport! [laughs]
-[whirring]
-[exclaims]
What?
[Po] Glowy thumb.
Weird.
-[whirring]
-[exclaims]
-[grunting, exclaiming]
-[tense music plays]
Watch the rock!
[grunts, groans]
-[Po coughs]
-Dramatic.
-[whirs]
-[weakly] You forgot me. [groans]
I was gonna show you my secret way
through the Kai Yu River Pass, remember?
I said I was leaving in the morning.
The sun rose three hours ago.
Oh. You know why?
My mornings usually start around 11.
I don't know. I guess the sun
rises earlier in England or something.
That's not how the sun works.
Well, I can still help you.
You're going to help me?
The panda I just watched
trip down an entire mountain?
That wasn't my fault. It's this thumb.
[Po] It's got a mind of its own.
[Po] Uh…
Hm. I dunno,
maybe it's asleep or something.
[scoffs]
You've been hiking for three hours
and I caught up to you in one.
You need me.
Hm?
[sighs] Fine.
-You may show me your shortcut.
-[gasps] For real?! I mean…
[clears throat] For real?
[scoffs]
[Po] Okay, okay, so, like,
if we're gonna partner up--
We're not partners.
You can teach me how to be a knight,
and I can teach you kung fu.
And then we can become kung fu knights!
Knights of kung fu? Kung foots?
Hm. I'm workshopping it. [chuckles]
You? A knight?
It takes years.
You start as a knight's page.
If you're lucky,
you're promoted to squire.
And then, maybe,
if you've managed a heroic deed,
they'll recommend you
to the Queen for knighthood.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So how do I become a page?
[sighs] Impress me.
That's kinda my whole thing.
I'm pretty impress-- [exclaims]
[Po] Tushie-smash!
[groans] Let me just take five. Ooh, yeah!
[peaceful music plays]
-[blowing]
-[grunts]
Nice.
-Uh, looks tasty.
-[crunching]
-I'm not concerned with tasty.
-Try this.
My dad's world-famous red chili crisp.
[sniffs]
Hm?
Oh. Oh, my-- [coughs]
-[gasping]
-[kettle whistles]
Yeah, it's pretty hot-- Whoa!
-You poisoned me!
-What?
No, I didn't! [grunts]
[grunting]
[Po] It's just spicy!
It'll pass, I promise!
[groans]
-[muffled exclaiming]
-[tense music plays]
[gasping, coughing]
[sighs] Pretty good, right?
[groans]
Uh, pretty quick with that sword.
[sighs] Don't put
your grubby paws near it.
This sword was forged with
the Black Steel of the Equinox.
[ethereal music plays]
[Po] Black Steel of the Equinox?!
I don't know what that means
but it sounds awesome.
Black Steel of the Equinox!
That is so fun to say.
Try saying that, go ahead.
Black Steel of the Equinox isn't fun.
It's the same metal
Sir Galaham the Brooding used
to forge his great axe, Bone Kisser.
There was an axe called Bone Kisser?!
That's nothing.
Sir Rabbit of Devon had a bow so strong
it could fire an arrow through
ten of her enemies at once, like butter.
You know what she called it?
Butter Bow?
Skullpiercer.
Wow, cool!
Gross…
So, how do you know all that?
It's all right here,
in the Knight's Code.
[soft music plays]
Okay, cool.
So, what's the deal with these weasels?
[sighs] Klaus and Veruca are mages.
[Blade] Well, a sect of mages,
ones with bad intent.
For hundreds of years,
they've used their dark powers
to manipulate their way into society.
Only recently
did the knights discover their plans
and banish them from England.
But not until after Klaus and Veruca
infiltrated the Queen's inner circle,
and made an attempt on her life,
destroying any who stood in their path.
[menacing music plays]
[Blade] The Queen survived
and Veruca was captured.
But Klaus eventually freed his sister
and fled here, and now I know why.
The gauntlet. With its power, I fear
they will tear through England's defenses,
leaving a river of carnage
right to the palace doors.
You see now why I cannot wait?
[soft music plays]
Why I must stop them
before they leave these shores?
Oh, yeah, right.
I should go.
-So, am I--
-Guiding me on your shortcut
so I refrain from boiling your innards
for my next cup of tea?
Up to you.
You want shortcuts? [laughs]
We'll get you there yesterday.
[Po] Me, a knight's page,
serving you and your very long name.
[sighs] It's Luthera of Landreth,
the Wandering Blade,
Daughter of the Saxon Guard,
Knight of England.
[scoffs] Yeah,
that's like half a day saying that.
If I'm gonna be your page,
can I just call you Wandering Blade?
Or WB? Ooh, that's pretty good.
WB. W, W, W… Debby! Yeah.
No?
Okay, Wandering Blade. Okay, yes.
That's the coolest part anyway.
If you were going to be my page,
you would have to scrub my boots,
carry my gear, make camp.
If necessary, a page
will give their life for their knight.
[chuckles] I can totally do some of that.
I almost die all the time!
[groans] You may start
by carrying my helmet. [grunts]
-[groans]
-[bones crack]
You impressed yet?
No.
Come on.
Oh, I'm so gonna impress you.
Just you watch.
If you really want to be my page,
you need to stop
messing around with silly shortcuts
and get me to this ri--
-[groans, gasps]
-[gasps]
-[dramatic music plays]
-River.
You didn't think it was worth mentioning
that this river is made of lava?
[laughs] I know, right?
It's pretty intense.
Don't worry, there's a bridge right over--
[whooshing]
Okay, the bridge is gone.
But hey, at least
we know for a fact they came this way!
[Po] It's one of them gauntlet craters!
[mystical music plays]
Huh? Huh?
-I'm running out of time.
-We are running out of time.
Come on! If we don't stick together,
how am I supposed to impress--
-[Po gasps] You…
-[hissing, bubbling]
-[gulps]
-[gasps]
-Ow!
[bubbling]
[groans]
You stopped me in Wankun,
as far as I know you took us the long way
so you could go vegetable picking,
and now I'm stuck on
the wrong side of a lava river
because your secret way across
was to take the bridge!
We're stuck on
the wrong side of a lava river.
You kinda gotta get used to saying "we."
[sighs] Go home, Po.
[Blade] There is no "we."
I never said the bridge
was my secret way across!
[takes deep breath]
[whispering] I am the river.
What is that?
What are you do-- What are you doing?
Just trying to summon
some inner peace here,
if you could just give me half a sec.
[inhales deeply]
-[wind blows]
-[soft music plays]
[Po] I am the river.
[Po] I am the rock.
I am…
Po the Page.
-[majestic music plays]
-[gasps]
Po!
[music chimes]
[exhales]
[gasps]
[peaceful music plays]
[sniffs] Huh? [exclaims]
This little piggy went to market,
this little piggy's on fire,
this little piggy got roasted…
[exclaiming]
[blowing, sighs]
So.
Impressed yet?
I, uh…
How did you do that?
Kung fu! I did have a life
before I was your page, you know.
Here. [grunts]
Tie it to that tree trunk.
I saw you walk the tightrope yesterday,
you can totally make this.
Where are you going to tie it?
[creaking, clattering]
Uh, I'll hold it.
Uh, y-yeah, no. Uh…
Oh, come on!
It'll be my first charge as your page.
[rope twangs]
You sure you're strong enough?
You have trust issues.
No, I have "you" issues.
-[rope creaks]
-[soft music plays]
[bubbling]
Whoa!
-[grunts] Alright, got it. Okay, yeah.
-[exclaiming]
Everything okay over there?
Oh, yeah. No sweat.
My arm just, uh, you know, fell asleep.
-[tense music plays]
-[laughs] Kidding. Just a joke.
Po, behind you!
[Po] Oh, I get it.
[chuckles] No, no, you aren't pranking me.
Behind you!
[ominous music plays]
Dragon Master?
[gasps] Chuntao!
Though I suppose
that's not your name anymore.
Whoa!
We all heard about
your little tumble from grace.
[laughing]
Friends of yours?
Uh, not exactly. This is Chuntao.
I kinda put him in jail a few years ago
for hijacking the old Emperor's new wagon.
All to impress a girl. I got this covered.
[exclaims]
Chuntao! How's Dai-Tai?
[sighs]
We broke up. [crying]
Oh, jeez, I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah. She wanted a bigger house!
And it's, like,
"I'm trying my best here, Dai-Tai!"
[Chuntao] And she's, like,
"We live in a literal hole in the wall!"
Po?
-[Blade] Po!
-[growls]
[dramatic music plays]
You know there's a fee
for crossing our river.
But since we have history and all, I'll
give you a friends and family discount.
Aw! See, there's nothing to worry about!
They're giving us--
Whoa. Interesting discount.
-[laughing]
-[menacing music plays]
We'll take the sword! [laughs wildly]
-[tense music plays]
-[rope creaks]
-[grunting]
-[dramatic music plays]
Ow!
[gasping]
Po!
-[Blade] Stop moving!
-[gasps] I'm doing my best over here!
-[menacing music plays]
-[growling]
-[grunting]
-[dramatic music plays]
[grunting]
[growls]
-[grunting]
-Maybe we just give them the sword?
No one touches my sword.
[music intensifies]
-[groans]
-[yells]
-[grunts]
-[echoing]
So cool.
-[thumping]
-[grunting]
[laughs]
[tense music plays]
[groans] It's slipping. Blade!
Blade! I can't hold it.
-[grunting]
-Yes, you can!
[groaning]
[groans] It's too heavy!
You're strong enough!
[groans]
-[suspenseful music plays]
-[grunting]
[strains, yells]
[dramatic music plays]
[strains]
[grunts]
[yelping]
[screaming]
Ow! Ow! Ooh!
[exclaiming, muttering]
[tense music plays]
[groaning]
[growling, chuckling]
[Blade] Do not drop that rope, Po!
-[straining] Ooh, yeah. Come on!
-[snapping]
[exclaims]
[grunts]
-[grunting]
-As your page, that wasn't my fault.
-The rope just broke.
-Will you shut it and run?
[chuckles] You better turn tail and run.
This is the tail end of your story.
Tail pun.
[dramatic music plays]
[grunting]
[gasping]
[dramatic music plays]
-[exclaims]
-[gasps]
-I'll hold them back.
-Yoink!
-[gasps] No!
-[echoing laughter]
Now we're even, Dragon Master.
-[grunts]
-[yells]
-Okay. You just wait there.
I'll get the Black Steel of the Equinox
after I take care of these guys.
[grunting]
[groaning]
It's called Luthera's Shield,
and no one touches it but me.
[grunting] Your sword
is named Luthera's Shield?
But it's a sword!
But it guards me. Like a shield.
-[dramatic music plays]
-What are you doing?
Getting my sword back,
before he gets away with it.
[laughs] Is this what you're after?
Come and get it.
-[laughs]
-[grunts]
[wind rushing]
[exclaims, groans]
Blade! [grunts]
-[suspenseful music plays]
-[grunting]
-[grunts]
-Gotcha.
Blade, come on. Soloing isn't working out.
Let's do this together.
[soft music plays]
I mean, what's the worst that can happen?
We fall into a little lava, maybe we die.
Or maybe we do something heroic!
-As knight and page!
-[sighs]
[dramatic music plays]
[laughing]
[grunts]
-[growling]
-[grunts]
[groans, yelps]
-[growls]
[gasps, groans]
[groans]
[growls, gasps]
[grunting]
[yells]
[crocodile lizard 2] Ow, ow, ow! Hot!
You're running out of
mountains to hide in, Chuntao,
and you're out of lizards.
And when we catch you, we're taking back
the Black Steel of the Equinox!
[Chuntao] This thing is black steel?
Wow. I'm gonna be rich!
And then Dai-Tai
will have to take me back!
[yelps]
Nice try, Dragon Master,
but there's always more lizards.
-[laughing]
-[dramatic music plays]
-[grunting]
-[yelling]
[wind whistles]
[echoing grunt]
[echoing] Po!
[groans] Po!
[wind whistling]
[peaceful music plays]
[music chimes]
[growling]
[exhales] I am the river.
-[grunts]
-[dramatic music plays]
I am the rock.
I am Po,
the former Dragon Master! [laughs]
-[grunting]
-[thrilling music plays]
Hiyah!
-[yelps]
-[grunting]
Whoa, what? Sorry, Jim!
Sorry, Ralph! Sorry, Mom!
Can't you take it easy on me?
I'll give you the friends
and family discount. Skadoosh!
Nice callback!
[stirring music plays]
Whew! Okay.
-So?
-Po.
I'm impressed.
-Aw, yeah!
-[triumphant music plays]
[whirring]
-Po?
-No, it wasn't me. It's the thumb!
It's awake! [gasps]
[exclaiming]
[grunts]
-[mystical music plays]
-[gasping]
[reverberating]
-[wind blows]
-[exclaiming]
-[whirring]
-Whoa. The thumb.
[gasps] The thumb wakes up
when they use the gauntlet.
Seems safe to say.
[soft music plays]
So…
Looks like you kinda do need me.
No.
-But I do need your thumb.
-[dramatic music plays]
[rhythmic music plays]