[exclaiming, grunting]
Skadoosh.
[peaceful music plays]
[groans, snorts]
Ow!
What now, Zhen?
Cramp! Do you think
it's 'cause I'm working too hard?
It's only midday. Now, finish your scroll.
[groans] But I'm so tired!
And I'm done with this one.
Then put it in the library.
[groans]
-[grunting]
-[scoffs]
-[grunts]
-[uplifting music plays]
-[Veruca cackles]
-Contain yourself, dear Veruca.
We got the scroll.
[ominous music plays]
[gasps]
[chuckles] Think how fun it'll be to see
these giant rocks fall like dominos!
-Smashed to little bits, bits, bits!
-[whirring]
-[dramatic music plays]
-[whoops, grunts]
-[whirring]
-Po?
It's the thumb! It's awake! [gasps]
[grunting]
[gasping]
-[dramatic music plays]
-[reverberating explosion]
-[wind blows]
-[gasps]
[dramatic music plays]
[fast-paced music plays]
[panting]
[distant yelling]
[exclaims, yelps]
[groans, gasps]
Leave it! There's no time
to pick up your miserable junk.
Not junk.
-[groans]
-[dramatic music plays]
[pulsing]
-[gasping]
-[hedgehog] The petal! Oh, the petal!
-[cracking, clattering]
-[hedgehog] It's going to fall!
-[Po] That thing's coming down!
-[exclaiming]
[yelling, exclaiming]
-Hold on!
-It's gonna fall! It's gonna fall!
Blade, let's ride!
Whoa!
I gotcha, buddy!
-Ow, ow, ow!
-Thanks, Dragon Master.
Heads up, people! Whoa.
-[screaming]
-[grunting]
-[crashing]
Thanks, Dragon Master!
[crashing]
Don't worry. I got this!
[panting]
Ska…
[grunts, yelps]
[grunts]
[gasping]
[creaking]
Was your plan to punch through the stone?
I mean, uh…
Could have worked.
[hedgehog 2] Yay!
-You did it! Hurrah!
-Our scrolls are saved!
-[soft music plays]
-[chuckles]
I'm Elder Huang.
We monks are the keepers of these scrolls,
which hold all of China's history.
We owe you a debt of gratitude
for saving them.
And us, Dragon Master.
[scoffs]
Ah, thanks, but you know,
the Emperor sort of took away
my Dragon Mastery.
Your devotion and service to China
is well-documented.
[soft music plays]
And we will not soon forget.
Emperors come and go,
but you are our Dragon Master.
[Elder Huang] You're a legend.
Uh, did you hear that? "Legend."
Yes. It's similar to the word "myth."
And who's this? Your apprentice?
[scoffs]
Uh, sorry about that.
She's got a little bit of a throat thing.
I'm actually her apprentice.
Her page. I'm training to be a knight.
[chuckling] My!
The Dragon Master, humble as ever.
Did you see who did this?
See them? We caught them red-handed.
[Blade] Klaus and Veruca.
[Elder Huang] Everything is taken care of.
The Imperial Guard is on their way.
W-W-We just need a minute with them,
if that's cool with you, your Elderness.
Well…
Alright then, Dragon Master.
-[atmospheric music plays]
-[distant chatter]
[Po gasps]
Whoa!
[uplifting music plays]
[whistles]
[grunting]
[creaking]
[whistles] This is gonna be awesome.
[lively music plays]
[chittering]
[uplifting music plays]
[grunts]
Sweet!
[sighs]
[suspenseful music plays]
[grunting]
[yells]
-[suspenseful music plays]
-[grunts]
[grunts]
[chuckles, groans]
[chittering]
[exclaims, yells]
[uplifting music plays]
[grunts]
[screams, grunts]
-[Po groans] That's gonna leave a mark.
-[Blade] Get off me!
-Would you get off me? [groans] Get off!
-[Po mumbles]
-This way.
-[Blade] Get off!
[groaning]
[sighing, grunting]
Head is… [groaning]
This is it.
-Finally, I have them.
-[suspenseful music plays]
Hey. They're in a cage.
We finally caught her in the act.
S-Sorry. "Her"?
Zhen.
Why'd you put a sheet on the crate?
Now my eyes hurt from the light.
[sighs] You've caught the wrong person.
Nonsense! She's been
a quill in our sides for years.
Complaining, lying, setting off fireworks!
But we finally caught her in the act.
I'm sorry, you believe fireworks
caused a crater that size?
Well, c-clearly her sparklers
and poppers were a gateway to…
that!
I told you, it wasn't me!
I didn't do any of those things.
I don't even know
what a firewor-firework is!
Fireworks? Is that how you say it?
Never heard of 'em.
[gasps] Aw, you poor, innocent,
little spiky monk-person!
-[soft music plays]
-We're leaving.
[groans]
You shouldn't let your apprentice
disrespect you like that.
-[snarls]
-Oh, uh, she just drank some bad tea.
Let me talk to her.
Blade, wait.
She's innocent.
Of course she is, but these monks
clearly want to get rid of her,
and no one even saw Klaus and Veruca!
I saw them.
[soft music plays]
Two weasels? Big, glowing glove thing?
What were they doing?
Did you see where they went?
[shushes]
[quietly] Yes. I'll tell you everything.
But first, you gotta bust me outta here.
Like, with a series of appeals
to the high hedgehog court?
Done.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Back the cart up! That's a crime!
Not really. She's innocent.
They don't know that!
These monks are the only people
in China who still trust me,
but not if we break
their prisoner out of jail!
Being a knight means
making difficult choices.
Leaving her in jail means Klaus and Veruca
will destroy another city, and another.
You must learn to choose
the lesser of two evils.
[Blade] So, choose.
Hm…
[soft music plays]
[groans] Fine.
We break you out,
you help us find those weasels.
[suspenseful music plays]
[Po] Blade, wait up! Blade!
-♪ Sneakin', sneakin', sneakin' around ♪
-[crashing]
[grunting]
-[grunting]
-[crashing]
[yelps]
Vault to the cave,
take out the guards, and free Zhen.
I'm getting the cart.
No way. I'm not fighting monks.
I'm trying to earn my title back,
not get on China's Most Wanted list.
Then be clever.
I don't care how you free her,
just free her.
You said you wanted to be my page?
Well, it's time to start acting like one.
[groans]
[suspenseful music plays]
Alright, Po.
You can do this. Nice and quiet.
No one will ever know it was you.
[inhales] I am the giant pole thingy.
I am the giant pole thing.
[creaking]
-[clattering]
-[grunts]
[grunts] Ow, ow, ow!
[grunting] Okay, maybe a running start.
[panting]
[grunting]
[yells]
[panting, grunting]
-[panting]
-[creaking]
[yelps, grunts]
-[groaning]
-[creaking]
-[exclaiming] Whoa!
No, no, no! [grunts]
[exclaiming, groaning]
[suspenseful music plays]
Come on, Po. You got this.
You are the giant pole thingy.
[yelling]
[grunting]
-I'll never get used to this! [screams]
-[uplifting music plays]
[grunts, groans]
This giant pole thingy is, uh,
kinda rough on the old nose.
[groans]
[suspenseful music plays]
[grunting, panting]
Okay. You got this.
You can break someone out of jail
and potentially break the hearts
of the only people who believe in you.
[imitating Blade]
"Remember, it's the lesser of two evils."
[normal voice] I know.
[imitating Blade] "For Queen and country!"
-[sighs]
-[soft music plays]
-[suspenseful music plays]
-Sh!
[door squeaks]
[door creaks]
-[door creaks]
-[exclaims]
-[tense music plays]
-[rattling]
[clattering]
-[banging]
-[rattling]
-[laughs]
-What?
Oh, right, right.
[sing-songy] Stealth mode.
-[rattling]
-[Po] Okay.
[grunts] Just gonna…
-[cracking]
-[Po] Ease it in… [grunts]
-I don't know what the…
-[rattling]
[Po] What to use this for.
Hurry up!
I'm not good at being bad, okay?
I'm doing my best!
[guard] You got me!
Just pick up the cage
and we'll open it later.
Fine.
[grunting] Just gonna…
This is pathetic.
It's heavy!
[Po grunts]
-Is that…
-Yeah.
[grunts] Okay.
[guard] Hold up!
Hey, Dragon Master.
Oh! Hey, guys. I was just, uh…
The thing was, I, uh…
Nice quills.
You, uh… You freeing our prisoner there?
Yeah, yeah, you, uh, you freeing him?
What, whatcha doing there?
Just knock them out and run!
Oh! I'm actually here
to take this prisoner
straight to the Imperial Guard myself.
Oh. We weren't informed of this.
Oh, uh, Elder Huang
didn't wanna tell people.
Wanted it to be a surprise.
A surprise?
Yeah. 'Cause it's her, uh…
birthday.
Oh! I love birthdays.
Wow. You're really stepping in it.
[intriguing music plays]
-[sighs] Where is he?
-[snorting]
[ominous music plays]
-[Blade] The Imperial Guards?
[music intensifies]
So, she asked for no cake.
Huh. Cake is the best part.
But the Emperor, he was all, like,
"Come on, Elder, everyone loves cake."
Yeah. Who doesn't like cake?
So, he sent me ahead
to make sure she didn't eat cake.
Sure, sure. Lotta carbs.
-Yeah. Sugar, too.
-Yeah. S-Sugars are carbs.
-Is that right?
-Yeah. A lot of people don't know that.
So that when he sent the guards
with the cake that he made,
she'd still be hungry.
What, uh, does that
have to do with our prisoner?
Yeah, Po. What?
Wow! I gotta get me one of those.
Uh, one of what?
-[dramatic music plays]
-Does he mean the wall?
Dragon Master?
-The Dragon Master left.
-You thinking what I'm thinking?
-You wanna get some cake?
-Exactly.
-[dramatic music plays]
-[yelling]
[groaning, yelling]
[groans]
[gasping, blowing]
[whimpering]
[Po gasps] Oh no! Imperial Guards!
-[dramatic music plays]
-[grunting]
[grunts] Hey! Whoa! Ow!
[grunting]
[wails]
[grunting, groaning]
-Ow. Ow…
-[groans]
Ow.
Well, well, well. Look who it is.
Seems like the former Dragon Master
has a new job.
He's a delivery boy.
[laughing]
Thanks a lot, panda.
You've made our jobs a lot easier.
[Imperial Guards laugh]
[sighs] I'm sorry.
I did the best that I could.
The monks caught me and-- Blade, no!
Those are the Emperor's men!
[Blade grunts] Hand over the prisoner.
[unsheathes sword]
[dramatic music plays]
[laughing]
You think your little sword's
going to intimidate us?
There's four of us and one of you.
Stop us. I dare you.
[dramatic music plays]
[cackles]
-[yells]
-[grunting]
-[panting]
-[yells]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[gasps]
-[laughs]
-[gasps]
[grunting]
Hey! That's my friend!
[snarls]
-[tense music plays]
-Uh, I don't wanna hurt anyone.
[laughs nervously]
-[grunts]
-Sorry. Sorry.
[grunting]
Sorry. Sorry.
-[grunting]
-Sorry. Sorry.
-[clanging]
-[groans]
-[thudding]
-[grunts]
[triumphant music plays]
You sure you wanna do this?
[chuckles] Not really.
I apologize
for everything I'm about to do.
[grunting]
[groans]
[groaning]
Thanks.
-Lesser evil, right?
-[soft music plays]
Uh, hate to break up this lovefest,
but I'm still in a cage over here.
Get me out of here
before the soldiers wake up.
[whimpers]
[groans]
[atmospheric music plays]
[Zhen] Right here.
We freed you. Now, tell us what you saw.
Deal's a deal.
I saw them steal a scroll.
Which one?
The Tianshang Weapons.
Huh. [grunts]
In a time before the Lotus,
before history,
the world was one great landmass.
[Zhen] Pangaea.
Kind of a dopey name.
Anyway, some of the people
who lived there had a great power.
They could control the elements.
And for a long time, everything was cool.
Until it wasn't.
Because one day, a group of them decided--
Well, I'm not totally sure
what they decided.
But they basically wanted to
rule Pangaea with an iron fist,
and destroy anyone in their way.
But, a team of elemental warriors
banded together to stop them.
They used their own magic
to create four weapons that
could trap those evil guys inside forever.
-[whirring]
-[dramatic music plays]
[Zhen] But when they did,
the elements were thrown off balance,
and the world split apart.
-[Blade] What were these weapons?
-[Zhen] One was a helmet.
There was some sort of glove.
-[Blade] It's a gauntlet.
-[Zhen] Whatever.
And, like, a fire whip, or something.
And one other. I don't remember.
I'm not the expert here.
That's quite literally what you are.
But anyway, there's four of them.
[atmospheric music plays]
[Zhen] They were scattered,
so no one could have this power again.
Then lost to time.
Separately, they are all dangerous.
Together? Oh, boy!
Klaus and Veruca must be after all four.
Wait, wait.
Did you say one of them was a whip?
A whip of flame, a whip of flame…
That sounds so familiar!
She's escaped!
The Dragon Master and Zhen are in cahoots!
-We have to move.
-They'll see us!
Wait. Where's Zhen?
[fireworks whizz]
[Zhen] Woohoo!
This'll keep them occupied!
[gasps] So,
you did do all those other things?
You do know what fireworks are.
Oh, and it feels so right, baby! [laughs]
[fireworks whizz]
[atmospheric music plays]
Po, we need to leave. Now.
[emotional music plays]
[sobbing]
Dragon Master, how could you?
Po.
Yeah, I'm coming.
Four weapons. Four!
I thought I had a chance.
But now we've lost the trail,
and they're just getting started.
If we follow the thumb,
we'll always be one step behind them.
We'll always be too late.
[gasps] Unless we know
where they're heading!
Hm, the Whip of Endless Flame…
[gasps, exclaims]
The whip… Aha, aha!
Look at this. Huh?
Fictional drawings for children.
We prefer the term graphic novel,
and it's based on fact.
Okay, Whip of Endless Flame.
Uh… Here! Here, here, here.
[Po] The Whip of Endless Flame,
like Zhen was talking about!
Too powerful for any one man to use,
so it must be hidden from the world.
[intriguing music plays]
"Master Long-Tooth,
now that I have the Whip of Endless Flame,
I know exactly where to hide it."
Told you this wasn't junk!
Our answer lies on the very next page!
[suspenseful music plays]
-[sighs]
-"To be continued."
To be continued? To be continued?!
I hate when it says--
[rhythmic music plays]