I'm glad
all four of us are finally together.
Daddy, I want to see Lin Bing the panda.
Of course, son.
We will go today.
We will all go together.
I would rather sleep.
Please, can we go?
Please, Nan.
Please.
LADDALAND
-You like it?
-Yes.
Mom, I want to take a look inside.
Wait, let's take a picture first.
Take a picture later.
Pay off the house first.
Do you like it?
Dad did this himself.
How nice, you can see the mountain
from your window.
You don't have a view like this
in Bangkok.
Mom, do you know what Bangkok has?
Grandma, my school, and my friends.
You aren't the only one
who left everything behind.
I told you that I don't want to be here,
yet you still dragged me here.
Why, did you love me all of the sudden?
There was only Nat back then.
You guys were fine.
NAT
Ben 10!
Wow, Gekiranger.
Dad, what is that?
Why is it following you?
Yes.
It follows us everywhere
no matter where we walk.
Do you know what it is?
It's a...
magic eye.
Moron.
It's called an eye sensor.
All the new air-conditioners
have this feature.
It's called a "magic eye."
How else does it know where we are?
If you want to be an idiot, be my guest.
Cut it out.
No fighting at the dinner table.
I'm glad all four of us are finally...
Hi, Grandma.
Oh, I was busy unpacking.
It's okay.
It's a housing project.
If it was run down,
it won't be able to sell.
My own TV?
We're already lucky
to have one for the whole house.
Nan,
don't take a phone call during dinner.
Yes,
my teacher taught me
not to take a phone call during dinner.
It's bad manners.
And has your teacher ever taught you
not to interrupt during a conversation?
Nan, speak nicely to your brother.
What's so funny?
I tried really hard to surprise you.
Okay. Sorry.
I'll open it then.
Put the glasses down first, maybe?
Yes, I forgot.
Do you need my help?
No, just stand over there.
Show off.
-Damn it!
-Oh, my god!
Thee, get the water!
Shit!
Hold on.
Hurry up, Thee.
Instead of christening the house,
you celebrate with a bottle of wine
and almost burned the house down.
It will be fine.
Just get the maid to clean up.
When you went to pick up the kids,
I hired a Burmese maid.
She does a fine job.
Let's save as much as we can, Thee.
You earn 60,000 baht a month.
The mortgage alone is 30,000 baht.
Parn, don't worry.
Don't forget that I take commissions too.
Yoi told me I can expect at least
another 20,000 baht a month.
Or else I wouldn't dare to live here.
Everyone who has joined our business
could say that they are financially set
for the rest of their lives.
EMPIRE
DIETARY SUPPLEMENT
My assistant, Mr. Theera,
is a great example.
He used to work at
an air condition company in Bangkok.
He has a dream like you all.
To own a house one day.
He had worked for 14 years.
Fourteen years!
In the end, that company couldn't make
his dream come true.
But within only three months
since Mr. Theera has joined us.
Would you like to know
what he got last month?
Mr. Theera, why don't you tell everyone
what you got last month?
I put the down payment on a house.
A down payment! Wow!
Let's give him a round of applause!
Excellent.
Mom?
How come Nan has to
take the bus to school?
I gave you the car
to take my children home.
It's not for your husband!
I helped raise Nan for over ten years.
I have never put her
in an unsafe situation.
Mom, your grandchild is also my daughter.
And Nan is already 14.
There are kids younger than Nan
who take the bus.
Stop making excuses for your husband.
I'm not making any excuses.
But you got to be fair to him, too.
You never congratulate him
when he bought the house.
And now I don't have to work anymore.
Why should I give him credit
for doing what he is supposed to do?
Mom, I got to go now.
I need to go buy some groceries.
Go ahead. You got to catch a bus.
Hurry up before it gets
any hotter outside.
Okay.
Hey. Go away.
Go!
You always say that my mom
likes to spoil her kids, so what's this?
There's a zero percent interest promotion.
Don't worry. I can make the payments.
Nat will want one, too.
Whose cat pooped here?
Here you are.
Thee!
What the heck?
Do you have a problem?
I am sorry.
I was trying to hit the cat
that pooped in my yard.
My cat did that?
-Yes.
-Then I'm sorry.
I will take care of it.
Okay.
Nid.
-Nid.
-That's okay. It's not a big deal.
Don't worry.
I'm Somkiat.
I went to work in Bangkok for a month
so I didn't get to say hello.
I am Thee and this is Parn, my wife.
-Hello.
Chowguay took a dump in their yard.
Get a broom and clean it for them.
I am so sorry.
I will take care of it.
Oh, don't worry. I'll take care of it.
Oh, no. I better do it.
Take this and clean it for them too.
Excuse me, I got to go now.
I think Somkiat's family is a bit strange.
Just let them be.
Hey!
About my offer to work at my house...
Hey, you.
Hey.
-I'm serious, Mom. Taew has a crush on me.
-Why do you think so?
Because I am handsome.
Yes, you are the most handsome boy
in the world.
Mom, a police car. Hurry!
Nat, don't run.
Nobody lives here.
The foreigner owns the house
but he barely comes to stay.
He usually comes around the New Year.
When was the last time you saw the maid?
Several days ago.
I noticed that the door
was broken this morning.
So I called the police right away.
Mom, lift me up.
Mom, what are they doing?
Maybe they are filming a movie.
Lieutenant, the back door was pried open.
I will go inside to check.
Affirmative. Be careful.
Lieutenant, the house
has been ransacked...
and stinks.
Oh, shit!
What happened, sergeant?
There is a female body
stuffed inside the fridge.
Her face is completely disfigured.
There was a homicide at house no.8
in Laddaland Village, Muang district,
Chiang Mai province.
The police have found
the body of a Burmese woman
who is believed to be about 20 years old.
The body was beaten
with a thick wooden stick
and her face was severely burned by acid.
The murderer tried to hide
her body inside the refrigerator.
The police suspects that
the murderer must have known the victim.
The motive for this homicide
is an extramarital affair.
Thee.
Someone died in our village today.
It was the Burmese maid
at the foreigner's house on the corner.
How is that possible?
Why?
Nothing.
Has Nan heard about this?
Not yet.
Good, don't tell her yet.
Or else your mom will call
and complain again.
It's bad that this had to happen
in our village.
There are dead people in every village.
We just didn't know about it.
Shit!
LADDALAND
EMPIRE DIETARY SUPPLEMENT
CHIANG MAI MAP
MR. NATTACHAI
MR. NITIWAT
Parn, take her to bed.
Let's go honey.
Let me go!
-Let me go!
-Please calm down.
Makin! Let me go!
She is here! Let me go!
Let me go!
Someone died in our village,
and you didn't think of telling me?
It got to the point that
Chat's husband is selling the house.
They saw Makin walking around their house.
Nobody would want to stay.
I wouldn't even come back to pack
if I were them.
Please pray for her soul.
I almost hired her to work at my house.
I'm lucky that I didn't.
Else, I'd be freaking out now.
Thee, do you remember the girl
that you wanted to hire?
That girl left a long time ago.
Stop listening to
all that nonsense already.
Are the kids asleep?
Nat is. But Nan is not home yet.
She went to her friend's house
to work on a report.
We just moved
and she is already coming home late?
You should lecture her.
What happened?
A girl came out of nowhere
and ran in front of my car.
I almost hit her.
So close.
Ma'am.
Are you okay?
Shit!
Do you want to come live with me?
LADDALAND
Thee, let's go to bed.
Nan called that she's almost done.
Her friend will drop her off.
I will go downstairs to finish up my work.
Nan.
Your move, punk.
Thee!
I don't think he took anything.
I came downstairs just in time.
Yes, correct.
Yes.
Yes. Laddaland Village.
Thank you.
What happened to you?
Who dropped you off?
-My friend.
-A girl or a guy?
It's just a friend.
What's the difference
if it was a girl or a guy?
-How come you're home so late?
-I already told Mom.
I know that!
But what kind of report
took you until 1 a.m.?
The kind that wasn't finished!
I would have come home if it was done.
Don't you think I wasn't sleepy too?
I have to get up for school tomorrow.
-Nan!
-I will go talk to her.
Hey!
Don't point the gun at anyone like that.
It's not loaded.
It's a gun. It's always dangerous.
You better be careful
if you want to use it.
I just wanted it for protection.
A burglar just broke into my house.
Always spending.
Ever think of earning money?
I've tried to find more customers.
You mean your sewing business?
That doesn't earn crap.
All the food you eat.
It comes from money I earn!
Why don't you stop buying
our kid expensive toys then?
Don't you dare lecture me!
Chowguay, wait!
Chowguay, stop!
Stop!
It's good for them to play together.
We don't have to tire ourselves out.
How is your mother-in-law?
She has the same disease.
But now it's getting worse.
The doctor recommended
a complete checkup in Bangkok.
You're not scared
that it's just the two of you?
What can I do?
How about this? When Mr. Somkiat
isn't home and you are free,
you can hang out at my house.
Dad, Chowguay is a spy.
His collar has a camera.
My dad said it is very popular in Bangkok.
-Dad, let take a look at the photos.
-Okay.
Hurry, Dad.
My notebook is upstairs. This way.
Nat, don't run upstairs. You might slip.
Parn, can I ask you something?
Shall we see where the cat went?
Here, Dad.
That's a pool.
-That's Aunt Dang
-It's the pool at our village.
-I can see just the legs
-It spied on us too.
Hey, those are my legs and Golf's.
Look at this photo.
What's the matter, Parn?
Pip, why did you stop?
Because Pai did.
Hey, what are you doing?
Just take me home.
Is this the house where that person died?
Don't you see the yellow tape?
It looks just like in the movies.
Let's check it out.
Are you nuts?
Why the heck do you want to go inside?
Let's check it out.
It will be quite a thrill...
I don't want to get home late.
My dad already yelled at me last time.
Are you that afraid of your dad?
You guys go in. I'm wearing a skirt.
I don't want to climb the fence.
She doesn't want to climb up
because she's wearing a skirt.
Up to you.
-Okay.
-Fine.
Wait.
-I'm feeling cold with no reasons.
-Let me take some photos.
Hey, what's that?
Stop.
I'm just messing with you.
Damn you.
Come on.
You're bad.
Pip.
-Don't go inside.
-We will go in just a few minutes.
PIP
Sorry. This number...
Pip.
Pip!
-Stop messing around. It's not funny!
-Got you there!
What are you doing here?
I thought you said you aren't coming in.
That was fun!
Hey! what are you doing? Open it!
Open it!
Mai.
Pip.
Nan.
Nan, wait!
Nan, I said wait!
I said wait! Didn't you hear me?
Open the door!
-Thee.
-Nan!
-Thee, calm down.
-Open the door. Come out and talk!
What's going on, Mom?
It's nothing. Go back to bed.
What did you do last night?
I saw a ghost last night.
What did you do last night? Answer me!
I'm serious. I went to that haunted house
with my friends last night.
And there's a dark shadow that floated by
and we all screamed.
If you can't come up with a better story,
get out of my face!
It's nothing, son. Eat your food.
Not now, Mom. I have a splitting headache.
My granddaughter saw a ghost
and no one cares.
Mom, Nan was lying.
She went out with her friends
and told us she was working on a report.
Even if she went out,
it doesn't mean she lied about that.
Seriously, do you agree with your husband
that she lied about seeing a ghost?
Are you going to blame everything on Thee?
If he wants to be the head of the family
then he has to take the responsibility.
If you didn't get knocked up,
I would've never let you marry him.
Mom.
And if your dad were still alive...
Mom, stop comparing Thee to Dad, okay?
Dad had passed away for many years now.
And even if Dad was still here,
no matter how much Dad hated Thee,
Dad wouldn't have made Nan
hate her own father!
You're willing to put your kids at risk.
You're so selfish.
Hey, how is your new home?
Everyone is happy, right?
It's fine.
Okay, another thing.
Our salary will come late for this month.
What? Don't act like you're shocked.
Come on.
It is all our fault.
We didn't reach the sales target
that our Bangkok branch expected.
It's just a little problem.
It's not a big deal, right?
And?
This had happened to me before.
It was for three months at that time.
I was so stressed at first.
I thought, how could there be
no salary for three months?
But then, I got paid in a lump sum.
And there's the compensation, too.
Now, when the company says
they will pay late,
I'm actually very happy.
Don't be stressed.
Every cloud has a silver lining.
Don't worry. It's not a big deal.
JUNE 2010 INVOICE
TOTAL OVERDUE BALANCE 31,224 BAHT
TOTAL BALANCE 714.27 BAHT
PREVIOUS BALANCE 1,316.10 BAHT
Let's cancel Nan's
Blackberry calling package.
It's too much for a ninth-grade student
to have a thousand-baht phone bill.
I already told you so, but you insisted.
Is Nan asleep yet? I will go talk to her.
She went to her friend's dorm for a report
and she will be home late.
What?
She still dares to come home late?
I thought I made myself clear last time.
Nan is very stubborn. She resists harder
when you are harder on her.
Your mother makes even the nicest kid
become a spoiled brat.
It's fortunate that
she didn't raise Nat too.
Sorry. I was being too harsh on you.
So which friend
did she spend the night with?
Hey, what did you guys see
the other night?
I didn't see anything myself.
But when I heard Mai scream,
I ran.
What a jerk!
Maybe Mai had fooled us?
I don't think so.
When she screamed,
she looked horrified.
Jerk!
Nan!
This is "working on a report"?
How dare you behave like this?
Like what?
I was just playing with my friend.
Do you know how embarrassing
that was for me?
Embarrassed?
Aren't you embarrassed
to touch a guy like that?
Didn't your grandma teach you that?
She always does. You never did.
Don't think of having kids
if you can't raise them.
I still haven't excused you
for lying to me last time!
And you dare to talk to me like this?
Have you ever listened
when I talked politely?
I already told you I saw a ghost.
Yet you called me a liar
instead of being worried for me.
-That's because you lied!
-No, I didn't!
-Your village is haunted!
-Stop that nonsense already!
It's not nonsense.
Your village is haunted!
The whole village knows the truth!
-You are the--
-Stop talking!
You are the only one in denial!
Your village is haunted! There are ghosts!
Stop it! I said there are no ghosts! None!
-There are!
-No there aren't!
There are! Your village has ghosts!
There are ghosts here!
What are you doing?
-Get out!
-Let me go!
-I said get out of the car!
-What are you doing?
-No! I'm not going!
-Get down!
Let me go!
-Come here.
-Let me go!
-I told you to come here.
Come in!
Let me go, Dad! I don't want to go in!
I said let me go already!
No! I don't want to go in!
Come in!
Let go of me!
-Come in!
-Let go of me!
Let go of me!
-See?
-Let go of me!
-Look, are there any ghosts?
-I won't look!
Let me go!
Let me go already!
Bye, Mom.
Nan.
Nan is going to stay with her friend.
She will be back on the weekend.
Why did you let her go?
My mom will take her back to Bangkok
if I don't let her go.
Do you want that?
Where are you?
I am at the airport now.
I am about to board my plane to Bangkok.
I got called back
to take care of the marketing there.
What about me, Yoi?
Thee.
We are all adults here.
Don't you get what I mean?
Yoi.
Yoi!
You bastard.
It's good that the company is stable now.
We got to this point because of your help.
I was so surprised when I saw you.
I didn't think you know where I live,
Mr. Manop.
It's good that you came here early
or I would have gone out by now.
How come you have never called me?
I know you are very busy.
I was afraid to bother you.
My life is so hectic
because I don't have you nowadays.
I heard that
your new secretary is very good.
But I liked it better
when you were working for me.
I will be very happy
if we can work together again.
Hey!
Thee.
Why are you home early today?
I have a headache.
So I left early.
Thee, I'm going to pick Nat up.
Parn.
Thee.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I just have a headache.
JOBS - EDUCATION AND OCCUPATION
WANTED: URGENT
We already hired someone
for that position.
We posted that ad a while ago.
APPLY NOW
We only accept people
from 20 to 30 years old.
SALES MANAGER, MALE, 25 - 35 OF AGE
I'm sorry.
You're older than we wanted.
KIDCHAROEN LIMITED
Excuse me, I need to mop the floor.
The floor.
URGENT
CONVENIENCE STORE STAFF NEEDED
You already look handsome, sir.
Time for work.
Are you coming
to that village with us tonight?
Laddaland Village?
Damn that creepy place.
You still dare to go?
Right. Only the idiots still live there.
Go right ahead.
I hope you find what you're looking for.
Hey!
Shit!
-Hey!
-Let me go!
Hey, I need help.
Hey, stop!
What's wrong with you?
How could you do that to the customer?
He was shoplifting!
Just call the police!
This is unacceptable.
Leave now. You're fired!
I'm not leaving!
If I go, how the hell will I live?
SAVINGS DEPOSIT PASSBOOK
What's that voice?
Golf, what are you doing?
Nat, come here.
What were you guys playing, Golf?
What if something happened to him?
He hid inside the closet.
I was just joking with him.
Joking?
If you are going to play like this,
then don't play here anymore.
Go home now.
Your son locked my son inside the closet.
What would happen if nobody was home?
Golf.
Did you do that to his son?
Satisfied?
Go inside.
LADDALAND
Parn.
Parn!
-Parn!
-Yes?
Where is Nat?
He went to play outside with Golf.
Nat!
Nat, is that you?
Hello, Parn.
Hello, Thee. Where are you now?
Nat is already home.
Why did you play
inside that foreigner's house?
Answer me.
Why did you play inside that house?
Golf told me to go get Chowguay.
Your son is too much now!
He forced my son to go
inside that foreigner's house.
What are you going to do
if something happened to my son?
Has anything happened?
How dare you say that?
Are you done?
What kind of a father are you?
If you can't teach your own son
then just call him out here.
I will teach him in your place!
I can teach my own son.
You go tell your wife
to mind her own business.
Give me back my money first.
When did I ever borrow your money?
Your wife asked my wife
for 10,000 baht last month.
It's you who can't handle your shit.
If you're damn proud,
take care of your family with your money.
Why do you have to bother others?
Here's your money!
And keep out of our business!
Damn cat!
Excuse me?
I'm ready to pay.
Oh, okay.
Do you want some more sausages?
How much?
Twelve baht.
Keep the change.
Why didn't you tell me?
How would it help if I told you?
Is it any better to keep it to yourself?
I have a job interview
the day after tomorrow.
I just need to borrow the money for now.
I will put it back when I get paid.
I am going back to work.
Mr. Manop has opened a new branch here
in Chiang Mai.
You want to go back to work
or go back to him?
You used to do marketing in Bangkok
for about ten years.
It should be easy for you to expand
the market for us here.
Actually, different people
in different locations
have different natures
that will vary accordingly.
From my experience,
my marketing strategy would be...
I'm sorry.
From my experience,
any time we want to change the consumers
or change the consumers' habits
we should...
I'm sorry.
There must be some emergency at home.
Parn, I'm having a job interview.
Mr. Thee.
Mr. Somkiat shot everyone in the house.
He was probably stressed about work.
His factory went bankrupt
with ten million baht in debt.
It's true. Nid borrowed money
from so many people.
Did she ask you too?
I thought she only asked me.
Me too.
I am reporting a homicide.
One male, two females,
one boy at Laddaland Village.
Poor Golf.
Someone said his skull caved in
where he was shot.
Didn't you hear anything, Mr. Thee?
Mr. Somkiat has been dead
in that house for days.
I don't want to live here anymore.
- Let's move out.
- Where will we move to?
Our home is here.
I'm about to get a new job.
Everything will get better.
It is not about work anymore, Thee.
Didn't you see?
They have been dead for days.
-That means the last few days--
-It was just all in our heads.
Pack up.
Let's go back to Bangkok.
Let's start over.
It's easy to say that, Parn.
But we still have to pay off this house.
If we move now,
I will lose the house
and the installments.
What would I have left?
You have me and the kids.
Weren't we happy back then,
even when we didn't have our own house?
I don't want to go back
so your mom can look down on me.
You care how she feels about you.
But don't you care
how the kids and I feel?
I don't care, Parn?
Who do you think
I'm doing all of this for?
I bought this house for you and our kids.
So we can all be together.
Is this "not caring," Parn?
Let's go back to Bangkok.
If we can't afford a house,
we can rent like before.
And Nan will stay with us.
I will help.
I will go back to work.
Do you want to go back to work that bad?
You keep nagging me about going to Bangkok
because you want to see him, right?
Hey, wait. Listen to me carefully.
How many times do I have to tell you
that Mr. Manop is just my boss.
Just your boss?
Why did he come all the way here
in Chiang Mai?
And so? I wasn't the one who went to him!
Who comes or goes isn't the point.
The point is,
what were you two doing?
I will try to believe that
you are saying all of this
because you are angry.
But if you really think that
I am that kind of person,
we can't live together anymore.
FOR SALE
LADDALAND
Nat!
Nat! Come down right now!
How many times did I tell you
to put your toys away?
I didn't take them out.
So I did then?
Golf did.
Nat.
Don't lie to me.
They all went to Bangkok
and they are not home.
They already came back.
We are playing hide and seek now.
Don't lie to me!
They haven't come back yet!
They did.
Nat, stop lying!
Golf!
-Nat!
-You can come out now!
I don't want to play anymore!
-Nat!
-Please come out!
Golf.
Golf, I don't want to play anymore.
Come out.
Golf, come out already.
I don't want to play anymore.
Golf!
Nat!
Golf, I don't want to play anymore.
Golf, come out now.
-Nat!
-Golf!
My mom is yelling at me!
Golf. I don't want to play anymore.
Come out.
Golf!
Enough. Stop lying to me!
I'm not lying.
Nat. Don't lie to me!
I didn't lie.
I told you to stop!
I'm not lying.
So what were you doing just now?
I'm not lying!
You said Golf is here. Where is he?
I guess he already went home.
That's not true. Nat, don't lie to me.
Stop lying to me!
I'm not lying.
Why are you a bad child?
Didn't I already tell you?
Why? Stop it!
Stop crying now!
-Parn!
-Stop!
-Stop crying!
-Parn!
-Stop!
Why are you hitting him?
Are you out of your mind?
What's wrong with you?
Goodness, am I dreaming?
I'm honored that
you are actually calling me first.
Mom...
It's okay.
Even if I hate your husband's guts,
you are still my daughter.
And I love my grandkids.
If you can't stand staying there anymore,
feel free to move back here.
I can tolerate looking at your husband
once or twice a week.
It's better than seeing you
and my grandkids haunted by ghosts.
Do you want me to talk to him?
That's okay, Mom.
I will talk to him tomorrow.
Nan,
pack up. We're going back to Bangkok.
Excuse me.
Is anyone home?
I'm sorry.
EMERGENCY ROOM
Please calm down.
Please stay calm.
There's nothing there.
Nat, please stay here.
Parn.
Go away. Leave me alone.
Do you love that house so much?
Do you love it that much?
How about your kid? Look!
If you love that place that much,
then just go back and live with it.
Nan is so damn unlucky
to have a dad like you!
Go to hell!
-Parn
-Go!
Dad,
can you sleep with me tonight?
Okay, son.
Nat.
Do you like this house?
Yes, but I like our old house more.
Nat.
Nat!
Where are you?
Parn,
Did you come to pick Nat up?
Is he with you, Parn?
Nat!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Golf.
Is Nat here?
Where is he?
Thee!
Nat!
Nat.
Nat! Are you in here, son?
Mr. Somkiat, where is my son?
Asshole! Where is my son?
Nat!
Nat, wake up!
Nat, Wake up! I am here!
Nat!
Nat, wake up! I'm here.
Thee!
NA
Nan, did you know?
Up until my final year of university,
I had so many plans.
But when...
I knew I have you in my belly,
all my plans fell apart.
I kept thinking,
how can I be a mother at that age?
How can I raise a child?
Then I made a decision
to tell your dad...
that I wanted an abortion.
I thought we would break up.
But on the next day,
he went to see your grandma.
He told her
that he will propose to me.
Grandma yelled at him like crazy.
But your dad didn't say a word.
He just said...
"It's my family,
I can take care of them.
It's my family,
I will look after them."
Nan, he really loved you, you know.