This is me, my name is Sun
and I have a special power.
I can hear other people's thoughts.
But should it be called special?
Well, if I hear
a lot of other people's thoughts,
I will be stressed
and get headache like…
my head will explode into pieces.
So I don't want to be close to anyone.
And that made people around me,
including my fan club,
nickname me…
the Arrogant.
ONE DAY BEFORE
Hey, come on!
Or our page’s followers would go down
from 100K to two.
Nah, at least three.
You, me and Keuan.
Sun, get it together, man.
How many years have we worked on
"Everyday with Sun" page
before we got this far?
You said you don’t want a full-time job,
don’t want to meet lots of people
because you can hear
other people’s thoughts
so you asked me to create this page
on YouTube and Facebook.
Now that you have
lots of fan club followers,
you're practically running away. Why?
I don’t want to hear the voice
of their thoughts,
it causes headache. I don’t like it.
So? You will keep running away?
You want to be the Arrogant?
You know, your fans
are becoming anti-fans,
the subscriber count
could have been negative by now.
Can I ask you something,
between subscribers, views and me,
which one is more valuable for you?
Views!
Because it is money,
if there are no views
I will quit and find another job.
Why are you grumbling about everything?
Now I am here with you
creating content to get views.
You're here, but you're not really here.
I can hear what you think.
I know. You don't want me
to grumble, right?
Then hear it from my brain instead.
Enough! Stop thinking.
You're giving me a headache!
Then you better think straight.
Love to listen to this?
So just listen to it,
music or anything you want!
Will you get in?
Let's go.
Stop, stop, please.
Wow, thank you for stopping the car.
My car broke down.
Can you give me a ride to the village?
This is Sun! That arrogant YouTuber.
He actually looks cute.
Too bad he is not a nice guy.
Arrogant, so arrogant, still arrogant.
I smile to you this much,
shouldn't you smile back to me?
And his friend? He seems so bad as well.
Or do you have some gasoline?
Should I have it?
How are they going to get there?
There are many cars around here,
they will find one.
Keuan!
Sun! Pete! How did you get here?
We drove.
Brownie.
What’s wrong with you?
Ouch! Are you crazy? Get out of the way.
I'm sorry. Is it firm?
What is firm?
Disgusting!
Why, what’s the difference
between me and Sun?
Everything. Move!
Sun, my name is Brownie
I am a fan of yours.
Hello.
Miss you.
Miss you, too.
Haven’t seen you for so long. How are you?
It's been so long.
I am good.
Good, good.
I will take you around.
Why didn’t you tell me you would come?
Hey!
Tubtab.
How did you get here?
Cracked eggs.
You broke the eggs as soon as you came.
Did it get all over you?
Take them. Ew!
Ew! Nasty.
I told you, they would get here.
She is my master degree’s junior.
She is writing a thesis
about community ways
so she asks me to help with information.
Never knew that she is your FC.
It’s good to have other people around,
so he can get used to it.
How about you?
Do you have any content ideas to suggest?
Like, going to the dam
or walking around the village?
The dam is not a problem,
what you need to concern is… him.
To make him look more friendly,
approachable,
not an arrogant YouTuber like this
is a very hard work.
Very hard!
Yes, but I have to do this.
If I don’t do this,
our page will be closed,
then we gotta separate on our own ways.
You are really good at threatening.
Okay, okay.
I will do anything you want.
Except two things.
Didn’t you just say anything?
Just two things.
Okay. All right.
First, Keuan!
You have to be MC with me.
Second,
I must not be in a group
of more than five people.
Deal! Let's do it.
Keuan, take your friends to grab a bite.
What’s on the menu, Dad?
Whatever you want.
Just don't grab each other.
Your dad said
"Just don't grab each other."
How did your dad know I want to grab him?
How did your dad know
I want to grab you too?
What! Don’t say that you want to grab me?
Don't tell me you can read my mind.
Nah, I am not like you,
I can control myself.
Hello, boys.
What are you guys doing here?
Tubtab!
Have you cleaned yourself up?
Why? If I haven’t,
will three of you help me out? Wow…
So what are you doing in Bangkok?
I have never seen you come home at all.
I don’t want to,
I will tell you my job position
over there.
Listen carefully.
My title is the manager of a rising writer
whose pen name is Sixth Sense Writer.
Her work doesn't
make you see ghost spirits,
but it makes you, while reading,
enchanted and obsessed.
Are you a manager?
Me, too.
I am the manager of a famous YouTuber.
-Every video we made was a hit…
-Really?
Yeah. Hit the floor.
You better not say it.
Oh, you heard what I said
with the headphones on?
Everyone said that the MC is so arrogant.
Is it true?
Why, any problem?
No, nothing.
I just want to share that people like us
need lots of support from our fans.
If you act arrogant like this,
it is not surprising that
your work would fail.
Whether it's a hit or a miss,
arrogant or friendly,
it’s my business, not yours.
Today, Mae Rawan villagers.
We are going to learn about
brown rice milling, with support
from the EGAT at the Bhumibol Dam.
Sun, go for it.
I know you don’t like
to be bothered while filming,
so I will cheer you up over there.
Good that you know!
So please do your thesis over there
and be out of the way.
Bad mouth.
If you are not Sun’s friend,
you will see me.
Good. I love seeing you.
Funny jokes. Let's start.
What?
People here are more than
what we agreed.
Just ignore them, okay?
All right?
Sun,
five, four, three, two, action.
Hello, now we are here
in Mae Rawan community,
one of the communities
around the Bhumibol Dam.
I've heard that the rice here is superb.
EGAT bought rice from the villagers
to use in the restaurant of Bhumibol Dam
and some are sold to tourists as well.
So, it's a sustainable income
for the community, right?
Yes, it is.
So, let’s see the demonstration of
how to use rice milling machine.
Let's go see it.
Next.
Excuse me! May my friend try it?
Of course! Come on.
No. No way.
Do it. Just once. You can do it, dude.
Please give him a hand.
Hey! Sun!
Does he have panic disorder?
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Do not bother me.
Hey!
I'm worrying about you
that’s why I’ve asked.
Why would you care?
Are we friends?
Wait!
What?
Do you have an empty head?
Don't you have any thoughts?
Hey!
What a bad mouth.
That's too harsh, don't you think?
I want to tell you something.
You are such a faker.
You're using these people
to get more views,
acting like you're a laid-back person.
But I know it is hard,
because you are not.
You don't have the right to judge me?
You don't have the right
to call someone empty-headed, either.
Not someone,
just you!
What are you doing?
Why can't I hear her thoughts?
Teenagers in your village
don't go to sleep?
Doesn't sound like people in my village.
Hey! Can I take your bike?
Now?
What kind of mood he is in?
Bro! Do you have a lighter?
Nope.
You look unfamiliar. Are you local here?
This area? No.
Good.
Why?
Let’s go.
Keuan,
I have posted a short video that we
filmed on the rice milling demonstration.
Yeah?
How was it? The views spiked up?
Spiked down!
I think Sun shouldn’t launch a short video
because there are still
lots of bad comments.
I think you should post something
to make people curious what you are up to.
And the schedule of video release dates.
You know it all.
Why don’t you make your own channel?
I don’t know it all.
Only because I am Sun’s fan
and follow his page.
You seem to know everything about Sun.
How about your thesis?
I am working on it.
Don’t you need me to review it?
Actually, you should change
your thesis subject
from local wisdom to fan club wisdom.
Pete.
Don't be so harsh!
Are you in my fan club?
How can you know
what I am doing or not doing?
So confident!
Anyway, I can be in your fan club
if you want me to.
Jerk!
Sun, are you all right?
I have something to tell you.
I don’t feel hungry anymore.
I’ll leave.
What is it?
Well…
At home, we usually put
dried bamboo shoot in Kai Palo,
make it more delicious.
Hmmm! So delicious.
This fish is yummy too.
Easy girl. Or you are going to choke.
Your mother is a really good cook.
Look. Kai Palo with dried bamboo shoot,
stir-fried mushrooms
with glass noodles in oyster sauce,
and this fried fish is so fresh.
Of course!
Because my house is near the dam.
Where there's water, there's forest.
Where there's forest, there's food.
There's food, we're full.
We're full, we sell the food.
Then we get money to pay for men. Wow.
Well, life is so good.
This is why they say men are life.
Water is life!
Ah, you knew it.
But your life is a novel.
How's it going? Got the plot yet?
Not yet.
Brownie! Where are you going?
I am finding a place to write my thesis.
What are you guys doing?
Exercising maybe?
Don’t you see we are eating?
I am getting hungry now.
Honestly, I don’t like her.
Come on!
We might get something new from her.
Ask her to eat with us.
Brownie, let’s eat together.
Chubby, give me a seat.
Go get the rice.
Who asked you to join? Bored!
Give it to me!
Don’t you follow your favorite one today?
Sun is busy today.
What’s so busy?
What gossip girls.
You see,
I don’t know. They didn’t tell me,
but they acted so strange.
I think it must be a very important topic.
The more important it is,
the more I want to know.
I think you are good at writing
because you are so…
curious about other people's lives.
I will take that as a compliment.
Yes, it is.
But I really want to know
what those three are up to.
Sun, are you sure they are thieves?
I'm sure.
Never, idiot,
wait and see thieves
will rob the whole village tomorrow.
Let’s go.
Hey!
Let’s do it 11 pm tomorrow
everyone should be in bed.
I really heard that.
Wait, bro.
What's happening?
Can you please reveal your face?
Why!
Reveal your face, please!
Sun!
Calm down.
Hey! Sun!
I know you. You are the net idol.
And people call you the Arrogant guy!
Now I know not just arrogant
but also bad manners!
Have you unfollowed his page yet?
Sorry.
Don’t worry, friend!
They are tired of working
in hot weather all day long.
It’s okay.
Come on.
Let me give you a hug.
It’s okay, dude, calm down.
What in the world…
It’s all right.
What are those three going to do?
Hmm. Village headman,
I mean Keuan’s father.
Maybe he wants them to check something.
Really?
There is only one thing
coming in my mind now.
Are you in a hurry to hell…
to find cows or buffaloes or what?
Don’t curse at them!
How come! What if something happens here?
Isn’t it frightening?
What’s up?
Do you have number?
Number? I feel numb-er
when I don’t have enough sleep.
Not funny!
Yes, but I won’t give you.
You think you are beautiful
and can be arrogant?
And you have problem with that?
They should have come when I was alone.
Pete.
Where is Sun?
You’re breathing in and out Sun?
What do you like about him?
Don’t you think he is arrogant?
Nope, I like everything he is.
Why?
Because he is a good man.
How?
He is good in every way.
I am shy now.
How long have you followed him?
Well…
From the beginning.
It’s a very long time.
So, do you have any idea of
how we could get more followers
on the page?
Yeah, I think there's a way.
But I need something in exchange.
What is it?
You need to help me be closer to Sun.
Okay? Otherwise, I won’t help you.
Fine. Deal.
You promise?
Yeah.
-Okay?
-Okay, yeah. Okay.
Good fan club.
Not only his fan club,
later I will become his girlfriend.
Well, I am going to work now.
Hey!
What?
Why?
How dare you!
There they come to help us…
Fucking slow!
Wait! Stop! Don’t kill them.
I hit the target.
Good job.
They are the ones
I talked about yesterday.
You sure?
Are you going to rob the village?
Yeah, well…
it was just a brief idea,
not a serious one.
It’s wrong even thinking about it.
And you two make loud noise revving up
during the night, right?
I will inform the police.
Please don’t!
We're sorry.
We will not do it anymore.
Please don’t inform the police.
Please!
Where are you going?
Thank you for helping us.
Don’t ride if you’re not good at it.
If you'll complain, then don't help me.
Stand up on your own then.
Are you okay?
I am okay.
Thank you, anyway.
Sun!
What happened?
I fell off the bike.
Really? Or you meant to fall.
Come on, Sun! Let me help.
Everything is okay?
You can go,
I’ll help Anna.
Hey, Sun! Wait for me.
Bye.
Do you like Sun?
No.
That’s good. Let’s go.
I’ll help you. Come!
Interesting.
I got it.
What’ve you got?
New story plot, isn’t it?
Tell me, tell me now.
Uh! You always think
about new story plots.
How’s it?
I won’t tell you for now.
No! You can't keep it.
Let me know so I can help you to prove
and see whether it’s good or not.
If not, then I won’t let it pass.
Otherwise, you will lose your reputation.
I'll hit your mouth now!
Did you forget already?
I am Anna, your richness bringer.
Exactly, you are.
I have to hit my mouth
because you are my money spinner.
Hey! Did you just give me
a compliment or not?
Yes, it’s a compliment.
Wait. What’s the story about?
I won’t tell you.
Let me see.
I haven't even started.
Tell me some! How does it feel?
Morning, guys.
You two woke up so early.
Why are you coming here?
I am finding the place to write a story.
Where is Sun?
He is coming here soon!
Why?
Can't we ask about him?
No, you can't.
You are a dog or what? So fierce!
Where are you guys going to film today?
Can we join you?
No!
-Who…
-Why?
-Who?
Who’s asking you?
Ugh! Very ancient joke.
Ugh, yeah! I have to say it!
Couldn’t think anything at the moment.
Well, Kit, while we are recording,
I will ask you questions
and you can answer truly.
Just answer as what I’ll ask.
Take it easy and no worries.
Not excited at all,
I'm about to pee myself!
Don’t be excited!
You can go to the toilet now, if you want.
We still have time.
Thank you.
All right.
Sun! Set your hair.
Hey!
Don’t scream.
I am cheering Sun up. Why?
Everyone!
During the record,
please do not make a noise.
Fine.
Listen! Don’t make any noise.
Yeah, I heard. I just acknowledged.
Sun! Take the headphone off
and zip your pants.
Stop screaming!
Not yet…
No one’s screaming!
He's losing his mind.
Okay, let’s get started! Ready?
Five, four, three, two, action!
Hello! Now we are at the Bhumibol Dam,
with me Sun, Keuan and our guest
I am Kit.
Kit.
Kit is one of EGAT's staff.
Today, he will provide useful knowledge
and present this beautiful place.
Kit,
what do we call where we are standing now?
We are standing on
the crest of the Bhumibol Dam
located in Sam Ngao District, Tak.
Gotta fart to you!
The headspring of our Bhumibol Dam
has is from Chiangmai.
Why you keep looking at me!
See! Wanna fight?
Sure, Wanna fight? Come!
Stop it!
If you wanna argue, just leave here.
Let’s continue.
Come here you two.
Ouch! You're hurting me.
Come here.
You two, stay here.
So you don’t disturb Sun.
Disturb him?
I didn’t make any noise, nothing at all!
I am so confused.
Because you are a giant!
You disturb Sun’s eyes. Got it?
Are you bullying me?
No, I just stated the truth. Look at you.
Look at yourself!
Thank you for correcting me!
But yeah, you're huge. It’s disturbing.
I am not that big!
Enough! Stop it!
Your sound will be in.
Shhhhh! Stop! Stop!
She doesn’t stop.
-You started it!
You!
Well,
if you two want to come,
just make yourself useful.
Sure! What can we do?
Chicky, chicky!
Here, I got it! So fresh.
I think it’s enough.
We don’t eat that much.
Want some more?
-We call it a surveyor's telescope
-A surveyor's telescope.
It’s used to measure
subsidence level of the dam,
-to ensure its security.
-I see.
What you see over there is a staff gauge.
We used this camera
to read the subsidence scale.
I see.
And do you have to do this
every month or…
Yes, we do it every month.
Ah! Every month.
Yes, we keep the record every month.
If this camera is lost,
will your salary be deducted?
Definitely!
All right. Great.
Okay. Now we're finishing it up.
All right.
So, for today, our trip
at the Bhumibol Dam ends here!
Please follow, give likes,
and share our page.
And we will see you
on the next trip, Everyday with Sun.
Cut! Okay.
Pete, give them some money.
Okay.
No, it’s okay.
-10K!
-It’s okay, really.
-100K then!
-Deal!
I am already okay since 10K.
Just kidding, I don’t need it.
Thank you very much.
Let’s go.
Hey, Sun!
I think Anna is curious about you.
What is she curious about?
You go and read her thought.
I also want to know.
Don’t you have something in mind?
I can’t.
Can’t? What do you mean?
I can't hear what she is thinking.
Huh?
Really?
Ouch!
Let’s go! That meddler’s here again.
Hey, wait!
Why are you following me?
I'm not. My house is just this way.
Tell me, what do you want to know?
Can I really ask?
I will try to answer.
All right.
I want to ask
if I can know you more or not.
No.
So mean!
I just want to know
how YouTubers do their work.
If you want to know,
you just search it on Google.
Why do I have to ask Google
when I can ask you? What's the big deal?
Then, can I be your friend?
I don’t want to be your friend.
Arrogant!
You know, everyone wants
to know and be close with me.
Do you?
Hey!
I won’t give up!
Wait for me.
Hey, Sun!
Why couldn’t you hear Anna’s thoughts?
I don’t know, either!
Maybe she doesn’t have a brain.
No way.
Why?
You like her?
-I can help you.
-It’s okay.
That time with Nun was enough.
You helped me to read her mind
but when you were not around,
I just didn't know what was on her mind.
Yes, that’s why.
You need to learn
to love by yourself, dude!
Where are you guys going? Can I come with?
Did you hear something?
I just want to know
how travelling YouTubers work!
Maybe I can try this job.
Why don’t you answer me?
So annoying.
Why so arrogant! What’s up with him?
Hey, Sun!
Where is he going?
Are you okay?
Yes, I am. Just a bit hurt.
I am okay, really.
Let me help you.
Thank you so much. I can go by myself.
I’ll ride you home.
No thanks, it’s okay. Thank you again.
Thank you. Thanks a lot.
This young man is so handsome and kind.
You know sign language?
No.
If you don’t know,
then how could you know what she said?
Don’t be quiet!
Explain to me now.
You know sign language, don’t you?
Just a little bit.
See! You lied to me.
You've just said you didn't know.
You slipped up, dude.
You've just said you didn’t know.
Well, I know here and there.
What on earth you want from me?
Why did you lie to me then?
Up to you!
I don’t need to explain it.
If there is nothing behind that,
so just tell me.
He must be hiding something.
Coffee is ready.
Okay.
Here it is.
Specially served.
This is the coffee planted
over all the dams in our country,
and EGAT provided knowledge
and developed this coffee’s recipes.
Wow,
you seem very knowledgeable.
I’ve asked them just now.
-Tastes good?
-It’s great!
It’s great.
Hey, Tubtab.
I need your help.
About what?
Well…
I want Sun’s information.
I’ve already asked him,
but he didn’t give me any.
Why do you want to know about him?
It’s for my story.
What?
You want to write about him?
Yeah.
I finished writing its summary.
Really? Let me see.
I think this guy has a secret.
I got to find out.
I think we should let Sun
have dinner for now.
Just let him work.
Don’t bother him.
It’s your duty, isn’t it?
I’ve done it all day.
Let me eat for now. Let him do it.
He won’t have time to eat then.
Let me do it.
Eat some!
I'll feed you.
Hey!
Don’t tell me you guys are on a date.
Since you can see us through, Dad,
I guess we should come out then.
No way!
How come?
Stop messing with him.
He would think it’s real.
It’s not like you think, Dad.
Don’t misunderstand.
We’ve been close
since we studied in university
and because Sun didn’t let anyone in.
Do you want some more, dear?
I was so shocked.
So crazy, so cute.
How is it?
Pete!
Have you done it with EP1 video?
Why?
You want to see?
I want to see so bad.
Here!
If you want to see it,
come and wash the dishes for me.
So I can finish up the video.
Oh, yeah! You need time to do that.
Yeah, right now!
-Okay.
-All right, come on.
Okay, okay.
Pete!
Do you want me to upload the video
and set the timer?
Upload?
You finished it, didn’t you?
Yeah.
You fooled me?
He fooled you.
Yeah, I got fooled to wash these dishes.
My hands got all dirty.
Pete!
Wait and see,
they'll end up being a couple.
Please, God!
Let our first clip be on point!
Give us 100 million, billion views
Ten thousand views are enough.
God blesses me, please.
As long as we’ve done good on content,
we don’t need any spiritual help.
We do need help in all way, dude!
It’s a bet. If we don’t get high views,
I will just sell toast
in front of the school then.
Tomorrow,
at 9:09 a.m.,
don’t forget to watch
a released video on trip by Sun.
And don’t forget to click like,
share and subscribe, guys.
Here we go.
Hey, Sun!
They're your supporters.
Looking forward to see you, Sun.
Arrogant!
Let’s change the MC!
Jerk!
This arrogant guy, nobody want to see him.
They are just being mean.
Just don’t care!
They're brave only on social.
We can sue these guys,
and we'd probably get a lot of money,
even more than our work income.
Meet me! I'll take screenshots.
Let them say what they want.
I don’t care.
The only thing I care is
that you're with me.
Yes, I will marry you.
What’s up with you?
You just impressed me.
Don’t you see? I'm irritated.
Come on.
Feel better now?
It's good to laugh a bit.
Don’t think too much.
I'll go to sleep now.
Tomorrow is another day.
All right,
I won’t think too much.
Excellent, young man.
How about his hearing people's thoughts?
Nothing’s changed much.
Oh! There is one thing.
He couldn’t hear Anna’s thoughts.
What?
Really?
-Yeah!
-What?
He told me. Seems this is the first time.
Ah, I see!
That’s why Anna can follow him,
without him being upset.
He's not upset?
He gets even angrier.
He tells her to go away all the time.
But Anna doesn’t seem to care.
She still keeps following him.
Perhaps, Anna has fallen for him?
Maybe, if he’s as handsome as me.
What are you watching, girl?
Today is an auspicious day.
Sun will release his first video.
Don’t bother me, otherwise I'll hit you.
All right. I got you now.
This arrogant Sun…
Why do you really like him?
Top FC like me,
Not only do I like him
but I'm crazy about him.
Very excellent idea,
give me a hand.
It’s coming soon!
If the views are not high,
I think Sun would feel
sad and stop doing his video.
Let’s cheer him together.
Also my duty?
Yeah! Let’s help.
Okay, okay.
Give a heart.
Press here, right?
Yup, Dad.
Appreciate you all
for opening this released video.
Everyone, are you ready?
Five, four, three, two, one, zero.
Dad, you’ve pressed the wrong button.
Here it comes.
You almost gave me a heart attack.
Let’s see his video.
He's so handsome.
But there aren’t many viewers.
Hey, look!
There are seven of them.
Still not stopping.
Why are the views not climbing?
Calm down.
It’s still early.
Who would wake up this early to watch?
Why don’t we upload in the evening?
This is the auspicious time, dude.
Auspicious,
but no one wakes up to watch.
The views get so high now, it’s unstopped.
Look!
Thank you, Dad.
ONE DAY WITH SUN
There are so many viewers.
I gotta give him a compliment.
Sun, I am Brownie.
Hey! What’s that?
Why do they give such mean comments?
-What happened?
-This!
What did they say?
Such a faker!
Arrogant!
I guess you're afraid to get low views.
So you're acting dramatic.
You never even smiled before.
Good acting.
Fake.
Calm down!
Don’t be too crazy on this.
Are you stopping me?
No.
I just want to remind you
to know what you're doing.
Fight back. Get even!
Exactly.
Good! Do it!
Do it!
Hey, guys!
Are you sure? Isn’t it too harsh?
You're escalating it.
But…
Will you let them bully Sun like that?
No worry. Leave her.
Her spirit’s already come.
We will get in trouble on it.
Don’t you think that dude
will get caught up in it?
Don’t call him dude.
Don’t you think Sun
will get caught up in it?
A-ha!
You care about him, don’t you? Right?
What?
You're acting that way, girl.
You like him, don’t you?
What? Who likes Sun?
What? Who?
No one!
Hey girls, you are arguing now.
Over there, it’s there.
Enough.
Sure?
Let me see it.
I DARE YOU TO COME HERE,
FOUL MOUTH.
You really want to do that?
Already done it.
-You can delete it.
-No.
I would like to give
big thanks to everyone
for our success on this video clip.
Cheers!
Let’s do this. Today is a good day.
You got 100K views.
I will play the guitar for you guys.
Let’s do it!
Can you also sing?
Not only can I sing a song,
I can cry a song!
Don't you cry, dear.
Cheap little joke,
don’t put it in your story.
Sun’s so handsome!
Come on, ready?
Let’s clap your hands.
Damn it!
Aww, who’re you talking to?
A guy? Will he come here?
Not like that.
You remember that anti-fan who…
I defied him to come here?
Anti-fan?
He is here.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I already warned you not to do that.
You didn’t listen to me.
What should I do now?
Sun will be angry at me for sure.
If it's gonna be big trouble
then why did you defy him?
Because he attacked my Sun.
I have no choice!
And how? Who is he?
He used to be Sun’s number one fan.
Now that he is an anti-fan,
he is still his number one anti-fan.
I see.
These number one fans
are people who love hard, hate hard.
Exactly.
What should we do now?
Should we tell Sun?
No, we can't!
If we tell him, he will be upset
and it's going to get worse
and all messed up.
Calm down.
I think this guy just only bullies
on the comment. That's it.
No way!
If they confront with each other,
everything will get crashed down.
OMG!
What should we do?
Hey, Anna! Where are you going? Toilet?
But she grabbed everything with her.
Maybe to work in the toilet.
It’s inspirational in there.
What do you want from me?
Nothing.
I have something to tell you.
What?
Well…
Someone's coming to see you.
Is that it?
Who?
Hello, Sun.
Why are you here?
I am here to keep an eye on you.
Keep an eye on me?
You should go see a psychiatrist.
Hey! That’s rude!
Not your business!
You'll treat me the way you did
two years ago?
Keep it.
I don’t need such a stupid thing.
Isn’t it your favorite?
Sun!
Let’s make a selfie then.
It's too much! Aren’t you sick of it?
Because I am.
Are you stressed out today?
You are not like Sun I know.
I am stressed out with you!
Just get away from me.
I don’t wanna see you!
Just go in class.
I will let everyone know
who you really are!
Just do what you want.
I will record you
when you lose your temper
so other people will know
how fake you are.
Get what you want,
and then just leave me alone!
Absolutely!
I won’t touch
such a dirty person like you!
Hey! That’s rude, man!
Hey, wait.
You better not follow him.
Who are you?
His fan?
And these are all vegetables…
Fake man!
Come on,
don’t make that faked smile.
Everyone knows.
I will let people know.
You'll be out of character one day.
All villagers plant these…
Drive your fan away.
Like how you did to me.
Do it. Come on.
You still have the audacity to come
here after what you've done?
I didn’t mean to do it.
I really apologize.
You know well, he has
a lot of public journalist friends.
And he also destroys
many superstar’s future via his own page.
Right?
You are such a poison fan!
Uh… I think…
Just ask him to leave here.
I feel sorry for Sun.
Okay.
Sun.
Sun, I am sorry.
Don’t be sorry,
just get away from me!
Sun.
Stop doing anything for me from now on.
I don’t want it,
especially from a fan like you.
Sun.
Sun, I am sorry.
Leave me alone!
Go!
Calm down, man!
She didn’t mean to do it.
Sun, I am sorry.
I didn’t mean to do it.
I said, go away!
Sun.
I am sorry.
Stop doing that!
This?
This is real.
You just saw it.
That YouTuber just said
he doesn’t need fans.
It’s enough.
You know nothing, girl!
You know it very well.
Your parents want you
to stop following Sun's fan club.
Because you couldn’t juggle
between studying and following
someone you're obsessed with.
Sun used to be nice to you.
Later, he changed,
and he drove you away
to go back to focusing on study.
Do you think it’s a coincidence?
Ask you parents.
Maybe they have something to do with it.
How do you know all this?
It’s not important of how I know this.
The thing is you need to realize
and stop blaming Sun.
If you want to destroy the person who has
done things for you and your family,
then it’s up to you.
Hey you!
Why do you keep following me?
What…
you have said to Brownie was too rude.
You should say sorry to her.
Why do I have to do so?
Just leave me, that’s all.
You can be arrogant or a jerk
to anyone,
but not those who care about you.
Trouble maker, I'll say.
Then you are also a trouble maker.
Don’t come close to me!
Who wanted to?
So annoying!
You can feel annoyed,
but you can't cowardly refuse
what you have
and take it out on other people.
What do you mean?
Your special power
doesn’t make you afraid
of being with other people.
But your heart chickens out
and you blame it on the power you have.
What are you talking about?
How do you know that?
Pete, you told her?
No, I did not.
Let’s speed up!
Hey, you! Come here.
Nope, you don’t want me
to stay near you, do you?
Hey!
Move here and talk.
Go to say sorry to Brownie then!
Stubborn!
It’s dangerous.
I will. But now you come here first.
No way! I will just sit here.
I will sit here. Have a problem?
I won't let you win today.
-Come on.
-What?
Hey!
Why in such a hurry!
Are you okay?
Your head!
Hey! Sun, are you okay?
Are you all right?
You sure you're okay?
It’s little.
I mean, your leg or hands might hurt.
I’ll tell you one thing.
About your special power,
if you know how to deal with it,
you can help a lot of people.
Like you helped me just now.
Even if I didn’t help you,
those riders could have steered away.
Talking with you
is like talking with a wall.
Always argue. Never listen.
Sun!
I’ll help him first.
Are you comfy?
Let’s clear things first.
Come. Let’s sit here.
So,
do you believe in special powers?
Isn’t that crazy?
I read a story about
a lady with a special power.
She can see other people’s pasts.
Every time she touches someone's hand,
she can feel their pain.
It makes her get scared of
touching people.
But this is reality,
not a story.
I will help you.
I will help you to deal with it.
With the sound in my head?
Yeah.
These can help.
No.
It’s me who can help you.
I am different from other people.
I will try to think positive
and let you hear.
Sun!
It’s good we have the nurse here,
don’t need to go too far.
Let me clean your wound.
Okay.
Will it hurt?
It’s a saline solution for cleaning.
I know all the truth.
My mom asked you to do this for me.
Why didn’t you tell me?
You won’t listen, anyway.
I am so sorry.
It’s okay.
I was mean to you, too.
I also need to apologize to you.
Why did you change your mind?
Who told you about
what your parents asked me?
Anna.
It's on me!
No…
No denying.
This is yummy.
Are you free today?
Let me think first.
Anything you want?
Don’t you remember?
You said you’ll help me.
Why don’t you answer me?
Well!
I did.
You should know what I am thinking now.
You are the only one
whose thoughts I couldn’t hear.
Huh?
Really?
So…
I can call you all kinds of names, huh?
Are you giving me a compliment?
Let me listen to that!
Am I that sexy when eating ice cream?
My nose
looks perfect?
Am I that cool?
Handsome? Smart?
And you want to look at me closer?
Hey! Are you crazy?
Uh, I’m sorry.
It’s okay.
I can deal with it.
Anna! Hey!
Your plot summary got accepted now.
Congratulations!
Hold on!
Why do you need to shout? We’re both here.
I am tired.
Excited, too.
I think your plan
of being close with Sun
is really great.
Now you deserve it, girl!
Your plot is very good.
Awesome!
Actually, I …
I think…
Wait!
Don't tell me
that you secretly fell in love with him.
No, not that.
Yes or no?
After work’s done
then we both go our own way.
Yeah, that’s what I wanna tell you.
Aren't you happy?
Sun.
Sun?
Oops!
I wish I could read your mind.
Then I could know,
you are also the same as others.
TWO DAYS LATER IN KANCHANABURI
This is what it’s called heartbroken.
What's heartbroken, man?
Listen to your brain’s voice,
then you will know it.
You finally met the one you can be with.
Why do you keep saying that?
Huh? Pete!
Then you ran away from it.
Why don’t you face it?
You ran too far!
It’s good, isn’t it?
I want to see no one, just stay alone!
It’s all.
You want to be friends only with me?
Yeah!
Sun is not in the mood
right now, everyone. So I will
just keep following him this way
and see what he is gonna do.
Such a nice breeze!
Do you feel better? Say something, man!
Please just stop, see the view.
Hey! Don’t say that.
Just stop it!
-Hey!
-Eat!
First word is out.
I thought he wouldn’t
open his mouth today.
Guys, he is talking to the trees.
Hey, dude! How’s it?
Better than talking to people.
Hey!
Don’t say that.
How am I gonna use the footage now?
People might think
you are even more arrogant.
Here.
Dried banana with solar power.
You see, how useful solar power can be.
Your name is Sun,
have you thought about the good
you could do for others?
I am not a social worker.
You can be the light for others.
People still love
and support you, come on!
I gotta say one thing
since I just realized it.
May I ask you?
Let’s think about your fan like Brownie.
Have you ever heard
any bad thoughts from her?
As a fan of yours,
she truly loves and cheers you up, man!
Why did you bring this up?
Because I don’t want you to act this way.
I am really tired
of dealing with you, man!
Try to think of others
so you will have more friends.
If you are tired,
then you just leave me.
I want to do that
but I just can’t. I am worried about you!
If you really don’t need me, I'll leave.
I will coordinate with the staff for you.
Why? Are you from the same sector?
Each sector has
different responsibilities.
EGAT is responsible
for producing electricity.
If you have problems
with electricity usage,
you have to contact
Provincial Electricity Authority.
If you are in the areas like Bangkok,
Pathumthani, or Nonthaburi,
you may contact
Metropolitan Electricity Authority.
Dried banana with solar power.
You see, how useful solar power can be.
Your name is Sun,
have you thought about the good
you could do for others?
Oh, I see! I just realize that.
Can you help me to contact them?
I don’t know how I can contact them.
Sure, I will do that.
What do you guys argue about?
How ridiculous!
Just don’t say anything.
Sun!
I have told you before.
Pete really cares about you.
He would be glad
if he could change the job.
I think he still wants to work with you.
Pete always cares about friends!
And he is very worried about you
so he didn’t leave you.
You know?
I know that.
Pete!
I am sorry.
It’s okay!
I can never stay mad at you.
If I were there,
I'd just beat you!
I wanna hug you guys.
It’s okay.
Let’s hug. Come on.
Hug me tight.
Hey, it’s too tight. I can’t breathe.
It’s okay now.
What do you think about me?
I am not angry.
Too sweet.
Even though the sunlight is gone
but my power is still here.
Are you serious?
Let’s make the recording.
I'll grab the camera.
Go.
Anna.
Brownie.
I didn’t really mean it that way.
I heard it from your mouth,
now what excuse do you want to say?
It’s not making an excuse.
You come here for the excuse, don’t you?
It’s really not an excuse!
I am here
to apologize you.
No need to say sorry.
I don’t need it.
We are not that close to care about it.
If you don’t care,
why did you react to me so strangely?
I am normally strange.
I am unusual.
Why do you have
such a complicated mind, man?
Then leave me alone.
Are you driving me away?
I did. Go now!
Why are you still here?
I don’t want to.
I came a long way to get here.
So, I'll stay here.
Just go back where you’re from.
I will stay here! I will sleep here!
Fine. I will leave.
Hey! Wait
Where are you going? I will go with you.
I'll follow you everywhere
till you forgive me.
Argh! What on earth are you?
I wrote about you,
I followed you…
because…
I feel good with you.
You are more special than others.
Have you finished it?
If yes, then we won’t need
to see each other again.
I wanna make it a happy ending.
Don’t pretend.
That doesn’t work.
Won’t you help me? It really hurts.
Here it is.
Do you really want to sleep here?
Yeah!
Two ladies here
and it's dark already.
Where’s Anna?
Why do you ask me?
You'll leave her alone in the dark?
She can come back on her own.
She just pretends that she hurt her leg.
Hey!
If you don’t really know
how she feels about you,
then you just try
to hear your brain’s voice.
Here. Take it.
Anna.
After you're gone, what’s next?
I’ll just let Sun think of
how much he cares about me.
I feel sorry for him, though.
No need to, girl!
He deserves it.
One more thing.
You guys try not to let him
read your minds and thoughts.
You too, Brownie,
If you are with him,
just try to hum a tune
or think of something.
Anna, where are you?
After he cares and worries about me,
then I’ll be open to him.
Anna!
Are you all right?
Another slip and fall?
Like in the drama,
the actor and the actress
watch each other closely.
Are you okay?
I am fine.
Come on. Ready, one, two, three.
It really hurts.
What?
My ankle hurts.
Get up here!
Come on.
Hold tight.
Thank you.
Don’t forget to add it in your story.
That he gives his lady a piggyback
and walks a mile
even though she is super heavy.
That’s too much!
Am I that heavy?
I'm serious. You are very heavy.
By the way,
you really want me to be your lady?
No answer!
You're thinking of what
you’ve just said, aren’t you?
Just don’t!
I am still angry at you
so don’t talk to me.
Liar!
Your anger is gone already.
Who told you?
I can read your mind.
It’s as planned!
What was the plan?
The weather is very nice.
Pete!
Banana pie fresh milk shake
This is recommended.
This is yummy with the jelly!
Banana pie.
If reconciling with Sun is easy as pie,
it would be really nice.
Still trying to link this?
Where are you going now for the record?
Memory Park.
Memory of how he is still angry.
Enough!
Get a grip, girl.
Let’s go.
Go where?
Go and say sorry to him!
-No.
-Just go.
-Why?
Come on.
This is a good time to do it.
I don’t dare to do it.
Just go! It’s okay.
Sun,
are you thirsty? I can buy you some water.
Sun, I…
Don’t!
You don’t need to explain anything.
I know
that you were always good to me,
saved me from those anti-fans.
You support me and you don’t even care of
how other people think of me.
Thank you so much.
I apologize for treating you badly.
Sun.
I am so sorry.
I love you the most, Sun!
I promise you.
I won’t be anyone's fan except you
for the rest of my life.
Are you jealous?
Isn' that too much?
Saying sorry is enough,
but she hugs him so tight.
Are you that happy?
He just gave you a hug.
Most ever in the world!
What?
Nothing!
I did what I’ve said now.
We’re even now.
We gotta meet each other anyway.
Meet again?
I’ll always follow Sun anyway.
Ah!
You mean you wanna meet Sun.
And…
I also wanna meet you too, brother Pete.
Really?
Absolutely!
Don’t call me brother,
it seems old.
Well…
When I like someone, I always say that.
Sister Brownie.
Silly!
Crazy man!
Since we first met,
you seemed to be a very nice person.
But one thing came up was
why you are so mean to others?
Lately, I’ve seen you more,
I wrote the story about your life.
I’ve gotten to know you more,
we know each other more.
I feel…
I'm really interested in you.
You are an author.
You can make words as you want to.
I really wish you could hear
what's in my head right now.
I can hear your heart.
We're sitting not even that close.
I still can hear
your heart beating like…
Lub-dub.
Too much!
When I am with you,
I feel really good.
I really want to be your friend.
But I don’t want to be your friend.
Let’s add the scene where the actor
kisses his lady in your story.
Silly!
Great job, dude!
It’s too early!
Kiss his lady?
This is me.
I am Sun.
I have a special power.
I can hear people’s thoughts.
It makes me forget
to listen to my own thoughts
and so I miss out many things.
Even though people think I am arrogant,
it’s okay.
From now on,
I will be with my special power.
And if it could be used to help others,
I will do exactly that.
One thing that is very strange.
I don’t know why it's only her
that I couldn't use my special power with.
The story you have told me
about the lady
who could read people’s past.
She is not in the story.
It’s you!
If I can see people’s past
by touching hands,
then I gotta know about you already.
No need to figure out from others.
You may have not seen my past
like I don’t hear your mind.
With your work,
do you need my help
to read people’s thoughts?
So, you won’t need to be nosy.
Hey!
You said I am a nosy?
But… yeah. Deal.
This is how you read people’s past, right?
What are you talking about?
So where are you going next?
I think I will visit Rajjaprabha Dam.
In Thailand, there are many dams where
you can visit and take beautiful photos.
The villagers are nice,
foods are delicious,
the local market is also good.
And the most important thing,
those places have handsome guys like me!
Everything is good, except the last…
So, deal!
Do you wanna hug me?
And kiss me?
Dreaming! You are dreaming now.
Didn’t you say
you couldn’t hear my thoughts?
You want to be my girlfriend?
No. Who? No way!
I'm not thinking about that.
THE END
So what are you thinking?
Why do I have to tell you?
Thank you everyone for watching
and following our video clips.
We promise that we will
create good content
to repay all your support.
That’s so touching, dude.
For me,
I will promise that…
I will make myself better.
I won’t be that arrogant guy
anymore from now on.
Smile!
See you again, everyone.