♪ "Comfortable" by LANKS playing ♪
[chuckles softly]
‐ ♪ Why didn't you call me
when you fell apart ♪
♪ You know I need you
like a light in the dark ♪
♪ There's blood on my side of the car ♪
♪ Too ♪
♪ Now you're packed up on the inside ♪
‐ Hey, Felix. Are you awake?
Over.
[radio clicks]
FELIX [over radio]:
[yawns] I am, now. What's up, man?
Hey, man.
‐ Hey.
I, I could have come to yours.
‐ Oh, no. No.
My, um, my mom's a really light sleeper.
So what's up?
‐ I don't know how I'm gonna say this,
but...
I know that if I don't say it now,
I'm gonna lose my nerve, so, um...
Here it goes.
Can you turn around?
‐ Seriously?
‐ I'm, I'm sorry, it's just
too much pressure with you staring at me,
especially since you hardly ever blink.
‐ What are you talking about?
I blink a normal amount.
‐ Felix, uh...
I...
like guys.
[Victor chuckles]
Like, I'm into them.
I thought I might for a while,
but I wasn't totally sure, and...
I really wanted to
make things work with Mia, because...
she's awesome.
But I, but I can't. Because...
I like guys.
‐ Can I turn around now?
‐ Yeah.
♪
‐ I, um...
I really don't know
the perfect thing to say.
But I'm really happy you told me.
And this doesn't change
anything between us, obviously.
‐ Actually, as...
As far as perfect things to say go,
that was pretty good.
Felix, don't cry.
‐ I'm not crying. You...
made me aware of my blinking.
Irritated my eye.
[Victor chuckles softly]
Whew. So...
How does it feel to get
all this off your chest?
‐ Kind of amazing.
[both chuckle]
But, um, you were the easy one.
‐ Yeah. Telling Mia's gonna suck.
‐ Yeah.
‐ But she'll understand.
It's not like you cheated on her,
or killed her cat.
‐ I kind of kissed Benji.
‐ Whoa.
♪ upbeat music playing ♪
‐ ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Waiting for the time ♪
♪ Waiting for the place ♪
♪ And I, I, I ♪
♪ I, I need ♪
♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be all right ♪
it'll be just fine ♪
♪ If someone has been there before,
say it right now ♪
♪ 'Cause I just need to hear it ♪
♪
‐ Hey.
ISABEL: [gasps] Hi, my love!
[kisses]
[laughs]
I didn't hear you come in last night.
How was your basketball trip?
‐ It was... It was perfect.
‐ I'm so glad.
[Victor chuckles]
[phone dings]
‐ Um...
I have to get ready for school,
but good luck on your
first day of piano lessons.
‐ Thank you. Hey, is this a new jacket?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Suits you.
‐ Macho.
Welcome home, huh?
‐ Hey.
[chuckles]
‐ Oh, wow.
Did, uh, somebody turn our living room
into a piano academy?
[both laughing]
So, uh, who are your new students?
‐ Like, what are their names?
‐ Nah, I just mean, like,
um, what's their deal?
Are they, uh, guys? Girls?
How old are they?
‐ Well, let's see.
There's Kyle, the ninth grader
who wants to be the next John Legend.
There's Lisa, the fourth grader.
She's all thumbs.
And there's Fabian,
the male underwear model
who insists on playing without a shirt.
Sorry. I was going for a joke
to break the tension.
Didn't work.
‐ Nope.
‐ Mando. Don't worry.
Just say good luck.
‐ Good luck.
[both chuckle]
Good luck, and have
a great first day of lessons.
Okay?
‐ Okay.
‐ Bye.
[bell rings]
FELIX:
[chuckles] Aw. The school dance.
The perfect place for a night of romance
with my sweetie.
[Victor chuckles]
If my sweetie didn't think
being seen with me was social suicide.
‐ What's the latest with you two?
‐ [sighs] She still doesn't want
anyone knowing we're hooking up.
‐ Mm.
‐ But she did tell Mia, so baby steps.
Or what's smaller than baby steps?
Fetus steps?
‐ Ugh.
‐ No, no, no. It's okay. I totally get it.
She is completely out of my league.
We're kind of like if Taylor Swift
was dating the dog from A Dog's Purpose.
‐ Hey! You're not a dog.
Okay, you're charming,
you have thick, shiny hair,
and really nice brown eyes.
‐ You are literally describing the dog
from A Dog's Purpose.
‐ Okay, do you want to
be with Lake for real?
‐ Of course. I mean, I've thought of
so many ways to ask her to the dance.
I mean, skywriting, flash mob,
a cappella serenade...
‐ Then ask her.
But, you know, in like, a, a normal way.
‐ Okay.
‐ Oh, God.
‐ So, what's the game plan with Mia?
‐ Uh, I'm gonna ask her
if I could come over tonight
so she has some privacy
when I tell her the truth.
[exhales] Am I doing it?
Am I walking towards her?
‐ Nope.
You are fully rooted in place.
Now, let me just give a tiny... Yep.
‐ Hey.
How dope is Mia for letting me
borrow these for the school dance?
I've said it before and I'll say it again.
She's way too good for you.
Thanks.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Hey, look, before you say anything,
I, I know I've been M. I. A.
It's just, it's‐‐
between work and this trip...
I've been really crappy
at keeping in touch.
And I'm sorry.
‐ So, just because you're aware
that you've been acting crappy,
I'm supposed to forgive you?
‐ That's the hope. Yeah.
What if we hung out after school today?
Maybe I could come over to your house?
Are you free?
‐ My dad and Veronica are going
to a Billy Joel concert tonight,
so I have the house to myself.
And I had kind of a weird plan.
Um, I'm making homemade sushi.
‐ Really?
‐ Yeah. [chuckles]
Ever since I saw, um, that
Jiro Dreams of Sushi documentary,
I've been dying to try it.
So, are you in?
We'll either have an amazing dinner,
or we'll get mercury poisoning.
‐ I'm in.
‐ Well, mata ne.
It's, uh, it's Japanese for
"I'll see you later." [laughs] Okay.
[kisses]
‐ Bye.
‐ Mm, Lake. Lake.
I've been thinking.
I should be more honest with you
about what I want.
Look, I think we should
go to the dance together.
‐ [sighs] Uh, I,
I'm not really into dances.
‐ What? You love everything dance‐related.
Dancing With the Stars. World of Dance.
Dance Dance Revolution. Dirty Dancing.
So You Think You Can Dance.
‐ [huffs] You're such a good listener.
‐ Mmm.
‐ Felix...
[Felix sighs]
Couples who go to dances are scrutinized,
and I'm just not ready to put us under
the Creekwood microscope.
‐ So we can only see each other
in a supply closet?
I can't live in the shadows, Lake.
I'm pale enough as it is.
[Lake groans]
‐ Well, uh, my parents
won't be home after school.
Wanna come over?
Maybe it'll be so hot you'll catch a tan.
‐ Oh, my God. Um...
‐ And just to be clear,
we're not advancing bases.
We're just advancing to an actual bedroom.
‐ Totally understand.
Just one thing.
Is this a no‐shoes household,
because if so, I want to plan
my sock situation accordingly.
‐ Shh.
[kissing]
‐ Hey.
Didn't think you were working today.
‐ I'm not.
I'm clearing out my stuff.
Starting next week, I'm transferring
to a different location.
‐ Is this because I kissed you?
‐ I guess... kind of.
‐ You don't have to switch stores, Benji.
What happened on our trip, it...
it won't happen again.
‐ Look.
[locker slams]
My relationship with Derek isn't perfect.
But I don't want to lose him.
And when you kissed me,
it put me in a tough spot.
‐ You told him?
‐ No. There's no reason to.
He'd just get upset.
But the idea of working
with you every day makes me feel...
...guilty.
‐ Why?
You didn't do anything wrong.
‐ I know that.
‐ Well, I guess, uh...
Guess I'll see you at school?
‐ I think it's best if we stay
out of each other's way.
‐ Right.
[keys jangling]
VICTOR:
Dear Simon, I'm coming out to Mia tonight.
And if that wasn't enough,
Benji won't even talk to me.
Why does everything have to be so hard?
‐ Lake, your room is beautiful.
[laughing]: Oh, my God.
Is that you as a little girl?
Oh!
Look at your little baby cheeks.
I could just bite 'em.
‐ Okay, could we not make this
about me as a baby?
We finally have some privacy.
‐ You're right. What's wrong with me?
[door closes]
GEORGINA: Sweetheart, I'm home!
‐ Uh, crap. Uh, my mom's home early.
Just...
Just get under the bed. Okay? Go.
[Felix sighs]
Go.
Hurry. She's coming. Okay? Go, go!
Hi, Mom.
‐ Whose bag is that?
‐ Uh, mine.
Boy bags are the new trend.
‐ Oh, honey, no.
Even as far as boy bags go,
that is a very ugly backpack.
[chuckles]
‐ Um, thought you were getting
your hair toned tonight.
‐ Well, my stylist bailed,
because her "child has croup."
Wah‐wah.
Anyway, I was already at the mall,
so I did some shopping for you,
so... fashion show.
‐ Oh, uh, that's okay.
‐ Lake, you're traipsing around school
with a boys' backpack.
This jacket just makes your shoulders
look like you're a bouncer.
Please? I really want you to
go through some of these looks.
‐ Uh, okay.
‐ Yay! Fun!
♪
[phone chimes]
[phone dinging]
SIMON:
Hey, Vic.
I'm not gonna sugarcoat it.
Telling Mia is gonna be
really, really hard.
You just gotta rip the gay Band‐Aid off
and hope that eventually she forgives you.
As for Benji,
when I screwed things up
with all with my friends,
they wouldn't talk to me, either.
So, I wrote them a big apology
on Creek Secrets.
I'm not saying you should do that,
but maybe try and help Benji understand
where you're coming from.
♪ "You and I" by Caribou playing ♪
‐ ♪ For things that I can't explain ♪
♪ You and I ♪
♪ You were always with me ♪
♪ Like a light ♪
♪ The things I can't throw away ♪
‐ Hey.
[door closes]
‐ You, um...
You made me feel like such an idiot
this morning when I
asked about your students.
‐ What?
‐ You told that stupid joke
to make me think that
your students were all children.
That you weren't giving lessons
to grown‐ass men in our apartment.
‐ Armando!
‐ But of course you would lie to me
about something like that.
That's exactly what somebody
who betrayed her husband
and her family would do.
[toilet flushes]
‐ That man you saw wasn't a student.
He was dropping off a student.
‐ So, how long until I can play
"All of Me"?
In a month, I'd like to serenade
Kira Brownstein at her bat mitzvah.
‐ That sounds amazing. Okay...
Where were we? Okay. Yeah.
‐ Oh, honey. This one's a keeper.
‐ Thanks, Mom. Um...
I really appreciate it,
but I think I can do my own shopping.
‐ Oh, you just worked so hard
to lose all that weight,
and I just want you to present yourself
in the most flattering light possible.
‐ I think I'm presenting just fine.
‐ Just fine?
I mean, do you think I'd be
the top‐rated anchor in greater Atlanta
if I presented "just fine"?
‐ I guess not.
‐ No, you bet your ass, I wouldn't.
I mean, when I first started
as a production assistant at Channel Nine,
do you know what they called me?
"Omaha."
Because I was a small town girl
from Omaha
with a crappy haircut
and polyester clothes.
So I lived on ramen and air
until I could afford an appointment
at the nicest salon in town.
And on the weekends, I scoured
thrift stores to find designer clothes.
A year later,
"Omaha" was the youngest field reporter
in Channel Nine history.
Now look, you do fine in school,
but clearly, your grades aren't gonna
open any doors,
so you need to get used to
putting your best foot forward.
And that means knowing how to look curvy,
but not big.
And attractive, but not like a floozy.
Public perception is crucial.
‐ Uh, yeah. You're right. Thank you.
Um, I'll just... try the rest on later.
‐ Oh, that's my girl.
[laughs]
‐ [sighs]
Okay, for the record, she is insane.
Your body is literally perfect.
‐ Felix, please.
I'll just sneak you out the back door.
I can't even look at you,
knowing you heard that conversation.
‐ Actually, I want to take you somewhere.
Show you something.
[crickets chirping]
‐ We should probably eat these
before they get cold.
[both chuckle]
Just a good old‐fashioned sushi joke.
Um, you okay? You seem kind quiet.
‐ No, yeah. Yeah, I'm great.
Aah. Cheers.
‐ Cheers.
[both laugh]
Should we drop out of high school,
run away, and start a sushi restaurant?
[laughs]
Mm.
‐ Hey, Mia, look. I, I wanted to talk‐‐
[door opens]
HAROLD:
Mia, we're home!
‐ Why are they back?
Uh, wow. I guess you're finally
gonna meet my dad.
‐ Oh, look at this.
I didn't realize we were
having company over.
[both laugh]
Hey.
‐ Hi, I'm Victor.
‐ Hello.
‐ Victor. Nice to meet you. Hi.
‐ Veronica.
Nice to meet you.
VICTOR: Nice to meet you.
‐ Uh, what happened to the concert?
‐ Ah, we decided to bail.
Veronica, she wasn't feeling too well.
‐ [exhales] I guess I'm not really
in a New York state of mind.
It's a Billy Joel reference.
You know that song‐‐
Never mind.
HAROLD: Here you go, sweetheart.
‐ Thank you.
MIA: Well, did you guys eat?
‐ Uh, no. Actually, I'm starving.
‐ Well, we have plenty of sushi.
[chuckles]
‐ Thank you. I'm okay.
I'm not a huge sushi girl.
[Harold chuckles]
‐ Yes, you are. You eat it all the time.
‐ So, Victor, um...
You wouldn't know this,
but we are big fans of your Instagram.
VICTOR: [laughs] Thank you.
VERONICA: Harold!
You can't tell him
we look at his Instagram!
‐ Oh, my God. Are you pregnant?
[scoffs]
‐ Mia. [chuckles nervously]
Come on, that's ridiculous. She's, um...
‐ Honey...
Yes. I'm, I'm ten weeks pregnant.
HAROLD: I thought we were gonna
wait for the right time to tell her.
‐ I think it became the right time
when she figured it out.
‐ Maybe I should go.
‐ No.
No. Uh, stay.
Did you guys plan this?
‐ No. It was... [chuckles]
...an accident, actually. Um...
But a happy one.
Because it really brought into focus
how serious we are about each other.
VERONICA: Mm.
‐ And on that note, uh...
Mia, we're getting married.
We were gonna tell you.
We were just waiting for the right moment.
‐ Um...
Much more exciting to have
figured it out on my own.
I'm sorry. I just... I, I need a minute.
‐ Honey, you...
[Harold sighs]
VICTOR: Well, uh...
Congratulations.
‐ So, this is where I live.
I've never shown my apartment
to anyone before.
Not even Victor.
[key clicking in lock]
[door opens]
Believe it or not,
didn't always look like this.
My mom and I have lived here
since I was born.
Used to be normal.
Fun place to live.
I had a ton of toys.
All my Legos went in that corner.
I had an Xbox over there, at one point.
And I had this trampoline
that drove the downstairs neighbors crazy.
But, uh, I realized eventually
that my mom was buying me all that stuff
to distract me from
what was really going on.
She always suffered from depression.
Over time, it got worse.
And she developed this inability
to part ways with stuff.
‐ [sighs] So your mom's
like a... a hoarder?
‐ [chuckles] I like to think of her
as a... overactive collector.
But yeah, no, hoarder works, too.
‐ Felix, why are you showing me this?
‐ I saw your life.
I wanted you to see mine.
Look, this might be where I live,
but this is not a reflection of who I am.
The way your mom sees you
is not a reflection of you.
You are already
the best version of yourself.
You're smart.
You're funny.
You're beautiful.
And for the record,
I know what beauty looks like.
There's about a thousand Cosmo magazines
in that corner to prove it.
[chuckles softly]
[crickets chirping]
♪ blues music playing
through headphones ♪
[exhales]
[knocking on door]
MIA:
Hey.
Sorry I'm being so angsty.
VICTOR:
This isn't angsty.
Angsty is when my sister
gets so mad at my parents
that she drops their keys
down the garbage disposal.
‐ My dad is, like, the only family I have.
And now he's gonna have a new wife.
And a new baby.
He's moving on.
Just like my mom.
‐ He's not moving on.
You're still gonna be
his whole world, Mia.
Look, he might suck at showing it,
but that man is crazy about you.
And that's never gonna change,
no matter how many wives
or children he has.
He's not your mom, Mia.
[kisses, then sighs]
‐ What would I do without you?
[chuckles softly]
FELIX: So... um...
Thank you for coming.
‐ Thanks for bring me. Meant a lot.
[car approaching]
Oh. Looks like my Lyft's here.
So... [chuckles softly]
‐ Lake.
[sighs] Come to the dance with me.
I mean, who cares about public perception?
We're great together.
‐ I can't.
It's just...
I care too much about
what other people think.
‐ I understand.
‐ Thank you.
‐ But whatever this is, Lake,
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry. This is over.
♪ "I Lost a Friend" by FINNEAS playing ♪
‐ ♪ Like sleep on a red‐eye ♪
♪ Like money on a bad bet ♪
[silverware clanking]
♪ Like time worrying about every bad thing
that hasn't happened yet ♪
♪ I know I'll be all right ♪
‐ Um, this is really good turkey, Mom.
Just the right amount of cumin.
‐ ♪ I know I'll be all right ♪
♪ But I'm not tonight ♪
‐ What's wrong?
You guys think it's too much cumin?
‐ ♪ I lost a friend, I lost a friend ♪
‐ I'm gonna go take Adrian
out for ice cream.
Let you guys hash out the source
of this awkward‐ass dinner.
Come on. Put on your shoes.
ADRIAN: Okay.
‐ I don't feel comfortable
with you giving piano lessons.
‐ Wow.
And here I thought
you were going to apologize.
[Armando exhales]
No, Armando.
I'm not gonna give up doing what I love.
I messed up.
But I am tired of being
this family's punching bag.
You screwed up, too.
If you hadn't have beaten the crap
out of Roger after what happened,
you wouldn't have been fired,
and we would have never had to move here.
[door closes]
‐ ♪ I'm on the mend ♪
[Armando sighs]
‐ Hey, Victor. Um, we were just‐‐
‐ Fighting.
Yeah, what's new?
Dad beat up his boss?
‐ We didn't want to overwhelm you guys
with all the details.
‐ Right. But you're cool with overwhelming
us with your constant fighting.
You don't think we could all tell
how off you guys are?
‐ You and Pilar know we've been
having some problems,
but I don't think Adrian‐‐
‐ Adrian can sense it, too.
He's little. He's not dumb.
Look, I get that you guys
are going through something.
And I'm sorry.
I'm sorry it's been so hard for you guys.
I really am.
But you make this house feel like
a shitty place to come home to.
You need to do better.
For all of us.
‐ ♪ If it was black and white ♪
‐ I'm sorry for swearing.
But, um, I'm gonna go and take a shower.
[shower water running]
‐ Hey, Vic, can I borrow
ten bucks for ice cream?
VICTOR:
I can't hear you!
‐ Okay. If I can go into your room
and take ten bucks out of your wallet,
say nothing at all.
‐ ♪ Nobody believes me ♪
♪ Say I know that he don't need me ♪
♪ 'Cause he made a little too much money
to be twenty and sad ♪
♪ And I'll be fine without 'em ♪
♪ But all I do is write about 'em ♪
‐ Hmm?
‐ ♪ How the hell did I lose a friend
I never had ♪
VICTOR: B, first of all,
I am so sorry for kissing you.
But please, just hear me out.
‐ Who the hell is "B"?
♪