♪
[students chattering]
RAHIM:
Dear Victor, I hope it's cool
that I'm reaching out.
[bell rings]
My name is Rahim.
I'm a friend and
"colleague" of Pilar's.
♪ "Vibe"
by The Blah Blah Blahs playing ♪
RAHIM: She said you might be a good person
to reach out to because...
I'm gay.
But it's still scary
to say the words out loud.
‐ ♪ ...on my patio set ♪
♪ Whatcha gonna do with
all them good good vibes ♪
♪ We moving, we shaking ♪
RAHIM:
Especially because my mom and dad
are super traditional.
And super Muslim.
Not having my parents' approval
has always seemed like
the worst thing imaginable.
Until recently, that is.
Now, the worst thing I can imagine
is that I never get to experience
what you and Benji have.
Hoping you might have
some words of wisdom.
Sincerely, Rahim.
Wait, is it weird to end with "sincerely?"
Whatever. I'm going for it.
Sincerely, Rahim.
[phone bloops]
‐ ♪ Vibe ♪
♪ Whatcha gonna do with
all them good good vibes ♪
♪ theme music playing ♪
‐ ♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be all right ♪
♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be just fine ♪
♪ If someone has been there before,
say it right now ♪
♪ 'Cause I just need to hear it ♪
♪
ISABEL:
[humming] Yes!
Ay, mijo, you look so adorable.
‐ I look ridiculous.
Even I want to punch me.
‐ Why does Adrian look like Willy Wonka?
‐ Mom is going to sing
at church this Sunday,
and now she wants us all to
show up looking insane.
‐ Wow. Uh, congrats.
‐ Thank you.
Can you come?
I know you haven't
been to church for a while, but...
it doesn't feel right singing
without my biggest fan there.
‐ Uh, I, I don't know.
You know, they don't exactly
welcome people like me.
‐ Wait, what do you mean,
people like you?
‐ People who don't make their beds.
‐ Again with the bed? You're obsessed!
‐ He's just a little kid.
He's not ready for that.
[sighs]
VICTOR: How am I supposed to give
another gay kid advice
when I can barely talk to my own mom?
She still won't tell Adrian that I'm gay.
‐ And have you told her how any of this
makes you feel?
‐ No, no. Not really.
We live in a constant state
of unspoken weirdness.
It's the Catholic way.
‐ Right.
‐ I don't know.
Maybe I'll just see if Rahim
wants to come over later.
‐ Oof. So your mom can give him
her trademark judgment eyes?
‐ She has choir practice.
And it's more like‐‐
‐ Oh, yeah. That's good.
[both chuckle]
Hey, you know, it's kinda like
you're this kid's Simon.
‐ Oh, yeah! I should text Simon.
I bet he gives great advice
on how to give advice‐‐
Yeah. Yeah, I heard it.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
FELIX:
[sighs] Come on, Mom. Just take it.
DAWN:
No.
They make me feel like a zombie.
Plus, they make my eyelid twitch,
and then when I go to the bodega,
the guy thinks that I'm winking at him.
I mean,
you wish, Glen.
‐ Dr. Fischer said the side effects
will go away if you keep taking it.
‐ Dr. Fischer is a joke.
All he cares about is getting me
on a new drug,
and getting the next patient
in his office.
[knocking on door]
GEORGINA: Felix, it's Georgina Meriwether!
‐ [whispers] You didn't tell me
that Lake's mom was coming over!
‐ I didn't know.
‐ Hey.
‐ Oh, hello. You must be Dawn.
‐ Hi, y‐yes. Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry about the mess.
I, I mean, you know
how teenage boys can be.
‐ Yep. Yeah. No. No, this all me.
‐ Well, I hope I'm not interrupting.
I just wanted to come by
and give you a little something
to thank you for having Lake over
the other night.
My guy at the farmer's market had pears
out the wazoo.
So‐‐
‐ Oh, wow. Thank you.
That's so generous.
‐ Um, sorry.
Uh, if I knew you were coming over,
I, I would have gotten dressed.
‐ Oh, please. As soon as I come home,
I take off my bra
and let the girls swing raw.
'Cause stars, they're just like us.
[laughs]
DAWN:
I, um, can I get you something?
A, a cup of coffee, or some tea?
‐ Oh, well, I'm on my way to the station,
but I could have a quick cup of‐‐
‐ No‐‐ [stammers] We understand
the news waits for no man‐‐
sexist‐‐ no woman.
Say goodbye, Mom.
I'm gonna walk Georgina out.
‐ Oh. Bye.
‐ Bye. It was nice to meet you.
[door closes]
‐ Did Lake say something to you?
Is that why you're here?
‐ Lake cares about you, honey.
She's just concerned
about your situation.
‐ Oh, so this is a welfare check.
'Cause we're fine.
‐ And I see that.
But if things are ever not fine,
I want you to know that I'm here
if you need me.
‐ Yeah, well, we don't.
Thanks for the pears.
‐ Hey.
‐ Hey. Uh, what are you doing?
I told you to text me from the driveway.
‐ What am I, your date or Postmates?
No, when I pick up my girl,
I come right up to the door
and say hey to her father.
‐ Mmm, that's okay.
You really don't have to do that.
HAROLD: Ha ha ha!
Thought I heard that voice.
What's up, man?
How you doing?
ANDREW: You getting fit for the wedding?
You look swole!
‐ Aah, see? [laughs]
I may have gotten a Peloton.
Listen, are you two kids hungry?
Because, uh, we're in the middle of doing
an appetizer sampling for the wedding.
‐ Uh, no, actually,
we're headed to a movie.
‐ Come on. It'll take two minutes.
Come on.
Taste this food.
Hey, check this out.
I brought in reinforcements.
‐ Good. Andrew, hi. Nice to see you.
Sorry, I got started a bit early.
The potato's hungry today.
‐ She likes to call our baby a potato,
because she refuses to give him a name.
‐ If you're still taking suggestions,
might I recommend Andrew?
[both laugh]
‐ He's hot and funny!
Did I say hot? I'm so sorry.
Um, it's the hormones.
‐ You know, these two actually
beat us down the aisle.
In first grade, they had the cutest little
playground wedding.
‐ I was just in it for the tax break.
‐ Mmm.
‐ Um, you about done with that slider?
‐ Mia, why don't you show Andrew
your dress for the wedding
so you guys can coordinate?
MIA:
We just started dating.
It's way too soon to talk about
Andrew coming with me.
Sorry, I mean, I just‐‐
‐ No, no. Mia's right.
It's too soon.
Yeah, I‐I guess we gotta
get to that movie.
But thank you so much. This is great.
PILAR: Hey.
‐ Hey.
‐ Rahim, this is Victor.
Victor, this is Rahim.
I'm not sure why he's wearing
an old‐timey bowling shirt.
‐ Uh, my dad drove me here,
so I had to get this polyester nightmare
from my brother's closet.
‐ So you can't get away with
a Blackpink shirt,
but you can get away with
purple nail polish?
‐ Uh, I told my parents the nails
are for drama club.
They've been waiting for Creekwood's
production of Wicked for the past year.
‐ You pretend that you're straight
by saying you're in a musical?
‐ I already told you, I need advice.
You know, from someone
who came out to their parents
and had it go kind of okay.
‐ Yeah, I'm not so sure
what Pilar has told you.
ISABEL:
Hope everyone's hungry!
Choir practice ended early,
so I got Thai.
Oh. Hello. I didn't‐‐ Sorry.
Didn't realize you had company.
PILAR:
This is my friend, Rahim.
He's pretty much the only kid at Creekwood
that doesn't suck ass.
‐ Wow. Very moving introduction.
Hi, Mrs. Salazar.
Can I just say, I'm really digging
these terracotta accent walls.
‐ Thank you.
Sweet.
♪
Rahim, honey, would you like to stay
for dinner?
‐ Really?
‐ Yeah. Adrian's at your dad's house.
I have enough pad see ew to feed an army.
What do you say?
‐ Uh, j'adore Thai food.
Let me just call my parents,
and I'll help you whip up
a quick tablescape.
[Victor chuckles]
‐ He's nice.
[door opens]
‐ Lake.
What are you doing here?
‐ You weren't answering my texts,
so I figured I'd stake you out.
You didn't hear me throwing pebbles
at your window?
‐ What window?
‐ Second floor, far left.
I mean, I literally flashed you,
and you straight up ignored me.
‐ That's Victor's little brother's window.
‐ Well, I either traumatized him
or made his night.
[both chuckle]
Anyways, Felix,
I, I really had no idea my mom
was going to show up like that.
‐ That's not the point.
You promised you wouldn't tell anyone.
‐ No, I know that, but I‐‐
Listen, I know my mom can be a lot, but,
she's actually kind of amazing
when it comes to stuff like this.
‐ I don't need her help.
‐ No, I, I know you don't need it,
but you're allowed to want it.
Our family friend is this insanely
legit psychiatrist.
She usually has a year‐long waitlist,
but my mom asked,
and she agreed to see
your mom whenever you want,
free of charge.
Just promise me
you'll think about it, okay?
Ugh. What? Do you‐‐ Do you hate me?
‐ No. No. No, it's just...
No one's ever cared about me enough
to try this hard to help me.
‐ I am your girlfriend.
You know, that's kind of part of the gig.
[Felix grunts]
‐ I, I can't believe you flashed Adrian.
‐ Well, at least now he knows
what perfect breasts look like. [laughs]
‐ You're in theater?
That is so great.
I loved high school theater.
‐ No way. What roles did you play?
‐ What roles didn't I play, baby?
‐ Did she just call him "baby"?
ISABEL: Frenchy in Grease.
RAHIM: Mm‐hmm.
‐ Anita in West Side Story.
Type‐casting, but when it makes sense,
it makes sense.
Oh, and senior year,
Audrey in Little Shop.
♪ Suddenly Seymour ♪
‐ Oh, my God...
‐ ♪ Standing beside you ♪
‐ ♪ He don't give me orders ♪
‐ [joining in] ♪ ...orders ♪
ISABEL and RAHIM:
♪ He don't condescend ♪
‐ I will pay fifty dollars
to make this stop.
‐ You know, you are such
a delight, Mrs. Salazar.
Yeah, my parents
definitely won't be this Zen
when I come out to them.
‐ You don't think they'd understand?
‐ They're devout Muslims
who emigrated here from Iran.
Let's just say we don't sing
Little Shop of Horrors over green curry.
‐ Well, I hope they surprise you.
But, if they do take it badly,
just know that they love you so much.
And part of the reason they might
struggle is because...
they thought they knew
everything about you.
And then all of a sudden, they didn't.
So even if they say the wrong things,
I hope you don't give up on them.
♪
‐ I just think it's unlikely.
Like, that all the superheroes
know each other.
Like, Spiderman is in high school.
And Thor is a god from another planet.
Or Sweden, maybe.
Like, how did they even meet?
‐ All right. Next time,
I'll pick a movie that's more you.
You know, if there is a next time.
I mean, who knows if we'll still be
hanging out next weekend.
‐ Okay.
I know that was weird earlier,
but I just...
I just didn't know if you wanted to come
to some boring, stuffy wedding.
‐ Okay. Whatever you say.
I, I should go home.
‐ Okay. I'll see you tomorrow?
[door opens, then closes]
‐ The whole thing was weird,
but a good weird.
My mom sang showtunes,
and gave Rahim this big speech about how
even if his parents don't react well
when he comes out,
they still love him.
‐ Well, I'm glad she was nice...
to Rahim.
‐ What does that mean?
‐ I mean, she's never been
that way with me.
Or you.
‐ I know, but she's‐‐ she's really trying.
‐ I just don't want you
to get your hopes up
because of one good night.
[knock on door]
‐ Um, I have to go. Goodnight.
[phone beeps]
‐ Hi, mi amor.
Just wanted to say goodnight.
Um, Victor do you wanna
go get lunch sometime soon
so we can finally really talk?
‐ Yeah. Yeah, how about after you sing
tomorrow at church?
‐ You'll come?
‐ Yeah. If that's cool.
‐ Yeah, it's cool.
It's really, really cool.
[chuckles]
Just gonna leave
before you change your mind.
[door squeaks, closes]
VERONICA:
Mmm. Hey.
Do you wanna have some tea?
My stomach is being so weird.
I probably should have quit
after the third slider last night.
‐ Veronica, uh, we need to talk.
I'm glad we've gotten closer now,
but we need to set some boundaries.
Uh, first, please stop saying
that the guy I'm dating is hot.
He's a teenager, and it's, um, weird.
‐ Noted, and, uh, agreed.
‐ Second, please don't invite him
to your wedding
when we just started dating.
‐ Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to‐‐
I thought that things were going
so well between the two of you.
‐ They were. Uh, but now
he thinks that I'm not into it.
‐ And that's my fault for inviting him,
and not your fault
for being weird about it?
‐ What? Y‐yes.
Why do people think that I'm‐‐
Look, just because
I want to take things slow
with him doesn't‐‐
‐ I‐‐ [groans]
‐ Are you okay?
‐ [groans] I think so.
It's just... little cramps. Um...
So... oh, my‐‐
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Okay, that, that feels like a contraction,
and, and it can't be,
because it's way too early.
Will you hand me my phone
so that I can call your dad?
‐ Um, y‐yeah. Uh‐‐
[groans]
Okay, we can call him from the car.
I'm taking you to the hospital.
‐ Yeah, okay.
‐ Okay.
Oh, yeah...
‐ Guess what? I found a 1956 Thunderbird.
The exact same car that your grandpa had.
I mean, it needs ton of work,
but once I'm done with it,
it'll be worth a hundred grand. Easy.
‐ You're restoring old cars now.
‐ You can learn how to do
anything on YouTube.
‐ Hey, Mom, um,
would you be open to
trying a new doctor?
There's this psychiatrist, and she's on
all of the "Best of Atlanta" lists.
Plus, she has like six more letters
after her name than Dr. Fischer, so‐‐
‐ Honey, that doesn't sound like someone
who would take our insurance.
‐ Normally she wouldn't, but, um,
in this case, we're really lucky,
because she is a friend of Lake's family.
‐ Did her mom say something to you
after she came by here?
‐ No, okay? They just know
you're having a hard time,
and they want to help.
‐ We're not a charity case!
‐ And nobody thinks that.
But I think it might be good
if we actually‐‐
‐ No, I‐‐
I'm the parent.
Okay? And what I want you to say is...
thank you, but no, thank you.
‐ Okay. Yeah, I'll drop it.
‐ Love you.
‐ Love you, too.
[indistinct chatter]
‐ Hi.
‐ I got you some...
‐ Oh, thanks.
‐ Yeah, um, s‐‐ uh...
So what did the doctor say?
‐ She said that I have
"an irritable uterus,"
which feels vaguely misogynistic,
even though she's a woman.
[sighs] They're gonna keep me
for a while longer for observation,
but they said that everything looks fine.
[sighs]
‐ Thank God.
‐ Yeah.
[sighs]
‐ Sorry, I don't‐‐
I don't know why I'm crying.
[chuckles]
This is weird.
‐ Hey. It's okay.
For a minute there,
this was really scary.
‐ Yeah.
How are you so calm?
‐ I'm not. [laughs]
I was a mess. I'm‐‐
I think I just hide it well.
Mia, this isn't my first pregnancy.
I had a miscarriage
when I was in grad school.
I had to have two surgeries.
And the doctor,
she said she didn't know if I'd ever have
a viable pregnancy after that.
‐ Wow. So, this was one
really was a surprise.
‐ Mmm‐hmm. It's kind of
felt too good to be true.
That's why I call him the potato,
and not the baby.
[Mia chuckles]
I thought maybe that would help...
Make it hurt less
if something bad happened, but...
sitting here in the E. R. and...
I realize that if I lost this baby,
it would hurt just as badly
with or without a name.
I guess I was trying so hard
to protect myself that...
I didn't realize how attached
I'd already gotten.
‐ Yeah. Hmm. I know what you mean.
VERONICA:
Hmm.
[church organ warming up]
‐ Victor. It's good to see you.
It's been a while.
‐ Yeah, yeah. Couldn't miss
my mom's big day.
‐ Mmm.
Your mother tells me you've got a lot
on your plate right now.
‐ Oh, no, not really.
‐ Listen, I know you're at
a crossroads, son.
Your mother is praying for you
to find your way back to the Lord.
But you gotta put the work in, too.
♪ piano music playing ♪
♪ singing in foreign language ♪
♪ ominous music playing ♪
♪ singing continues ♪
♪ continues singing ♪
♪ tense music playing ♪
♪
‐ No, no, no, we're not gonna open
with gun control legislation.
I want to lead with rat poison
in chicken nuggets.
This is the news, not the snooze, right?
DAWN: Ooh, no, I, I am telling you...
‐ Oh, no.
DAWN: She knows me. No, no. What?
She knows me. Georgina, hi.
‐ It's okay, Lois.
It's okay. She's a friend.
‐ I told you.
‐ Hey, Dawn.
What a totally unexpected surprise.
Why don't we step into my office?
‐ No, I don't want to go
anywhere with you, okay?
And neither does Felix.
‐ I'm sorry. What are you talk‐‐
‐ You're trying to take him away from me.
He said that you called a doctor.
Who else did you call?
Georgina, did you call the cops?
Did you call CPS?
‐ No, of course not!
Let's just take a breath.
‐ I don't want to take a breath!
You think that I'm crazy and you're trying
to take my son away from me!
‐ Lois, call security please.
DAWN: This is not your business.
He has a mother.
Why would you try and break up my family?
He is all that I have.
This is not your problem!
[church bell chimes]
‐ There you are. Why did you leave
in the middle of my song?
‐ Mom, I thought we were finally
making some progress,
and then I find out that you're trying to
pray me into being straight?
‐ What? Who told you that?
‐ Father Lawrence.
Is it true?
[Isabel exhales sharply]
You know, I am trying so hard
to be proud of who I am.
And it's almost impossible when
my own mom thinks I need to be fixed.
‐ I am doing the best that I can, Victor.
‐ This is the best you can do?
Because Benji doesn't feel welcome
in our home.
And you still won't tell Adrian
that I'm gay.
‐ Adrian's just a child.
‐ Don't say that.
That's what people say when they're
shielding their children from bad things,
like murder.
Or drugs.
Not that their son has a boyfriend.
‐ You're right.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
You don't know this,
but growing up, I had an aunt named Yoli,
who never got married.
She never wore dresses.
She always had a "roommate."
And when I asked my mom
why she didn't have kids,
she just said,
"De eso no se habla."
‐ "We don't talk about that."
‐ You have to understand, Victor,
from a very young age,
I was taught that being gay
was shameful.
I don't, I don't think that way anymore.
At least not up here.
But these things that I was taught
when I was young, they are so...
engrained in me.
I wish I could just snap my fingers
and be a perfect mother for you.
But for now, I will say this...
The next time Benji
wants to come over to the house,
I promise I will make him feel welcome.
And I will tell Adrian. We...
We will tell Adrian soon.
‐ Was Aunt Yoli the one in the pictures
with, like, a whole bunch of dachshunds?
‐ She had seven.
[chuckles]
Is that a gay thing?
‐ I don't know.
MIA:
Andrew.
What are you doing here?
‐ I know you didn't ask me to come,
but I just wanted to make sure
you were okay.
You know, in like a cool,
casual sort of way.
‐ Mmm. I'm glad you're here.
Even if I don't deserve it
after how I treated you.
You know, I, I think I've gotten used to
people I care about leaving me.
You know, my mom took off.
My dad travels all the time...
And Victor...
Which, you know,
obviously wasn't the same,
but it still hurt.
And I've known you ever since
I can remember.
But the deeper things get,
the more I start to care.
And, uh, that's just
kind of terrifying for me.
‐ Mia, I've waited
pretty much my entire life
to be exactly where I am right now.
I'm not going anywhere.
♪
SOCIAL WORKER:
They've admitted your mom
on a 72‐hour psychiatric hold.
Once the three days are up,
she can choose to remain
voluntarily, or‐‐
‐ C‐c‐can I go and see her?
‐ No visitors right now,
but they're gonna take
good care of your mom.
Do you have a family member
you can stay with?
‐ Uh, he has me.
Um, he can stay at our house.
I already asked my mom.
Hey.
Hey, it's like she's getting a‐‐
a tiny little glow up,
then she'll be back,
better than ever.
‐ You think this is just gonna be
three days and that's it?
‐ Well‐‐
‐ Lake, I'm a minor.
Which means that social worker,
who's known my mom for thirty minutes,
is in control of our whole lives.
She can petition a judge to keep her here
as long as she wants.
She can remove me from her custody.
‐ Felix, we'll get through this.
‐ No.
No. Not "we."
♪
‐ Hey.
I'm really sorry about last night.
You were excited about your mom,
and I shit all over it.
‐ Thanks.
I think we had a major breakthrough today.
She told me about her lesbian aunt
who had a thing for dachshunds.
‐ Dachshunds?
‐ Uh, it's a long story.
I really do feel like she's changing.
‐ [scoffs] Yeah, well, heard that before.
‐ Well, that apology lasted
all of ten seconds.
‐ Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You're right. And I'm sorry.
Okay? For real.
‐ Okay.
[dinging]
CUSTOMER: Excuse me?
♪ "Brave" by Riley Peace playing ♪
[knocking on door]
‐ Felix, what's going on?
‐ Is your mom here?
PILAR: Mom?
‐ Mrs. Salazar, I'm Alison,
Felix's case worker.
‐ Can, um...
Can I stay here for a couple days?
‐ Of course.
Honey, what's wrong?
‐ ♪ I'm trying... ♪
‐ You can stay here as long as you need.
‐ ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I'm just trying to be brave ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It's the body of water ♪
♪ That splits us right down the middle ♪
♪ And I'll be coming back for you ♪
♪ I'll be coming back for you ♪