PILAR:
Last season on Love, Victor...
VICTOR:
Mom, Dad.
I'm gay,
and I'm with Benji now.
I don't want it to be a secret anymore.
- When did you decide this?
VICTOR:
I didn't decide it. I just am it.
Benji's my boyfriend,
and I'd like you to call him that.
Some guys on my team
don't want me changing.
- You should be around people
who want you to be you.
- Say the word,
and I will ditch these gays
like a corporation after Pride Month.
- Wait, are you and Felix
gonna do it this weekend?
- So on three,
we're gonna drop our towels.
- Benji's had sex before,
and I have no idea what I'm doing.
- Mia, I've waited pretty
much my entire life
to be exactly where I am right now.
- Last night was...
- Yeah, it was.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
ISABEL:
What excuse could you possibly have
for doing that in my house?
- Sex or gay sex?
FELIX:
She's been depressed for a while now.
She barely gets out of bed.
- I think we need to get you some help.
- No.
- He asked you not to say
anything about his mom and now
she's being detained.
- Wait, wait, you're sober?
We tell each other everything.
- I've put up with a ton of your shit.
♪
RAHIM:
Dear Victor. My name is Rahim. I'm gay.
- You're a catch, Rahim.
- Someone has a little crush.
- On Felix? Yeah, right.
FELIX:
Last night was, like, more fun
than I had in, like, forever.
- I can't just pretend that
everything between us is normal
after I kissed you.
FELIX:
Lake and I broke up.
♪
- I'm not giving up on God.
I'm giving up on you.
Thank you for being so patient with me.
- The president of Stamford is retiring,
and he offered me the job.
ANDREW:
Ripping her away from her home.
I don't think she'll ever
come back from that.
MIA:
Let's go see my mom.
- I never really saw you with him anyway.
- Who'd you see me with?
- Someone totally different.
♪ I know that it's hard sometimes ♪
RAHIM: I swear I never meant
to get in between you and Benji.
- I feel like such an idiot.
- I'm not allowed to have a friend?
- I don't think that's all this is.
- Now, imagine all the future things
you wanna do with your boyfriend.
Who do you see?
♪ We'll be making sense of this ♪
♪ Together, we can work it out ♪
- Hi.
♪ This could be the end of it ♪
[door creaks open]
- Hi.
- I-I couldn't let the night end
with you thinking that I moved on.
- Victor, I, uh...
- Did I ever tell you
about the first time that I saw you?
It was my first day at Creekwood,
and you were at the water fountain,
uh, by the teacher's lounge,
looking insanely cool.
♪
And at that moment, I realized
this lie that I've been telling myself
for my whole life just...
went up in smoke.
You changed my life.
I love you, Benji.
It's always been you.
- I love you, too.
CHARLES:
Good god, man.
Benji's mom is always on me
about being more romantic.
I should take lessons from you, Victor.
[laughs]
- Dad, can you get out of here?
- Actually, maybe we can get out of here.
There's, uh, somewhere I wanna take you.
But, you would have to drive.
I-I kind of ran here.
- And he ran here? Go. Have fun.
Take my car.
But not too much fun.
Don't have sex in my car.
I just got it detailed.
♪ "Electric Indigo"
by The Paper Kites playing ♪
- You know, when you said
you were taking me somewhere romantic,
I wasn't really picturing school.
- Yeah, but where exactly
at school are we?
♪ Never meant to
cause you trouble ♪
BENJI: The bench where
we had our first real kiss.
Spring Fling.
♪ But you holding me
with something ♪
♪ Locked behind your eyes ♪
- Can we just...
go back to that perfect moment?
You know, start over?
- Are you sure nothing's
going on with you and Rahim?
- Rahim...
kissed me at the wedding.
And I didn't stop him.
I thought we were friends, and...
things got confused,
but I-I'm not confused now.
I swear.
- Is he a good kisser?
- I feel like I should say no,
so I'm just going to go with no.
[both laugh]
Benji, I'm sorry.
♪
- I'm sorry...
for being such a jerk about your mom.
I... I just-- I hated seeing you get hurt
over and over again,
a-and I wanted to protect you. I just...
didn't know how.
So, I lashed out.
- I'm sorry I didn't fight for us sooner.
I wish we could've just...
talked like this before.
- We wasted so much time.
♪
♪ Somebody to tell me it'll be alright ♪
♪ Somebody to tell me it'll be just fine ♪
♪ If someone has been there before ♪
♪ Say right now,
'cause I just need to hear it ♪
♪
- That's the third time
you've looked out that window tonight.
- Just admiring the window dressings.
Is this raffia?
- You know they are. You picked them out.
Who are you waiting for?
- I thought someone might show up.
Now, I'm not so sure.
- Is this someone a boy?
Why don't you pray?
- That's your answer for everything.
- Or you could look out the window again.
That seems to be working.
- Good night, Maman.
- That's four times.
♪
- Mm! Fun fact.
Did you know your tongue print is
as unique as your fingerprint?
So, you know, you shouldn't go
committing crimes with your tongue.
- How about less fun facts, more kissing?
[knocking]
- Hi, Pilar.
- Felix is waiting for Victor
to get back from the wedding.
That's why he's here.
- Okay. Uh, hey, Felix.
So, we have a little news...
BOTH: You're back together!
- What? How did you--
- It was either that or divorce,
and it'd be really weird to announce
a divorce while holding hands.
♪
ARMANDO: Look at that.
[both giggle]
Yes. Uh, your mother and I,
we really want to make it work.
- I'm sure you have a lot of questions.
- Nope. No questions. I'm happy.
Good job. Congratulations.
- Guys, just bring it in here!
[laughing]
Oh man.
Gosh, I love love.
Oh! And, you know, speaking of love--
- Ah! [laughs] Oh gosh.
It took a second for the emotions
to hit me, but, wow,
we really are a family again.
- Thank you, cariño. Look,
we just want you to know
that we love you so much.
Same, same, same. Go Salazars!
ISABEL: Yay!
- ¡Felicidades!
ISABEL: Oh. If you're hungry, just--
- So, from the way you flung me
clear across the room,
I'm getting that
you don't want them to know.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's just that we've been
together for, like, 10 seconds.
I just want to enjoy the fun
fooling around thing
a little bit longer before we
start telling people about us.
Okay?
- I guess our unique tongue prints
do have some acquainting to do.
[party chatter]
[music playing]
MIA:
Well, this is the address in the emails.
- It's not too late to turn around.
- Nope.
- I, uh, haven't seen
my mom in five years.
I want some answers.
- Then let's get you some answers.
♪
I also really have to pee.
[party chatter]
♪
- Sorry to just show up like this.
- Mia...
Oh my god, I can't believe you're here.
[sighs] I've missed you so much.
[sighs]
Look at you! [laughs]
[laughs]
♪
- Is it me or does champagne
just taste better when it's stolen?
- [laughs] It tastes better
when it's a $400 bottle.
- Hm.
[both laugh]
[insects chirping]
[wakes up phone]
- Still nothing from Felix?
[sleeps phone]
- Nope. [sighs]
I think it's really over with us.
- You sad?
- Yeah.
But, not in an Olivia Rodrigo
write-a-whole-album-wishing-
I-could-castrate-him kind of way.
[laughs]
I'm really glad I met Felix.
He helped me stop caring about
what other people think.
Were you sad
when you broke up with Andrew?
- Yes,
but mostly 'cause I left
my favorite hoodie at his house.
But, actually...
Dating him helped me
figure out some stuff, too.
- What kind of stuff?
♪
[door opens]
- Oh, shit. We got to go.
- Oh, uh, your parents?
- Oh my god,
I wish my house was this nice.
- Wait, Lucy, whose house is this?
- I don't know.
There was a for sale sign out front.
I thought it was empty.
- Oh my god.
- We got to go. We got to go!
[both laugh]
MAN:
Somebody there? Hello?
♪ "Silver Velvet" by
The Courtneys playing ♪
♪ The day is getting shady ♪
♪ Playing in the isle ♪
♪ There's nothing
in this life to do ♪
♪ But stay here for a while ♪
♪ The day is getting shady ♪
♪ Playing in the isle... ♪
- You know, my family's going up
to Aspen for the winter break.
Is there any chance
you'd like to come with?
- To Aspen?
I-I don't know how to ski.
- Oh, you'll pick it up.
Or you'll look cute
falling on your butt.
- Oh, okay!
[laughter]
- Now, hold on a sec.
[siren chirps]
- Think there's an accident?
OFFICER:
License and registration, please.
Have anything to drink tonight?
♪
It's a DUI checkpoint.
- Okay, so?
It's not like you've been drinking.
Benji?
♪
- So, before you came over,
I was upset.
Just a few drinks,
and I know I shouldn't have driven,
but my dad was standing right there,
and I just...
I-I didn't know what to do,
you know? So, I...
- Switch with me.
You just got your license back.
Put the car in park
and switch with me, Benji.
[seatbelts clicking]
Nobody saw. Everything's gonna be okay.
[police radio chatter]
[quiet street chatter]
- Carrot cake sans raisin.
Sans cake.
Just frosting.
- That's how I like it. [laughs]
- Mm. Mm.
- Okay, my parents are in the next room.
Could you kiss a little quieter?
- Alternative solution.
Why don't we just tell your parents?
Pilar, they've been really good to me.
They took me in when my mom
was going through all that stuff.
I just-- I don't feel great lying to them.
- After the first few times,
you get used to it.
- Don't you think they'd be happy for us?
- Can we slow down? I mean,
we haven't even gone on a date.
We just kissed.
- Oh, who did you kiss?
- What? No one. Who did you kiss?
- Pilar, come on.
I just heard you say you kissed someone.
Pilar:
I was reading a text.
- Honey! It's okay.
You can tell me if there's
someone special in your life.
♪
- There's nobody. I promise.
- Uh, yeah, I, uh--
You know, I think I should go.
I don't know when,
um, uh, Victor's coming home.
So, that's...
Um...
Yeah, that's-- I mean,
that's the reason why I came here, right?
[door opens, shuts]
- Such a sweet boy.
What the heck happened to my cake?
- [sighs] You don't think that
house had cameras, do you?
- Oh, Lucy, don't even joke.
I can't go to prison for this.
All that overhead lighting.
So unflattering.
[laughs]
- Hey, uh, do you think I could
borrow something to wear?
This uniform smells like shrimp cocktail
and minimum wage.
- [laughs] Yeah, sure. Help yourself.
You know, you never did tell me how you
ended up cater-waitering Harold's wedding.
- I pick up a lot of jobs.
I'm trying to save up as much as I can
so I can get out of here
as soon as humanly possible.
♪
- Um, you don't like Creekwood?
You know, if you're not happy
living in a town
with two Lululemons,
I don't know what to tell you.
- Three. They, uh, just turned
the animal shelter into one.
- Oh!
- I just feel like I'm kinda
stuck here. Like...
I'm waiting for my real life to start.
You probably don't know what that's like.
I mean, high school is always amazing
for the popular, pretty girls.
- Uh, I-I'm okay.
But you are, like, next-level gorge
and way cooler than I am.
Like "Twilight"-era Kristen Stewart,
but capable of smiling.
[giggles]
- Yeah, but you have, like,
the perfect hair,
and the perfect clothes,
and the perfect body.
- Uh, I'm hardly perfect. Um...
My right boob's a tiny bit
smaller than the left.
- Perfect to me.
♪
Um...
I...
thought I heard my phone.
Um...
Still no word from Felix.
- Oh, that's too bad.
You know, it's kind of late. Um...
I think I'm going to go. Uh...
Can I get this back to you another time?
- Yeah. Whenever you want.
- Okay.
- Bye.
[door opens, shuts]
[party chatter, cheering]
NAOMI:
I swear, I woke up this morning,
and I just knew something good
was gonna happen.
The universe brought you here.
- [laughs]
Actually, one of your emails did.
'Cause you mentioned
that you were crashing
with your friend Layla
in Savannah?
[laughs]
- Only since I've been back in the States.
- Oh yeah. You were in Ghana, right?
For a-a sculpture installation?
That's so cool.
- Well, Ghana is a marvel. Have you been?
- Um, not--
- To Ghana?
Oh, she's been meaning to,
and then she remembered
she's in high school.
[nervous laughter]
- Let's not talk about high school.
That's boring.
- I still can't believe you
ended up with Andrew Spencer.
Remember when he used to
chase you around on his scooter?
[laughing]
Oh! And he had the chunkiest cheeks!
Oh, Layla, honey.
Can you get over
how absolutely
breathtaking my daughter is?
- It's good to see you, baby.
Your mom talks about you all the time.
- Uh, guilty.
I'm very, very proud of you.
LAYLA:
There are two guys back there,
and one keeps talking about you--
- [quietly]
But, like, what is she proud of?
She doesn't know anything about you.
- Wait, wait. No, I know things.
♪ party music continues ♪
I-I get bits and pieces
from your dad's posts,
like your sophomore art show.
Those lightbox portraits.
They were gallery-ready. Hm.
I just... I wish I could have
seen them in the flesh.
- I mean, you could have.
It was a high school art show.
I can't imagine tickets
were very hard to come by.
- Andrew, it's fine. It's fine.
It's fine.
- I should have been there.
And I wasn't.
Uh...
Could you, uh, excuse me for a moment?
♪
- What the hell was that?
[sighs]
VICTOR:
Benji...
Look, it's okay. They waved us
right through the checkpoint.
- But what if they saw us switching seats?
I don't understand how you're
being so nice about this.
- Because...
I love you.
You drank. You slipped up.
But, you'll call your sponsor tomorrow,
and, and you'll start over.
- Hey, guys. Sorry to interrupt.
I just have an early morning,
so I want to get my keys back before bed.
♪
[keys jingling]
Why does Victor have my keys?
- Uh...
I-I never drove a Range Rover before,
so Benji let me drive it
for the last few blocks.
- Pretty sweet ride, right?
- [laughs] Yeah.
- Good night, guys.
VICTOR: Good night.
- Wait. Dad.
[sighs] I can't do this.
- What is it, Benji?
- I have to tell my parents.
I think you should go.
♪
- Hey, man. What are you doing?
- Hey! Waiting for you to get home.
- And annoying Mrs. Loo in 202?
Sorry. Things with Benji went
a little longer than expected.
- Yeah, they did.
- [laughs] No, not...
Not like that.
Benji's...
He's going through some, uh,
pretty intense personal stuff
that I can't really talk about right now.
- Okay.
- But, uh, [sighs] what about you?
Did you end up getting with my sister?
I tried to sound supportive.
[laughs]
- No, it's fine. Not yet. You know...
Everything with Pilar was great, but...
she got weird about your parents knowing.
- Hm.
- That was an ominous "hm."
Do your parents not like me?
Is my Salazar family crush unrequited?
- [laughs] No. My family loves you.
It-it's just that if they find out
that you're seeing Pilar, they might...
love you less.
- What? Why?
- Well, they're very protective over her.
Like. when she had
a boyfriend back in Texas,
my dad took her door off her bedroom.
- Okay, that is a little bit psycho.
- Listen, man, Latino dads
and their daughters, it's a real thing.
So,
maybe just let Pilar lead
the way on this one for a little while.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Hey, and whatever mystery thing's
going on with Benji,
you guys are gonna get through it.
If you're half as good at kissing
as your sister--
- Dude!
- I regretted that as soon as I said it.
[party chatter, cheering]
♪ "Shining All Night"
by Alex Nova playing ♪
♪ I don't need the... ♪
[door shuts, music muffled]
MIA: Hey.
Um, sorry about Andrew.
- Oh, I get it.
I'd be wary of me, too.
- Um... So, my dad got remarried today.
- And how do we feel about her?
Veronica, right?
- It took a minute,
uh, but she's actually pretty great.
It's my dad who I'm struggling
with right now.
He just got offered a new job.
He wants to move us across the country,
and he doesn't care at all what I want.
- Sounds familiar.
[sighs]
- Is that why you left?
I've only ever heard his side.
- When you were 4 or 5,
I got an offer to show
in this tiny gallery in Paris.
Nothing prestigious, but...
it meant something to me.
I'll never forget the look on his face
when I said I wanted us to go to Paris.
Like I was a stupid child,
living in a dream world.
- So, that's why you left?
Because he wouldn't go to Paris with you?
- No, no, of course not.
♪
Don't you understand?
I was losing myself in that house.
- What about me?
- I-I don't know what to say.
It was selfish.
And horrible.
And the worst thing I've ever done.
But...
I am not the person I was when I left.
And I would do anything
to have you in my life again, so...
tell me what I can do.
- You could move to Creekwood.
- What?
I mean, if you were there,
then I wouldn't have to move.
- Oh.
- And we could...
maybe work on our relationship.
And maybe, um...
I don't know. Try to...
heal? [laughs]
[sighs]
- I love that idea.
But I'm supposed to go to Prague
in a few weeks.
I accepted a residency at a gallery there.
♪
But, it's only for a few months.
So, maybe after that?
I-I think after that would work great.
- This was a mistake.
- Mia.
- I don't know why I thought
it would be different.
Can you take me home?
- Okay.
♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Oh, oh... ♪
[praying in Arabic]
[repeats prayer]
♪ "chance with you"
by mehro playing ♪
♪ Oh, I've heard all about you ♪
♪ All those things they had to say ♪
♪ You're a legend 'round this school ♪
♪ Locally famous drama queen ♪
♪ Turn my eyes, I see you stare ♪
♪ 'Cross the room and right at me ♪
♪ Now, you're smiling like you've got ♪
♪ Like you've got something on your mind ♪
♪ You're so beautiful ♪
♪ I don't want to turn away ♪
♪ You've been here before ♪
[sends text]
♪ Make me feel like you're a... ♪
♪ If I could go back in time ♪
♪ I'd shoot my shot ♪
[sends text]
♪ Just so I could have a chance ♪
♪ With you... ♪
SHIRIN:
Morning.
I saw your tasbih on your dresser.
Was somebody praying last night?
- Yes, Maman. But...
I don't think it worked.
Pretty sure you're not supposed
to pray for a boy to show up.
Isn't that, like, a big Muslim no-no?
- When I was pregnant,
I prayed every day for a boy to show up,
and God delivered
the greatest gift of my life.
Your brother Nasser.
- Okay.
- Rahim.
I know it may not
feel this way right now,
but I believe God has a plan for you.
And that plan includes
someone who will love you
with all his heart.
So, it is written.
♪
- It is written.
[doorbell rings]
- It's open!
Lucy! Long time no see.
- I just wanted to give you this.
- Oh.
- I washed it.
Actually, I didn't,
but I did spritz it with Febreze.
- Right. Okay, well, you...
didn't have to do that, but thanks.
I had a lot of fun last night. Um...
Sorry if I kind of killed
the vibe at the end.
- We don't have to talk about.
- No, no, I want to. Um...
I think I just got scared.
Not because I didn't want it
to happen, but...
because I did.
- Oh.
- Yeah. Oh.
♪ "Treat Me Like Fire"
by Lion Babe playing ♪
- So, what now?
♪ Treat me like ♪
♪ Treat me like... fire ♪
Holy shit.
[laughs]
♪ Fire, fire ♪
♪ Into the pain, into the pain ♪
♪ Into the pain ♪
♪ Into the pain... ♪
[knocking]
- Hey. Hey, don't worry.
I told your parents
that I was helping
your dad move back in today,
so now I get to lug
heavy boxes up the stairs.
- Hey, I'm sorry about last night.
- There's nothing--
There's nothing to be sorry about.
I ended up talking to Victor.
Why didn't you tell me
your dad's protective of you?
- Because it's humiliating.
I mean, the whole time I've known you,
I've been Victor's baby sister,
and I didn't want you to see me
as some little girl
whose dad watches over her like a hawk.
- I don't see that way.
Okay, I see you as a super-smart,
bad-ass, model-gorgeous neighbor
whose father would murder me
if he knew the thoughts running
through my head right now.
♪
- What kind of thoughts?
- Trust me, we're not there yet.
♪ Ooh ooh... ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh... ♪
♪ Oh oh... ♪
- Sweetheart.
Thank God. I was, uh,
I was worried about you.
Listen, um...
I handled things terribly.
I should have been able--
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh... ♪
We are going to figure this out.
Okay?
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh... ♪
[birds chirping]
- You, uh,
weren't responding to my texts,
so I just-- I got worried.
- Well, my parents took my phone away.
- Do we need to get you a burner?
L-like in the spy movies?
We could hide it under a floorboard.
- Victor, I'm...
I'm going to rehab.
- What?
- Yeah, my...
My dad set it up this morning.
It's an in-patient program.
- Wait, rehab?
This is crazy.
- Actually, it's...
It's not.
- You had a slipup. You drank one time
in a year.
- It wasn't just one time.
♪
I've been drinking sometimes.
- When?
- Before a big test.
After a fight with my parents.
The night I came over your house
and yelled at your mom.
Look, I've been running away from it,
just wanting it to go away,
but it-it won't.
And then, last night,
I lied to you.
I drove. I put you in danger.
Look, Victor, if you and I are gonna have
any real chance of working out,
then I have to figure this out.
And I have to do it alone.
Okay? So, that means three weeks,
no emails, no phone.
I think it's going to be
really good for me.
♪ "Can We Work It Out"
by Gordi playing ♪
- What do I tell people
when they ask where you are?
- I mean, I don't want
the whole world knowing, but...
you can tell anyone that you really trust.
- And what happens after three weeks?
- I'm not sure.
♪ I'm tired ♪
♪ Of just hiding away ♪
♪ Wrestling my ♪
♪ Instincts to keep it at bay ♪
♪ 'Cause forgetting you is
like ignoring the weather ♪
♪ Or wanting you ♪
♪ Takes as long as forever ♪
♪ And I don't know ♪
♪ How much longer I can keep it inside ♪
♪ Can we work it out? ♪
♪ 'Cause every fiber
of my being's agreed ♪
♪ That what you want can
become something you need ♪
♪ Can we work it out? ♪
♪ Go on ♪
♪ And get out of my head... ♪