♪
‐ Hey, can I talk to you for a‐‐
Oh...
Hey.
‐ Hey.
‐ What's up?
‐ Uh, can you go to Mia's
dad's wedding with me?
‐ Aw! That's sweet of you to ask.
Hard pass.
‐ What? Why?
‐ Let's see, all of your friends
are painfully boring,
and I couldn't pick Mia's dad and Veronica
out of a line‐up of old people.
‐ Pilar, please. I feel really bad
for showing up solo last second.
Why don't you bring Rahim?
He loves all that cheesy romantic crap,
he's always trying to start a conga line,
and he has fancy blazer napkins
for every suit he owns.
‐ Do you not know the term
"pocket square"?
‐ I'm just saying,
you two would have fun together.
‐ I mean, there's like,
it's like zero pressure, but,
w‐would you wanna go?
‐ Are you sure Benji'd be cool with it?
‐ Honestly, Benji kind of lost his right
to an opinion
when he bailed on me last second.
And besides, we're friends.
Why wouldn't he be cool with it?
‐ Yeah. Okay. Yes.
I would love to go with you.
‐ All right. Cool. Felix is meeting us
here around three o'clock.
‐ See you then.
‐ All right. See you then.
‐ ♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be all right ♪
♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be just fine ♪
♪ If someone has been there before,
say it right now ♪
♪ 'Cause I just need to hear it ♪
♪
‐ Well, I'm off to show my new listing.
The house was the site
of a pretty grisly murder.
I'm trying to distract with my cleavage.
‐ I would totally buy a
murder house from you.
‐ Aw! I'll see you at my place tonight?
‐ Yeah.
‐ I'm making fried chicken,
so have a light lunch.
And wear some loose pants.
‐ I'll be there.
‐ Mmm.
[knocking on door]
ISABEL:
Oh. Hi.
‐ Hi. I'm‐‐
‐ Shelby. Right?
‐ Isa. Uh, what are you doing here?
‐ Sorry. I just‐‐ I need to talk
and you're not answering my texts.
‐ Isn't he the absolute worst
with texting? [laughs]
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ All right, well, I was just
heading out, so, um...
It's nice to meet you, Isabel.
‐ You, too.
[door closes]
‐ You want a donut, or‐‐
‐ I'm sorry. I didn't know she'd be here.
I just... I'm worried about Victor.
He's barely left his room since
his "break" with Benji.
Which I know was at least
partially my fault.
I was pretty horrible to that boy.
‐ Well...
It's never too late to be un‐horrible.
‐ Yeah. Maybe you're right.
But it's not just Benji.
When Victor saw you with Shelby...
‐ Yeah, I know.
I, I could tell it really got to him.
‐ Mando, we've been separated
for six months.
And you're seeing another woman. It's‐‐
I believe we can save our marriage.
I want to save our marriage.
But if you don't,
then it's time to start this new chapter
in our lives.
This living in between is just...
it's too hard on the kids.
It's too hard on me.
It's time for you to decide
what you want to do.
‐ I know. You're right.
‐ Thanks for the donut.
[door opens, then closes]
[doorbell rings]
‐ Hi, sweetheart.
‐ Hi, Mom.
‐ Hi.
‐ Welcome home.
‐ Oh...
‐ I missed you.
I swear to you,
this woman truly believed
that she was the lost sister
of the Queen of England.
And when people would pass by her,
they would have to curtsy,
or she would just lose it.
[laughs]
‐ It seems like you're doing good, Mom.
‐ I feel good.
I mean, not that there weren't
tough days, but...
when it would get hard, I would just...
[sighs]
close my eyes, I would take a deep breath,
and I would think about all the things
that I would miss
if I didn't get my shit together.
Like having brunch with you...
Seeing you graduate.
Seeing you get married.
And that made it
clear as day what I needed to do.
So I would drag my ass out of bed,
I would take my new meds...
I would curse that place for not allowing
me to have Swedish Fish,
because, like... [scoffs]
And then I would go to therapy.
‐ You know, Mom,
I can bail on the wedding.
‐ No. No, you should go,
and I don't think that Lake would
take kindly to you standing her up.
[laughs]
‐ Yeah, um...
I was gonna tell you about that
once, uh, you got back up on your feet.
Um, Lake and I broke up.
‐ Oh, Felix, I'm so sorry.
What happened?
‐ She betrayed my trust.
I mean, she told her mom
about our situation.
‐ I understand why you feel betrayed.
But I want you to know that
whatever happens between you
and Lake in the future,
I will forever be grateful to her.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ She risked your relationship to make
sure that I got the help that I needed.
And I think that that makes her
pretty special.
Plus, that girl looks great in a crop top.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Okay, so which one of these says,
"Lake Meriwether is single
and ready to mingle?"
[laughs]
Who am I kidding? It's the jumpsuit.
It's always the jumpsuit.
‐ Look, I'm so glad that you are
ready to mingle,
but I only invited like
four people to this wedding,
and they're either gay,
my boyfriend or your ex‐boyfriend.
[door opens]
HAROLD: Morning, ladies.
‐ Good morning.
‐ Dad! Isn't the groom not
supposed to see the bride
before the wedding?
‐ Ah, well...
‐ I think when the bride
is hugely pregnant,
all the traditional rules
kind of go out the window.
WOMAN: Excuse me, Mr. Brooks?
‐ Oh. Excuse me, ladies.
VERONICA: Hi!
HAROLD: Hey.
‐ Uh...
This is for you.
‐ Mia!
Oh, it's beautiful!
‐ Yeah, it was my grandmother's.
And I know she would have loved you.
Except for you being knocked up.
And white.
Yeah, actually,
she probably would've hated you.
[both laugh]
But I‐‐ I like you,
and I, I thought it
could be your something old.
‐ I love it.
‐ I'm really glad we're gonna be a family.
[laughs]
‐ Oh.
Um...
I'm sorry. Harold...
‐ Yeah.
‐ I'm sorry, we can't‐‐
‐ I know. I know.
‐ Guys, what's going on?
‐ Hey, uh, sweetheart, listen, um...
[exhales sharply]
I'm gonna go ahead
and take the job at Stanford.
‐ What? I thought you turned it down.
HAROLD:
I know, but you know what, sweetheart?
I realized it's too big of an opportunity.
Now, I was gonna tell you.
I just...
wanted today to be perfect for all of us.
‐ Okay.
‐ Hey, Mia, come on. Look, let's just
talk about this for a second. Okay?
‐ I mean, there's nothing to talk about.
And I'm so stupid for thinking
that there ever was.
[knocking on door]
‐ Oh, hey.
‐ Hi.
‐ Uh, I'll tell Victor you're here.
Victor, Felix is here!
‐ So, uh, my mom, she got out
of the hospital this morning.
Yeah, she's doing really good.
‐ That's awesome.
‐ Yeah, you know,
I didn't, uh, really know what to expect.
Part of me was scared she'd be on
a ton of meds
and a completely different person.
But, uh, then I saw her‐‐
‐ Felix. I can't do this.
I'm really glad that
your mom is doing better,
but I can't just pretend that
everything between us is normal
after I kissed you.
‐ Okay.
‐ I like you. And you don't like me back.
Which is fine.
But I think it's best if you go back to
being Victor's nerdy best friend.
And I go back to being his moody sister.
And we'll say "hi" sometimes
when we see each other at school,
or when we're taking out the trash
or whatever. But that's it.
VICTOR:
Hey!
You okay?
‐ I'm, I'm good. Yeah, but...
Not as good as you. I mean the‐‐
the tie, the hair, the face.
I mean, hot damn potato chip!
[laughs]
RAHIM: Knock, knock.
FELIX:
Good God, you two.
Give the rest of us a chance.
‐ You do look really good.
‐ You clean up pretty well yourself,
Salazar.
‐ Okay, if someone doesn't give me
a compliment about how I look,
I'm not going.
[both chuckle]
‐ Come on. We've got a wedding to get to.
You look great.
♪ cello music playing ♪
[indistinct chatter]
‐ Don't worry. We'll figure this out.
‐ No, we won't.
But thank you for saying that.
CATER WAITER:
Sparkling lemonade?
LAKE:
Lucy.
Hey! I didn't know you'd be here.
‐ I'm not a guest. I'm a cater waiter.
Hence the super cool bow tie.
‐ Well, you are rocking the hell
out of that bow tie.
[distant chattering]
Oh, God. There's Felix.
He looks super cute in that little vest.
‐ I thought you guys broke up.
‐ No, we did.
I might not be as single and
ready to mingle as I'm pretending to be.
‐ If my boss asks, you're thirty‐four.
[laughs]
‐ Is this seat taken?
‐ No. No, you, you look, uh, beautiful.
‐ Thank you.
Where's Benji?
‐ Victor and Benji are on a break.
‐ Wow, Victor wasted no time at all.
‐ They're just friends.
‐ Please. "Just friends" is for two fives.
Not a pair of nines.
♪
HAROLD
I vow to always be your best friend.
I vow to always put your happiness first,
and my ambitions second.
VERONICA
I know there will be tough days.
It's on those days that
I vow to love you the hardest.
HAROLD:
I vow to always remember
that we are worth fighting for.
Forever. No matter what.
VERONICA:
No matter what.
♪ upbeat music plays over speakers ♪
[door closes]
ISABEL: Hi.
I think it's about time
you and I had a little talk.
‐ So, to what do I owe the pleasure?
‐ Uh, actually,
I wanted to bring you something.
[chuckles]
‐ A Tupperware of some chicken?
‐ It's my pollo guisado.
It's what we were supposed to have
for dinner that night
before the first day of school.
‐ I remember.
‐ I am sorry that I ruined that night.
I'm sorry for a lot of things, Benji.
But most of all,
I am sorry if I'm the cause of problems
between you and Victor.
‐ Mmm. Thank you for saying that.
‐ Please don't let me be the reason
that it doesn't work out between you two.
‐ [sighs] Okay‐‐
I appreciate you coming here.
But our problems are bigger than just you.
Too big for a couple of sixteen‐year‐olds,
that's for sure.
‐ Hey.
All relationships have problems,
whether you're sixteen or forty‐‐
Thirty‐nine.
What matters is how hard
you're willing to work at it.
How much of yourself you're willing
to put into it.
And I've never seen Victor
put more of himself into anything.
He even stood up to me.
For the first time in his life.
And we all know that Victor is the world's
biggest mama's boy. [laughs]
But he put our whole relationship
on the line to defend you.
That's how much he loves you.
Anyway, I just needed you
to know all of that.
Oh. Reheat that at 350 for twenty minutes.
Don't you dare put it in the microwave.
VICTOR:
Oh. I don't know if this is for me.
It looks so... creamy.
‐ I know, but YOLO. On three.
One, two, three.
‐ Clink!
[gulps]
VICTOR: Oh, my God.
‐ Yeah, I don't like that. Mmm‐mmm.
‐ I don't see the appeal.
But they're really expensive,
so we should probably have some more.
‐ [laughs] No.
‐ Thank you for inviting me.
I'm having a great time.
‐ Me, too.
‐ You know, you could always live with me.
House is pretty big,
you're pretty small...
‐ Hey, kids. Do you mind if I cut in?
ANDREW: No.
‐ Thanks.
[awkward chuckle]
‐ I can't do this.
‐ Hey, Mia, please. Just wait‐‐
[sighs]
She'll come around.
‐ Mr. Brooks.
Listen, you don't know this,
but I have always
respected the hell out of you.
Your drive, your success, the way
your suits always fit just right.
When I was younger,
I'd always think, "Man,
I want a big, impressive life,
like Harold Brooks."
‐ I appreciate that.
‐ But when Mia told me today what you did,
for the first time ever,
I lost some respect for you.
‐ Well, I'm very sorry to hear that.
‐ Harold, you and I both know
that Mia never fully recovered
from her mother leaving.
It is a miracle that she is the strong,
happy person that she is today.
But you doing this,
ripping her away from her home,
from her friends, from me...
I don't think she'll ever
come back from that.
All right? And that'll be on you.
[phone jingling]
‐ Hi.
‐ Hey.
I just wanted to tell you that
I stopped by Brasstown earlier.
‐ Oh, yeah?
‐ Yeah.
And I did my best
to be un‐horrible to Benji.
It wasn't easy and I don't know
if anything will come of it,
but at least I know I tried.
‐ Wow, Isa. That's... that's great.
[chuckles]
Well, if you'd have told me
a few months ago
that my wife would be trying to get
Victor back with a boy,
I, I wouldn't have believed it.
‐ [laughs] Yeah. Me, neither.
Well, I am going to celebrate my big
mama bear moment
with a glass of wine and a scoop of‐‐
‐ Chubby Hubby?
We both know you mean two scoops.
‐ Yeah, but the second one is‐‐
BOTH: So small it doesn't count.
[chuckles softly]
‐ Uh, anyway, I better get going.
‐ Yeah, I should let you go.
‐ Goodnight.
‐ Bye.
[phone beeps]
‐ Guess who got two offers
on the murder house?
‐ Yeah, you did!
[both laughing]
BOTH:
Mwah!
‐ Well, come on. I got a drumstick
with your name on it.
I know you like legs.
♪ "All My Life" by K‐Ci and JoJo playing ♪
‐ ♪ Ooh ♪
‐ Hi. Have any more champagne?
Could use a little liquid courage.
‐ That jumpsuit is all
the courage you need.
‐ ♪ I'm so glad ♪
♪ I will never find another lover ♪
‐ Hey. Wanna dance?
‐ ♪ Sweeter than you,
Sweeter than you ♪
‐ I'd love to.
‐ ♪ And I will never find another lover ♪
♪ More precious than you ♪
‐ I love this song.
[Victor laughs]
R&B from before I was born is my jam.
[laughs]
‐ Well, uh...
Do you wanna dance?
‐ ♪ You are the only one,
You're my everything ♪
♪ And for you this song I sing ♪
[both stammering]
‐ You go waist.
‐ Okay.
‐ ♪ I prayed for someone like you ♪
‐ I don't think I've ever actually
slow danced with a guy before.
‐ Oh, I definitely haven't.
‐ ♪ That I,
That I finally found you ♪
‐ Lake, there's, um...
There's something I should've
told you by now.
Thank you.
For giving me back my mom.
And I will never forget
what you did for me.
Even if I'm around at 100,
I'd still hobble about and tell people,
[imitating old man voice]:
"Lake Meriwether got my mom
the help she needed."
‐ Well, I like your old man voice.
‐ Mmm.
‐ What's in your pocket?
‐ Oh.
‐ ♪ You're all I'm thinking of,
I praise the Lord above ♪
♪ For sending me your love,
I cherish every hug ♪
♪ I really love you ♪
LAKE:
Okay. [laughs]
‐ ♪ All my life ♪
♪ I prayed for someone like you ♪
♪ And I thank God that I ♪
‐ Will you excuse me a minute?
‐ Oh.
‐ ♪ All my life ♪
♪ I prayed for someone like you ♪
‐ Sure.
‐ ♪ Yes I pray that you ♪
♪ Do love me too ♪
♪ All my life ♪
♪ I prayed for someone like you ♪
♪ And I thank God that I ♪
VICTOR: I need, I need to‐‐
One second.
‐ ♪ That I finally found you ♪
‐ Benji‐‐
‐ ♪ All my life... ♪
‐ Benji. Benji, wait.
‐ Wow.
I can't believe this.
‐ We're just friends.
‐ Okay, Victor.
I feel like such an idiot.
‐ Benji‐‐
That was crazy.
I'm not allowed to have a friend?
‐ I don't think that's all this is.
And I think you agree with me.
♪ "Infinity" by Fancy Hagood playing ♪
Victor, I like you.
The past few hours have been incredible.
The day we skipped school together
was incredible. You...
You're incredible.
I swear, I never meant to get
in between you and Benji.
But when we're together,
it feels like magic.
I can't stop smiling
when you're around me.
Even when we're just walking next to
each other not saying anything.
I've never felt more connected
to someone in my entire life.
‐ ♪ So wild inside ♪
♪ Let's go and never stop ♪
♪ Your clothes, take 'em off ♪
‐ I'm gonna go.
Let you figure out your shit.
But if you feel the same way I do,
you know where I live.
‐ ♪ Let's go and never stop ♪
♪ I don't know what's got into me ♪
♪ But I want it for infinity ♪
♪
[distant laughter]
‐ Aah!
‐ Oh, sh‐‐
‐ What are you doing in here?
‐ I am having a low‐key panic attack.
Lake is down there and she
wants to get back together,
and I might like someone else.
‐ What?
Who?
‐ Your sister. She kinda kissed me
the other day.
‐ What?
‐ Okay, first of all,
are you gonna hit me?
Please not the stomach, all right?
I ate a lot of oysters‐‐
‐ Felix.
I'm not gonna hit you.
[relieved sigh]
‐ I, I didn't know
it was gonna happen, either.
But we have the best time together,
and she is really hot.
‐ Okay, I'm being really cool right now.
Don't push me.
‐ Won't happen again.
[sighs] That being said,
Lake is Lake.
She's the first girl I ever loved.
‐ Wait, what's your deal?
‐ Actually, it's weirdly similar.
‐ You kissed your sister?
‐ No!
Benji just showed up,
and he wanted to get back together.
Which is all I've wanted
since we started fighting.
But then...
Rahim told me that he likes me.
And he kissed me.
And I can't pretend
I didn't feel something.
[exhales]
So what do we do?
‐ Close your eyes.
‐ What?
‐ It's something my mom did
in the psych ward.
Now imagine all the future things
you wanna do with your boyfriend.
Go to prom together.
Do the long distance thing
in college and...
fumble around awkwardly
with FaceTime sex.
But then you beat the odds.
You actually wind up together.
Who do you see?
Is there one person...
where it would kill you if you didn't
do those things with?
‐ Actually... yeah.
Yeah, there is.
‐ Me, too.
Way to go, Mom.
[laughs]
♪ "Time After Time" by Sam Smith playing ♪
‐ ♪ Lying in my bed ♪
♪ I hear the clock tick
and I think of you ♪
♪ Caught up in circles ♪
♪ Confusion is nothing new ♪
♪ Flash back, warm nights ♪
♪ Time after ♪
♪ Sometimes you picture me ♪
FELIX:
You remembered...
That my mom couldn't
have those at the hospital.
‐ It's not that big of a deal.
I got them for her a while back.
I just figured even though
we're not friends anymore,
it doesn't mean the woman
shouldn't get her chewy fish.
‐ Pilar...
I don't want to be friends, either.
‐ Um, okay.
It's kind of rude and unnecessary
to say, but‐‐
‐ ♪ If you're lost you can look
and you will find me ♪
♪ Time after time ♪
♪ If you fall, I will catch you,
I'll be waiting ♪
♪ Time after time ♪
[bottles clink]
‐ Hey.
How'd it go with Felix?
‐ Not amazing.
Yeah, he sort of just...
disappeared.
‐ I'm really sorry.
For what it's worth, I never really
saw you with him, anyway.
‐ Really? Who do you see me with?
‐ Someone totally different.
‐ ♪ You're wondering if I'm okay ♪
‐ You know, I'm just about done here.
Would you wanna go hang out?
‐ ♪ And the drum beats out of time ♪
[laughs]
♪ If you're lost you can look
and you will find me ♪
♪ Time after time ♪
♪ If you fall, I will catch you,
I'll be waiting ♪
♪ Time after time ♪
‐ Mia. Sweetheart.
I want to talk to you about Stanford.
I, uh...
[scoffs] I think I made a big mistake.
‐ ♪ If you fall, I will catch you,
I'll be waiting ♪
♪ Time after time ♪
‐ You sure you wanna do this?
‐ Yep.
Let's go see my mom.
‐ ♪ If you're lost you can look
and you will find me ♪
♪ Time after time ♪
[knocking on door]
♪ If you fall, I will catch you,
I'll be waiting ♪
♪ Time after time ♪
‐ Mando, what are you doing here?
‐ Hey.
I, uh... I brought hot fudge.
‐ ♪ And I fall behind ♪
‐ You still have some of that ice cream?
‐ Oh. Um...
‐ ♪ And you will find me ♪
♪ Time after time ♪
♪ If you fall, I will catch you,
I will be waiting ♪
♪ Time after time ♪
[phone jingling]
♪ Mmm ♪
‐ Simon. Hey.
‐ Victor. Hey.
Hey, I'm so sorry.
Things have been crazy with finals,
and, um, I totally missed your DM,
but catch me up.
‐ Actually, I‐‐ I think I'm good.
‐ You're good?
‐ Yeah. Uh, I spoke to Felix about it,
and he helped me figure it out.
‐ Well, that's great.
‐ Yeah, it is. It's crazy.
When I first reached out to you, I‐‐
I didn't have anyone to talk to.
And now I have all of these people,
because everyone important in my life
knows that I'm gay.
You have been so amazing to me.
But I think that...
I'm ready to figure out this next chapter
of my life without you.
‐ Wow.
I think you're ready, too.
Don't be a stranger though, okay?
‐ I won't. And Simon...
Thank you for everything.
‐ Good luck out there, Victor.
[phone beeps]
♪ "I Want Love" by Gryffin & Two Feet ♪
[doorbell rings]
‐ Hi.
‐ ♪ I feel okay ♪
♪ Talk to her face about it ♪
♪ I act insane every day ♪
♪ Every day ♪
♪ Don't go that way ♪
♪ My mind will break and shatter ♪