[bell rings]
[students chattering]
♪
‐ Must be nice.
Not having to wake up at 5 a. m.
to practice with those homophobic morons.
‐ They're not all morons.
‐ Yo, what's up, my bromos?
Listen, I'm so glad we got to
hang out last weekend.
Loved the cabin, by the way, Benji.
Such a warm color palette.
Oh, and that fireplace nook
was positively dreamy.
I watched Queer Eye,
so I know what's good.
‐ Andrew, why are you being so weird?
‐ I'm just trying to show you
that I am a queer ally.
Or is a straight ally?
Look, point is, I'm an ally.
All right, what happened
with the team was messed up.
Yes, but whenever you're ready,
we want you back.
‐ Okay. Uh, what about the guys
that didn't want me to shower with them?
‐ Oh. Um, that‐‐ see‐‐
‐ You want me back on the team
for the first game of the season
because you know
you're screwed without me.
Good luck.
‐ Yeah.
♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be all right ♪
it'll be just fine ♪
♪ If someone has been there before,
say it right now ♪
♪ 'Cause I just need to hear it ♪
♪
[bell rings]
‐ Hey, did you ever think that
maybe this is for the best?
I mean, you started basketball
because your dad loves it, right?
‐ Yeah. Maybe you're right.
Maybe I just played basketball
because it seemed like something
a straight kid would like to do.
‐ Exactly.
Screw basketball.
‐ Yeah, screw basketball!
[Victor and Mia laugh]
Sorry. I just wanted to fit in.
‐ Well, hi. [laughs]
‐ Hi.
Uh, are we still going to Benji's
friends and family concert after school?
‐ Yes. Been working with the new band
on some music,
and we need brutally honest feedback.
‐ Ah. So tell you you're great,
even if you suck.
‐ Pretty much.
[Victor chuckles]
♪
‐ Is it just me,
or is the Hundred Years' War
just, like, really, really sensual?
‐ I know you're trying to distract me,
and I am immune to your
feminine wiles.
‐ Even if I ask you to ravage me,
like the Black Death ravaged Europe
in 1348?
‐ Dammit. You know I can't resist
historically accurate dirty talk.
GEORGINA: Knock, knock!
[door opens]
‐ Mom! I really wish you'd actually knock,
instead of saying "knock, knock"
once you're in my room.
‐ Listen, I just got some incredible news.
Mary Lou Gordon's gallbladder
just straight‐up exploded,
so guess who's taking over hosting duties
for Good Morning Atlanta this week?
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Is she okay?
‐ Me! This is beyond exciting,
but if I want to get my
eight hours of beauty rest,
I have to go to bed like, now.
‐ Okay. Good night.
GEORGINA: Oh, no. No, no, no.
I've seen every episode of
Teen Mom
and that is not going down
on my watch. Now, Felix,
honey, you know I am just
very fond of you.
But get out of my house
so I can lull myself into a low key coma
with the edibles my assistant
gave me, okay?
‐ Ugh. She is the actual worst.
‐ Actually, you, um,
wanna come to my place for a bit?
‐ Really? Is your mom not home?
‐ Oh, no. No. Sh‐she's there. Um...
[grunts]
You know, I didn't want to tell you,
because I didn't want to jinx it,
but she is on these new meds,
and she is doing a lot better,
and I kinda would love for you two
to finally meet.
‐ Yes, Felix. That is amazing.
Um, let me just throw a respectable
parent look together.
I want your mom to go crazy for me.
Sorry. Poor choice of words.
GEORGINA:
Uh, less talking and more leaving!
[knocking on door]
ARMANDO:
Isa, it's me.
[clears throat]
[door closes]
‐ Hey, Mando!
‐ Hey.
I, uh, have the rent check.
‐ Oh. Thank you.
‐ Of course.
[sighs, clears throat]
‐ I can't stop thinking about
what happened with us the other day.
‐ Me, neither.
Wow. Big fan of your work.
[both laughing]
‐ And I of yours.
‐ Yeah.
[both laugh]
But sex was never really
our problem, was it?
‐ No. Mmm.
‐ Yeah.
‐ But I think we should talk about
what it means, uh, for us.
‐ Hmm.
‐ You wanna have dinner tonight?
‐ Uh, I have PFLAG.
You can come with me.
Yeah, there's... there's a
great barbecue place next door.
They have fried pickles,
just like back in Texas.
Hmm?
Okay. You're still not ready to go
to a meeting with me.
‐ I am working on it. I swear.
[Armando exhales]
Dinner tomorrow night.
‐ Tomorrow's perfect.
‐ Good.
‐ Okay.
Okay, so I'll see you.
I don't‐‐
‐ I‐‐
I don't‐‐ Let's do cheek.
‐ Okay. [laughs]
Great.
‐ Bye.
‐ [laughs] Okay, everyone here is,
like, intimidatingly cool.
‐ Yay! I'm so glad you guys are here.
Cabin crew.
‐ Hey.
‐ Hey, guys.
‐ So, Benji played me
some of their tracks,
and they sound so amazing.
Like if Satin Jackets and Bleachers
had a baby,
but then they died in a car crash,
so the baby had to be raised by
Empire of the Sun.
Does that make any sense?
‐ No. But I love your passion.
Come on, Salazar.
Let's get the ladies some drinks.
‐ What‐‐ Uh, okay.
ANDREW: Yeah.
‐ [sighs]
Andrew, what do you want?
‐ Well, I want your ass back on the team.
Be honest. Don't you miss it?
‐ Being around a bunch of guys
that think I'm some sort of
locker room perv?
No, I'm good.
‐ No. Nobody thinks that.
A couple of guys are just weirded out,
but they'll get over it.
I mean, you're basically the least gay
gay person alive.
‐ Good to know.
I'm gonna go and say hi to Benji.
‐ I‐‐
‐ Guitar‐‐
VICTOR: Hey.
‐ Victor! Hey.
Uh, meet the band.
This is Mylo, Stevie,
that's Coryn, and that is Tosh.
‐ Hi. It's so nice to finally
meet you guys.
‐ Yeah, us, too.
Benji will never shut up about you.
STEVIE: [laughs]
It's cute and annoying at the same time.
Is that Lucy's boyfriend?
CORYN: Yeah, such a basic
high school sports person.
MYLO:
Coryn! Victor plays basketball.
‐ Oh.
‐ I actually just quit,
so I'm not a
"basic high school sports person" anymore.
‐ Yeah, Victor's in the early stages
of jock recovery.
He just escaped the cult of cheap
body spray and casual misogyny.
[laughing]
STEVIE: That's probably why you like him.
The sports. The church boy haircut.
He's your perfect straight boy fantasy.
‐ [laughs] Oh, trust me.
Victor is much more than just
a handsome jock.
STEVIE:
He's a handsome ex‐jock.
‐ Yeah. Thank God.
Now I don't have to sit
with the basketball girlfriends
and do the whole
"Go Grizzlies" dance.
[all laughing]
CORYN:
Kill me dead.
[band laughing]
‐ Oh, wow.
Felix, it looks so much better in here.
‐ Mmm‐hmm. First time in years
my mom's actually thrown stuff away.
I do kind of miss the leaning tower
of pizza boxes, though.
DAWN: Felix? Is that you?
‐ Uh‐huh.
DAWN:
I just made schnitzel!
‐ Mmm.
‐ I‐‐ Oh!
Oh, I didn't know we had company.
I... I'm so sorry about the clutter.
You caught us
in the middle of our spring cleaning.
‐ That's our story
and we're sticking to it.
Mom, this is Lake.
‐ Oh, gosh. You're Lake!
You're the Lake!
LAKE: Hi. It's so nice to meet you.
‐ Oh, God! [laughing]
Oh! Oh, and you're so gorgeous!
Oh!
‐ Okay, Mom, uh,
don't break my girlfriend.
[laughs]
‐ Okay. Okay. I know. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I just, I know how much
you mean to my son.
Would you like to stay?
Because I just made some schnitzel.
‐ Homemade German? I am so in.
DAWN:
Oh, great. That's great.
Honey, will you come to the kitchen
and help me,
so I can gush about your girlfriend
in private?
[laughs]
‐ That went great. Right?
Yeah, I mean, I, I, I, I thought it would,
but I wasn't really sure,
but that actually went really good. I‐‐
‐Yes, it, it did. It did.
It went great. Your mom is awesome.
‐ Okay.
[Lake laughs softly]
BENJI and CORYN:
♪ But I still want your ♪
♪ Young, young love ♪
‐ ♪ Eh eh eh eh ♪
BENJI and CORYN:
♪ Young, young love ♪
♪ Now right back into ♪
♪ Young love ♪
‐ ♪ Is the worst to come ♪
‐ ♪ Worst to come ♪
‐ ♪ Worry
BOTH: ♪ If I don't use it ♪
♪ Then I'm gonna lose it all ♪
♪ But I still want your ♪
♪ Young, young love ♪
‐ ♪ Eh eh eh eh ♪
BOTH:
♪ Young, young love ♪
CORYN:
♪ Eh eh eh eh ♪
[clapping and cheering]
‐ Thank you, guys. We're gonna take five,
and we'll be right back.
[clapping]
AUDIENCE MEMBER: Whoo! Yeah!
‐ So, what did you guys think?
‐ Oh, I loved that last one.
‐ It was really, really good.
[laughs]
‐ Victor?
‐ Uh, it‐it was cool.
‐ Uh, can I talk to you for a second?
‐ Yeah. Yeah.
‐ Okay. What's up with you?
‐ Nothing. It's just...
a little weird to hear you
and your friends talk about me
like I'm some sort of dumb jock.
‐ They were just joking around.
‐ I'm sorry. I'm just...
messed up right now.
And it's not your fault.
It's just...
I'm, I'm gonna head home.
‐ Okay.
‐ You guys really do sound great, though.
Uh, hey, I have a lot of homework,
so I'm gonna get going.
But, uh, I'll see you tomorrow?
‐ Yeah. Sure.
‐ Okay. All right. Bye, guys.
‐ Yep.
MIA: Bye.
‐ Actually, I think I'm gonna
head out, too.
I gotta get up at the ass crack of dawn
for practice tomorrow.
You mind hanging with Mia?
LUCY: Yeah, of course.
‐ Oh, okay.
‐ Cool. Well, thank you.
‐ Hey, Shelby.
SHELBY: Oh.
You have a little extra pep
in your step today.
‐ Just feeling good about
where I'm at in my life. You know?
ISABEL:
Armando and I were intimate.
We're just separated. We're still married,
so it's not a sin. [laughs]
Although I guess he would be
the judge of that. [laughs]
[clears throat]
We're having dinner
to talk about getting back together.
We have our problems, but, I, I,
I really want things to work out.
‐ What kind of problems?
He... He doesn't really know
how to talk about his emotions.
‐ Yeah, it's like since
I started coming here,
I feel way more in touch with my feelings.
You know? And‐‐ thanks.
And it just feels so good to not have
everything bottled up inside.
I feel like I'm growing as a person,
which feels dumb to say,
since I'm in my forties.
‐ Oh, no. It's not dumb.
Having a kid come out,
it changes you.
I mean, last month,
I went to drag queen bingo.
‐ How was that?
‐ It's... fun.
I barely recognize
the woman I used to be.
All because my kid was brave enough
to say "I'm gay."
FATHER LAWRENCE:
He is? When did he share this with you?
‐ A couple months back.
Armando has been surprisingly
accepting of all of this,
considering his machismo.
But I am struggling.
And I, I know...
I know that Victor didn't choose
to be this way...
‐ You're a good mother.
That's very clear.
But I think you're, you're right
to express your disapproval,
if you want Victor to know God's love.
‐ Oh.
‐ You sound disappointed.
‐ That's what I was always taught.
I just thought maybe the church
was a little more flexible nowadays.
‐ Do you think God is in the business
of providing loopholes? [chuckles]
ARMANDO:
I just thank God for giving me the courage
to come here, and...
to love my son for who he is.
‐ Oh... [laughs softly]
Meeting's starting.
‐ Right.
‐ [grunts] Oof.
‐ I thought you were done with basketball.
‐ Andrew, what are you doing?
You following me now?
‐ Come on. Let's go.
All right.
You live for this.
‐ [sighs] Listen.
How many times do I have to tell you
I'm not gonna be part of a team
that doesn't want me?
‐ And how many times do I have to
tell you they will come around?
‐ Right.
Because I am "the least gay
gay person alive."
‐ I'm guessing that was
a stupid thing to say.
‐ No.
No, it was perfect.
Please, tell me what's the exact level
of gay I should be.
What is a perfect level of gay
that will keep everyone happy?
Because apparently,
I'm too gay for the locker room,
but I'm not gay enough
for Benji and his friends.
So, where do I belong?
‐ You belong on a basketball court.
‐ [sighs] Let's say I do come back.
What happens if one day I do
want to be more "gay gay?"
And I change the way I dress,
or, or I dye my hair pink.
Then what?
‐ Are those things that you really want?
‐ I think the pink hair thing
could be kind of dope.
‐ Well, then, I think you should do it.
If anyone has a problem with it,
they can answer to me.
‐ Andrew,
do you really think that you're an ally
because you watch Queer Eye?
This whole time,
you haven't said shit to the guys
that don't want me changing
in the locker room with them.
Because at the end of the day,
you don't want to risk your
reputation for the gay kid.
[Victor grunts]
‐ Benji and Victor are such a hot couple.
Not that you and Victor
weren't a hot couple.
[Mia chuckles]
You guys were a really hot couple.
But I should just stop talking.
‐ [laughs] It's okay.
I just want Victor to be happy.
I want all my friends to be happy.
You, uh, seem to make Andrew very happy.
‐ Oh, thanks.
[chuckles]
To be honest, I'm surprised
we've lasted this long.
‐ Really? Why?
‐ We're just so opposite.
Earlier this summer when we hooked up,
I just thought it was gonna be,
like, a hot fling.
And then suddenly I'm his girlfriend...
Can I ask you something?
‐ Sure. Yeah. What's up?
‐ When we were at the cabin,
I saw you and Andrew outside together.
And it just seemed like...
I don't know.
There was something about the way
you were looking at each other...
Is there something going on?
‐ We hooked up once.
A long time ago.
But there's nothing between us now.
I swear.
‐ Hmm.
‐ Is that, "Hmm, that's so random."
Or, "Hmm, hold my earrings.
I'm about to clock a bitch."
[both laughing]
‐ No, it's fine. Um, I'm just surprised.
Andrew never mentioned it.
‐ I'm, I'm sure he just didn't
want to make you feel weird.
‐ I don't. I mean, feel weird.
I should feel a little weird, though,
shouldn't I?
I mean, if I really cared
about this relationship,
shouldn't I, like, feel something?
‐ I shouldn't have said anything.
‐ No. No, I'm really glad that you did.
This is... really helpful.
[Lucy sighs]
♪ But you found somebody new ♪
‐ That was divine.
The perfect meal on the perfect plates.
Tres chic. Where did you get them?
‐ Oh, thank you. They're family heirlooms.
LAKE: Mmm.
‐ So, who wants dessert?
‐ Oh, uh, thank you,
but I should probably get going.
We have a test on the
Hundred Years' War tomorrow
and pretty much all I know
is how long it is.
‐ It's actually
a hundred and sixteen years.
‐ Are you freaking kidding me?
‐ Oh.
‐ I'm sure Lake will be back soon, Mom.
‐ I'm gonna start cleaning up.
‐ Well, hey, she's like me, you know?
Always...
down to keep partying. [laughs]
‐ I want you to have these.
And if you give me a couple minutes,
I can wash the ones that we used tonight,
and then you can take those home, too.
FELIX: What are you talking about, Mom?
‐It's j‐‐
‐ Those are our plates.
‐ Well, I, I know, but she likes 'em,
and I want her to have them.
Felix, help me find a box.
‐ She's not taking our plates, Mom.
‐ Felix, I told you,
she likes 'em, and I want her to have 'em.
[Dawn muttering]
[plates clattering]
‐ Did you take your medication
this morning?
‐ Why are you asking me that?
Are you trying to embarrass me?
‐ No! I mean, um, I'm, I'm sure he's not.
Uh... [sighs] You know,
this is just so generous,
and, you know, we have our own
family heirloom plates.
I, I wouldn't want there to be
any heirloom envy‐‐
‐ You know what? Fine!
[shattering]
‐ I ju‐‐ I... Oh, God.
[inhales shakily, then sighs]
Um... it was...
It was really nice to meet you, Lake.
Really.
[whimpers]
[footsteps departing]
[door slams]
[exhales]
[clinking]
‐ Felix. Felix, are you okay?
‐ Yeah.
Yeah, no. Um...
‐ Here.
‐ You know, this just‐‐
it happens sometimes.
When, uh, she takes new medication,
she comes out of her depression,
and then she stops taking it,
and then she has a manic episode.
You know, I don't even know
why I thought this time
would be different. [laughs] Um...
I‐‐
‐ I think we need to get you some help.
‐ The new medication was working.
She just needs to take it.
I'll get her back on them.
‐ Okay. Well, this is serious,
and, and I just really think
it's too much for you to handle.
‐ N‐no.
No.
I have been handling this alone...
for years.
I need you to promise me
you won't tell anyone what happened.
‐ I promise.
‐ Okay.
[clinking]
[Felix exhales]
[sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
[phone chimes]
‐ Uh, hello?
[distant chatter]
[chuckles softly]
Uh, what's going on?
‐ Well, I had a long talk with the guys
about you rejoining the team.
And, and this is our way of saying that
you can be as gay as you want,
in whatever way that you want,
and we will forever stan you.
TEDDY
And if you're gay, then... so am I.
So are all of us.
We're gay AF.
‐ No. Not what we talked about, Teddy.
[Teddy chuckles]
‐ So, where's‐‐ where's Wyatt?
‐The team wasn't a good fit
for him anymore.
‐ Wow. [chuckles]
‐ And I'm sorry, man.
You can watch me shower any day.
I don't mind.
‐ Oh...
No, no, I‐I really don't want
to watch you shower.
‐ Okay. Well, you don't
have to decide right now. So...
‐ All right. Well‐‐
ANDREW: Victor, come on.
[all chattering]
TEDDY: Welcome back.
‐ Whew!
‐ All right.
[clapping]
Let's hope this looks better on you
than it does on me.
‐ It definitely will. [laughs]
‐ You guys, this stuff better wash out.
I got a court date on Monday!
Oh, I wasn't supposed to say that.
♪ Everyone just move it, move it ♪
[players chattering]
[spectators cheering]
[whistle blows]
‐ Hey!
[cheering]
ANNOUNCER [over PA]:
That's a tie.
Grizzlies up by nine.
That pink hair seems
to be doing the trick.
‐ Wow. I like your hair.
‐ Ah, thanks. [laughs]
I didn't think you were gonna come.
I‐I know this isn't really
your scene, but um‐‐
‐ Victor, um,
I'm really sorry about all those
stupid jokes.
If basketball makes you happy, well...
That makes me a basketball boyfriend.
Girls?
♪ dance music plays ♪
VICTOR:
What are you doing?
‐ The "Go Grizzlies" dance.
Duh!
[cheering]
♪ dance music playing ♪
♪ Stay hungry, stay thirsty ♪
♪ Don't be afraid to get down and dirty ♪
♪ Don't stand on the sideline,
put in the time to ♪
♪ Stay hungry, stay thirsty ♪
♪ Don't be afraid to get down and dirty ♪
♪ Don't stand on the sideline,
put in the time to ♪
♪ Oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh, hey hey ♪
[cheering]
[laughing]
‐ [sighs] That's actually...
way harder than it looks.
I guess that's, uh, my punishment
for making fun of athletes.
[door opens]
GEORGINA:
Lakey. Hi! Did you watch?
I crushed it on Good Morning Atlanta.
I interviewed Sarah Jessica Parker
over Skype,
and she said I had pretty eyes.
Hey, what's wrong?
‐ Nothing.
Congratulations on the show.
‐ Lake, you know that you can
talk to me about anything, right?
[locker shuts]
‐ It's good to have you back, Salazar.
You really are the second best
player on the team.
[Victor laughs]
‐ Okay, Andrew.
‐ Hey, babe.
What's wrong?
‐ Hey, uh, we need to talk.
ISABEL:
I am so sorry I'm late.
I changed four times
before coming here.
What do you wear to a sort of date
with your husband
who you're sort of separated from,
but definitely had full‐on sex with?
ARMANDO:
[laughs] Well, uh...
I always liked you in green.
‐ Oh. Well, thank you.
I'm happy we're doing this.
I miss you.
‐ I miss you, too.
Okay, Mando, I'm just gonna jump right in.
‐ Okay.
‐ The affair with Roger...
It broke something,
and that is my fault.
And I am so sorry that I,
I pressured you so hard to get over it.
‐ No. But our problems
started before that.
Yeah, I‐I think the real reason
we separated was because
we were stuck in a pattern,
and the only way to get un‐stuck
is if we both change.
That's why I keep asking you
to come to PFLAG with me.
And every time you say no,
it just feels like
you don't want to change.
‐ I do want to.
I went to see Father Lawrence yesterday,
to talk about everything.
‐ How'd it go?
‐ He said if... Victor chooses this path,
that he will never know God's love.
And I'm thinking, how can that be?
He is such a good son.
He is such a good person...
Why is this happening to him?
‐ Is‐Isa, it's not happening to him, okay?
It's just who he is.
You know, this whole thing with Victor,
it's...
It's made me really look at myself,
and really try and change.
But if you're not going to change with me,
I don't know what the future holds.
‐ Andrew. What are you doing here?
‐ Lucy broke up with me.
She spent one night talking to you,
and she broke up with me.
‐ [sighs] Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
‐Lucy, she asked me if anything
had ever happened between us,
and I felt like I had to be honest.
But I really never meant to‐‐
‐ Mia...
‐ Yes?
‐ It's okay.
‐ It is?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Why is your hair pink?
‐ I was trying to make things
right with Victor.
Which is actually your fault, too.
‐ Why is that my fault?
‐ For as long as I can remember,
anytime I wanted to take the easy way out,
there was always this annoying voice
in the back of my head,
pushing me to do better.
To be better.
You know whose voice that is?
Even when you're not around me,
I always hear you.
So, when Lucy ended it,
I figured, hey.
I've taken a million shots with you,
but I am about to take a million and one.
Mia. Mia, will, will you‐‐
♪ It's something about you
that's so familiar ♪
♪ Something that's got me
wanting to know you ♪
♪ And I can't put my finger on it ♪
[laughs]
♪ But it feels ♪
♪ Oh, like I've been here before ♪
♪ It's something about me
that makes me wonder ♪
♪ I swear I met you ♪
♪ But you're a stranger ♪
♪ And I can't put my finger
on quite what it is ♪
♪ Oh ba ba ba ba,
Oh ah ah... ♪