VICTOR: Here you go.
CUSTOMER: Thank you.
‐ Sorry I’m late.
I had that dream again
where the Hemsworth brothers
teach me how to surf.
‐ Mmm.
‐ Still holding out hope
that it’s a premonition.
‐ [chuckles] Well, lucky for you,
today’s the only day
you’re allowed to be late.
Happy birthday.
[laughs]
And I’m glad you slept in,
'cause I can't have you tired for tonight.
I have big plans for us.
‐ Oh, yeah? What kind of plans?
‐ Uh, let's just say I may have "borrowed"
a bottle of champagne from
my mom's wine cabinet.
A little bit of drinking,
a little bit of fooling around.
And that’s all I have planned.
Should I have tried a little bit harder?
‐ No. No, that's perfect.
My parents should be out cold after this
bougie dinner they’re dragging me to.
‐ I'm sure it won't be that bad.
‐ You haven’t heard my mom
try and impress a French waiter
with her pronunciation of ratatouille.
[laughs]
[door opens]
Oh, wow. I accidentally summoned her.
‐ Hi, boys.
‐ Hey.
‐ Ooh!
Said it before and I’ll say it again,
the softest cheeks in Creekwood.
Can you believe this sneaky cat
left the house
without letting his own mother
wish him a happy birthday?
Happy birthday, darling.
It’s a pain au chocolat from Café Jacquot.
‐ Odd gift, considering I’m surrounded
by pastries all day.
But it's very sweet. Thank you, Mom.
MARGARET: Mmm.
Oh, Benji, before I go,
could you make me one of those
delicious oat milk lattes?
‐ Sure, Mother.
[Victor chuckles]
‐ Okay. The coast is clear.
I’m sure Benji mentioned that
we’re taking him to Chez Luisant tonight.
Well, I was hoping that you could join us.
As a fun surprise for him.
‐ Yeah! Yeah, of course. That'd be great.
‐ Oh, wonderful.
You may want to dress up a bit.
But don’t worry, it isn't, um,
hoity‐toity. It's more, um,
cozy chic.
Mmm. Oh, I'm gonna take a rain check
on the latte.
My, uh, my matcha's just kicked in
and I'm feeling a little buzzy.
I can't wait to celebrate you later.
Bye, Victor.
VICTOR: Bye.
‐ Did my mom just wink at you?
‐ That's how you pay your respects
to "the softest cheeks in Creekwood."
‐ Softest, huh? Let me see.
‐ [laughing] Hey! Come here.
‐ ♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be all right ♪
♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be just fine ♪
♪ If someone has been there before,
say it right now ♪
♪ 'Cause I just need to hear it ♪
♪
‐ This is nice.
‐ Yeah, it's fine.
[keyboard keys clicking]
Is it me or does it feel like
we have a very emotional chaperone?
MIA:
Give her a break.
Felix still won’t talk to her.
She’s a mess.
I mean, she's not even wearing heels.
Her motto is usually
“give me three inches or give me death.”
‐ So Felix just barely made the cut.
Ho‐ho!
‐ [sighs] Okay. Andrew...
If Mia accidentally got your mom
committed to a 72‐hour psych hold,
which of these surprise dates
would make you forgive her:
a visit to the Jimmy Carter
Presidential Library,
or a visit to the
Center for Puppetry Arts. Be honest.
‐ These are real places?
God, Atlanta sucks.
‐ [sighs] Guys, this is serious.
I‐I really have to think of
something amazing
to remind Felix
how much I love him!
‐ Lake. [grunts] Breathe.
[exhales]
I’ll help you find
the perfect thing. Okay?
‐ Thank you.
Okay. Now I’m gonna go order us
a bunch of Chinese takeout,
like they do in movies where the lawyers
have to stay up all night
cracking the case. Okay? [sighs]
‐ I thought we were gonna order pizza.
‐ I know. I just need to be here
for Lake, is all.
Look, if we finish early,
we can order pizza from the
comfort of my bedroom.
LAKE:
Oh, uh, can you hold on for a second?
Guys. Guys!
Smash on your own time, okay?
A relationship hangs in the balance.
‐ Betrayed by my lover.
They took away my mother.
Will I ever recover?
‐ Uh, hey, Felix.
When was the last time you took a shower?
RAHIM: Yeah, you're really making me
regret having a nose.
[Felix sniffs]
My nose is my second favorite body part.
Wouldn't you like to know?
‐ All right. I'll go.
‐ Hey, would you guys be able to
keep an eye on him tonight?
Benji’s mom invited me to
Chez Luisant for his birthday.
‐ I heard J. Lo ate there every night
while she was staying here
filming that new movie
about being a scrappy mom
finding true love.
‐ Hasn't she already made that movie?
[shower facet turns, water runs]
‐ Oh, and every Avengers movie
is uniquely different.
You're not actually
gonna wear that, are you?
‐ Uh, yeah.
Benji’s mom said it’s "cozy meets chic."
‐ Are you sure you’re gay? I‐‐
I wash my hands of this. Ugh.
‐ Okay, don't‐‐ don't mind her.
We'll find you something to wear.
Something clean and classic.
You know‐‐
Okay, wow. You, you really love
the non‐descript athletic tee.
‐ Uh, well I could probably borrow
one of my dad's button‐ups.
Uh, you know, he, he's a little bit
bigger than I am,
but I could tuck it in.
‐ We're probably the same size, right?
‐ Oh, no, no, no.
It's, it's okay. Really‐‐
‐ It's fine.
And it's, uh,
it's last season St. Laurent, so...
try not to spill anything on it.
‐ Well, uh, try not to spill
anything on this, either,
because it is present day Old Navy.
‐ Cute.
[laughs]
Just... yeah.
‐ All right.
[laughs]
Oh, damn, Victor! Lookin' good.
That will be the first and last
time I ever catcall my brother.
[laughs]
‐ Hey, guys, there's snacks
in the kitchen.
Rahim, Keto friendly. I got you.
‐ Oh.
‐ [gasps] Mira que handsome.
[Isabel giggles]
Hold on. Your collar is all crooked.
There.
So guess where I'm going tonight.
My first PFLAG meeting.
‐ Really?
‐ Yeah.
I need a little advice
on how to talk to Adrian about...
who you are.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Thank you for being so patient with me.
‐ You guys are out of towels.
[indistinct chatter]
CHARLES:
It was so good meeting you.
‐ Well, look who the cat dragged in.
CHARLES:
And what a dapper cat he is.
Wait, Victor isn’t the cat.
He’s what the cat is dragging.
That is such a strange expression.
‐ Victor, what are you doing here?
‐ Uh, good to see you, too.
‐ No, sorry, I‐I just meant‐‐
‐ We asked Victor to join us
as a little birthday surprise.
VICTOR:
Ah, well, you guys look great.
I wasn’t totally sure what “cozy chic”
meant, but now I think I get it.
‐ It sounds like my wife gave you
one of her indecipherable dress codes.
Last week, it was
“fireside fashionable.“
MARGARET:
Well, no matter what I say,
he always wears the same sweater vest.
[Victor chuckles]
‐ Oh, there's our table.
‐ Oh, Victor, you are in for a treat.
The food here is truly divine.
[laughs]
♪
[keyboard keys clicking]
LAKE: Any other ideas?
‐ Ponce City Market has rooftop
ice skating.
‐ Oof, no. Felix doesn't like ice skating.
He thinks it’s a recipe for disaster
to wear weapons as shoes.
Oh, my God! The aquarium has
a deep sea fish exhibit.
‐ Okay.
‐ Oh, uh, Felix taught me about this
weird glow‐in‐the‐dark deep sea fish
the very first time we kissed,
and it's kind of our origin story.
He would love this.
‐ All right. Aquarium it is.
‐ What's the look?
I just...
Okay, are you sure this is the right move?
I mean, Felix has a pretty
good reason to be upset.
And maybe what he needs more than a fancy
aquarium date is just...
time.
‐ Yeah, but what do you mean
he has a pretty good reason to be upset?
Mia, I was trying to help him.
‐ I know that.
But he asked you not to say anything
about his mom, Lake. And you did.
And now she’s being
detained at a hospital.
‐ 'Cause she's sick, and she needs help.
‐ I’m just saying Felix trusted you,
and you betrayed that trust.
I know what it's like
to have a mom go away.
And it hurts.
‐ I know it hurts.
Because I was there for you
when it happened.
Holding your hand and being your friend.
Which is clearly something
you can’t be for me right now. So...
‐ Lake, come on.
‐ No. No, uh, thanks‐‐
thanks for the support.
Now I just gotta figure out how to make
an aquarium romantic AF.
‐ And I think‐‐ Let’s put in an order
of le ratatouille
for the table.
SERVER: Great choice.
‐ Thank you, Henri.
‐ Your mom really does say ratatouille
like she's trying to win a Michelin star.
[chuckles]
[clinking on glass]
‐ Uh, Mom, can I actually
talk to you for a second?
‐ Sure. Right after the
sparkling cider toast.
Benjamin, we couldn't love you more.
We all know that the last couple of years
haven't been easy‐‐
‐ Mom, I, I just‐‐
‐ Let her have her moment.
She practiced this at home for an hour.
A very long hour.
‐ Shush!
After your car accident last year,
you were so hard on yourself,
and things were...
pretty dark for a while there, and...
you decided to put in the hard work.
Look at you now.
You're so committed to your...
your sobriety, and your AA meetings.
And last week,
you earned your one‐year chip.
We couldn’t possibly be
prouder of you, darling.
We love you so much, Benji.
Happy birthday, sweetheart.
‐ Wait, wait. You're, you're sober?
‐ I have to go to the bathroom.
‐ Did you not know?
‐ I, I knew about the accident,
but I didn't know that he was in AA.
[phone chimes, vibrates]
[cartoon chatters over phone]
[Felix sighs]
[bubbling]
‐ Hey, buddy. We’re having a J. Lo
movie marathon,
because apparently
if someone mentions J. Lo,
Rahim has to have a marathon.
Wanna join?
[phone vibrates]
‐ Oh, my God, uh, no. This is, um‐‐
This is my mom's social worker. Um...
Hi, Alison. Uh, what's up?
Okay, the doctor thought‐‐
I understand.
Yeah, uh, can, can I have a second?
Um, based on evaluations,
they are doing an extended hold.
It can, uh, it can,
it can be up to 14 days.
Hi. Yeah, sorry about that.
‐ This sucks, I mean,
no one deserves this less than Felix.
He's literally the sweatiest person.
‐ No, you were about to say sweetest.
Looks like someone has a little crush.
‐ On Felix? Yeah. Right.
He's like a sweet, goofy Muppet.
Humph.
♪ rap music playing over TV ♪
‐ I got bored waiting for you guys,
so I started Hustlers.
♪ rap music continues ♪
Two questions: What’s a lap dance,
and why is it so expensive?
‐ Um...
SHELBY: Hi, everyone. This week's meeting
will be starting in a few minutes.
‐ Thank you.
SHELBY: Now, y'all grab a snack
and take a seat.
‐ Hey.
‐ Hey, you.
I know. One creamer,
three Splendas. Right?
‐ You remembered.
Ah, bless you.
[both chuckle]
‐ Well...
‐ Lord knows I could use the caffeine.
Zoey kept me up watching
another Kristen Stewart movie.
I swear, my kid is obsessed
with that fidgety woman.
Kind of like you. [laughs]
‐ Oh, stop.
After you...
♪
‐ Hey.
I'm really sorry you had to
find out about AA like that.
What about at the cabin?
We, we were drinking vodka.
‐ I was drinking orange juice.
I switched out my cup
when no one was looking.
Whenever we’re around
alcohol, I, I just... fake it.
It’s easier for me to pretend that I drink
instead of explain why I don’t.
‐ I mean, I, I get that. I do.
With other people.
But why didn't you tell me that?
We tell each other everything.
‐ I don't know, Victor.
I, I guess I just...
didn't want you to think of me as
your boyfriend, the alcoholic.
‐ I would never judge you like that.
‐ No, of course not.
It’s just my own stuff. Look, can you...
[sighs] I’m sorry, okay.
Can, can you just forgive me?
‐ I want to.
It's just that you always push me
to be more open with you.
And this is like, a huge part of
your life that you just hid from me.
‐ You know, you could at least try and be
a little more understanding.
[scoffs] I’ve put up with
a ton of your shit,
and never made you feel bad
about any of it.
‐ Whoa‐‐
What is that supposed to mean?
‐ Oh, nothing. You know, just forget it.
‐ No, please, tell me. What shit
have you had to put up with?
‐ I don't know, Victor.
There’s the fact that you’re
completely new to being gay.
And every single thing that we go through
is this massively big deal
that we have to examine.
And then, then there's your mom,
who thinks that you’re going to Hell
for being with me.
And every time she takes
a tiny step forward,
I’m supposed to jump for joy.
I mean, I, I'm not even allowed
in your house.
But do I ever make you feel guilty
about any of that stuff?
No. No, I've been nothing but patient,
and, and understanding.
The very least you could do is just,
is return the favor.
‐ I guess I just didn’t realize
how much patience
and understanding it took to be with me.
Happy birthday, Benji.
[sighs]
‐ I can’t believe Lake's trying to
smooth things over
by bringing you to some aquarium.
‐ Me, neither.
And I can't believe Benji said
it's exhausting to be with you.
I think being around you is invigorating.
‐ Thank you. So you agree
Benji's being a total dick?
‐ Totally. Although, you‐‐
‐ What?
‐ [stammers] It's nothing. It's just...
Must be hard for him, you know,
to see you struggle so much with your mom.
And don't get me wrong,
I love me some Izzy Salazar, but...
watching her make you feel like crap
these past few months...
It's been tough.
And I'm not even banging you.
Or are you banging him?
Did you guys ever settle on that?
‐ Well, it must be hard for Lake, too.
You know, to see you
going through all this stuff,
and have to deal with
your mom all by yourself.
‐ So what, they just...
love us both so much they can't bear
to see us in pain?
[sighs] Damn.
It's a curse to be this beautiful.
‐ Where are you going?
‐ I am going to hear her out.
So, good luck with Benji.
‐ Thanks.
♪ rap music playing over TV ♪
‐ Can you believe J. Lo
looks this good at 50?
‐ She's 50?
Am I into cougars?
‐ [sighs] Hey, guys.
‐ Hey! Wanna join us?
‐ Oh, no, I'm actually gonna go meet Lake.
‐ Lake? Like, Lake, your girlfriend, Lake.
Cool. Cool. Good luck.
‐ Thanks.
‐ Hey, little man. You mind taking this...
[door opens]
...tempting bowl of carbs
back to the kitchen?
[door closes]
After six, it sticks.
‐ What?
‐ [imitating Pilar]: "Lake? Lake, like,
like, like your girlfriend, Lake?
Cool. Cool, cool, cool."
[normal voice]:
Are you sure you just see him as
a sweet, goofy Muppet?
‐ You're right.
I think he's the sexiest Muppet.
He's basically Gonzo.
‐ There it is.
Hey. If J. Lo taught us anything,
it’s that the hot, tough‐ass
Puerto Rican chick
usually gets what she wants
in the end, right?
And to wear sunscreen.
Always wear sunscreen.
[Pilar groans]
[clears throat]
‐ Isa.
I didn’t realize you were here tonight.
Were you at the meeting?
‐ Only long enough to see you
flirting up a storm with some other woman.
‐ Are you talking about Shelby?
[laughs] I mean, she's a new friend,
but I barely know her.
‐ You know her well enough to know
how she takes her coffee.
‐ [sighs] It’s not like that, Isabel.
‐ What's it like, Armando?
Because I know you like I know
the back of my hand,
and I saw the way you were
looking at that woman.
Is this what you want?
To see other people?
‐ When we decided to take
this time apart,
we agreed that we needed
to work on ourselves.
To find a way back to our marriage
with fresh eyes.
If we're meant to come back to it.
We've been together since we were kids,
and I just think...
I mean, what’s the point
of being separated
if we're not gonna try and find out
what we really want.
‐ I'm gonna need you to say the words.
‐ Yes.
I'd like to see other people.
‐ Thank you for your honesty.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[tank bubbling]
‐ Thank you so much for coming.
I really, really missed you.
‐ Missed you, too.
‐ Look.
[Felix chuckles]
‐ Anglerfish. [laughs]
‐ Felix.
You taught me about that creepy fish
on the night we first kissed.
And in a way,
it represents
the start of our relationship.
And...
I guess I was hoping that it
could represent a new start, too.
I am so, so sorry for
betraying your trust,
but when I saw how much pain
your mom's situation was causing you,
all I wanted to do was just
take that pain away.
‐ I know.
‐ You do?
‐ Yes.
‐ Oh...
Good.
‐ I understand why you told your mom
about my mom.
I really do.
But I trusted you.
And now she’s gone,
and I don’t know when she’s gonna be back.
[Felix sighs]
That night I kissed you,
I told you the only thing
a male angler fish wants
is to make its mate happy.
‐ Yeah, I remember.
‐ I don't want to be that fish.
[scoffs]
I think need to be happy, too.
And right now...
seeing you makes me really, really sad.
So, I'm sorry, Lake.
I don't think we can be together.
♪
[exhales]
[door clicks shut]
[distant footsteps, clattering]
‐ Victor, I'm going out for a sec.
You're on Adrian duty.
♪
MAN [over TV]: There is a rapper
that's named Ivan,
or, you know...
‐ Hey. You're back?
‐ Yeah. I'm back.
‐ What are you doing?
‐ I've, um, been coming up here
every night since my mom's been gone.
We never skipped Millionaire,
so I have been
keeping the tradition going.
‐ Are you taking notes?
‐ No. No, uh, keeping score.
My mom and I are very competitive.
[both chuckle]
‐ Mind if I join you?
‐ I'm not a very good hang right now.
‐ This might surprise you,
but sad and pissed
is kind of my ideal vibe, so...
‐ [laughs softly]
Okay. Um...
pretty simple. Just write down
what you think the right answer is,
and‐‐
‐ A: Wimbledon.
‐ Okay, pro tip...
you'll have a much better
chance of getting it right
if you wait to see if they phone a friend.
‐ Hmm.
MAN [on TV]: But you were right.
It's, it's Wimbledon. Yes.
‐ Ha! Pilar: one. Felix: zero.
‐ Well, they start out with
the easy questions first, so...
‐ You’re a dead man.
‐ It's on.
‐ Is it?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Oh, okay.
‐ Oh, ho ho!
You're about to enter a world of hurt.
[Pilar laughs]
[knocking on door]
‐ Hey.
‐ I was kind of surprised
when I got your text.
‐ Yeah, well, my, my mom's not here,
and even if she was, I‐‐
I needed to see you.
Listen, I‐‐ I know dating me
can be a lot sometimes,
and I know you try to be patient.
‐ It's fine, Victor.
Really. I was just...
really embarrassed that
you found out about AA.
I wanted to keep that part of my life
separate from you,
because I hate that part of my life,
and you're the part of my life
that I love.
♪
[both breathing heavily]
‐ Let's go to my room.
♪
‐ You're really thinking about Lake
right now. Aren't you?
‐ No, no. I'm super into this.
‐ Mmm.
[chuckles]
‐ You have your phone in your hand,
and you're waiting for her to text you.
‐ Yes. Yes, because I was gonna record us.
I'm, I’m secretly super kinky. Surprise!
‐ Mmm.
‐ You need to get your mind off of Lake.
[doorbell rings]
And this pizza is gonna help you do that.
[door opens]
Oh, hey.
LAKE:
Hey.
Mia.
Felix broke up with me.
‐ Oh, God, I am so sorry.
‐ No, you were right.
I messed up big,
and I was just dumb to think
I could fix it with some romantic
night fish.
‐ Mmm, no. Don't blame yourself.
ANDREW:
You know what'll make you feel better?
Pizza. And you're in luck.
It's just about to get here, so...
I'll bounce.
Give you two some privacy.
‐ [mouths]: Thank you.
[Lake sobbing]
Mmm. Aw... Tell me what happened.
Mmm.
[Lake sniffles]
[sobs]
Oh... [grunts]
[Lake sobbing]
♪ "Windows" by Tayla Parx playing ♪
‐ ♪ I've been talking to myself
in the mirror ♪
♪ Don't know why I burn the ends ♪
♪ Making up some shit that's wrong ♪
♪ Taking pictures off the wall,
see it clearer ♪
♪ You said, you said things
I'm too scared to say ♪
[door closes]
♪ And I go, I go turning love into hate ♪
♪ I swear you could read my mind ♪
♪ 'Cause you know me that way ♪
‐ How was your dinner?
[Victor gasps]
[panting]
Uh‐‐
♪ When it's just the two of us, yeah ♪
♪ I forget all my defenses ♪
♪ Wrapped in your arms,
I'm defenseless ♪
♪ I'm drowning alone ♪
♪ But I'm scared to need ya ♪
♪ Baby, face to face,
I need ya ♪
♪ When it's just the... ♪