[bell ringing]
[students chattering]
♪ "The Boy"
by Shannon and the Clams ♪
‐ ♪ When I was a boy ♪
♪ I learned not to cry ♪
♪ My daddy would scream ♪
♪ I learned how to rhyme ♪
♪ That fool cut off this ribbon of mine ♪
♪ If you ever change your mind ♪
‐ So I just saw Mia,
and for someone who found out
that their boyfriend was gay,
she looked very happy.
‐ Shh! I didn't tell her.
‐ Twist!
‐ I tried to, but her dad and Veronica
came home, and we found out...
Veronica's pregnant.
‐ Double twist.
‐ And they're getting married.
‐ Tri‐‐
‐ Don't say triple twist.
I just want to give Mia
an amazing night at the dance,
and then I'll tell her the truth
tomorrow.
So, did you ask Lake to the dance?
‐ Yeah.
I did.
She passed. Hard.
So I ended things.
But you know, if she liked it,
she should have put a boutonnière on it.
‐ Hi.
‐ Hey.
‐ What's up?
‐ Hey, guys. Um, Felix...
Come on, Wendy, you can do this. Um...
Do you want to go to
the dance with me tonight?
‐ Wow.
Yeah, no, I'd love to.
‐ Really? Amazing. You won't regret it.
Oh, uh, but if you do,
please don't tell me.
FELIX:
Wow.
Can't believe someone wants
to be seen publicly with me at a dance.
‐ Uh, well, just so you know,
I actually have a date tonight, too, so...
[bell rings]
See you tonight.
‐ See you tonight.
‐ Bye.
VICTOR:
Dear Simon, tonight.
I just have to make it through tonight.
♪ upbeat music playing ♪
‐ ♪ Waiting for the time ♪
♪ Waiting for the place ♪
♪ And I, I, I ♪
♪ I, I need ♪
♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be all right ♪
it'll be just fine ♪
♪ If someone has been there before,
say it right now ♪
♪ 'Cause I just need to hear it ♪
♪
MIA: Lake, I know you don't have
a date for the dance tonight,
and you obviously like Felix.
Look, why don't you just apologize
for how you've been acting?
‐ No.
What we had was fun,
but we're from different worlds.
No, Felix should be dating Wendell.
‐ You know her name is Wendy.
‐ And I should find myself a nice,
broad‐shouldered future iBanker,
just like God intended.
‐ Well, if it isn't the future
Spring Fling queen herself.
‐ Kieran, do you have a date
to the dance tonight?
‐ No way. We're all flying solo.
Just me and my boys.
We're gonna make fun of
all the lame‐ass couples.
‐ You and I are going
to the dance together.
‐ Oh, okay.
‐ What?
LAKE:
Great.
I'll text you my addy. See you at 6:00.
KIERAN: Cool.
‐ Bro.
‐ What? I have a thing for bossy women.
My therapist thinks
it's 'cause my mom's a judge.
[Andrew laughs]
VERONICA:
What do you think? This or this?
HAROLD: I'm not feelin' it.
‐ Okay.
‐ Oh, look, there she is!
[both laughing]
How was school today, huh?
Everybody excited about the big dance?
‐ Not as excited as you seem to be.
‐ Oh, come on, baby.
It's your first high school formal.
Now, do you need me to, uh,
show you some of these moves?
You know I got 'em.
‐ I'm good.
I'm good. Yeah.
‐ You sure?
‐ Can I actually borrow Mia
for a minute of girl time?
HAROLD:
Oh, yeah. Of course, of course.
VERONICA: Okay.
HAROLD: You know where
to find me, all right?
[laughing]
‐ So, I...
brought over some of my jewelry for you.
Just in case. I...
I thought you could pick some earrings,
maybe, to go with your dress?
MIA:
Oh.
You don't have to do this.
‐ Well, I never get to wear this stuff.
It's my‐‐
‐ No, no, no.
Not the jewelry.
This. Us.
Look, Veronica, I want you and my dad
to be happy. I really do.
And I'll wrap my head around the marriage,
and the baby, and the whole
happily‐ever‐after thing
you guys have going.
But I don't want to laugh with you
about the school dance.
I don't want to borrow your earrings.
We don't...
We just... We don't have
that kind of relationship.
‐ We don't have it yet, but I am hoping‐‐
‐ I have to go get ready
for the dance, so...
‐ Okay.
[birds chirping]
[distant dog barking]
VICTOR: Hey, um, which of these
do you think Mia will like better?
‐ I'd go with option "B."
‐ Uh, thanks.
Pretty crazy about Dad
punching his boss, huh?
‐ Yep. Not surprised
he kept it from us, though.
This family's full of liars.
‐ Okay. [scoffs]
♪ "Waiting for Tonight"
by Jennifer Lopez ♪
ARMANDO:
Portrait mode, baby.
Remember, you gotta
put it in portrait mode.
‐ I know what I'm doing! Portrait mode.
‐ But it's...
All right.
‐ Get the heck outta here. Okay.
Oh, my gosh. You all look so cute,
I can't stand it!
‐ Yes, yes!
‐ Mia, that dress is giving me life.
‐ Thanks, Isabel.
[chuckles]
‐ You really do look amazing.
‐ You, too.
[all chattering]
‐ You look absolutely beautiful.
‐ Oh, thanks. I make my own eye shadow
out of dehydrated beets.
‐ I make my own conditioner.
With coconut milk.
That's why my scalp
smells like an Almond Joy.
‐ Oh, my God. Kieran, PDA much?
This one and his hands, right?
‐ Lake, you're, you're hurting me.
‐ You're so funny.
ISABEL: Okay, now,
boys, stand behind the girls,
and put your hands on their waists.
‐ Oh, yeah.
‐ That is so cute.
Okay, Adrian, go do it to your sister.
‐ Please don't make me.
‐ Yes, I'm making you. Go.
Oh, that's so cute.
Thank you, papi.
[gasps] This is so cute.
‐ And we're done.
ISABEL: Oh, come on! That is‐‐ argh!
ARMANDO: Pilar!
ISABEL: Aah! You're a natural. Okay.
[camera shutter clicking]
‐ Okay. We're good.
ISABEL:
Aw. Mira.
Low how cute.
‐ Ah, all right.
I think we're gonna get going.
‐ Okay, well, don't do anything
I wouldn't do.
‐ Don't tell him that.
‐ [laughs] What?
‐ You guys seem good, actually.
‐ Yeah. We are.
After you yelled at us,
we stayed up all night. Had a long talk.
‐ Hey, we heard you loud and clear, and...
we're gonna figure out
how to be better for you guys.
ISABEL:
Yeah. So go. Show Mia a good time.
She's a really special one.
‐ Yeah. She is.
♪ "Maniac" by Conan Gray ♪
‐ ♪ And drive you mad ♪
♪ That I'm such a stalker ♪
‐ Wow.
So, um, what do you want to do first?
Do you want to dance? Do you want a drink?
Do you want to drink while dancing,
because that can also be arranged.
‐ Um...
‐ Come do a lap with me.
I need to take a break from Kieran.
He won't stop talking about
how fantasy football works, okay?
‐ All right. Sorry.
I'll, I'll be right back.
‐ It's okay. [chuckles]
MIA: Okay.
[indistinct chatter]
‐ ♪ Psychopathic, don't be so dramatic ♪
[door opens]
[door closes]
‐ Hey.
‐ Look, I wanted to tell you
I read your letter.
And I do forgive you.
‐ Really?
‐ But me forgiving you
doesn't change anything, Victor.
I have a boyfriend, and you kissed me.
So, I need to stay away from you.
I'm sorry.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[water running]
‐ Andrew. Andrew, wait. I can explain.
MIA: Hey, there you are.
Hey, Andrew. Uh, can we dance now?
VICTOR: Yeah.
‐ When are those two getting married?
‐ You know, I'm pretty sure that's not
gonna last much longer.
♪ "Les Cactus"
by The Last Shadow Puppets ♪
♪
‐ Okay, favorite Jimmy Stewart movie.
[imitating Jimmy Stewart]:
Be honest. Go.
♪
Oh, I'm gonna get another drink.
You want anything?
‐ Oh, sure. Another round
of Arnold Palmers would be great.
I like it more‐‐
‐ More Arnold, less Palmer?
‐ You so get me.
♪
‐ Has Victor told you anything lately?
A secret?
‐ A secret? Nope.
Well, you know,
Victor and I aren't close, really, so...
‐ Cut the crap, Felix.
Did he cheat on Mia?
‐ What? No. Why would you say that?
‐ I found a letter he wrote
about kissing some girl named "B."
You know something. I can tell.
‐ Oh. You know, that's,
that's just his creative writing class.
‐ You're Mia's friend, too.
If Victor's sneaking around
behind her back, you should tell her.
‐ He's not sneaking around.
It was a one‐time thing on a work trip,
and he's handling it.
So just give him a little bit more time.
‐ So "B" is someone he works with.
♪
[Isabel laughs]
[Armando chuckles]
ISABEL:
I hope they're having fun at the dance.
‐ Mm.
ISABEL: There's not too much drama.
I always feel like there's so much drama
at high school dances.
‐ Uh, that's 'cause you always
liked to start drama.
‐ What?
‐ You told Katie Sassel she slept her way
to prom queen.
‐ I didn't say that.
I said, "Congratulations on
sleeping your way to prom queen."
[both laughing]
‐ Feels like another lifetime...
[Isabel sighs]
...when we were going to
high school dances together.
‐ Were we crazy?
To get married so young?
Before we even knew who we were?
‐ Probably.
[chuckles]
But, 17 years.
[exhales]
And three perfect kids later,
I still think it's the best
crazy decision I've ever made.
‐ Me, too, Mando.
Whatever happens between us,
I will never stop feeling that way.
‐ Me, too.
[inhales]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ slow song playing ♪
‐ ♪ I know you're close to me ♪
DEREK:
Benji, I literally have two left feet.
Don't make me dance.
Why are you laughing at me?
BENJI: Why are you being so weird?
DEREK: I'm sorry, I just...
I feel kind of weird
being at a high school dance.
‐ Well, can we at least stay for like,
a couple more songs?
‐ Sure.
‐ Hey, guys. Quick "Q," Benji.
You and Victor work together,
like, every day, right?
‐ Uh, yeah. Pretty much. Why?
‐ Do you work with any girls?
‐ Uh, there's Sarah, but she's
more of an angry woman than a girl.
‐ Did Sarah and Victor
ever go on a work trip together?
‐ Um, no. Don't think so.
You know, uh, we were actually
leaving soon, so we're gonna go dance.
‐ Why are you asking him
all these questions?
‐ Something happened on that trip,
but... forget it.
‐ Benji, didn't you and Victor
go on a work trip together?
‐ Uh, yeah. So?
‐ Benji, what's going on?
‐ May I cut in?
I'd love to dance with my bestie.
‐ You want to slow dance with me?
[laughs]
MIA:
Um, okay.
‐ Did you write a letter to Benji?
‐ Yeah. Why?
‐ I think Pilar might have found it.
‐ I knew she was being weird to me.
‐ She was asking me all these questions,
and I was trying to defend you,
and I mentioned your work trip.
And I saw her talking to Derek and Benji,
so now...
[indistinct arguing]
‐ Oh, Pilar, what did you do?
♪
We need to talk. Now.
‐ All right, Salazar, what do you want?
‐ Look, I don't know what you
think you heard, but‐‐
‐ I heard you that kissed Benji.
‐ It's not what it seems.
Or, or I guess it is what it seems,
but, um...
I didn't mean for it to happen.
I've been confused for a long time, and‐‐
‐ Look, are you even into Mia at all?
‐ I love Mia.
Just not like that.
Are you gonna tell everyone?
‐ No. I would never do that.
Mia cares about you.
Okay? This isn't fair to her.
‐ I know. I know. I'm going to tell her.
I swear.
I just gotta get through this dance.
She's been having a really
rough time at home, and I just...
want to give her one last great night,
you know?
BENJI: Derek, it wasn't like that.
It wasn't like that!
‐ If it wasn't like that,
then why didn't you tell me?
‐ Something tells me this is about you,
so, good luck, Salazar.
VICTOR:
Hey, guys.
‐ Save it, okay? I'm done.
I'm out of here.
BENJI: Wait, wait, wait.
‐ It wasn't his fault.
I kissed him. And then he stopped it.
He stopped it, and then he switched
coffee shops to get away from me,
because he didn't want to mess up
your guys' relationship.
That's how much he cares about you, Derek.
So please don't blame Benji
for my stupid mistake.
He's too good a guy to walk away from.
He's thoughtful and sweet,
and patient.
My point is, Benji is the best.
And you guys are awesome together.
So please don't let me and my stupid kiss
mess it up.
I promise to stay out of your way.
Starting now.
♪ "Missing U" by Robyn ♪
‐ ♪ Baby it's so real to me,
now that it's over ♪
‐ But if Tuesday's leg day,
then Thursday becomes arm day,
which means I have to do abs
on Friday instead, actually.
‐ Wow, that is so interesting.
Um, will you excuse me a minute?
‐ Oh, yeah.
‐ Yeah.
‐ ♪ All of the plans we made ♪
♪ That never happened ♪
‐ Oh, hey.
‐ Oh, hi. Just recharging.
Kieran is unstoppable on the dance floor.
‐ Huh. Cool. Yeah, Wendy's, uh,
changing the Band‐Aids on her feet.
She wants to be in tip‐top form in case
the Cupid Shuffle breaks out, so...
[chuckles softly]
‐ ♪ But the picture's incomplete ♪
‐ I'm glad you're having fun, Lake.
‐ You are?
‐ Of course.
I want you to be happy,
and if Kieran is what you're
looking for...
I'm glad you found him.
‐ ♪ But the picture's incomplete ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm missing you ♪
‐ Hey, have you seen Victor?
‐ No.
‐ ♪ I miss you ♪
[footsteps approaching]
‐ Hey.
‐ We broke up.
‐ Benji, I, I'm so sorry.
I, I never meant for any of this‐‐
‐ No, no.
I broke up with him.
‐ Why?
‐ Something's been off with us
for a while.
He makes me feel bad
a lot of the time.
About the stuff I like to do.
About being a romantic.
I want to be with someone who doesn't
make me feel anxious all the time.
You know, someone who makes me feel like
I can just be myself,
and that's enough.
That's how you make me feel, Victor.
♪ "Lost Without You"
by Freya Ridings ♪
[chuckles]
‐ ♪ Watching you go ♪
‐ That's...
That's how you make me feel, too.
‐ ♪ I've ever known ♪
♪ To love someone so much ♪
♪ To have no control ♪
‐ [exhales, then chuckles]
Wow.
‐ Yeah.
What about Mia?
‐ I'm gonna tell her the truth tomorrow.
I, I promise.
‐ Victor, I want this as much as you do.
But I've been out for a while now,
and you...
I mean, have you even
said the words out loud yet?
"I'm gay?"
‐ I'm going to.
I am.
I'm ready.
‐ Okay. I believe you.
[exhales]
‐ ♪ I think I'm lost ♪
♪ Lost ♪
♪ Lost, ooh‐way ♪
♪ Ooh‐way ♪
♪ Ooh‐way, ooh‐way ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
‐ I should get back in there.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Um...
I'll call you tomorrow?
‐ Okay.
‐ ♪ 'Cause I've been strong for so long ♪
♪ That I never thought ♪
♪ How much I love ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Standing on the platform ♪
♪ Watching you go ♪
[chuckles]
‐ And the winners of this year's
Spring Fling king and queen are...
Victor Salazar and Mia Brooks.
[crowd cheering and clapping]
[inaudible]
Uh, Victor Salazar and Mia Brooks.
[chuckles nervously]
Okay, fine. If you don't want
the Olive Garden gift card,
then I'll take it.
[laughs]
‐ Okay, thank you. Um, hi. I'm Lake,
accepting on behalf of Mia,
who has disappeared. Um...
And I'd like to invite
Felix Westen to accept
on behalf of Victor.
Because, um...
[Lake breathes shakily]
Because he told me
he just wants me to be happy.
And the truth is...
That little nerd makes me happy.
Talking to him makes me happy.
Kissing him makes me happy.
And making him happy makes me happy.
CROWD:
Aw...
‐ So, Felix,
please join for me
for the king and queen's dance.
In front of everyone. Watching us.
And maybe someone will go live
and it will go viral,
and follow me through college
and my first year at a PR firm.
[exhales]
But it'll be worth it.
‐ Wendy, I, uh...
‐ It's fine, Felix. I get it.
You're in love with her.
It's kind of obvious. Go.
‐ Thank you.
♪ "Infinity" by Dejavoo ♪
‐ ♪ I'll give you forever
when time is stuck ♪
[crowd cheering and clapping]
♪ Infinity, infinity ♪
♪ Like a diamond in a rope ♪
BOY:
Yeah, Lone Stone!
‐ ♪ From the ground, we will rise above ♪
♪ I'll be the one who's lifting you up ♪
♪ Infinity, infinity ♪
‐ Mia! Mia, wait!
Look, I, I don't know what Andrew
told you, b‐but‐‐
‐ He didn't tell me anything. I saw you.
With Benji.
[exhales]
Just...
All this time, was any of it real?
‐ Yes.
Mia, you're, like, my favorite person.
‐ Goodbye, Victor.
[Mia crying]
‐ She found out. Didn't she?
That you've been cheating on her.
‐ Pilar, it's not what you think.
‐ I don't believe you.
Mom and Dad ripped us out of Texas
and moved us here.
I lost all my friends.
My boyfriend broke up with me.
Mom turned out to be a cheater.
And Dad got himself fired.
My whole world has been collapsing
around me all year.
But I thought,
at least I still have my brother.
At least Victor is still Victor.
You were the only person
I thought I could trust,
and now I feel like I don't even know you.
‐ Pilar, of course you do.
I've been going through something.
And I want to explain it to you,
but not here.
Okay?
So can, can we please go home?
Please.
‐ Yeah. Yeah, we can go home.
‐ Okay.
[car door closes]
‐ You gonna be okay?
‐ [exhales sharply]
I don't know.
I just feel really, really stupid.
‐ Oh, come on. Don't beat yourself up.
Hot girl with secretly gay boyfriend is
a tale as old as time.
‐ Thank you for being there
for me tonight.
You better watch out.
This whole nice guy thing is becoming
a bit of a habit for you.
‐ Don't worry about that.
I'll stuff someone
in their locker tomorrow
and make up for it.
[Mia laughs]
‐ Do you wanna come in?
Keep hanging out?
‐ Uh...
I don't think so.
You know, I don't really want to be
your rebound. I want to be your...
You know.
♪ "Slide" by James Bay ♪
[kisses]
Goodnight, Mia.
‐ ♪ Nobody teaches you how to reminisce ♪
♪ Nobody teaches you to hurt like this ♪
‐ Hey.
‐ ♪ Then we slide ♪
‐ Mia.
‐ ♪ Into the arms of someone else ♪
‐ What's wrong?
‐ ♪ Yeah, we slide ♪
[sobbing]
♪ No more coked up, broke nocturnal kids ♪
♪ Was that ever even us,
Do we know what we missed ♪
♪ Then we slide ♪
[phone chiming]
♪ Into the arms of someone else ♪
SIMON: Victor,
I totally understand wanting to give Mia
the perfect night before you come clean.
But here's the thing about the truth:
You can't control
how people will react to it.
All you can do is be honest
with the people you love.
The rest is up to them.
Whatever happens, you'll always have me.
Love, Simon.
‐ You both are home before curfew.
That's a first.
‐ Yeah. Um...
I have something I need to tell you guys.
‐ Uh, so do we.
ARMANDO:
Come. Sit.
Um...
Okay, uh...
Your mother and I,
we've been talking a lot,
uh, about the way things have been
between us lately.
And, uh, and about the way things
used to be.
What happened back in Texas
between your mother, and...
[sighs]
Roger...
It happened for a reason.
We've been off for a long time.
And after you called us out, mijo,
we were able to admit it,
and stop pretending that we're okay.
And it took so much weight off,
for, for the both of us.
ISABEL:
We were so young when we met.
We were basically your age.
Um, and over the years, we've changed.
So...
We just need to take a step back, and...
...figure out if after all this time,
we still make sense together.
‐ Yeah. And we think that
the best way to do that is...
...for us to spend some time apart.
‐ W‐what do you mean, apart?
‐ We're separating. Just for now.
After what we've been through this year,
we just needed to take a breather.
I'm so sorry, mis amores.
I know this is hard.
‐ I'm gonna change.
‐ Wait, Victor.
What were you gonna tell us?
‐ Nothing.
No.
Not nothing.
Mom... Dad...
I'm gay.
[exhales]
♪ "Home" by Morgxn ♪
♪ Uh ah, ah ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Uh ah,
ah ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Uh ah, ah ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Huh ah, ah ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Uh ah,
ah ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Uh ah, ah ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Uh,
ah, ah ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Uh ah, ah ah ah ah ah ♪