♪
[laughing]
- That was really fun.
Except for the fact that you
kept cheating at mini-golf.
- I did not! I just happened to cough
every time you were about to putt.
[both laugh]
- So, um...
would you want to come up?
- Uh, do I want to? Absolutely.
[laughs] But, I don't think we should.
- Really? Mr. Hookup
doesn't wanna hang out?
- Okay. It's hard to believe,
but, um, I want to
take things slow this time.
When do I get to see you again?
- Well, um, I'm free basically
the whole week.
Except for, um, the Winter Carnival.
- Oh, cute.
Are you gonna drink some hot chocolate
and ride the Ferris Wheel?
[laughs]
You couldn't get more
adorable if you tried.
- So, um...
- Yeah.
- Are you sure you don't want to come up?
- I'll see you soon, Victor.
- Bye.
[laughs]
[text notification chimes]
[sighs]
- There he is!
- Ah!
- Hey. Uh, wh-what's going on?
- Uh, what's going on
is that a little bird told me
that someone is getting a very big honor
at the awards ceremony
before the Winter Carnival.
- Wait, am I getting MVP?
- No. Um...
But, this award is equally important.
I mean, maybe even more important
because you, my friend,
are winning the Bravery Award!
- The... the Bravery Award?
- Right! You know,
for being so brave and open
a-about, you know, being...
- I'm...
getting an award for being gay?
- Yes! I mean,
"yass, queen."
You know, you're getting it for slaying.
Look, Victor, you coming out
made us a-a better
and more inclusive team,
and we all just really want to
celebrate that, okay?
- [sighs] Um, look, can I get
back to you tomorrow
about whether I want to
accept the award or not?
- I didn't realize it would take
any thinking, but, um...
Okay, yeah, sure.
♪
I've already paid the 3D printer
for the award,
so I really hope the answer's yes.
♪ Somebody to tell me it'll be alright ♪
♪ Somebody to tell me it'll be just fine ♪
♪ If someone has been there before
say right now ♪
♪ 'Cause I just need to hear it ♪
- There's nothing else to say.
- I'm not going to beg you
to stay with me.
Goodbye, Stuart.
[puts down phone]
- Mom?
- Oh god!
[Felix laughs]
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I-I didn't see you there.
- Um, e-everything okay?
- Uh, Stuart...
thinks that our relationship
journey has run its course.
- [sighs] Okay.
Hey. Hey, look at me.
Any guy who cannot see
how great you are...
- Aw.
- ...or uses the phrase
"relationship journey..."
- I know.
- Total idiot.
- Yeah. [sighs]
- Do you want me to stay home from school?
We can write mean Yelp reviews
for his meditation video.
- [laughs] No, no. I'm...
I'm fine.
I will be fine.
I want you to walk
that gorgeous girlfriend
of yours to school,
so...
- Yeah. Um, Pilar and I are...
♪
are walking separately.
Hey, I love you.
[kiss] I'll be home soon. Okay?
- Okay.
[sighs]
[school chatter]
VICTOR: The Bravery Award?
Seriously?
Like, what have I been brave about?
- You walked out of the house in that
pajamas-and-hoodie combo.
That takes balls.
- I mean, you don't see people winning
awards for being a straight athlete.
- Yeah, you do.
Literally every other award.
- A-and then the thing is-is, like,
why do I always have to be "Gay Victor"?
Why can't I just be Victor?
- Okay, but this is a chance for you
to stand up in front of our entire school,
and say you're out and proud,
so maybe just take it.
- But, I feel like I am out and proud.
I-I don't need to prove that to anyone.
You know what I mean? And if anyone
deserves a gay award, it's you.
I mean, picking up a hot waiter
while you're at dinner
with your family? Come on.
- I know, right?
And Connor's actually really great.
We've been texting nonstop, and...
his emoji game is fire.
Like, none of that heart-eyes bullshit.
We're talking Draculas,
we're talking flamenco dancers,
even tornadoes.
- Sounds like you really like him.
- We're actually meeting up
for the first time tonight
in real life. I'm a little nervous.
Do you think maybe
you and Nick want to come?
- Yeah! Yeah. Let me--
Let me shoot him a text.
That sounds like something he'd be into.
- Okay, cool. Let me know.
- Yeah.
♪
- Morning.
What's wrong?
- What? How do you know something's wrong?
- We were lovers, Lake,
and I know what you're gonna say.
"Ew, Felix, don't say lovers."
- It's nothing.
[sighs]
Actually, it's not nothing.
It's everything,
and, usually,
I would talk to Mia about it,
but she had to go
meet her stupid baby brother.
- Okay, hit me. I could be Mia for you.
For once, I'd actually feel
good about my legs.
- Okay, fine.
Lucy told me that she's graduating early
and moving to Portland,
which means our relationship
has an expiration date.
- No, no, no.
I don't believe in expiration dates.
That's just a myth big grocery
invented to sell more soup.
Sorry. Go on.
- Well,
I invited her over tonight to talk,
but I have no idea what I'm going to say.
This is usually where Mia would give me,
like, really sage advice.
- Oh, oh, sorry. Um... Yeah, no, uh...
You know, I'm not really much
of a... relationship expert.
I mean...
Pilar dumped me and...
- Wait, Felix. I'm so sorry.
- Thanks. Um... Okay, listen.
You still have a few months
before Lucy leaves, right?
So, instead of stressing about the future,
why don't you just have
a blast with her while you can?
♪
- Okay, that's pretty good advice.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Right?
Suck it, Mia! Who's your bestie now?
- Mm, still not you.
[birds chirping]
- Wait, you guys still haven't
decided on a name?
[both inhale]
- Okay, okay.
Through the entire pregnancy,
I wanted Camden, he wanted Noah.
Everybody said just wait till
he comes out, and you'll know.
Well, he came out,
and he looks like a Camden.
- Camden is a city in New Jersey.
Andrew, come on. Talk to me.
You gotta weigh in here. Hm?
- No, no, no, no. I'm here
just to score some boyfriend points,
not make enemies.
- Smart.
- [laughs] Yes. Very smart.
[phone buzzing]
- Oh.
Excuse me.
Coach, I know this was
a very important opportunity,
but this trip meant a lot to Mia.
There will be college recruiters
at other games.
Yes, yes. I will be back in time
for the awards assembly.
♪
- Hey, Andrew, I was about
to go pick up some takeout.
You wanna come with?
- Yeah.
- Alright.
[hallway chatter]
- Hey.
Is everything okay?
Uh...
Yeah, I guess. I don't know. I-I just
spoke to Coach Ford this morning...
You know what? Actually,
don't worry about it. It's all good.
- Hey-hey, Victor.
I know I said we can't hang out,
but I didn't mean
we can't have a conversation.
- Benji.
There's nothing I'd rather do
than tell you what's going on with me.
It's already killing me
that we're not hanging out,
but now, you're sending me
all these mixed messages,
and I'm just confused.
- Yeah, y-you're right.
I-I'm sorry. Just forget it.
♪
- Thanks for taking me shopping,
and for standing outside the store.
- [laughs]
Well, a little retail therapy is good
for a broken heart sometimes.
But if you ever cut any of these
new shirts into crop tops,
I will ground you again.
- You know me too well.
- Oh! Hey, Isabel. Pilar, oh.
Look at you. Stunning as always.
- Thanks, Ms. Weston. Um,
I'm just gonna put all this stuff down.
Good to see you.
- Oh. Um...
- Sorry about that.
- No, I-- Did I...
- No.
I think anything that reminds
her of Felix is hard right now.
- W-what do you mean? Why?
- Because they broke up.
- Oh...
- Felix didn't tell you.
- No.
No, he did not.
♪
LUCY: Hey.
- Hey, hot stuff.
- What is all this?
- I was thinking we could make a pie
from Dua Lipa's new cookbook,
Dua Lipa's Doin' Pizza.
- Oh. that sounds fun.
I just...
I kind of thought you invited me over
to talk about the whole Portland thing.
- Mm, I mean,
you moving is future us's problem.
I want to live in the now.
Savor every moment we've got.
You know?
- Yeah.
I mean, I guess so.
- Great.
Now, come savor the epic mess
I'm about to make.
[restaurant chatter]
- Man, I love eating
in straight restaurants.
We're the cutest people here.
- We're the cutest ones everywhere.
[laughs]
- This is true.
- Oh! Hey!
Uh, Nick, this is my friend Rahim.
- Hi.
And you must be Connor!
It's so nice to meet you.
I've heard so much about you.
- Really?
- Um, actually, he's heard
a totally chill amount about you.
Almost nothing at all.
- Mm-hmm?
Stalker much? [laughs]
- Look at this jacket!
RAHIM: Oh...
this old thing?
[laughter]
I convinced the Poshmark seller
that I was dying
and wanted to get buried in it, so she
gave it to me at a discounted price. Shh.
[laughter]
VICTOR:
So, Connor, where you from?
[quiet laughter, chatter]
NICK: So, how long you been out here for?
CONNOR: Like, four years.
VICTOR: Okay, cool.
NICK: Nice.
- Dad came here for a job.
Came with him.
- Hey. Sorry, guys. Um...
Is it cool if we sit at the patio?
Those guys are not the vibe.
♪
- Alright, what? Sorry. Go on.
- It's fine. Just ignore them.
- Okay.
NICK: So, um, what were you saying?
Uh, guac for the table?
- Yeah. Can we get some calamari, too?
[insects chirping]
- So I'm sure you probably have guessed
that I really didn't need
any help picking up any food.
[laughs]
- Harold, you are the most
impressive person I know.
You do not need my help
carrying a bag of...
shrimp enchiladas. [laughs]
- Look, I, uh,
I just happened to overhear you
on the phone with your coach.
Sounds like you skipped out
on a big opportunity to be here.
- Yeah.
I missed a game
while we were traveling,
and there were recruiters
from Northwestern at it.
♪ jazz on radio ♪
- Mia didn't understand how
important that would be for you?
- Actually, I didn't tell her.
- Alright, look, Andrew.
I love how devoted you are to my daughter.
I just...
just want to make sure that devotion
doesn't get in the way of your future.
You know, Mia wouldn't want that.
- Mia is my future.
Everything else comes second.
GROUP LEADER:
Alright. Welcome, everyone.
As a reminder, this is a safe space.
Alright, who'd like to start us off?
- I'll go.
I... talked to my ex-boyfriend today.
And it made me...
really sad.
So sad that I wanted to drink,
but I didn't.
And I came here instead.
He's staying away from me right now
because I asked him to.
But...
I'm not even sure
if that's the right thing to do.
[sighs]
See, my parents,
they think he's a trigger.
That the stress of our relationship
made me start drinking again.
[sighs]
They even suggested I go
to boarding school
for a fresh start.
I told them that was a little extreme.
I don't know if they're right
about Victor.
I mean, we were fighting a lot
before we broke up, and...
♪
Yeah, that-that made me want to drink.
But, he also made me
happier than anyone else in the world.
He was the first person
that ever made me feel safe...
and loved.
And I am torturing myself,
staying away from my favorite person
when I'm not even sure
it's the right thing to do.
NICK: [laughs] Wow. A Gay Bravery Award?
- Yeah.
[laughter]
- That sounds even more made up
than the award my mom used to give me,
which was, um,
"Best Recycling Buddy in Atlanta."
[laughter]
- Yeah, I know. It-it's ridiculous.
- What's so wrong about the school
actually wanting to celebrate
Victor's queerness?
- I don't understand why
you're so pressed about this.
It's just, if I win an award,
I want it to be for my talent,
not my sexuality.
- I'm not pressed.
- Um, shall we?
- Yeah. Let's get going.
- I'm gonna go hit the bathroom.
NICK: Me, too.
- We'll see you guys outside?
VICTOR: Yeah.
♪ quiet music ♪
Hey, a-are you okay?
Y-you just seem upset.
- I'm fine.
- What are you looking at?
[distant siren]
Yeah, you wish, fag.
- I wish?
I wish what exactly?
- You know.
- Come on. [scoffs]
- You really think that I would go
for someone like you?
'Cause look at me
and then look at yourself.
Your face is so busted, your hairline's
literally running away from it,
and I am a Persian Clark Kent.
I am tall. I am fashion-forward.
I am the moment.
You are sad. You're ignorant.
You're yesterday.
So, I think you
and your little backup dancer
should probably get going.
You might be late
to your micro-dick meeting.
♪
NICK:
Whoa, is there a problem here?
- It's not worth it, man.
Let's get out of here.
- Holy shit. Are you guys okay?
- Yeah. That was intense.
How did you come up with that on the spot?
- I didn't.
The second I saw those guys,
I was thinking about
what I was gonna say if they bothered us.
I'm constantly in situations like this,
so when there are guys laughing at me,
I can't just ignore them. Not like you.
♪
I really don't want to do this right now.
Wanna go to Brasstown,
get a latte or something,
just the two of us?
- Yeah. For sure.
- It was great meeting you, Nick.
- Yeah.
- Good night, Victor.
♪
- Not going to lie. This whole
1950s housewife role-play
is surprisingly hot.
[soft laugh]
♪ Falling for You
by T. Scarlett playing ♪
♪ Feels like I'm back from the dead ♪
- Are you okay?
[exhales]
- Mm-hmm. Easy breezy.
- Lake, we need to talk.
- No, I don't want to. Okay?
I am keeping things fun and light.
Just Felix and his stupid not-Mia advice.
♪ ...from my apartment window ♪
I just...
I can't live in the now, Lucy.
♪ I want to walk with you ♪
♪ Through stars in the shallows ♪
I just don't understand
why you have to go.
♪ Every time I... ♪
- Lake, I've been sad
for a really long time.
Like, since I was 9.
- When your mom died?
♪ The only things keeping me awake ♪
My step-mom can't stand me.
My dad gets depressed when he looks at me
because I'm the spitting image of my mom,
so he just pretty much never looks at me.
I need a fresh start.
- I get it now.
♪ Falling for you... ♪
I just can't keep falling more
and more in love with you
until you leave me.
- What are you saying?
You want to break up?
- No, no, not at all.
But, I think we have to.
♪ For you, for you, for you... ♪
[sighing]
- They do say
the best revenge for
an almost gay hate crime
is to be really...
really gay.
♪
You're thinking about Rahim, aren't you?
- Yeah, a little bit.
- Give you a ride to Brasstown?
- Thank you.
- I'm doing it for me.
You're gonna be much more
fun once you talk to your friend.
[keys jingle]
- That was...
the best 20-minute nap of my life.
Bless you.
- Are you kidding? It was my pleasure.
Hm.
It's harder than I thought. Being away.
- Yeah, I can tell.
- I fought so hard to stay at Creekwood.
I was sure it was what I wanted,
and, a lot of the time, it is.
It's just joking around
with you and my dad today...
being with the baby...
It's like I finally have a family.
- You want to know what I said
to your dad after our first date?
- I don't know. Do I?
- We didn't get to that stuff
till after our third date.
- Veronica.
- Hey.
After our first date,
I said, "You seem great,
but I am not looking for
anything serious right now."
And I meant it.
But, I agreed to a second date.
And by the time he dropped me off,
I could not imagine my life
without your driven, passionate,
terrible dancer of a father.
- Mm. He's really bad.
- Mia, sometimes we think
we know what we want
with every fiber of our being, and then...
life happens.
♪
- But... [inhales]
Andrew.
It would... it would break him.
- Andrew loves you.
I think he would understand.
- Yeah. Maybe.
What about Zahair?
For his name.
It means shining bright.
- Zahair.
Zahair.
♪
[door opens]
- Hello, movie star.
Did you, uh, do something
different with your hair?
'Cause you are looking like
a young Angela Lansbury.
And I got you
your favorite beef stroganoff.
We are going to get over
this breakup in no time.
- Okay. Well...
we're going to do that another time.
I want you to come with me. Come on.
FELIX: Huh.
What's with the root beer floats
and Millionaire?
- I ran into Isabel, and...
she told me about your breakup.
- [sighs] Okay.
Look, I'm fine.
- You're fine. I know you're fine.
You have been putting
my emotions before yours for so long
that you have gotten really good
at pretending to be fine,
at least in front of me.
- Okay, that's not true.
- It is.
And, Felix, that's done.
You're my son, I'm your mother,
and I am finally well enough
that I can act like it.
So tonight,
we're going to have root beer floats
because you love them.
We're going to watch Millionaire
because Kimmel?
I mean, right? He soothes.
And then, you're going to tell me
how horrible you feel
because I can handle it.
Okay?
Come on.
- D-- [sighs]
♪
I really do miss Pilar.
[sighs]
- I know you do.
I know.
[laughs] Does that help?
- Mm. Yeah.
- Hey.
- Hey. Coffee?
- Oh, sure.
- Oh, fair warning.
Those donuts are so old,
they're basically bagels.
[laughs]
- Hey. W-what you were saying
earlier about wondering
if you're doing the right thing?
- Yeah.
- Only you can answer
that question, Benji.
You have to do what's right for you.
♪
[cafe chatter]
[quiet music playing]
- Hey, what's going on? Wait.
Where's Connor? Did he--
- He's just peeing. Chill.
- [sighs] Okay.
♪ indistinct singing ♪
- We kissed on the walk over here.
- Really?
- Yeah. It was perfect, if you must know.
Not all bitey and slobbery
like the last guy I kissed.
- I'm really glad.
Uh, look, I don't want to take up
too much of your time,
but I just wanted to say sorry
about saying the wrong thing
about those guys.
- It's fine, Victor. It's just...
[sighs]
You're telling me you don't want
the team to give you an award
because you're tired
of always being Gay Victor.
Well some of us can't hide it.
You...
You say you're out and proud,
but you're out and proud
on your own terms.
When you're in the mood.
And I just can't believe
you're not in the mood
to stand in front of our school and say,
"This is who I am."
I don't know, it just...
It feels personal.
- I'm...
I'm going to accept the award.
- Don't do it for me.
- I'm not doing it for you.
I'm doing it for me.
- Okay, great. Now, get lost.
- You better call me later and tell me
all about this magical kiss.
- Okay. Bye-bye.
[insects chirping]
- There you are.
Your dad is ecstatic.
He has said the name Zahair
maybe 500 times in
the past five minutes. [laughs]
[fire crackling]
I need to--
- Andrew, I wanted--
You first. [laughs]
- There was a recruiter
from Northwestern at the game I missed.
♪
- W-why did nobody tell you in advance?
- They did, but I wanted
to be here with you.
- Andrew.
- No. Don't "Andrew" me.
Nothing is more important to me
than being there for you.
I don't like keeping things from you,
so I just wanted to tell you.
Right. Your turn.
What did you want to talk about?
- I just wanted to thank you.
Uh, you-you've been incredible
these last few months.
[laughs]
[doorbell rings]
[game show music playing on TV]
- Okay.
- I'm so sorry.
I didn't know where else to go.
- Uh...
- Lucy and I broke up.
♪
- Y-you're going to be okay.
[insects chirping]
VICTOR:
Thanks for being so cool about tonight.
Things kind of went off
the rails there for a second. [laughs]
- Victor, when I came out
of the restaurant today,
and I saw those guys messing with you,
I just wanted to protect you.
I guess scary shit finds a way
of making you realize
what's important to you.
- Yeah. It does.
- Yeah.
♪ Low Tide by DRAMA playing ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mmm... ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm not just anybody ♪
♪ My love won't be ♪
♪ Taken down by a bullet ♪
♪ And I've tried everything ♪
♪ And I'm best at disappearing ♪
- I thought I heard you come in.
♪ And your love used to bring out... ♪
Did you have a good night?
♪ The best in me... ♪
- No, not really.
Hey, you know how...
you and Dad wanted me
to think about boarding school?
- Yeah, why?
- Because I want to go.
♪ You're too cool to fall in love ♪
♪ You're too smooth to get caught up ♪
♪ In something you can't ♪
♪ Walk away from ♪
♪ And I know it's safer to believe ♪
♪ That you don't mean a thing ♪
♪ To me, but... ♪
♪