[cell phone chiming]
[sighs]
[cell phone continues chiming]
SIMON:
Victor!
[exhales]
In honor of your first day
back at Creekwood,
I wanted to say
I'm proud of you.
You and Benji
coming out as a couple at school‐‐
that's huge!
If you're anything like me,
you're probably trying to pick
the perfect look for your coming out‐‐
your "coming outfit"?
There's a lot of pressure
on gay guys to be stylish.
‐ Good morning.
‐ Are you going to school,
or back in time to play jazz?
‐ Uh, lose the hat?
‐ Burn the hat.
‐ Okay, come on,
it's your first day of school.
We're already late.
I wanna see more shoes on you.
Less belly button on you.
‐ Hashtag free the belly button.
‐ Um, honey,
I know things have been, uh...
not the same between us.
But I love you...
so much.
‐ I know.
‐ Good.
Good. So, this thing
between you and Benji...
your boyfriend...
I don't have to tell you how unkind
kids in high school can be
when you're different.
‐ No. You don't.
‐ And once you start telling people,
you know, you can't take it back.
People are gonna hear your name,
it's the first thing
they're gonna think about.
I just want to make sure that
that's something that...
you want.
‐ Yeah. It is.
‐ Okay.
‐ Are we done?
‐ ♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be all right ♪
♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be just fine ♪
♪ If someone has been there before,
say it right now ♪
♪ 'Cause I just need to hear it ♪
♪
‐ I'm sorry, son,
but the rent is due in full.
And you can't keep
bribing me for extensions
with homemade banana bread.
‐ Okay. Okay, fine.
I didn't want to do this,
but I have some old pills
from when they thought I had ADD.
Now, they're very expired,
but if you crush 'em up,
I'm sure they're gonna
give you a little bit of a rush.
‐ Felix, uh...
I haven't seen your mother
around in weeks.
Is everything okay?
‐ Yeah. You know, she's, um,
feeling a little under the weather.
But, you know, we've lived here
for twelve years,
so, you know, we're good‐‐
we're good for the money.
‐ Yeah. Get it to me by Friday.
But no more grace periods.
And, uh...
Leave the ADD pills in my mailbox.
‐ Hey. What was all that
with the landlord?
‐ Nothing. Nothing. But, uh, "landlord"
is a f‐‐ is a funny word.
Landlord. I mean, what is he?
[with British accent]:
Lord of the land? [chuckles]
[normal voice]: Oh! Victor. Good.
Should we walk to school? I vote yes!
♪
[engine revving]
[tires screeching]
‐ Lake!
Oh, my God.
That felt like Ford v Ferrari.
I can't believe you passed
your driver's test.
‐ No, I know. I can't believe it either.
I'm, like, a danger to others.
Okay, can we talk about
the gay elephant in the room?
‐ Look, it's gonna be a strange day,
but the sooner that everyone knows
Victor is with Benji,
the sooner we can move past it.
‐ Okay, yes, queen.
Love how glass half‐full you're being.
I do feel like we need to
get on top of the story
and make it absolutely clear
you did not turn him gay.
‐ What?
Oh, come on. Nobody's gonna think
that I turned him gay.
‐ Ugh. Sweet, naïve Mia.
You know that kids here love to gossip.
Remember that time I went to
a Harry Styles concert,
and everyone was saying
we hooked up in his dressing room?
‐ [chuckles]
Nobody was saying that, except you.
[both chuckle]
‐ Oh. Good for Andrew.
I mean, how many times did you have to
tell him you're not interested?
Move on dot org. Am I right?
‐ Mm‐hmm. Let's go this way.
‐ ♪ Whoa oh oh oh ♪
♪ Whoa oh oh, oh oh oh ♪
BENJI:
God, I love the first day of school.
You get to see who got bangs,
who got boobs...
who got a new boyfriend...
[laughs nervously]
Are you stressed
about telling everyone?
‐ No. I'm good.
Mia.
Hey. I, I didn't see you there.
‐ Yeah. Well, at, at least I didn't
walk in on a make‐out sesh this time.
[both chuckle]
‐ Yeah. Uh...
It was really weird
not talking to you all summer.
I mean, I totally get
why you were ignoring me,
but, um, it's really good to see you.
‐ I should go.
‐ Well, that was horrible.
‐ Yo, Salazar.
You still, uh, Vic deep in that?
[Wyatt laughs]
You get it? It's like, dick deep, but‐‐
‐ No, no. Yeah, yeah. I get it.
Just... not funny.
Um, also, we broke up.
‐ What? Why?
‐ Uh...
Uh...
You know.
I, I was here for the summer,
and she was 200 miles away
at some summer camp,
you know, eating s'mores,
or whatever.
It was just really hard to do
the long‐distance thing over FaceTime.
‐ Yeah. Well, you know what they say.
You know, camp brings out the tramp.
[all laugh]
‐ What?
No, she didn't cheat on me or anything.
It was‐‐
‐ Don't worry, Salazar.
We'll find you a new honey soon.
‐ For sure.
[Teddy chuckles]
‐ What was that?
I thought we were gonna be honest.
‐ We will be.
Okay, it's just the first minute
of the first day.
Can we just kind of ease our way into it?
‐ Whatever you want.
♪
WYATT: Victor Salazar and Mia Brooks
broke up this summer.
Don't let your girl
go to camp!
♪
STUDENT 1:
Aw. Why'd they break up?
STUDENT 2:
She cheated. Obvies.
STUDENT 3:
I heard she was FaceTiming with Victor
right before she had full‐on sex
with some lifeguard,
and she left her camera on,
so he saw the whole thing.
STUDENT 4: I heard she put his junk
between two graham crackers,
and the next thing you know,
s'mores.
STUDENT 5:
Did you hear about Mia and this Victor?
STUDENT 6: Yo, what was Mia thinking?
STUDENT 7: They broke up.
STUDENT 6:
Mmm, she's so fine.
STUDENT 7: That slut.
STUDENT 8: Oh, my God.
Victor and Mia broke up?
STUDENT 7: Oh, my God.
STUDENT 6: Can we not slut‐shame, please?
STUDENT 8: Mia and the s'mores!
STUDENT 8: That's gross.
STUDENT 6:
S'mores?
‐ Oh, hell, no!
[bell ringing]
[students chattering]
‐ Well, hello, everyone.
‐ I think his tongue
is so far down her throat
it's cutting off her hearing.
‐ Sorry.
This one can barely keep
her hands off me.
Can you blame her?
My body's been next level
ever since I started drinking
raw eggs for breakfast.
‐ He's had food poisoning twice.
So, have you guys started telling
people you're dating yet?
‐ Nope.
‐ Um, hey, can I talk to you for a second?
Look, I want to tell people.
Just maybe not today.
‐ Victor, all I wanna do
is reach across that table,
and hold my boyfriend's hand.
And, and I know why
that sounds scary, but...
sometimes in the long run,
doing something scary is worth it.
LAKE:
Mia, Mia, Mia, Mia, Mia!
‐ Hey, boo. Where do you want
to sit this year?
‐ Can't talk. Girl drama.
Have you seen Creeksecrets?
‐ I never read Creeksecrets.
Why are you gasping for air?
‐ So, um, there's a rumor going around
about you and Victor.
It's not actually that bad.
That's a lie. It's horrible.
Maybe we should just transfer schools?
‐ Oh, my God. I‐‐
Wait, I thought‐‐
I thought Victor was gonna
tell the truth about him and Benji.
‐ Yeah, well, obviously he didn't,
and you know the rumor mill here
is just absolutely disgusting.
WYATT:
Hey, Mia. Got you something.
Since you love s'mores so much.
[students laughing]
‐ It's not true, dumbass.
‐ Victor's our boy, right?
And something happened,
or you'd still be together.
WYATT: Yeah.
‐ Just tell them, Mia.
KIERAN:
Yeah, Mia. Tell us.
‐ Come on. We're leaving.
WYATT Okay, if it's not true,
why are you walking away?
‐ Yo, what's your problem?
‐ She cheated on you.
We were just having your back, bro.
‐ Yeah. You don't need that
s'more whore.
[all laughing]
‐ Ah! Ow. What the hell?
CROWD: Whoa!
STUDENT:
Oh, shit!
[students murmuring]
[knocking on door]
‐ Come in.
‐ Oh, no.
Sweatpants. Sad girl music.
What was it, a lousy first day of school?
Come on. What's wrong?
‐ Nothing.
I just had a day.
You look nice.
‐ Oh.
Well, thank you.
It's the botany department gala tonight.
As a matter of fact,
why don't you come with?
[sighs]
Come on, Beans.
Look, Veronica is stuck at work.
This is a great opportunity
for you and me to hang out.
One on one.
We don't get to do it that often.
‐ All right. All right, I'm in.
‐ That's what I'm talking about.
‐ But...
if you call me Beans in public,
I'm out of there.
HAROLD: You got it, sweetheart.
Now, let's get dressed.
Fifteen minutes, we leave.
‐ Okay.
ARMANDO:
Victor, when your principal called us
to tell us that you
shoved another student,
I thought she had the wrong number.
‐ Yeah. Because our son
doesn't do things like that.
‐ I'm, I'm so sorry, okay?
I, I messed up.
‐ Yeah, you did.
But we told her that things
have been hard at home
because of the separation, and they're...
they're letting you off with detention.
‐ Okay.
That, that's it?
ARMANDO:
Well, the principal told us that
Wyatt was spreading
nasty rumors about Mia.
‐ Yeah. So we understand
you felt you had to...
stand up for her.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Whatever else you're going through,
it's clear that you still care about her.
‐ So, I‐I'm not grounded.
I'm not punished.
‐ Did you want to be?
[chuckles]
‐ I'm just getting the rules straight.
So, I, I'm allowed to shove someone,
as long as it's over a girl?
‐ No.
We just understand why you're upset.
‐ No, you don't.
Do you want to know
why I'm so upset?
It's because all day,
I could hear your voice in my head
begging me not to tell anyone
that I was gay.
[scoffs]
‐ Isa?
‐ No, I was‐‐
I just told him to be careful.
I was just trying to protect you.
You know how cruel kids can be.
‐ You're the only one that's being cruel.
The only reason why you don't want me
telling anyone that I'm gay
is because you don't want me to be gay.
‐ You're putting words in my mouth.
‐ Then tell me I'm wrong.
Tell me that you're okay with it.
Tell me that you support me.
‐ Victor, this...
this is all really new for us.
But of course we support you.
No matter what.
‐ Not you.
Her.
♪
[sobs softly]
[indistinct chatter]
MIA: And Lake is making me take AP French,
because she thinks
that the teacher is hot,
but he's actually not.
She's just kind of confused by the accent.
‐ Hey, Philip. How you doing, man?
Good to see you.
Look, I gotta get a little face time
with the donor committee.
Now, as soon as I'm done,
I'm all yours, all right?
I'll be back in two, maybe three minutes.
♪ soft piano music playing ♪
‐ Don't judge.
I'm not on the meal plan,
so this is my dinner.
Starving artist and everything.
‐ Hmm. You're an artist?
Me, too.
‐ Tyler.
‐ Mia.
‐ What year are you?
‐ Um, freshman.
College freshman.
‐ Same.
‐ So, what brings you to this rager
for the botany department?
‐ Oh, is that what this is?
‐ Yeah.
‐ I literally just saw food
and an open bar,
and like, walked right in.
[cell phone chimes]
[sighs]
‐ Do you want to get out of here?
Or‐‐ I mean, not like that.
I mean just, like, go do something fun?
I could really use a little fun.
‐ Sure.
A couple of my roommates are having
wine and cheese on the quad.
‐ That sounds perfect.
‐ It's BYO wine.
[door closes]
‐ Hey. Whatcha doing?
‐ Homework.
Which you shouldn't do in the dark.
Strains the eyes. Causes migraines.
‐ Okay, boomer.
‐ Boomer? I am ten months older than you.
‐ Yeah, but you're such a grandpa.
You probably have a Werther's Original
in the pocket of your cardigan.
‐ I wish.
‐ You know, sometimes I come out here
to escape the badness of my apartment.
My parents' separation,
and how weird my mom is being with Victor.
So, what are you escaping?
‐ Mom stuff. Money stuff.
‐ Yeah, I kind of eavesdropped
on you with the landlord.
‐ We're basically broke.
My mom always goes through
these episodes
where she's either depressed or manic.
She usually bounces back
after a week or two.
But this time, um,
she stopped going to work.
And lost her job.
Anyway, um...
I'm two hundred dollars short on rent.
And she won't get out of bed.
I don't know what to do.
‐ Two hundred, right?
‐ Holy shit.
Pilar, how did you get that?
‐ It's from my summer job
selling mall pretzels.
[chuckles]
You get a lot of tips when you smile
and bat your eyes at old men.
I guess pervs love pretzels.
‐ I, I, I can't‐‐ I can't take your money.
‐ Don't be stupid.
Me and my friends were saving up
to see Billie Eilish,
but it's sold out now, anyway, so...
You'll pay me back.
‐ Pilar, um...
I can't believe this.
‐ You've been a good friend
to my brother.
And if you can't pay rent,
and had to move out,
he'd really miss you.
‐ Oh.
And Victor would be the only one
who'd miss me.
‐ Don't make it weird.
[laughs]
[group laughing]
‐ So, the whole time you were together,
you had no idea he was gay?
‐ None.
Which is crazy,
because I watch so much Bravo.
[all laughing]
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Uh, I don't know why I'm going on
about my embarrassing life.
[laughs] Mmm, it's probably because
you guys are strangers.
‐ Oh! I have had at least
two gay boyfriends.
And the jury's still out on Steve.
[all laughing]
Gay guys are better looking.
They're better listeners.
They're just better at everything.
[Lisa laughs]
‐ Well, not everything.
LISA: Okay. [laughs]
[Mia chuckles]
[cell phone buzzes]
‐ Ah... I, I really needed this.
So thank you guys.
‐ You headed out?
Which dorm? I'll, I'll walk you.
‐ No, no, no. You stay.
Um, I live off campus.
But...
Here's... here's my number.
Um, I want to see you again.
‐ I'd love that.
‐ So that's why you couldn't
come out today?
Your mom got in your head?
Vic, you could've just told me.
‐ It's just embarrassing to care about
what your mom thinks.
You're lucky that your parents
are so cool with it.
‐ Yeah, now they are.
It took my dad a minute.
VICTOR: Really?
What do you mean?
BENJI: Well...
A month after I came out,
my dad said he wanted to have lunch.
But as we're parking in the restaurant,
I realize it's not a restaurant at all.
It's a strip club.
‐ What?
‐ I know. So, we go in,
and he's sweating and beet red,
just trying to act like
this is a totally normal thing
for us to be doing together.
He tells me, "It's cool if you're gay,
but how can you be so sure?"
And he waves over a stripper
to give me a lap dance.
‐ No!
‐ Swear to God.
Her name was Jacuzzi.
Anyway, some Pussycat Dolls song
comes on,
and Jacuzzi puts
her glittery boobs right in my face.
‐ So, so what did you do?
‐ I shut it down.
Gave Jacuzzi a nice tip,
told her I was gay, and marched out.
On the ride back,
I told my dad
nothing was ever gonna change who I was.
What?
‐ I'm sorry.
For not being as brave as you are.
I promise I'm trying.
Just... just please don't give up on me.
‐ Victor.
[exhales]
I don't think I could give up on you,
even if I wanted to.
We'll tell the school
when you're ready, okay?
And, and if I wanna hold your hand,
or do something boyfriendy,
then I'll just...
I'll just do this.
[chuckles softly]
It'll be our little secret.
Okay?
‐ ♪ We're only halfway... ♪
ISABEL: Hi.
‐ Hey.
‐ Adrian! Papi's here
to drive you to school!
‐ Is Victor here?
After that fight last night,
I just wanted to see him.
‐ No. He said he had to go to school early
for a "thing."
Pretty sure that "thing" was avoiding me.
[tea kettle whistling]
‐ Well, I didn't sleep a wink.
Instead, I ended up going down
an internet rabbit hole.
Do not Google "dad with gay teen,"
by the way.
[liquid pouring]
I'm not sure I can call myself
a Catholic anymore.
[Isabel laughs]
But no, I, I did wind up
finding something useful.
There's a group for parents with gay kids.
They have a chapter in midtown.
Meets every other Tuesday.
‐ I am not airing
our family's dirty laundry
in front of a group of strangers.
‐ Well, Isa, something's gotta change.
Right now we're losing him.
[sighs]
‐ I actually think you're actually getting
worse at driving.
‐ I lightly grazed a mailbox. Boo‐hoo.
[Mia chuckles softly]
Hey! I see you spreading rumors,
Marjorie Nelson!
Mind your business,
or I will tell everyone
you have two vaginas!
I don't know why, but like,
that seems believable to me.
‐ Ah, just ignore her.
All the gossip will blow over eventually.
‐ You're being very Zen about this.
‐ Mmm.
[cell phone chimes]
[chuckles] I guess I'm just over
the high school drama.
VICTOR:
Hey. Mia. Can we talk for a second?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ I don't know if you saw,
but I, I texted you a bunch last night,
and‐‐
‐ Yeah. I saw.
‐ I just‐‐ I want to say sorry.
For everything, like‐‐
All these rumors started
because I was too scared
to come out, and‐‐
‐ The rumors started
because it's high school. [laughs]
I mean, Creekwood gonna Creekwood.
‐ Yeah. I, I guess,
but still, you don't deserve this,
and if there's anything I can do‐‐
‐ Okay. Victor. Victor.
You don't owe me anything.
You're not my boyfriend anymore.
‐ I know I'm not your boyfriend.
But we're not nothing to each other.
Are we?
‐ I don't know what we are.
I'll see you around.
‐ What do you mean
you can't afford to go to Billie Eilish?
Tickets go on sale tomorrow.
‐ What about your pretzel money?
‐ Something more important came up.
‐ Hey, handsome.
‐ Careful.
♪
‐ What are you doing?
‐ What I should have done yesterday.
Excuse me. Hey!
Uh... so...
Not that it's anyone's business,
but Mia didn't cheat on me.
And it's also not her fault
that we broke up.
It's not anyone's fault. Um...
The truth is...
I'm gay...
and I'm with Benji now.
[students murmuring]
STUDENT: Aw, that's so cute!
VICTOR:
I‐I don't want it to be a secret anymore,
because I'm happy about it. Like...
Like really, really happy.
STUDENT [softly]: That's cool.
STUDENT 2: Yeah.
‐ So, uh... yeah.
Uh, we won't be
taking any questions at this time.
‐ ♪ I didn't know then
what I know now ♪
VICTOR:
Dear Simon,
it wasn't as smooth as I planned,
but Benji and I are
officially out at Creekwood.
To be honest, I don't know
how people are gonna react,
and I don't care.
You taught me everything I know
about being brave.
And, and who knows?
Maybe one day I can inspire someone
to be themselves,
the same way you inspired me.
‐ ♪ Don't let go ♪
♪ 'Cause heaven is a hand to hold ♪
VICTOR: Love, Victor.
‐ ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ Ooh‐ooh‐ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ Ooh‐ooh‐ooh ♪