[indistinct chatter]
♪
‐ Wow, we're pretty high up, huh?
It didn't look that high
when we were on the ground,
but now... [laughs]
‐ Are you afraid of heights?
‐ Oh, no. No. This is amazing.
I love this. [laughs]
‐ The trick is not looking down.
Just... look at me.
♪
[crowd booing]
‐ Wait, wait, what's happening?
[loud booing]
‐ I think they're... booing us.
‐ [screaming]:
Boo!
‐ Boo!
‐ [yelling]:
Boo!
[panting]
♪ upbeat music playing ♪
‐ ♪ Waiting for the time ♪
♪ Waiting for the place ♪
♪ And I, I, I ♪
♪ I, I need ♪
♪ Somebody to tell me
it'll be all right ♪
it'll be just fine ♪
♪ If someone has been there before,
say it right now ♪
♪ 'Cause I just need to hear it ♪
♪
‐ Good morning.
ARMANDO: Morning, flaco.
I didn't see too much of you
at the carnival last night.
Did you and that boy have fun?
‐ Wh‐what boy?
ISABEL: The weird kid from down the hall
who looks like Rachel Maddow.
‐ Oh. Felix.
Yeah. Yeah, we had a good time.
‐ Oh, my God!
That thirsty little b‐‐
‐ Aah, aah.
Pilar, I don't think Jesus
wants you to finish that sentence.
‐ Eric just liked one of
Giselle Rodriguez's selfies.
‐ Okay, so your long‐distance boyfriend
clicked hard on a picture.
Nobody died.
‐ Giselle might. Next time I visit Texas.
‐ Hey, so, I need $500
to join the basketball team.
Uh, it's for travel and uniforms.
‐ What are the uniforms made of?
Fifty‐dollar bills?
‐ I would also like $500.
‐ Nobody's getting $500.
You guys want some spending cash,
you get an after‐school job.
‐ Okay. Vámonos, vámonos.
Can you please make sure that your brother
really brushed his teeth?
‐ Yeah.
ADRIAN:
I did. I'm a child, not an animal.
VICTOR:
I'll check if his toothbrush is wet.
ADRIAN: Good luck finding it.
VICTOR: Come on.
[sighs]
‐ Amor, Victor is the most responsible
kid on the planet.
We can't just give him the money?
‐ I'm sorry.
‐ But if he needs it to join the team‐‐
‐ Moving across the country
is expensive, okay?
And it's not my fault we had to do that.
FELIX: So, you turnt up
for day number two?
‐ I don't know,
I just wanna fly under the radar today.
[phone buzzing]
You know, just go 24 hours without
appearing on that stupid Creek Secrets.
‐ Well, the bad news is
you made it zero hours.
But the good news is
this time the story is positive.
You've been dubbed a hottie?
I would give my appendix
to be called a hottie on Creek Secrets.
I mean, if I still had an appendix.
Thanks a lot, Dr. Azarian.
‐ I went on a Ferris wheel
with some girl. Why is this news?
‐ Mia is not just some girl.
Everyone is obsessed with her.
Even the bathroom graffiti
about her is respectful.
SARAH:
Next.
‐ Hello. My friend here will have
the cold brew, and I will have the usual.
‐ Wait, are you guys hiring?
‐ Here. Just, mm,
fill out this application.
‐ Okay, great.
‐ Not here!
On your own time, buddy. Next.
‐ You're getting a job?
‐ Yeah, I have to pay for basketball.
My dad's doing well,
but we're not Creekwood rich.
[doorbell rings]
‐ Hey, yeah, door's open.
[door opens]
All right, give me, like, two minutes.
[door closes]
[Mia sighs]
‐ So, did you see the post about you
and the new kid on Creek Secrets?
Can you believe it?
‐ Yeah, I can believe it. You posted it.
‐ Wait, your dad lets you write checks?
Also, your dad still has checks?
‐ Yeah, somebody has to pay
the housekeeper when he's not here.
‐ Ugh. Where in the world is
Harold Brooks this week?
‐ Uh, Berlin?
Some, uh, fundraising thing
for the university.
‐ Oh. We have to have a party.
You know. Small, curated guest list,
some digestifs, fromage, aperitifs...
Whoa, do I speak French?
‐ No more parties, Lake.
‐ You can invite Ferris wheel boy.
Come on. I know you wanna tap
that Tex ass.
‐ Oh, okay. Okay,
there is something about him.
I mean, that entire time
we were on the ride,
he didn't brag about himself,
or do any of the, the lame stuff
guys usually do,
like accidentally graze my boobs.
‐ So, yes? It's Friday night.
Come on. Who else has a baller mansion
with zero parental supervision?
FELIX: Hey. Now that you're dating Mia,
you think you can put in
a good word with Lake?
I kind of have a thing for her.
I've been writing a period
romantic novel about us.
The year is 1875,
and a young sheriff named Felix
has just moved in next to
a widowed candle maker named Lake.
‐ No, no, no.
‐ And‐‐
‐ Don't spoil it.
Also, I'm not dating Mia.
‐ Well, Creek Secrets says otherwise.
One of the commenters already
gave you a combined couple name:
Victor‐ia.
‐ Dude, you're insane.
No one's gonna care about this.
♪ "Pop Panic"
by Lex Junior Feat. JustJohn. ♪
VICTOR:
Hey, Simon.
So, last night, I asked this girl Mia
to ride the Ferris wheel with me.
She seems really cool,
and I don't know,
maybe I just wanted to fit in.
But I guess I overshot,
because literally overnight,
I have become...
popular.
[bell ringing]
I'm telling you, nothing happened
on the Ferris wheel. I swear.
‐ He's lying, man. Look at that smile.
He's in the mile‐high club.
[laughing]
‐ He said nothing happened.
And by the way,
a Ferris wheel is a not a mile high.
Idiots.
[Pilar sighs]
‐ Nice greeting.
‐ Eric just got tagged in a photo
with Giselle at the mall.
The mall, Victor!
‐ Whoa, she's hot!
Oh, sorry.
[whispers] She's hot.
‐ Eric loves you. Don't be crazy.
‐ Hi.
Uh, I, I hope people haven't been
giving you too much crap
about the Creek Secrets post.
This school is desperate for drama.
People are,
are still talking about the time, um,
a pigeon flew into the cafeteria,
and ate a chicken nugget.
‐ Hashtag "cannibal pigeon."
Never forget.
‐ Hi. Hello. Victor's best friend here.
[in Irish accent]:
Top of the mornin' to ya, lassies.
‐ Okay. It's actually 1:00 p. m., but, uh,
Victor, did Mia tell you she's hosting
a little get‐together tonight?
‐ What's the occasion?
‐ The occasion is a free mansion
with zero adult supervi‐sh.
Starts at nine.
Also, it's a stoplight party,
so dress accordingly.
MIA: Wait, what?
‐ Dude, I always want to go
to a stoplight party.
Or really, any party.
‐ Um, what's a stoplight party?
‐ Oh. Everyone wears a color
to show their relationship status.
If you wear green, it means you're single,
ready to mingle.
Red means you're in a relationship,
and yellow means you're
into someone at the party.
You guys didn't have this in Texas?
‐ We had church barbecues.
If you wear a sundress
that's above the knee,
it means you go to Hell.
[Victor chuckles]
‐ Huh. Victor, you have to wear yellow
to declare your feelings for Mia.
I mean, you like her, right?
Why wouldn't you?
‐ Why did you say it's a stoplight party?
‐ Because. People hook up faster
at themed parties.
Haven't you seen Eyes Wide Shut?
ANDREW: What's up, nerds?
LAKE: Andrew. Hey.
Did you get a haircut?
‐ I did not.
‐ Right on. Uh, well, we're having
a stoplight party at Mia's tonight.
‐ Really. You know, it's funny.
I would have thought you'd be too busy
taking random charity cases
on carnival rides.
‐ Bye, Andrew.
‐ Oh, you know what?
There's a freshman with scoliosis.
You could take him
on the spinning tea cups.
‐ I can't believe you like him.
He's such a jerk.
‐ [laughs]
I know. He's so mean.
[exhales]
‐ Excuse me?
‐ Oh, hey, man. What's up?
It's Benji. From school?
‐ Oh. Oh, I, I just wanted to interview
for the barista job.
But it, it's cool‐‐
‐ Lucky for you,
I'm the assistant manager.
Come on back. Let's talk.
So, Victor, you have
any experience making coffee?
‐ Um, I have experience drinking coffee.
‐ [laughs]
Well, it's not rocket science.
You know, once you can pull
a shot of espresso,
you can basically make any drink.
Here. Watch.
First, you take the portafilter,
and fill it with grounds.
♪ "Real Games" by Lucky Daye ♪
‐ ♪ Think I just need
to kiss you goodbye ♪
BENJI: And then pack it real tight.
See how tight that is?
‐ Um‐hmm.
‐ ♪ These words will keep
them in this bed ♪
♪ Ah ♪
BENJI: And while that brews,
we steam the milk.
‐ ♪ But I know this as good as it gets ♪
‐ Now you try. Here.
‐ ♪ So baby we can take it slow ♪
‐ There you go. You're a natural.
‐ ♪ Ooh ♪
[splashing]
‐ [grunts] I am so sorry.
‐ It's fine.
‐ You know what?
This, this was a bad idea.
I'm, I'm sorry to waste your time.
[scoffs]
[exhales]
♪
‐ [laughs]
You wore yellow!
‐ Yeah, I did.
And like you said, why wouldn't I?
‐ What about me? I want to make it
super clear that I'm into Lake.
‐ Yeah. I think it's clear.
‐ You two look like a couple of bananas
getting ready to split.
‐ We're dressed like this for a party.
‐ Uh, you didn't tell me anything
about a party. Whose party?
FELIX:
Oh. This girl, Mia. She likes Victor.
‐ Oh! All right! Who is this girl?
Is she cute?
‐ Dad, don't be weird.
‐ Oh, she's gorgeous.
Kind of like a young my mom.
‐ All right, macho.
Well, uh, you go to your party,
and, uh, show this Mia girl
a good time, okay?
‐ Okay.
‐ Right.
[Armando chuckles]
Hola, mi nena.
How was your day?
[slams]
[imitating Pilar]
"Great, Papi. Thanks for asking."
‐ Come on, people are here!
Why aren't you wearing yellow?
‐ Oh. I just... I thought if
there is something between me and Victor,
I'd want it to be natural, you know?
Not forced by some weird party game.
Wait, why are you wearing red?
You're single.
‐ Because. There's nothing hotter
than being unavailable,
so, when Andrew sees me wearing this,
he'll think I'm dating someone,
and want to get with me.
‐ But you're not dating anyone.
‐ Sure, I am.
His name is Bruno.
He's a freshman at Georgia Tech.
Here. Look how hot we look together, hmm?
‐ That is one‐hundred percent
your cousin Robert.
Wait. Lake, that picture's from
your nana's funeral!
‐ Whatever. Nana would have wanted me
to find love with Andrew.
[exhales] Back to you.
Want to know what I think?
‐ Not really.
‐ You like a boy for the first time
in forever,
and you're scared to
put yourself out there.
Sometimes in order to be happy,
you need to be vulnerable.
So just yellow up. Oh‐kurr?
[doorbell rings]
[gasps] Ooh!
♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ "Killa Shit Funk"
by Black Caviar Feat G. L. A. M. ♪
‐ ♪ Angel I drop on, I was up too ♪
♪ Y'all sister at?
Y'all ain't really nothing knew ♪
♪ I'm into that
Kick clap in the boom ♪
♪ Now bitches whack
Step back, any room ♪
‐ Yo, mile‐high, what's up?
VICTOR: Hey, bro, how ya doin'?
BOY: What's up, man?
VICTOR: How ya doin'?
‐ ♪ Sub, sub, sub, subliminal ♪
LAKE:
Andrew.
You are so lucky you get to wear green.
I just had to wear red.
'Cause of my boyfriend. Bruno.
He's in college. Yeah.
Uh, lacrosse scholarship.
‐ Hey, Salazar.
Why don't you come on back?
The rest of the crew's out here.
‐ Sorry, it's a team thing.
‐ Do you mind? Uh, I'll be right back.
‐ Oh. Sure. Yeah. I'll be, I'll be fine.
Oh. Hey.
So, uh, this Bruno guy.
Is it, uh, is it, is it serious?
[exhales]
‐ So, you're not actually friends
with that loser, are you?
‐ Uh, no, no. We're just neighbors.
‐ Hey, Vic, you seen Mia yet?
VICTOR: Why, is she looking for me?
[all laughing]
‐ Look, man, I know that you like her.
You just‐‐ You can't wear that shirt.
‐ I can't?
‐ Well, it's just so...
...desperate.
Unless you want to come off thirsty.
Is that what you're going for?
‐ No.
‐ Here. Why don't you take this?
I have to exercise my
second amendment, anyhow.
Yeah, that would be
the right to bear arms.
♪ "Electricity" by
Silk City, Dua Lipa ♪
‐ ♪ Falling into you ♪
♪ Ooh baby ♪
♪ I'ma love you differently ♪
‐ Mia, you are so lucky.
I'd never be allowed to
throw a party like this.
My parents are up my butt
about everything.
I'm always like,
"Guys, get out of my butt."
[chuckles, sighs]
VICTOR: There is no way.
I can't do that. No.
[laughing]
‐ ♪ This love has no ceiling,
I cannot deny ♪
JOCK: What's up, man?
VICTOR: Hey.
‐ ♪ Even if I could,
I wouldn't turn on you ♪
♪ And I would stop the world
for you and I ♪
♪ I wanna let you know ♪
♪ I'll never let this feeling go ♪
♪ This love has no ceiling,
I cannot deny ♪
[line ringing]
ERIC [over voicemail]:
Yo, leave a message.
[beeps]
‐ Hey, boo.
Wondering what you're up to tonight.
Um, call me. Miss you.
[phone clatters]
[groans]
‐ Adrian told me I have to
step up my bedtimes stories,
because they're getting a little...
basic.
‐ [chuckles] Oh, well, uh,
I got a scary story for him.
It's about a man,
about a vasectomy that didn't take.
And him and his wife have
a third kid they never planned for.
[scary breathing]
[laughing]
Oh, um, do you think that, uh,
Pilar's okay?
She was in one of her moods before.
She was just stomping around
slamming cabinets.
‐ Well, did you ask her about it?
‐ Here we go with the judgment.
ISABEL:
Whatever.
[camera shutter clicks]
[knocking]
ISABEL: Pilar, honey, it's me.
‐ Mom, what are you doing?
‐ What are you doing?
‐ Nothing!
Oh, my God. Go away!
‐ No.
Not until I get an explanation.
‐ Eric's not answering his phone,
and I know he's hanging out with Giselle,
and I had to do something
to get his attention.
‐ So you're sending him dirty pictures?
What if those got out, huh?
You would never be the first
Latina President. Phone.
‐ You're gonna take away the iPad
and the laptop, too?
I'm not a little kid. You can't stop me.
‐ Pilar. Camila. Salazar.
‐ What?
What am I supposed to do, Mom?
He's a thousand miles away
and I'm losing him.
Do you know how hard it was
for me to find someone I like
who actually likes me back?
I don't know if you've noticed,
but I'm not for everyone.
‐ Ay, honey.
You don't have to be for everyone.
You just have to be for yourself.
And if Eric is your person,
then he's not gonna
do anything with Giselle,
because he loves you for you.
Not because you're throwing
your boobies in his face.
But...
...you are a young woman now.
And I can't stop you
from making your own decisions.
So...
I am going to trust you...
to make good ones.
‐ Mom, let go.
‐ I'm trying.
‐ Okay. Thanks.
‐ Okay.
And can I just say,
your body is developing beautifully.
‐ Get out.
‐ You get that from my side.
[door closes]
♪
[laughing, indistinct chatter]
‐ And then, I was like,
"If I kiss you, do I get an A?"
[all laughing]
[Lake clears throat]
‐ Sorry. Yeah, I just got like,
a really funny text
from my boyfriend Bruno. So...
‐ You're not even holding your phone.
‐ Right.
‐ Where've you been?
‐ Oh, hey. Um, I've been with the guys.
Are you okay?
‐ Ah, well, you were gone a while.
So, in order to calm
my crippling social anxiety,
I made a new friend.
[laughs]
Can you believe Lake
has a boyfriend? Ugh.
Bruno.
Even his name is cool.
‐ All right.
Let's take it easy, all right?
[grunts]
[phone dinging]
SIMON: Victor, happy to hear
that things are going well at Creekwood,
and that your social standing
is on the rise.
There's nothing wrong with
wanting to fit in.
Sophomore year, I tried to grow a goatee,
because I thought it would
make me look badass.
Instead, it made me look like
an armpit with lips.
You just have to make sure that
if you're riding the Ferris wheel
with a cool girl,
it's because you want to.
Not because other people want you to.
Don't be so desperate to fit in
that you betray yourself
or the people you care about, okay?
TEDDY: This is hilarious.
JOCK: Funniest thing we've ever done.
[laughing]
‐ What is this?
‐ Here, take the marker.
‐ Leave him alone.
What the hell are you doing?
‐ Dude, what do you care?
He's a, he's a loser.
‐ He's my friend, okay?
Come on, Felix.
[Felix groans]
And it says "looser," you idiots!
‐ That's on me.
‐ Honey. What is it?
‐ Eric broke up with me.
‐ What? Voy a matar ese rata sucio!
Oh, I am so, so sorry.
‐ He said long distance was too hard.
At least I didn't send the picture.
‐ Ay, mi amor.
I know it hurts.
And I know it's hard to see right now,
but there are way better guys
out there than your high school boyfriend.
‐ But you and Dad were
high school sweethearts.
And you were meant for each other.
‐ We were lucky.
[Pilar exhales]
[Pilar sobs]
‐ [whispers]: Okay.
[pants]
All right. There it is.
Over here. Come on.
Oh. Hey!
‐ Hey. Uh, what are you doing there?
‐ There was a Sharpie situation
and a line for the bathroom downstairs,
so...
‐ Uh, you can use mine.
VICTOR: Great. Thank you.
All right. Come on, bud. Okay.
Yeah. You're fine. You got this. Okay.
‐ [groans] I can't believe Lake
has a boyfriend.
‐ No, it's just her cousin.
FELIX: That's worse.
I can't compete with family.
No, I'm just gonna lie down
on this nice, cold floor.
Ooh.
[Felix groans]
‐ Okay, um...
Let us know if you need anything, buddy.
FELIX: Mm‐hmm.
MIA:
You're a good friend.
‐ Thanks. I try.
[chuckles]
So, um, have you been hiding up here
the whole party, or...
‐ Sorta.
Yeah. I'm not a big party person.
Lake made me throw this thing.
‐ So, your parents don't mind?
‐ Uh, well, my mom's not in the picture,
and my dad travels a lot for work, so,
I can pretty much do whatever I want.
‐ That sucks.
I didn't mean to be rude. It's just...
you know, living in this big house
all by yourself,
it sounds a little lonely.
‐ Yeah.
We didn't always live here.
Before my mom left and before
my dad was university president,
we lived in an apartment across town.
It was always cluttered
with books and papers.
And there was never enough
hot water for the shower.
‐ Yeah, that sounds rough.
‐ Yeah.
I'd do anything to live in
that apartment again.
But instead, I pretend I love it here,
because I have my own bathroom,
and a pool.
And no rules.
And who wouldn't want that?
Sometimes it's easier to just
plaster on a smile,
and let people see what they want,
you know?
‐ Yeah. Yeah, I do.
Um, I'm basically scared shitless
of not fitting in here.
It's, like...
how am I supposed to know
how to fit in,
or who I'm supposed to fit in with,
when I have no idea who I am?
‐ I get that.
[Mia chuckles softly]
FELIX:
Guys?
Could I get a blanket?
Thank you.
‐ You, you wore yellow.
‐ Yeah. I did.
[stumbles]
[Felix laughing]
‐ Shh! Shh! Shh!
‐ Hey. You're late.
‐ Dad.
‐ You guys been drinking?
FELIX: What?
Drinking? I've never been sober‐er‐er.
‐ No, no. Too many "ers."
Go home, have a glass of water,
and sleep it off.
Good night. You come inside,
before your mom hears.
‐ Don't be mad at me. I'm, I'm not drunk,
and I know it's past my curfew,
but the bus took forever, and‐‐
‐ It's okay, Vic.
I know you were being responsible.
[whispers]:
How'd it go with Mia?
That girl, Mia. How'd it go?
‐ Good, I think.
‐ All right.
That's great. That's fantastic.
That's great.
‐ Uh, hey, Pap.
How did you know that Mom
was the one for you?
‐ Oh. Um...
Well, um...
we both had, uh, these after school jobs
at this crappy diner.
Oh, she was a terrible waitress, your mom.
Like, if you'd ask her for a Coke,
she'd bring you an iced tea.
If you asked for an iced tea,
she brought you a hot tea.
But nobody cared, though, you see,
because she was that charming.
She was that beautiful.
So, I asked her out.
I mean, at that point, I was mostly
thinking about how I was gonna,
you know‐‐
‐ Dad, come on.
‐ So, we went out for pizza,
and she started talking about
her grandfather,
and how he had just died a few months ago,
and about how close they were.
And while she's telling me this,
she starts to cry.
And the next thing I know,
I start to cry, too.
I mean, here I am,
one minute I'm just trying to hook up,
and the next minute, I'm crying about
some dead old man I never even met.
I never felt so connected to anyone.
Ever.
And that's when I knew.
Or whatever.
[both chuckle]
‐ Thanks.
‐ [whispers]: Yeah.
[door closes]
VICTOR: Hey, Simon.
Thanks for the words of wisdom.
All day, everyone liked me because
they thought I liked Mia.
Here's the twist:
Now that I've spent some time with her,
I do like her.
She's funny, and kind, and she gets me.
Did you ever feel super connected
to a girl and think,
I don't know, maybe this could work?
[phone vibrating]
Hello?
‐ Victor, it's Benji.
Sorry. It's late.
I hope I'm not waking you up.
‐ I‐I'm up, up. Wh‐what's going on?
‐ Look, I know today's barista lesson
didn't go perfectly,
but since none of the
rich‐ass kids at school need jobs,
you're kind of my only applicant.
So, the position is yours.
‐ Um...
‐ If you want it.
♪ "Too Many Colors"
by Twin Shadow ♪
‐ Yeah. Thanks.
‐ Well, see you tomorrow,
and every day after school,
until the end of time.
We're gonna be spending
a lot of time together.
‐ Cool. I can't wait.
‐ ♪ I wanna be loved,
don't wanna be hated ♪
♪ I'm too mixed up ♪
♪ Too mixed up ♪
♪ I'm too many colors ♪
♪
♪ Am I in love or just obsessed ♪
♪ I didn't stop this gorgeous mess ♪
♪ I played this song like half to death ♪
♪ And everything's all right ♪