WE WANT TO ENCOURAGE EVERYONE
IN SOUTHEAST ASIA
WHO DREAM TO PLAY IN THE WORLD CUP.
THIS FILM IS FICTIONAL
AND NOT BASED
ON ANY EXISTING ORGANIZATIONS,
INDIVIDUALS, AGENCIES, OR REAL EVENTS.
This is the moment Thai soccer fans
have been waiting for.
Thailand's first World Cup.
The players are making their way
onto the pitch.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the man responsible
for the reason why we are all here today.
Pongnarin Ulice,
the greatest coach in Thai history.
What are you doing?
PONGNARIN TO TAKE THAILAND
TO THE WORLD CUP
My nephew is coming.
This time,
Thailand is going to make it
to the World Cup.
-What should I bet on this time?
-You can't go any further.
-Checkmate!
-Black tea, please.
-Great.
-I only have Nescafe.
-Did you lose again?
-No.
-Good.
-Last night, I won big.
Good.
I'll win big on tonight's match for sure.
You're going to be rich, right?
Then pay your gambling debts.
Yeah, I haven't forgotten.
Right.
If Chelsea win on Saturday,
you can have it all.
Not again.
You can't keep doing that.
Have I ever stiffed you?
Saturday, I'll pay up.
You can't. Not this time.
Or...
Is our football whiz stone broke?
You shit!
Don't look down on me.
I have a lot of money in the bank.
Money in the bank, are you sure?
Mui.
I'll buy the whole lot of lottery tickets.
All of it?
That will be 27,300 baht.
I'll give you
the extra 25,000 baht next time.
-Ming!
-Ming.
-What about your gambling debt?
-Dad.
-She gave me--
-And you haven't paid for your coffee.
The officials will select
the winning two-digit lottery prize.
We are going to announce
the winning number.
The winning last two-digit prize
is...
two
and seven.
-I repeat.
-Christ!
Two and seven.
Now, Mr. Jira,
-Chatuchak District Attorney...
-Hello?
...will draw the number for us.
The winning lottery prize...
-Tonight? Fine.
-...from Government Lottery Office
is ready to be announced.
-I want Real Madrid and odds on Juventus
-The winning
-and Liverpool.
-number
-is...
-Lottery?
-I bought some but lost on all of it.
-five, eight,
-seven, zero,
-What a crap.
two and eight.
I repeat.
The winning number
is...
the sixth set.
Number five,
eight, seven,
zero, two and eight.
-Wait.
-The Government Lottery Office...
I won.
...would like congratulate
-the winners.
-I... I won!
-Please appropriately buy the lottery...
-Hey!
-for you own happiness.
-Anyone's here? Hey! I won.
I won the lottery.
I won the lottery!
PAPAYA SALAD VENDOR
SERVES UP WINNING PRIZE
184 MILLION LUCKY LADY LOTTERY WINNER
LOTTERY WINNER: PONGNARIN'S AUNT
What are you going to do with the money?
I'm going to donate it
to the Thai national football squad.
The Thai national football squad.
DONATES 184 MILLION TO THAI'S WC BID
But...
Coach Pongnarin,
my nephew,
must be the team's coach.
PONGNARIN
MING WANTS PONGNARIN BACK AS COACH
FOREIGNERS PRAISE PONGNARIN
PONGNARIN WANTS TO COACH THAI TEAM
LET'S VOTE
DO YOU WANT PONGNARIN TO COACH OR NOT?
OF COURSE, DON'T BOTHER,
STAY IN ENGLAND
How likely is it that Pongnarin will take
the reins of the national squad?
From our initial discussions,
Mr. Pongnarin has proposed
an appealing strategy.
But I have to admit
that the budget is quite enormous.
SUTHEE MUENBANCHA,
THAI FOOTBALL FEDERATION CHAIRMAN
DEAL WITH COACH PONG ALMOST WRAPPED
COACH PONG RESIGNS TO HELM THAI TEAM
"WORLD CUP IS NO LONGER JUST A DREAM
FOR THAI PEOPLE." PONGNARIN
PONGNARIN WILL ARRIVE TOMORROW
AT TERMINAL ONE
PONGNARIN IS ARRIVING TOMORROW.
LET'S GREET HIM AT THE AIRPORT.
WELCOME PONGNARIN
FANS WELCOME PONGNARIN
PONGNARIN BRINGS HOPES TO THAI FANS
READY TO TAKE THAI TEAM
TO THE WORLD CUP QUALIFYING ROUND
Hey, Teep.
What is all this?
Don't you know?
You're our national hope.
PONGNARIN IS HERE
READY TO TAKE THAILAND TO THE WORLD CUP
Beckham, steal the ball,
and win five baht.
You're on.
Quit playing around.
We'll be in trouble if we're late.
Tuk, how many fish do you need today?
They're good for some larb.
Sanglek has a way with kids.
With skills like that,
I would want him to be the father
of my child.
How many fish would you like?
Sorry.
I forgot that we're going to be
vegetarians tonight.
ISAN GARDEN GRILL
PONGNARIN ULICE
Pong.
Hey, stop reminiscing over there.
Please sign your autograph.
Come here.
That's too many. My hand will cramp.
Please.
I need them for my customers.
Please help me make a living, okay?
Sure.
Sign right here.
Right.
Here's your coffee, coach.
-Let me see.
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
Is that your new cook?
That's Ting from Arvee.
Sanglek's mother.
He plays in the Thai League.
I told you about him.
But now he's made
the Arvee national squad.
Madam Ming!
Big news!
Arvee entered the qualifying round.
-Hello, coach.
-Hi.
You're up early today, Pong.
How did that happen?
Weren't they eliminated already?
This is how it went.
One of the teams withdrew,
which opened a qualifying spot,
and Arvee was chosen as the replacement.
How come? Let me see.
-Where? I can't see your breaking news.
-Right here.
"Lucky losers, Arvee,
enter the qualifying round
for the first time in history."
I see.
What does "lucky loser" mean?
How about that?
Are we ready to win?
Which team are we going to play?
For our group, we have India,
Uzbekistan,
and North Korea.
That's why...
we have to be prepared!
I've proposed to take
the whole team to Thailand
to have training in Pattaya.
Pattaya!
What about Pongnarin?
I'm not so sure.
Sir.
There isn't anyone more qualified
than Coach Pong.
Also, the fans want him to be the coach.
That was proven in every poll that we did.
I don't care about the polls.
My main concern is getting Thailand
into the World Cup.
Then...
What about the 184-million baht offer?
-What offer?
-Wait.
Sir.
Haven't you been watching the news?
Above all...
I must thank everyone,
all Thai football fans,
who have supported me all along.
That's not good.
I should be more concise.
What?
Hi, coach.
My name is Jo.
I'm a regular customer here.
Can I get your autograph?
PONGNARIN ULICE:
FROM FOOTBALL ACE TO DIAMOND COACH
Smile, coach.
One, two, three.
Hey, Jo.
My body is all sore.
Come here and give me a back rub.
Give me a back rub. Come on.
Madam Ming.
I'm a trainer, not a masseur.
Here's my album.
AEROBIC DANCE
Something to thrill you.
Thank you.
I'm so thrilled to meet you.
Don't worry.
He's from the same town as us.
Hey.
What time are you leaving for Pattaya?
Early afternoon.
We should get there by evening.
Why?
Nothing.
Madam Ming wants to know.
Do you have a cold?
Have you taken any medicine?
It's okay. You don't have to worry.
Give me an onion.
Hurry up!
Idiot.
Wash up, too.
Sanglek, when you're done peeling onions,
bring me the garlic.
Yes, Mom.
Breaking news of the hour.
A passenger bus veered off the road
into a ditch
on Udon Thani Highway.
Twenty passengers were seriously injured.
Sixteen suffered minor injuries.
But there was no loss of life.
The bus was carrying
the Arvee football team
who is on its way
to have a training in Thailand.
Including the players,
staff, and coaches,
there were 35 people on the bus in total.
Arvee became the lucky loser team
to enter the qualifying round
of the World Cup
after Nepal and Philippines withdrew
from the competition.
But they may be forced to withdraw
after this accident.
Hurry up, Pong, or we'll be late.
LUCKY LOSER, ARVEE ENTERS
THE QUALIFYING ROUND: MAKES HISTORY
I'd like to go to Udon
to check on my friends.
If they're fine, I'll be back right away.
Go ahead.
Don't worry.
But how are you going to get there?
I'll go to the corner
and grab a taxi to the bus station.
Don't be silly. Come with us.
I'll drop you at the bus station.
It's on my way.
I'll take you there. Come on.
Hurry, or I'll be late.
Pong, hurry up. We're late!
The National Federation is determined
to push Thailand
into the final round of the World Cup.
Hurry up. We're late.
The directors have
unanimously decided to appoint...
I knew it. It's Coach Pong.
One hundred million, right?
I'm sorry.
That's not right.
The person who is going to be
Thailand's national coach
-is Mr. Jose Luis Cardinho.
-Hi.
-What? Cardinho?
-Hello, everyone.
And the federation would like to thank
Ms. Mingkwan Ulice
for donating 184 million baht
to support
the Thai national football squad.
The federation guarantees
that the donation
will be spent efficiently.
Why are you still here?
Right, I forgot about you.
I'm so sorry I completely forgot.
What happened?
The coach left.
The press conference is over.
Pong isn't going to be the coach.
They chose a foreigner instead.
I'm really mad.
We've been betrayed.
I'm not giving them my money anymore.
I'd much rather give the money
to the Arvee team.
Why are you not donating the money
to Thai team?
Why is that?
What are you going to do with it?
Are you really going to donate the money
to the Arvee team?
What about Thai team?
MING ABOUT FACE
DONATES 184 MILLION TO ARVEE
MING GOING MAD PUSHES PONG TO COACH ARVEE
ARVEE GOT LUCKY BOTH MONEY AND COACH
MR. BUNTERNG
ARVEE FOOTBALL ASSOCIATION CHAIRMAN
I'd prefer Pongnarin as a coach.
He has a world-class experience.
But if the Brazilian coach can take us
to the World Cup, then that's great.
Pongnarin is great.
I guess Pongnarin
will have to prove himself more.
The Brazilian is okay.
I don't see why he's going to coach
the Arvee team.
Is he that confident with his skills?
We've heard some opinions
from Thai football fans.
Mr. Buranath, can you give us your opinion
on the current turmoil
in the Thai Football Federation?
Personally, I was surprised as well.
I'm an avid fan of Coach Pongnarin's.
But that aside,
I respect the federation's decision.
I'm sure Coach Pong would concede
that Cardinho is an exceptional coach.
Therefore, I think saying
he'd be better off coaching Arvee
is overstepping his boundaries,
even though he has every right.
If he wants to snub the federation
or the nation,
I think it's highly inappropriate.
See, look at all the trouble
you've caused.
Hey.
I spoke in anger.
But I can't take it back now.
I'm really sorry, Madam Ming.
And to you too, Pong.
I'm the secretary
and I couldn't even do anything.
See how happy the Arvee people are.
PONGNARIN CHOOSES ARVEE
Perhaps we should really do this.
Is that a good idea?
It's an excellent idea.
On behalf of
the Arvee Football Association,
I'd like to thank Ms. Mingkwan
and Coach Pongnarin
for volunteering to help our team.
I've prepared a welcome party
in Arvee City for you.
If there isn't any problem,
I can call the federation
and let them know we can still compete.
Wait.
I haven't made any decision yet.
Really?
I had a feeling
a topflight coach
like Pongnarin
wouldn't want to coach
an underdog like Arvee.
It's okay.
I'll make the phone call and...
withdraw the team from the competition.
I'm going to call now.
I'm about to call them now.
Come on, Sanglek, let's head back.
Wait.
Hello, dear Arvee Sport Radio listeners.
Today, Coach Pongnarin,
a top-class Thai coach
has arrived in Arvee City.
Please welcome him
to Principality of Arvee,
our country by the South China Sea
with major exportation
and with non-aligned policy.
This is our squad.
Pisay is the captain and defender.
Kraisorn is assistant coach.
Lumnow and Bundee are midfielders.
And that's Tong Daeng.
Srimaen is the former goalie coach,
now he's a goalie.
Including Sanglek, that's makes six.
Now, you've got to fill
the rest of the roster.
Yeah, I like that one.
That number two, he plays fullback.
It's really fun.
It's fun to watch him attack.
Really great!
Right now,
we don't have any strikers.
We need to find at least three or four.
But from what I've seen
from the taped matches,
we need to work on defense
and quick counterattacks.
Right. Here.
That is Tom, son of a vendor.
He's hardworking and skilled.
He's been on television too.
Tom!
What are you doing?
Everything is wrecked.
They are for sale!
Coach.
I have two friends
I used to play football with.
I'd like you to give them a tryout.
How are you, Dueng?
This is Kamdueng.
He likes to say a smart striker
uses his head, not his foot.
I've stopped playing football.
Hurry up, man.
Try coming to the practice.
If it doesn't work, you can quit.
You'll also get a per diem.
Yes. Hey!
You lost. Pay up, man.
Pay up.
Pay up now.
Come on, pay up.
Hey.
Can I include the old debts as well?
No.
If you don't pay,
I'm going to chop off your legs.
How much does he owe you?
I'll settle his debts.
But you have to join the training session.
Do you have enough cash?
He owes us a lot.
How much?
Five million.
Phusamhing is good at almost every sport.
He played football in junior high.
But he stopped playing in high school.
He said it's not cool.
Girls don't like it.
Girls, where are you going?
You look so beautiful.
Hey, Sang.
Long time no see. What's up?
-Hey, Mhing.
-What?
I want you to play for the national team.
Interested?
No one is into Arvee football.
Hey, it's not like before.
We've made it
to the qualifying round this year.
-Take a photo with me.
-Hey, girl.
-Is he that famous?
-Totally.
Sanglek is a national football player.
He's really famous.
I've got to get his autograph.
Yo, when does the practice start?
PHUSAMHING
KAMDEUNG
I'm whacked.
Fifty laps.
Who can run that far?
Coach said, in England,
you have to run even farther.
Take a two-minute break,
then run 20 more laps.
Sticky rice, too.
Who cooked the food?
I did. You can't eat it?
It's edible.
But it's not good for the players.
It has too much fat and high cholesterol.
It's low in protein.
It's doesn't conform
to dietary standards, Aunt.
Athletes need to eat food
that is rich in protein,
which would provide them a lot of energy,
such as pasta.
I see.
I didn't know.
Let's do this, then.
I'll bring Tuk to help me out
with the cooking.
-She's studying at culinary school.
-Okay.
Hey.
Let's celebrate this tiring day, man.
Players of the Arvee team must refrain
from drinking alcohol.
We've got a match coming up.
Keep the discipline.
Good evening, dear viewers.
Let's welcome the Arvee football team.
This is the first qualifying match
for Zone Asia Group A.
Today, our Arvee team
is hosting North Korea.
Now, Arvee has the opening kickoff.
Today, the Arvee side
is dressed in red uniform,
-while North Korea is in white.
-We've got a fighting chance.
They're just trying us out.
Park Sung Young
passes the ball to number ten.
Heads it for a goal.
-I knew it.
-Arvee gives up their first goal
to a header by Ahn Moo-hoon.
North Korea's long ball
into Arvee territory.
Srimaen, our skilled goalie, catches it.
Arvee goes on the offensive.
But Pisay's pass is intercepted
by number eight.
He shot past Phusamhing
and simply into the goal.
North Korea leads Arvee
by two to zero.
Sanglek has the ball.
He dribbles past two defenders.
Can he make it?
He is stopped by the third.
North Korea has the ball
and passes it back up.
Number eight, Ryu Hong Sun gets through.
Rounds off Srimaen
and sends the ball into the net.
Arvee gives up its third goal
at the end of the first half.
What was that disaster?
Our game plan is to counterattack.
If you just play as you like,
how are we going to beat them?
Focus. Focus.
Playing football requires finesse
and precision.
You can't rely on raw instinct.
If you don't want to lose,
you better go out and get some goals.
Go, Arvee!
-Yeah.
Hey!
Now, listen up team!
Anyone who gets a goal,
I'm going to pay ten million each!
-Yeah!
North Korea scores again.
Another goal sinks Arvee,
five goals to none.
I think Coach Pong
will need more time to adjust
and improve the Arvee side.
We've made it
to the qualifying round anyway.
Right? Let's go, dear.
THAI BEATS JORDAN 2-0
ARVEE DEFEATED BY NORTH KOREA
WON THREE POINTS
ARVEE LOSES
THAI BEATS JORDAN 2-0
ARVEE LOSES 0-5
Kids.
What are you doing?
We're marking the wall with the ball.
I see that.
Why are you doing it?
I don't know. Grandpa told us to.
He said in the past, whenever Arvee lost,
he would get drunk to drown his sorrow.
One day, while he was drunk,
he kicked the ball against the wall,
and it made a mark.
On the wall, he would write the score,
and to which team Arvee lost.
Hey, there's more over there.
You better start thinking of what
you're going to mark when Arvee wins.
Kids.
Help me out.
I'm lost.
What's her name?
Tukta.
She flew here just to cook for us?
She's studying culinary,
so we asked her to help.
Is she your girl?
What? No.
Your mouth says one thing,
but you're blushing.
She really isn't.
Look at this.
It's all Western food.
How can we eat this?
Isn't this a bit drastic?
They're Arvee people, you know?
If they don't eat fermented fish,
where will they find the strength
to play ball?
Aunt.
But those local foods
don't have any dietary value for athletes.
Right. I'm going to see Bunterng.
I want a physical trainer for the team.
Not sure if we can find one.
Why do you want one?
To keep everyone fit and train the team.
Just one more move.
Why do we have to dance like this?
It's called "body combat."
It improves your agility.
-Good!
-Hey, man.
-Do you think he's a fairy?
-Good!
I think not.
I'm not sure if he's gay or not.
Right, I think we play
too much zone defense.
It's like we're inviting them to attack.
-We should chase down the ball.
-Right.
Since we can't keep possession,
we have to press the opponent
to diminish their control.
-Hey!
-What happened?
Excuse me.
What's your name?
Sompon.
Do you know how to play football?
SOMPON
Hot coffee, please.
That's Wernsawan.
Excuse me?
Wernsawan.
The best football player
Arvee has ever seen.
If he is still playing,
maybe we could do better.
Was he injured?
No.
He's facing a lifetime ban from football.
He has a short temper
and can't control himself.
He gets into fights with his opponents.
In his last match,
he kicked the referee and broke his ribs.
It was a huge scandal.
This is Ngid.
Ngid is a local hunter-gatherer
from the Karenni tribe.
He knows Wernsawan well.
Can't you find
a less temperamental player?
Ngid, slow down.
-I'm here.
-Hey!
Hurry up. It's getting late.
Wernsawan is dangerous.
From what I've seen from the tapes,
his opponents provoked him.
It's been over ten years.
He should be much calmer.
Hey!
You want a fight?
Hi, Wern.
It's like I told you.
What do you say?
Would you like to play football again?
I stopped playing a long time ago.
Football disrupts my mind.
Why don't you try it out?
I'd better not.
When I play, I lose self-control.
I don't want to hurt anyone again.
Why don't you give it a shot?
-I don't want to play.
-Just a shot.
-No.
-It will be fun.
No!
No, I'm too old.
Ngid, pass me the ball.
WERNSAWAN
NGID
I spent millions so you'd be comfortable.
Train your hearts out, team.
-I want a room with air conditioner, then.
-Sure, you can. Come on.
Come with me.
From what you've seen,
India isn't that strong as a team.
Just trust in me
as much as I trust in you.
This next match is the real deal.
Starting tomorrow,
we're going to train really hard.
We'll use a 4-5-1 formation
with four defenders.
Natee as a left-back.
Two center backs.
Phusamhing as a stopper.
Pisay as a sweeper.
Tong Daeng as a right-back.
Both full-backs must press in
on the opponent.
If the ball gets to the two center backs,
I want you to clear the ball first.
The five midfielders will cover the zone.
Lumnow and Sompon, chase down the ball,
-and disrupt the opponent's game.
-Ouch!
Why did you kick me?
Sorry, I forgot.
Wern is going to be midfield general.
If there's an opening,
pass the ball for Kamdueng to setup.
Sanglek, once you get the ball,
I want you to try to draw a foul.
Don't forget that everyone must help
chase down the ball in defense.
Get it?
Let's practice shooting.
Pass the ball to Kamdueng.
He'll head it back for you
to shoot the goal.
Next.
Wait!
Kick the ball softly
to that tall guy's head,
and when it bounces back,
slowly run in to kick the ball
into the goal, okay?
But kick it
with only half of your strength,
or else it will enter the stratosphere.
Broken arm?
Yes.
Broken in two halves.
It will take three months
before he can play again.
Do we have enough time
to find a new goalie?
That won't be necessary.
I have someone in mind.
Help me carry it.
Put it over there.
Cramps!
-Easy.
-Be gentle.
-Let me see.
-I'll do it.
Please be gentle.
It doesn't hurt there.
You're fine. It's only a cramp.
Gently.
Is anyone else hurt?
-No. Everyone is healthy.
-No one.
You might be wondering why I'm having you
practice so many penalty shots.
Players like Zico,
Baggio, Henri, or Beckham,
have all missed
important penalty shots before.
Anything can happen in a football match.
-Wern.
-Hey!
Be careful.
USA is out.
Guys.
Watch and see. Arvee will win the crown.
Just wait, guys.
I doubt it. Venezuela is much prettier.
She can win.
-How can you say that, Jo?
-Right.
How can you say that?
-Miss Arvee is much prettier.
-Venezuela's prettier.
-Arvee!
-Venezuela!
You want to bet on it?
Are you sure?
Your luck hasn't been so good lately.
Let's make it 500.
-Arvee!
What's the racket all about?
It's not cold in India
at this time of the year.
Are you still sick?
No.
It's just allergies.
Here.
Team.
Give me your attention.
Look who's here!
It so happens,
Petchdawan just arrived.
So I asked her to wish us all good luck.
Try your best to win.
Don't lose face to Petchdawan.
Let me take a photo with her.
-Me first!
-Me too!
Aren't you going to ask for her autograph?
I'm not that crazy about celebrities.
Don't be shy.
You're just as famous as she is.
Right.
She's a beauty queen
and I'm just a lousy football player.
Thanks. I have a pen.
No. I want to get your autograph.
Here's my autograph.
See you later.
Breaking news!
Big news!
Arvee has won!
Arvee?
-Arvee really won!
-Can you keep that for me? I'll be back.
What's the rush?
I'm going home to mark the wall
with the ball.
We won. Why do you have to mark the wall?
Yes! Nine! I won.
Wait.
Hey.
Just in time.
What's this?
Rub it on your chest, back, and neck,
so you can breathe better.
Thank you.
-Rub it every time you play or practice.
-Okay.
Tukta, dear.
My heart is sore.
-What should I rub on it?
-Right.
-You're crazy!
-Ouch.
I may be crazy,
but is love a crime?
Sang, you're just on time.
Wait.
What are you guys doing?
Check this out.
We have to go international.
Everyone has bleached his hair.
You're the last one.
For team unity, man.
I had someone to buy bleach from Thailand.
You think it's a good idea?
-How come you didn't bleach your hair?
-Who says I didn't?
I did.
I was the first one.
The Uzbeks use a 4-3-3 formation
for a full-on attack.
The most dangerous player
is their center midfielder.
Do anything you can to stop him.
Damn it!
I can't stand this.
Whose idea was this?
Why didn't you bleach yours?
There wasn't enough bleaching product.
Sanglek, wait.
Did you rub this on?
No, I forgot.
There isn't enough time.
I'll rub it after the first half.
Pull up your shirt.
Hurry up.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
All finished. You can go.
Welcome Arvee football fans.
Today, the Arvee team
is sporting a new bleached blond look.
I don't know what they were thinking.
How can this build up their team unity?
Game starts. Uzbekistan kicks off.
Chase the ball!
Arvee concede a foul early in the game.
The Uzbeks have possession
and pile up pressure for 11 Arvee players
to retreat into their own half.
Arvee are still packing a tight defense.
Pongnarin's tactic today
is to shield the Uzbeks' attack.
Chase the ball!
Wernsawan, Arvee's commander,
has the ball.
Wernsawan to Sanglek on the left.
Sanglek bursts forward.
A tackle! He's fouled!
Arvee gets a free kick on the left flank.
-Now.
-Left.
Sanglek.
Sanglek curves a long ball into the box.
It's in! It's a goal for Arvee!
Wernsawan scores for Arvee!
Arvee leads Uzbekistan 1-0.
Arvee just scored their first goal.
What are you doing?
Our next match will be in North Korea.
They say that the weather there
is freezing cold.
I need to get used to it.
It's freezing in there.
What's the point of all this?
Isn't it a bit sadistic?
It's a lot colder in North Korea.
We have to prepare ourselves.
There's no need to go this far.
We have to trust the coach.
Focus, Sang.
Focus.
Ngid, pass me the ball.
No, don't kick it.
Billboards smash to pieces
with the monster kick from Ngid,
the number 12.
We're down to the final minutes.
The game between Arvee and North Korea
remains tied at zero.
If no one scores,
North Korea will go through
to the quarterfinals.
Arvee has only seven points.
While North Korean has nine points.
Arvee needs nothing less than a win
to go through.
Ngid blasts another monster kick.
It throws the North Korean goalkeeper
to the ground!
This is him, Ngid, "The Clearance,"
sent in to clear the ball.
A draw is enough for Arvee.
It looks like Kim Eun-ji,
the goalkeeper, can get back on his feet.
The match is deep into injury time.
At this point, we must say that Arvee
has done all that needs to be done.
Ngid has the ball, blasts it away,
and runs back into position.
The ball flies over the keeper
and into the net.
In the net?
What? The ball is in!
How come? Arvee snatches
a last-gasp victory!
Unbelievable! Arvee leads 1-0!
Arvee are going through the quarterfinal!
ARVEE 1-0: STEAL DRAMATIC VICTORY
TO ENTER QUARTERFINALS
ARVEE WON
PONGNARING BOASTS:
ARVEE READY FOR THE WORLD CUP
THAILAND WINS GROUP B
AFTER BEATING JORDAN 3-0
You lose because you never try
It's a shame
Don't hide it
If it's for someone you care
Give it your best
In love, there's nothing fair
-Happy, huh?
-If you hide it
You've exerted great effort
preparing this.
They won't know about it
Wow, we will play
with Iran, Japan, and Qatar.
Do we even have a chance to win?
Everything is possible in a football game.
GOAL: TO THE WORLD CUP
Captain.
We'll be playing the heavyweights.
Do you think we have any chance?
Hey.
We have a great coach.
At least, if we finish third in the group,
we'll earn a quota to be in a playoff.
If we won,
we'll play with the winner
from Central America.
And with another win,
we'll proceed to the World Cup.
I dont get it.
It's too complicated.
Who are we going to compete first?
Iran.
Looks like a long queue.
Shouldn't we take a shower together,
so we won't have to wait?
-No.
I can wait. No rush.
We can wait, right?
I've got cramps. Help!
It's all right! I'm fine!
Help! I'm okay now!
I'm fine!
Help!
THAI STRIKER DEFECTS TO ARVEE
Do you know the Thai player
who's going to play with us?
Yes, but we never talked.
We played for different clubs.
He was Thai League's top scorer.
Why do you want to play for Arvee?
I want to make my father's dream
come true.
On his deathbed,
he told me...
"You must join the national squad
and play in the World Cup."
And I trust you.
I have faith in you.
I believe that you can make our dream
come true.
I'm asking you seriously.
Give me a chance, coach.
We suffered the same tragedy.
We were rejected by our own people.
Do it as a favor for me, coach.
Go! Run!
How are you doing, Sanglek?
Remember me?
I'm Saman.
Thai League's top scorer
who beat you by a couple of goals.
Don't worry.
Now we're in the same squad.
You pass, I score. I pass, you score.
Having us on the same team
is like two tigers unleashed.
I'm Saman, man.
Hey, stay focused!
What devil has got into you?
You think you're on top of the world?
You boys think you're celebrities?
Where's your focus and discipline?
You think you'll die and go to heaven now
that we're in the last eight?
Whose phone is it?
Must be Miss Universe calling.
From now on,
switch off all communication devices
during practice.
Tell everyone not to call you
during the training session.
I don't care if it's your parents,
your family,
or girlfriends.
Where are you? Yes, I'll call you back.
I'll bet on Liverpool.
Hey, Sang.
Set me up for a goal
when you spot a chance okay?
I'll rip their defense apart
with my incredible speed.
But the coach told us to play defense.
Come on.
To play great football...
is to attack.
I'm too good to play defensive tactics.
Saman's dribble is blocked again.
-Damn it. What's he doing?
-Arvee's new striker
has recently rescinded
his Thai nationality.
He earned his cleats
as Thai League's top scorer.
Skilled he is.
But he's not a team player.
Iran's counterattack.
The ball is in the box.
Number eight charges. It's a goal!
Iran is up 1-0.
Saman!
Why don't you stick to the game plan?
We have to attack when we have a chance.
That's exactly the reason why they scored.
Cut it out!
Let's play. We still have time.
Iran doubled their lead.
Again, from number eight.
A clear header from Kahlil Karimi
since he's left unmarked.
Iran are up 2-0.
What are you doing?
Run!
Chase the ball!
Karimi has the ball again.
He's storming forward.
Phusamhing tackles.
This is dangerous for Arvee.
What did the referee say?
Phusamhing is shown the red card!
It's a professional foul.
Penalty for Iran.
It's a goal!
Hamid Daiei sends
the ball past the keeper.
Iran are up 3-0.
Arvee decides to take Saman off.
Number 11, Bundee, is coming on.
There's a fight.
Wernsawan is cooking trouble
with Kahlil Karimi from Iran.
What? Has he gotten hit?
Karimi is down.
The Japanese referee rushes over.
This foul play is unprofessional.
And it's another red card!
Can you believe it?
What will they do next?
Oh, Wernsawan is charging at the referee.
Wernsawan lost his temper now.
His teammates now
-try to hold him back.
-Stop it, boys. Stop it!
Boys, don't fight!
Stop it! Don't fight!
I don't know where to begin.
I could lecture you until tomorrow.
I'm not saying that if you'd stuck
to the tactic, we would've won.
But at least if you'd listened to me,
it wouldn't have been this humiliating.
Where is Wern?
It's your fault, Saman.
You spoiled our game plan.
I did my best.
You guys don't know
how to play decent football.
You're only good at committing fouls.
Shut up, Thai boy!
You have no heart to fight for Arvee.
You're playing for your own glory.
What about your coach?
Isn't he also a Thai?
What about the woman who feeds your team?
Even the chef?
-They're all Thai, aren't they?
-I never asked for your charity.
Don't think that your money can buy us.
Madam.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Forget it.
It's all right, Pisay.
Let it rest.
Arvee and Thailand are like siblings.
When we fight, it's like a sibling fight.
From now on, we're one and the same,
be it Thai or Arvee.
Saman's mother came from Arvee.
And me, I'm 100 percent Northeastern Thai.
Right?
We speak the same language anyway,
don't we?
ARVEE TO THE WORLD CUP?
PONGNARIN'S HEADACHE
AS IN-FIGHTING BREAKS OUT
I'm sorry, Aunt.
Sorry for what?
We haven't been eliminated.
It was just one defeat,
and you're acting like
it's the end of the world.
Our World Cup dream
is going to end in this round.
Who cares?
I still have a big stash of cash left.
If we're knocked out,
I'll fly everyone to go see the World Cup.
Coach.
-I'm sorry.
-Wait.
Why aren't you changed yet?
I thought you had kicked me out.
If you don't get changed in three minutes,
you're out.
Are you not feeling well?
No, I'm fine.
-Can we get your autograph?
You're so cute.
What's your name?
It's Pim.
Excuse me. I need to use the restroom.
Sanglek, you have a missed call.
TUKTA
You have a cold?
No.
Just allergies.
With some balm. I'll be fine.
She's gone back to Bangkok?
When did she leave?
This morning.
She said she'd drop by her house
in Udon Thani first.
I didn't want to keep her here
since school has started.
We've got help.
You boys won't starve without her.
Good evening, dear viewers.
Welcome to the live broadcast of
the World Cup Zone Asia qualifying match.
This is the first leg
of a crucial play-off
between Thailand and Arvee.
Played at the National Stadium
in Arvee City.
Let's take a look
at both team's qualifying campaigns.
Arvee began the quarter finals
with a humiliating defeat
after being thrashed 0-7 by Iran.
They visited Japan
and suffered a 1-0 loss.
They drew Qatar 1-1 at home,
but lost 0-1 in the away game.
Then came the surprise from Arvee,
1-0 home victory over Japan.
Before holding Iran to a goalless draw.
This vital match has kicked off.
Arvee, wearing blue, kick off the match.
While Thailand is in all-red outfit.
Let's see what Arvee will play
against Thai.
Vitoon intercepts the ball and passes,
but it's offside!
ARVEE - THAI
Anurak passes a long ball,
but it's offside again.
Thailand open aggressively,
but get caught by the offside trap.
Could that be Pongnarin's tactic?
Setting the offside trap against Thai.
Now, Wernsawan passes
to Sanglek who turns around and charges.
He's loose!
It's one on one with the goalie!
Slides and knocks the ball in!
Arvee goes ahead
at the end of the first half!
Unbelievable.
As expected, this Arvee team
can play fast counterattack
and it's all Thai's fault.
Let's continue our live broadcast.
The second half is about to start.
Five minutes to go,
and Arvee is still leading with 1-0.
Thailand presses nonstop,
but Arvee's defense is a tough one.
Thai want at least one goal to level.
If they have an away goal,
next match in Thailand,
they'll have an advantage.
Now! They level!
It's a goal. Vitoon levels for Thailand!
The game is tied 1-1!
That's the final whistle.
It's a 1-1 draw between Arvee and Thailand
in Arvee City.
The second leg in Bangkok
will decide the World Cup destiny
of both nations.
ARVEE 1-1 THAI
They are tied. It's unbelievable.
Pongnarin shakes hands
with Thai and Arvee players.
But he seems disappointed with the result.
His team almost won.
And now he faces a do-or-die match
in his home country.
He certainly looks stressed out.
No one could feel more pressure
than he does right now.
THAI FANS SIGH IN RELIEF FROM NEAR LOSS
NEXT MATCH IS MAKE-OR-BREAK
VITOON LEVEL 1-1
CARDINHO ADMITS, ARVEE IS TOUGH
PONGNARIN AT THE CROSSROADS:
THE TIE ADD MORE PRESSURE ON PONGNARIN
PONGNARIN WILL TAKE ARVEE TO THE WORLD CUP
DUTY OR HEART
WHAT WOULD HE CHOOSE?
Such a shame.
We almost did it.
Should we appoint Adisorn as a coach?
But we must believe in Pongnarin.
He has brought us this far.
GOAL: TO THE WORLD CUP
ARVEE 1-1 THAI
People may be wondering
about how I'll maintain my position
at situations like this.
I'm Thai.
And like all Thais.
I've always dreamed of seeing Thailand
in the World Cup.
My aunt,
Mingkwan Ulice,
is also a supporter of the Thai team.
All her life, she's dreamed
of seeing Thailand in the World Cup.
But now,
Mingkwan
has a responsibility
as an Arvee team manager.
And myself,
as their coach,
my priority as a coach...
is to make this team win.
Emerge victory.
There's no question about it.
Tomorrow,
Arvee will fight
with heart
and dignity.
I hope that...
both Arvee and Thai football fans
will enjoy tomorrow's game.
Thank you very much.
MISS UNIVERSE VISITS FOSTER HOME
Hey.
I couldn't reach you on the phone.
I've been studying.
I've been studying hard lately.
I got a lot of work too.
Why didn't you answer your phone?
I'm just a Missed Call, not Miss Universe.
What are you doing here?
Running away from training?
Here.
Come to the match.
You're still a member of the staff.
I'm not sure.
Let me see if I'm free.
Allergies still acting up?
Smell something?
Shoot!
Damn.
SHE'S NOT THAT PRETTY
BEAUTY QUEEN MAKE ME PUKE
You'll need this.
COME BACK AND RUB THE BALM FOR ME
Look at those two lovebirds.
Yeah.
And she said they're just friends.
We're closing.
Good evening.
Welcome to the live broadcast
of the second leg
of the Zone Asia Qualifying match.
This game is of paramount importance
for both teams.
Thailand are hosting Arvee  in Bangkok.
The winner of this second leg
will play against the winner
from Zone Concacef.
And the winner of that playoff
will earn a berth in the World Cup.
The most interesting match-up.
But looking at the statistics,
Thailand is in a different league
from Arvee.
Especially in a crucial game like this,
I'm confident that Thailand
won't shoot itself in the foot.
Arvee's trump card is Pongnarin,
who's already made history as a coach.
How do you anticipate his tactic today?
Remember that...
at this point,
our chance is as good as the Thais'.
This is the game of our life.
Stay focused.
And fight with all you've got.
What if we give it all and still lose?
We're not going to lose.
We've lost enough.
Go out there and believe that we will win.
Believe in one thing. Victory.
We're going to the World Cup.
Don't you want to go to the World Cup?
What for?
Because I want to!
-Yes!
-World Cup!
Arvee, please get ready for the game.
What did you say?
Brothers from Arvee,
please get ready for the game.
Here.
You're asking for too much.
Hurry up.
Hey, man, hurry up.
I didn't mean to interrupt.
Mhing! Wait up!
Sang!
THAILAND
-Thailand!
Grilled squid!
Grilled squid, anyone?
A historic game is about to begin.
Today's referee is Michael Shao
from Singapore,
and also the assistant referee
from the same country.
Thailand kick off the match.
-Arvee in red uniform with white socks.
-Chase the ball!
It's getting hairy early in the match.
Thailand's Torpong tackled hard
by Sompon from Arvee.
He is down.
Thailand has a free kick.
Sukmak-anan has the ball
and shakes off an Arvee player!
Passes to Vitoon.
Vitoon fires!
Toward the goal but well-caught
by Tom, Arvee's goalkeeper.
Thailand started off very well,
but still tied 0-0.
Ball is with Vitoon.
Vitoon's left foot shot
is way off the mark!
Thailand is more aggressive in the attack,
but Arvee defense is very good.
We can't underestimate them.
Beware of their counterattack.
We learned a lesson from the first leg.
Sukmak-anan fires a shot!
Tom palms it out of the way.
Thailand's got a corner kick.
Pongsak sends the ball,
flying into the box.
Tom catches the ball,
and quickly throws it to Sanglek.
Sanglek.
Showing off now.
-Sending the ball...
-Hands off me!
Thailand's Namchoke fouls Wernsawan.
That was harsh.
Wernsawan is down.
The yellow card is shown.
-Shame.
-Asshole!
Namchoke receives the first yellow card
of the game.
I called you an asshole!
Hey. Calm down, mates.
No, don't.
Arvee got a free kick outside the box.
Sanglek will take the free kick.
Let's see if he's going to shoot
or open it.
Sanglek kick with his left foot.
The ball is headed away.
Thailand clear the ball from their goal.
Now, it's time
for Thailand's counterattack.
Anurak takes the ball to the right flank.
Nicely shifts the ball pass Arvee.
Anurak to Sukmak-anan.
Now to Vitoon.
Vitoon.
Vitoon to Anurak.
Anurak passes the ball into the box
and charges!
It's in. That was beautiful!
They set it up beautifully.
Thailand leads 1-0 against Arvee.
This is classic football.
Thailand is up 1-0 against Arvee.
Wonderful play with a sublime one-two pass
and with a magnificent finish.
This is what I call real football!
Thailand has the momentum
and presses an all-out attack.
Wernsawan returns the favor.
Namchoke is down on the pitch.
Micheal Shao, the referee
shows the yellow card to Wernsawan.
Thailand will get a free kick.
What a good spot to take.
Let's see if they can make it 2-0.
Goal! Thailand doubles the lead.
It's now 2-0!
Thailand is up 2-0 against Arvee.
That's the end of the first half.
Thailand is leading 2-0 against Arvee.
Wern.
Watch out for number five.
He's trying to get you red-carded.
Don't let him provoke you.
I'm sorry.
So far, you guys have played well.
I've taught you how to not concede goals.
But today,
I want you to score goals.
Attack!
Don't hold back.
Boys.
Just march forward and fire at them.
You too, goalie.
Don't worry about catching the ball.
Forget stupid tactics.
We have 45 minutes left.
Give it all you've got.
In four years, you'll be singing lullabies
to your kids at home.
Give it your best shot today!
Win or lose,
do it with dignity.
Understood?
The worst thing...
for a coach
is to ignore the tactics.
So, this is our tactic.
Forget all the training that we did.
And play it the way you like to play!
You mean, make a mess out of it?
Yes!
Make a bloody mess out of it!
Get it?
-Yes!
A change of form for Arvee
in the second half.
Storming forward and firing away
like there's no tomorrow.
Thailand must stay composed
since we have two goals in the bag.
We enjoy a better chance of going through.
To put a nail in the coffin,
we must score a third goal quickly.
Nice and easy.
Now, Saman Komsantier is coming on.
The Thai fans in the stadium
are booing him.
Bringing a striker on
means Arvee are going for broke.
His one-man-show...
What the hell?
...and his unnecessary diving
often costs his team dearly.
Saman bursts forward
for a one-two touch to Sanglek.
Wow! It's a goal!
Thailand finally gives up a goal
to a wonderful strike.
-Arvee are back in the game at 1-2.
-Damn it!
Fifteen minutes to go,
and Thailand have to pack
a strong defense.
He's provoking the fans.
It's a foul taking off his shirt.
Saman is shown a yellow card
for taking off his shirt.
We must stay focused
and not lose our nerve.
It's crucial to keep this scoreline.
GO, THAILAND
Thailand on the attack.
Vitoon dribbles inside and blasts a shot.
-Ouch!
-A clash!
They are at it again.
A clash occurs
between Wernsawan and Namchoke.
What is going on?
Is Wernsawan confused?
-Wernsawen is hitting himself!
-What do you want from me?
-What do you want?
-The referee is dumbstruck by his action.
-How should he judge this?
-Tell me!
What?
Now there's substitution.
Arvee is bringing in number 12,
Ngid, "The Clearance".
Thailand has to be careful.
His "clearance shot"
once made the Koreans weep.
Taking Arvee through.
Namchoke is tackled hard by Ngid!
That was harsh.
Might need to be substituted.
Five minutes to go in regular time.
Thailand has got another free kick
in scoring range!
This is scoring range.
-Need to take this one carefully.
-Interpreter.
-What is the coach shouting?
-What?
What is the coach shouting?
Charge the ball.
He said to keep the ball in possession.
Otherwise...
Otherwise, they'll attack our counter.
What?
Just look at me.
Take a good look at me.
It's an advantage ball for Arvee.
The referee waves the play to continue.
Saman is brought down in the penalty box!
He might have taken a dive.
But the referee said it was the penalty!
Thailand concede a penalty
in the last minutes of the match!
No doubt this is our own fault.
It was really a foul.
That's right. If Arvee level at 2-2,
they will go through
due to the away-goal rule.
This is because Thailand could score
only one goal in Arvee's home.
The goddess of luck
is sitting on Arvee's side.
-Miss it!
Sanglek.
You take it.
I'm scared.
But I'm hurt.
-Miss it!
Good afternoon, brothers and sisters
of Arvee.
Our Arvee boys fought bravely
in the World Cup.
First match.
Defeated by France, 8-0.
Second match.
Defeated by Mexico, 5-0.
And in the last match,
beaten by Cameroon, 4-0.
Altogether,
we conceded 17 goals
and scored none.
Subtitle translation by Kong Rithdee