He's given me permission to go out.
Nobody gave you permission.
Yes! He has!
No your father certainly has not!
First of all, he is not my father.
Really?
Whose father is he then? Mine?
Anyway, I don't know.
I need to go now.
Go where?
I have to go...
Go where ?
I told you, I have to
go to the college festival.
Don't you dare lie!
Why are you talking bullshit?
Don't lie ! I know
you are going out for a night out...
...dressed like a slut!
Don't think I'm stupid.
Ma... don't be so dramatic.
Dramatic? Who is being dramatic?
All those TV soaps have really messed up
your brain !
Messed up ? Yes I'm messed up ! A daughter
like you will drive anyone insane !
Where do you think you are going
dressed like this? Huh!
Where are you going for night out?
Ria! Just try stepping out!
I swear Ria!
I will break your legs!
Ria! This is the last time!
I will see you!
I'll never ever let you in again!
Rickshaw!
Ria! Don't forget what I told you!
Shit!
You left your phone back at home?
I'm not sure...
Look again!
Do you have Pele's number?
How will I have it?
Just call Babai!
Uff...
Hey! Where are you?
My balls have grown fungus
waiting for you!
Hey sexy! Say something!
Hey bro! What's up?
Bro I am fucking screwed...
...I called up Ria,
I said that I am waiting,
and was generally talking...
...called her sexy and all...
Told her to stop cock teasing and come...
Spoke to her for a bit...
Then, you know,
this serious voice answers...
I will cut your fucking balls off.
What the fuck man!
You find it funny?
That's why I don't tell you shit!
Stop laughing you fucker!
Asshole! Fucker hung up!
All three together?
Who sits where?
First you, then her, tight!
Are you ready?
What's up?
Just hanging.
So tell me...
Hey pass me a smoke.
Uff... What style man!
Motherfucker it is then?
Is this your brother's scooter?
Just sit here!
What, tell me...
Did he buy this with his bodyrub money?
Don't you guys know?
His brother is a masseur!
Fuckers, he is not a masseur!
Then what?
How much was this for?
50 bucks.
What bullshit man!
50 bucks for this crap?
Where did those two go?
So? Think you will score tonight?
Confidence dude! Whatever you do,
do it with confidence.
And don't fuck this up.
I set this up just for you!
Okay cool! But, where?
In a hotel.
In the same room?
Full orgy, brother!
What a shitball show!
You call yourself a manager!
Fuck man how was I supposed to know?
Not a cat around.
You call this a show?
There are more bands than fucking people.
What do you mean? Fuck you!
We need shows!
How the fuck do I know everything?
I am a manager, not a pimp.
Hey you, what
the fuck's going on?
Yeah? Who the fuck are you?
Don't you see what's going on?
Blind fuck!
Don't touch me!
I'll break your balls motherfucker!
Stop fucking around!
What did you say?
I'll give it to you
real good motherfuckers!
I'll shove this up your cunt,
you little fuck!
Come alone if you have the balls fucker!
Babai let's go!
Go, go, go!
Fuck your mother, fucktard!
Something,something yes I want
It's something that I want
It's what I see what I say
Yes I chant, I want
The city, the bridge
the corporation, railway station
Crooked words dirt and turds
The buildings they have fangs
They bite at night
I know it's bad to want
But then I'm sunburnt
A little hot juicy
I want a little pussy
Drool spills from my lips
Dark shadows lurk blood drips
Hungry for blood restless as fuck
If you can get away, do it, good luck!
The game must be played
It's time that you prayed
You must play the game
You can't stay the same.
Something something yes I want
It's something that I want
It's everything that I want
A little something that I want
You! Put that down.
Don't drink openly.
We could get into trouble...
Enjoying the holiday huh?
Is your daddy wearing the helmet at home?
Sir, please let us go, it's a holiday.
Take out your license!
Sir please, I've left
my license at home...
Then come, let's go the police station!
Sir, please sir, let us go...
Please sir!
Call the patrol car.
Sir, we really need to get back home.
But sir, we didn't do anything.
You're harassing us just like that.
Just like that? Huh!
Stinking of booze!
'Just like that'!
Here, dear girl!
Don't be scared!
Let me see your bag!
Pass the bag!
Come on then, get going!
Go home!
Now fuck off!
Go, Fuck off!
They fucked us good, those dumb fucks!
They took the money.
Didn't leave us any cash!
They literally turned us into beggars
fucking shitheads!
I'm telling you man, let's go back home!
How many times are you going to count?
We are fucking broke.
Oi Payel, come here...
What?
Just give me your hand...
Why?
You Bitch!
What the fuck!
Crazy!
So, then let's check out the hotel?
Hotel?
Fresh as fuck
Fish fry I want
To fuck everything
that's what I want
It's not light
But dark I want
To cut the night in two
a sharp knife I want
I want to fuck
Gimme my space I want
Fuck the face
It's tits that I want
A cool dress a hot chick
One night is what I want
And if you can't give me shit
A bomb is what I want
Husband and wife! Really?
Where's your marriage certificate?
We've to tell cops everything.
We have only dormitories.
Will that do?
We don't want any more trouble!
We've only single beds.
Where have you come from?
Sorry nothing for just one night!
No, we don't want any police problem!
How can we let students stay overnight?
Find some other spot.
Amar Hotel
I hope there are no
identity fuck ups here...
Maybe we should offer more money?
Sir? Do you have any vacancy?
Hello sir!
Sir, can we get a room?
Strange!
Sir?
What a fucking hotel!
We just got in and the power's gone?
Weirdo!
What a dick, shining his torch
on our faces like that!
Where do you think that fucker went?
Just wait!
He asked us to wait.
Now what?
Where's this guy?
Come let's check upstairs.
I mean...must we?
He said he'll be back.
Careful, watch the steps!
Just shine the torch will you!
Fucking dickhead!
Was that really necessary?
Come on!
Let's go!
You have to behave like a dick!
Fucker!
What happened?
You go first.
Bloody dick brain!
I'm so, so hot
My burning bad
I feel sooo hot
So so hot
I'm a furnace inside
Believe it or not
It burns a lot
It's so so hot
I'm so, so hot
My burning bad
I feel sooo hot
So so hot
I'm a furnace inside
Believe it or not
It burns a lot
It's so so hot
What the fuck was going on in that hotel?
Dude, you didn't see it!
What the hell was happening?
What was happening?
What the fuck was happening?
Sir, please turn on the AC
What was happening?
Fuck! What?
You think Ria will do me?
Yeah yeah she will...
you think you can manage ?
Yes boss, but where?
Where! where where fuckface!
What the fuck was happening!
You shouldn't play with something hot!
Didn't your dad tell you boy?
I'm burning in the flame of beauty
I feel sooo hot
So so hot
There's a heatwave in my body
I feel sooo hot
So so hot
I'm burning in the flame of beauty
I feel sooo hot
So so hot
There's a heatwave in my body
I'm sooo hot
So so hot
Let's go!
Did we miss something?
-Forget it man!
-Hey where you going?
Hello! Popuda!
Do you have a room available?
Oh Popuda, you don't have to
call the cops...
Hello!
What did Popuda say?
This sucks!
Ria...
What?
Strawberry...
Blueberry.
Extra Dotted.
Shall we just put the condoms
on our thumbs or what?
What a fuckall place we live in.
Can't even get laid!
You said it...
And then those two useless fuck faces!
And this bitching heat!
A.C. (air conditioning)
Shopping mall
Come on.
Ready!
Set.
Go!
Fucker!
Come on!
What ? Let's go!
Your mall idea was kickass!
Well, someone had to do something!
So what shall we do now?
Do I have to spell that out as well?
Put your hand on your waist.
Why?
Just do it!
No!
Please do it, please!
I want to take a picture.
You're looking good in that dress.
You are looking like a model.
Put your hand on the waist.
Drop the sari a bit?
Come down? Let me do a close-up.
Come...
Want to take one together?
Hey dickhead!
Where's the booze?
How the hell am I supposed to know?
Whose bag is it?
Yours...
Whose bottle is it?
Who is going to bring it?
Your dad will bring it you fuck!
Why do you pull his leg all the time?
No not this way.
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
What happened to you?
What happened bro?
Why are you panting like this?
Where's the booze?
Hey asshole!
Where are you running from?
Just shut it ! Fucker...
You want booze, this, that, everything!
I am not your father's servant you moron!
Oh really...
You keep drinking that.
I will eat this.
Hey!
What?
Don't go there...
Why?
I am telling you...
Come with me...
Why?
Tell me.
Do you want to talk or play?
What the fuck!
Hey fucker...
What's there to see? Huh?
What's your problem huh?
Are you fucking deaf or what?
Do you think this is a free show?
You old pervert!
What happened bro?
Shhh, quiet! Stop shouting!
What do you want me to do?
Just shut up!
-What happened?
-I don't know.
Hey!
Fucker!
I've had it with you.
What the fuck?
Pele, what's wrong with you?
You fucking faggot!
What are you doing!
Get up.
Get over to that side!
Stand back over there and don't move!
This is too much man,
I'm warning you!
Fuck off and shut your face!
Just stand there and shut the fuck up.
I understand,
he's young, hot headed.
Fetch some water!
Do something.
Fuck! Just chill!
He's fine!
Shut up... I'm telling
you for the last time!
Babai!
There's no water.
We are old people...
We have nowhere to go,
We are stuck here.
Where have these shit heads come from?
What's your fucking problem?
Who are these people?
-Who are these people?
-I don't feel good about this.
I'm telling you, man...
Are you scared of a couple of oldies?
Bro, enough! Stop acting like a cunt.
Sorry.
Here, have some booze.
Drink up. Here,
have a sip.
-Here, have a sip.
-Why the fuck did you hit me?
I'm sorry,
My apologies!
Don't be so hot headed!
Just drink and be cool.
You seem tired.
Why don't you rest here?
We can all leave in the morning.
You guys wait here, okay ?
Yes, we can wait here, but...
He is not feeling well.
Do you guys have something to eat?
It's a long night...
You have any munchies in that bag ?
Nothing!
This is all there is...
I won't have it anymore.
Give it to me.
I don't think she should drink that!
My throat is burning!
Take it slow.
Find some water, please!
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
-Where are you going?
-Take it easy.
Take it slow.
Try to sit straight please.
Shall we play?
Which color goes to who?
Red green yellow blue.
These colours deceive.
Do you have a clue?
Choose your colours.
The game has chosen you.
I choose the game's choice.
Blue.
Green.
Yellow.
A six and a five.
Try and stay alive.
Now I've got the four.
No one's safe anymore.
Girl you got four in the cup.
Why don't you just eat him up?
Eat him up?
Eat him.
Should I eat him now?
Yes.
Ria!
Ria! Get up. Come!
Get up!
Get going!
Ria! Don't go to the escalator.
Don't go on the fucking escalator!
Babai got killed!
Oh God, Babai's dead!
God! You saw that Babai died.
I didn't do anything.
I've committed no sin.
It all happened because of these whores.
Babai got killed!
You saw it God!
Babai was eaten.
I've done nothing.
I didn't commit any sin.
Don't you want to fuck? Huh!
Come on. Let's do it.
I'll fuck you good today!
You think you can handle it?
Leave her!
Shut up bitch!
Come on, let's fuck!
Bloody whore.
I should fuck you first.
Fucking whore!
Enjoying it? Huh!
You want to Fuck? You Asshole!
Don't go there. Don't!
Listen! Listen to me.
We could get out that way. Come with me.
What is this place!
Why did I come here?
Listen.
Let me tell you a story.
A long, long time ago...
They made a mistake.
A grave mistake.
And so they fled. They ran.
But how could they escape?
They were immortal.
Since they were kids,
they used to play a game.
The game of "finding the game".
Everyone in the Irum family
knew about this mysterious game.
Mirumi and Kirama Irum.
They knew the story well.
The forbidden game called for them,
beckoned them, whispered to them at night.
The flute was the key to the game.
But they weren't supposed to know that.
They were fools. They did not know
that the game was a master of illusion.
The game had been
locked away for centuries.
The Irum clan were the chosen
keepers of the game.
The most dangerous game
of the world.
If the game ever found a way out,
It would result in disaster.
Fusing root magic and illusion,
with powerful chants,
the Irum clan had contained the evil game.
The game,eager for release,
was patiently waiting,
for the keys of fate to turn.
The ancient, cunning game
was thirsting for only one thing.
Blood!
Their father, Shaman Faruk Irum,
was an alchemist and occult practitioner.
The dirty old game had managed
to evade him and escape,
hallucinating Mirumi and Kirama.
Making them do as it pleased.
I curse you.
Father!
It was a cruel and inhuman
hunger they felt.
They couldn't eat human food anymore.
Every pore of their body
cried out for something moist.
As if their very life had been
suddenly sucked out of them.
Blood.
Sweet.
Fresh.
The elixir of life.
The game was playing with them.
It's not easy to be a monster.
The game didn't let them eat.
They rotted,wasted and withered away.
Mirumi and Kirama.
Death eluded them.
Their's was a poisoned life.
An unending,impossible existence.
An inhuman suffering.
Time stopped making sense.
As if it had ceased to exist.
They hid,for what
felt like centuries,
in the basement of
an old,dead temple.
And they hid
the cursed game with them.
But this was a game of fate and chances
and fate has its own twists.
The game was playing with them.
for thousands of years.
Exactly like it played with others,
Like it's playing with you right now.
Oh no.
They went insane,
blinded by their bloodlust.
Senseless, rootless, lifeless.
The devil had captured them.
The old game suddenly
sprung its surprise.
A new player.
Oshini Irum.
She was born of the same seed,
belonged to the same clan.
She had spent her whole life waiting
for the game to come to her.
They couldn't even begin
to imagine what was to follow.
Oshini had been handed down
the family heirloom.
The fatal flute.
Mirumi and Kirama had the cursed game.
But Oshini the Shaman,
she had the key.
Mirumi!
Your father had no clue
how powerful the game is.
you both are equally inept!
You and your lover,
I want that game.
I know what to do with it.
You don't know anything.
And you will never know.
One needs to transcend for that.
One needs to seek transcendence.
Who knows,when or what
how the dice will roll?
Drops of blood tears your eye
who knows, when how or why
The unbridled game wanted
a practitioner, a skilled hand.
Someone whose roll of dice could begin the
game's killing spree - across the world.
I won the game.
Do you have a room to rent?
This story isn't over yet.
The game has just begun.