[female judge] The defendant will stand.
Trevor Bingley, on all
14 counts of dangerous driving…
-[car horn blares]
-[sports car engine roars]
The destruction of priceless artwork…
-[grunts]
-[bangs]
Criminal damage…
[grinding]
and arson…
-[screaming]
-[flames roar]
You have been found guilty.
-[woman gasps]
-[man] Yes!
-[soft murmuring]
-[slow sad music playing]
[judge] Do you have anything to say
before you're taken down?
[sincerely] I'm just really, really sorry.
-You see… there was this bee
-[inviting music begins]
[buzzing]
[exciting theme music playing]
[female voice] Darling, the car's going
to be here any second.
Darling, did you hear me?
I can't find my espadrilles. The ones
we got in Aruba with the little, uh,
the scuba divers on the fronts.
Forget the espadrilles, where's Orlando?
Orlando isn't coming.
They're sending someone else.
[bell rings]
What?
[buzzing]
[Trevor] Shoo.
-[beep]
-Hello?
[Trevor] Shoo.
Good. Go away.
Hello?
Oh, hello.
[upbeat] I'm Trevor. From, uh,
from Housesitters Deluxe.
I'm house-sitting for you this week.
-Oh.
-[buzzing]
-Okay…
-[beep]
[soft electronic gate buzz]
-[gravel crunching]
-[epic adventure music swells]
Gosh.
[soft chuckle]
Good morning, Mrs… Kolstad-Burgenbottom.
Bergenbatten. Kolstad-Bergenbatten.
Kolstad-Bergenbatten, sorry.
Thank you.
On behalf of… er, House-sitters Deluxe,
may I apologize for the last-minute change
-in personnel and assure you that
-[phone rings]
all our staff are trained
to the same BSI404 house-sitting…
[Nina] Christian, the car's here!
[Trevor forlorn] …industry standards.
-[buzzing]
-[luggage banging down stairs]
[sighs] I found them,
in a drawer with the flip-flops.
-Is this him?
-Good morning, Sir. Pleased to meet you--
Yeah, do you mind if we get on with this?
We're in a bit of a rush
and I need to be quick.
Okay.
Everything you need to
know is written in this manual.
-Manual. Right. Good.
-[tentative music]
[Nina] It's all very straightforward.
Special edition Miele,
infra red beam to open.
[drawer clicks]
Taps are gesture operated.
Left for on. Up for hot. Down for cold.
[dog barks]
Right for off.
Oh, that's Cupcake. She's very friendly.
-[Trevor] Oh gracious.
-[licking]
[nervously] Yes,
you are friendly, aren't you?
[Nina] Sliding doors.
Keys are in this drawer.
-[Trevor patiently] Okay.
-And all the blinds are remote controlled.
Oh, right, I'll… sorry, just a moment,
[Nina] And here--
-[phone rings]
-[Trevor whispers] Down!
-[Nina] Yes, hello?
-[Christian] Er…
You'll find all the remotes here.
You need me to explain them?
[hesitantly] Um…
Uh, no, that's fine.
-[Nina] Okay, bye.
-The dog has a severe nut allergy.
[firmly] She mustn't eat anything
that isn't her prescription dog food.
Or there is, uh,
doggie doo-doo everywhere.
[Nina] We keep the dog food in here.
-[Cupcake barks]
-Oh.
[door clicks]
-So please keep the door closed.
-Door closed. Right.
And the chip in her collar
operates the dog flap in there.
Ah yes.
Because if she can't get out…
There's doggie doo-doo everywhere.
It's a recurring theme, yeah. Hey!
-[Cupcake barks]
-Who doo-doos everywhere, eh?
Cupcake, come say bye to Mummy! Yeah?
Good girl, good girl. Christian, bags!
-Yeah, going now.
-[metallic clanging]
-Woah! Careful!.
-Oh.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I paid £80,000 for that.
It turned out to be a Kandinsky.
It's worth a lot of money.
But not as much as this.
[magical music playing]
-[Trevor] Golly.
-[Christian chuckles]
You know what it is?
It's… an E-type Jaguar, isn't it?
The first E-type Jaguar ever made.
-Huh! Amazing.
-What do you think she's worth?
Oh, must be… thousands.
Two million pounds.
O… kay.
-Hello?
-Yeah, okay.
All the locks and the alarm
are operated by two simple codes.
I used the names of
famous naval battles to make it easy.
Uh, so to open, uh,
it's the Battle of Frisverhelwilen.
-[soft muttering]
-[alarm beeps]
1748.
-Yup. So, okay, there we go.
-Okay.
[door opens]
Okay.
And to arm the system, even easier,
uh, it's the Battle of Bulhornbører.
-[soft muttering]
-[Nina] 1513.
Oh… right, yes.
I think perhaps I should uh--
Oh no, don't worry.
It's all in the manual.
Oh, the manual. Yes, of course.
Yeah, if the panel locks down
for any reason,
Nina did have them add a voice override.
Yes, but that only works with my voice,
[impatiently] and he won't need it
anyway because it's all in the manual.
Right, yes. Okay.
The library is strictly
out of bounds to the dog.
There's an illuminated manuscript
in there that's worth millions.
[Trevor] Okay.
It's a no-go zone for
Cupcake, as is our bedroom upstairs.
Uh, you are in the maid's room,
far side down the corridor.
-Okay.
-Uh… any questions?
-Uhm--
-Good.
[luggage clattering]
You have done this
work before, haven't you?
Uh, no, actually. I'm new to the company.
[laughs]
You've never done house-sitting before?
No… not as such.
But please don't worry,
I have a house too.
Well, I used to have a house.
So all this is very familiar territory.
[Nina] Hm.
Oh here, let me… I'll get that for you.
[thud and toys sqeaking]
-Oh, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. Let me…
-[car honks]
-[Christian] Honey, we have to go!
-[Trevor] Oh dear, I'll just…
[Nina] Orlando used to call us every day.
-If you wouldn't mind doing the same.
-Absolutely. My pleasure.
[toy squeaks]
-Have a good holiday, Mrs.…
-Kolstad-Bergenbatten.
That's it. Bye!
[uneasy music playing]
Have a good time!
[door closes and music stops]
[sighs]
-[buzzing]
-[hopeful music begins]
[door rattles]
-[ball squeaks]
-[epic music crescendos]
-[clanging]
-[nervous yelp]
-[sighs in relief]
-[lawnmower outside]
[clinks]
-[Trevor sighs]
-[soft celebratory chime]
[rubbing]
[female voice] Please leave your message
after the tone.
-[beep]
-[buzzing]
Hello, sweet pea, it's Dad here.
I've got the most amazing news.
I managed to get a job.
[buzz]
Took me a little longer
than I was hoping, to be honest.
But you know what this means…
It means that we can
still go on holiday together.
Which is so great.
Just not tomorrow.
Shoo. Shoo.
[clattering]
[tense music crescendos]
Darling, I'll call you back.
Oh, my goodness.
-Oh, no!
-[lawnmower drawing closer]
[soft gasp]
[buzzing]
Glue.
Glue, glue, glue,
glue, glue, glue, glue, glue.
-[soft muttering]
-[tense music builds]
Manual.
The manual.
Come on.
-[door clicks]
-Ha!
[quaint music playing]
[lawnmower droning]
[buzzing]
[sighs]
-[soft whine]
-Good dog.
-[door closes]
-[soft muttering]
[excitedly] Oh.
-Aha!
-[hopeful music plays]
[squelching]
-[cat mews]
-[Cupcake barks]
[buzzing]
[wings fluttering more slowly]
There.
[squelching]
[soft gasp]
[blows]
-Oh!
-[door opens]
-Right.
-[clicking]
-[hairdryer blows powerfully]
-[statue head thuds on floor]
[Cupcake vocalizes excitedly]
Oh, no.
-[anxious music playing]
-Cupcake?
Hello?
[falsely cheery] Cupcake?
Ha!
[Cupcake panting, whining]
-[growls]
-Come on.
Give it to me.
[desperately] Give it to me. Come on.
Drop it.
[angrily] Drop it.
[plaintively] Please…
[surprised] Oh!
Ah… thank you!
[hairdryer blows hard, then soft]
[triumphant musical chord]
[eerie music starts]
Stay.
[soft whining]
[beep]
Hi Maddy, it's Dad again. Do give
me a call when you can. Okay, thanks, bye.
[sighs]
-[cupboard door clicks]
-[gasps]
[excited] Ooh!
Er… right!
[drawer clicks]
[soup spatters]
[gas ignition clicking]
[foreboding music playing]
[buzzing]
Buzz off.
[dramatic music tone]
Good.
-[muffled buzzing]
-Hm.
[soft scratching]
[soft quirky music playing]
Hmm.
[tense music builds]
[plastic cup clacks on counter]
[quizzically] Hey…
Huh!
[thud]
-[curious music playing]
-[footsteps and muttering]
[metal scraping]
[flames whoosh]
[buzzing]
[Cupcake whines and grunts]
[dramatic music crescendos]
-[door lock thuds]
-[Cupcake barking]
How… how did…?
Code.
Code… is in the manual.
[doom laden music playing]
[distressed muttering]
-[flames crackling]
-[groans] Oh!
-[hisses]
-Aha!
[exhausted] Oh, my goodness. [sighs]
-Oh, my goodness.
-[Cupcake barks]
-[frantic music playing]
-[Trevor] Oh no!
[desperately] The codes. The codes.
The codes.
-[disaster music crashes]
-[Trevor whimpers]
[hyesterical] The codes.
It's all in the manual!
[Cupcake barking]
[whimpers, screams]
-[barking]
-[buzzing]
-[clattering]
-[splashing]
-[buzzing]
-[dramatic music plays]
-[dramatic music builds]
-[bee drones like WWII bomber]
[music stops]
[closing theme music playing]
-[buzzing]
-[barking]
-[whimpering]
-[door rattling]
[electronic buzz]
[dramatic music playing]
What are those codes? The codes,
the codes, the Battle…
the Battle of f… [spluttering]
fish, f… fa-da-fet. Fish fillet.
17 oh, 17 something.
17, something, something.
[alarm blares]
-Oh!
-[noises from room]
-…5.
-[alarm blares]
-No!
-[Cupcake barks]
[clattering]
-…56.
-[alarm blares]
No!
[Cupcake barks]
-[loud thud]
-[ineffective banging on door]
-Aha!
-[battle music swells]
[whimpering]
[clattering]
[bang]
-[tearing]
-[foreboding music plays]
[soft grunt]
-[thud]
-[Cupcake barks, bee buzzes]
Oh… no! Um…
Voice override. She had a voice override.
[beep]
1746.
-[Cupcake grunting]
-[alarm blares]
[tense] 1746.
[alarm blares]
-[high pitched] 1747.
-[alarm blares]
[high pitched in song voice] 1747!
-[tense music playing]
[high pitched] 1748?
[welcoming beeps]
[high pitched] Yes! It was 1748.
Oh, thank God for that. Cupcake.
[whines]
[normal voice] Cupcake.
Cupcake, come on, you get out.
[door clicks]
[growls in determination] Right.
-Where are you?
-[curious music playing]
[sneakily] Are you over here?
[muted] Where are you?
[growls]
Huuh! Heh!
Come on…
-Come on.
-[music swells]
Oh my goodness. [gasps]
[whimpers and groans] Argh.
-[loud grunt]
-[thud]
[upbeat music playing]
-[grunts]
-[lid clunks]
[nervous humming]
[tearing]
-[exhales sharply]
-[drumroll and music fades]
[soft whimper]
-[sighs]
-[bustling music playing]
-[clink]
-[thuds]
[vaccum cleaner whirrs]
[loud sigh]
[bustling music stops]
[hopeful music plays]
[sighs cheerily] Huh.
[soft thud]
[drawer closes]
-Tsk.
-[squeaking]
Ugh.
Hm.
-[switch flicks]
-[hopeful music plays]
[switch flicks]
-[sighs with relief]
-[door opens]
-[switch flicks]
-[washing machine rumbles]
[water gurgling]
[zipping]
[happy music swells]
-[high pitched spinning]
-[rattling]
Hm.
[female voice] Please leave your message
after the tone.
[soft beep]
Sweetheart, it's just me again. Uh…
I'm just calling, uh,
to say I love you and
I miss you very much.
-And, uh… Oh…
-[phone rings]
-Dad.
-Darling! How are you?
Remember what I told you about
voicemails. No one does that anymore.
Oh, right, of course,
no voicemails. Sorry, I keep forgetting.
But isn't it great, sweet pea.
We're actually going to go away together.
I know. We're going
away together tomorrow.
Oh. Didn't you get my voicemail?
Oh no, of course,
you don't do, um, voice…
Um, well, the thing is sweet pea,
I've managed to get a job.
Amazing.
Mum! Dad got a job!
-[mum] What?
-I told you he would.
Oh, but wait.
Can we still go away tomorrow?
Ah, no, well that's
the thing. It'll have to be next week.
Oh, uh, wait. Next week?
Oh, hello Jess.
Sorry, yes, I have to
work this week now, so…
So you just want me to
change all my plans for you, Trevor?
Well, yes, ideally.
Do you have any idea
how difficult that's going to be?
Are you doing that thing again
where you don't move your face
and pretend the line's frozen?
Uh, no. No. No, I was just… sorry Jess,
all this has happened so last minute.
-Please, Mum.
-Oh for God's sake.
How can you be even
more annoying after the divorce?
So what is this job, anyway?
Well, I'm house-sitting.
So the job is just sitting
around a house all day doing nothing?
You finally found
something you're good at.
Well, actually, it's harder
than it sounds. You see there's--
Let's just talk about this
tomorrow, Trevor. Bedtime.
Yeah. Dad, I've got to go.
-Let's just keep in touch…
-[mum] Maddy!
and I love you
to the moon and ba-- uh… you've gone.
[high pitched] 1513.
-[high-pitched] Night setting.
-[beeps]
-[sighs]
-[sniffs]
[mysterious music playing]
-Ohh!
-[music builds and stops]
[resounding alarm blares]
[Trevor screams desperately]
1746! Er, 17… 1747! 1748!
[closing theme music playing]
-[alarm beeping]
-[theme music playing gently]
[Trevor in high-pitched voice] 1748.
[sighs]
Morning, Cupcake.
-Right.
-[soft whine]
Let's get you your special food.
-[Cupcake whimpers excitedly]
-There you go.
[soft thud]
[drawer clicks]
[sighs contentedly]
-[enjoying] Hm.
-[buzzing]
[yoghurt splats on the floor]
[tuts] Oh!
[door bell rings]
Oh, hello, good morning.
-Good morning, Sir. Sorry to disturb you.
-Oh, that's all right.
-Are you the owner of this property?
-[laughs bashfully] Oh, no.
[sing song] No, oh…
[bee buzzes inside his trousers]
[growls] No…
-You're not the property owner?
-[shakily] No, I'm here temporarily…
[spluttering] while, while the owners,
-while the owners are away.
-[fingers crackle]
[sighs and grunts]
-I'm the house-sitter.
-[flapping noise]
[claps]
Okay, well uhm… we had a notification
-of an alarm being activated.
-[shrieks] Ooh!
[covering] Oh! Oh, Really?
Really? [whimpering] Eee, ooo…
An alarm? Right.
Oh, right.
But it was de-set
before we could send someone out.
[grunting]
Uh, so is everything okay?
Oh, yes. I'm fine, thank you. Yes, yes.
Yes, just got a few things to
get on with around the house.
-[whimpering]
-[flapping]
Thank you so much for coming.
-[door thuds]
-[rapid breathing]
[unzipping]
[buzzing]
-Ha.
-[stapler clacks]
[triumphant music playing]
[sliding]
-[buzzing]
-[incoherent uttering]
[tearing noise]
[groans]
-Oh.
-[click]
[getting an idea] Ha…
[wheelbarrow squeaking]
[doors creak]
-[click]
-Yes!
[whoosh of fire]
[soft awkward whimper]
[whoosh of flames]
-[click]
-Ah!
-Ha!
-[soft whine]
-[drawer slides open]
-[clanks]
Good.
[dog paws clack on the floor]
[licking]
[buzzing]
[dramatic music playing]
Ha!
-[slam]
-Yes!
[phone rings]
-[ringtone]
-Oh, hello.
Is everything all right?
[awkwardly] Yes, fine.
It's just that we had a call
from the security company.
They said the alarm had gone off.
Oh, did you? No, no,
nothing to worry about.
Uh, just a little mix-up with the codes.
How's Cupcake? Is she eating her food?
Oh, uh, yes. Yes. She's, she's eating…
[dramatic music builds]
[mournfully] Oh…
What?
Oh, uh, nothing.
[falsely nonchalant]
Nothing, it's all, it's all fine.
[Trevor whispers] No!
-Did something happen?
-Um… no, no, all good here.
-[Cupcake groans and whines]
-[stomach rumbles]
[loud fart]
Oops. Pardon me.
Can I see Cupcake?
Uh, yes. Yes, absolutely.
Um, why don't I jus--
[frustrated] Ugh!
He froze.
[taps]
Oh…
[Cupcake whines, farts]
[sloppy fart]
-[resignedly] Ugh.
-[Cupcake whines]
-[dramatic music playing]
-Right!
[sighs]
[pensively] Hmmm!
-Oh! Oh, dear.
-[Cupcake's stomach gurgles]
[clanks open]
[grunting]
-Ha!
-[buzzing]
[epic freedom music plays]
[wings fluttering]
[determined music playing]
[Trevor panting]
Huh!
-[music intensifies]
-[buzzing deepens]
-[sighs]
-[defeated music playing]
-[rattling]
-Huh?
[buzzing]
[closing theme music plays]
[tense music playing]
[Trevor rattles door]
[soft whimper]
[rattling door handle]
[birds chirping]
[rattling]
[tuts]
[Trevor gasps with realisation]
Cupcake?
-[knocking on glass]
-[Trevor] Cupcake.
[overly cheery] Hello.
[muffled] Come on. Come on!
[whines]
[muffled] Come. Come on! Come on!
Ooh…
[muffled] Come on. Come on!
-[Trevor imitates barking]
-[Cupcake groans]
[birds chirping]
-[knocking on glass]
-[triumphant music playing]
-[cat mews]
-[Cupcake barks]
-[cat screeches]
-[thud, Cupcake whines]
-Cupcake.
-[Cupcake barks]
[Cupcake groans]
[electric beep and slide]
Yes!
Aha!
[grunting]
Oh dear.
[grunts]
-[beep and electric sliding]
-[Trevor yelps] Ow!
[gasps] Oh my goodness!
-[electric door revving]
-[Trevor grunting]
-[cat screeches]
-[Cupcake barks]
-Huh?
-[buzzing]
[Trevor] What?
[tense music builds]
-[crunch]
-[Trevor screams]
-[squelching]
-[Trevor groans]
[repulsed] Urgh!
Pwoar!
Ow!
[gingerly] Oof!
-[grunting and groaning]
-[buzzing]
Right.
[socks squeak]
[buzzing]
Ah!
-[clink]
-[Trevor] Aha!
[whirring]
[metallic clinking and whirring]
-Ahh!
-[buzzing]
Ha! Die!
-[metallic clinking and electric whirring]
-[Trevor whimpering]
[bang]
-[church bell tolls]
-[whispers] Oh no!
[buzzing]
[wings fluttering]
-Where's he gone?
-[buzzing]
[coughs]
[Trevor] I'll get you!
-[doorbell rings]
-Argh!
-[thud]
-[groan]
-[groans]
-[doorbell rings]
[tense music playing]
[radio voice] This is a stolen moped, sir.
[incoherent muttering]
[tuts]
[revelatory music plays]
-[Trevor falsely calm] Oh, hello again.
-We've had a…
[sniffs]
-We've had a tip-off, sir.
-Right.
I don't think this is real fur,
just in case that's what you were…
A tip-off about a gang
of professional burglars, sir,
who we believe might be
operating in this area.
Oh, that's good.
I mean, that you've had a tip-off.
Not that there are burglars.
Burglars, bad.
[oddly] Bad burglars.
We're asking everyone to keep an eye out
for any suspicious behavior.
And inform us immediately.
Absolutely. Well, I'm personally,
uh, very suspicious so uh…
So I'll be sure to…
Well, look, I should probably…
Yes, I'll let you get back to…
Thank you very much. Um, and look,
thank you so much for coming.
I've got my, uh…
-[door clicks]
-[deep sigh]
[phone rings]
[Jess] Right Trevor let's get this sorted.
Oh, Jess. Hi.
Oh my God, what are you wearing?
Oh, this. Well, it's the only thing that
I could find and,
and there was a policeman at the door.
-Why, what have you done this time?
-Nothing.
I got locked out. It wasn't
my fault though. You see there was a bee…
Of course, a bee. Blame it on a bee.
Just like the evil trolley that got you
sacked from Asda.
Or the shredder that attacked
you at the estate agents.
It did attack me.
Trevor, you need to stop obsessing about
stupid little things that
absolutely do not matter.
Not everything is out to get you, okay?
Look, if I rearrange my schedule, will
you swear not to ruin everything again?
You need to focus on Maddy.
You can't let her down, Trevor.
[with feeling] I know. I know.
Just, please concentrate on this holiday.
-For her sake.
-I will, Jess. I really will.
And the bee's gone now, I think, so…
-All right, well, good luck!
-Thank you.
And clean yourself up.
You look like a bloody panda.
-[disconnected phone tone]
-[slow thoughtful music playing]
[hangers clanging]
[thud]
[mischievous music playing]
[buzzing descends the chimney]
[closing theme music playing]
[serene music playing]
Oh!
[soft grunting]
Heh.
Oh…
-[soft beep]
-["Just an Illusion" playing]
Oh.
-[water squirts]
-Ow!
[enjoying] Oh.
[squeaks]
[buzzing]
[screams]
[incoherent muttering]
[buzzing]
[beep and music stops]
-Huh?
-[mysterious music playing]
[music reaches dramatic crescendo]
-[fluttering]
-[Trevor gasps] There you are.
[hairdryer blowing]
[whooshing]
[blows faster and louder]
[bumps and buzzes]
[blowing stops]
-[banging]
-[buzzing]
[Trevor exclaims]
[whispers] Where are you?
[muffled buzzing]
[tense music building]
-[grunt]
-[loud bang, piano wires clang]
Yes!
Ah!
[single piano note plays]
-[piano notes playing]
-[buzzing]
-[muffled buzzing]
-Tsk. [sighs]
[piano starts playing]
[buzzing]
[music stops]
[softly] Yes!
-[buzzing]
-[thud]
[screams]
You!
[screaming] Get out!
Get out!
[screams] Die!
Die!
[rattling]
[satisfied music playing]
[click]
[soft whirring]
[sucking noise]
[rattling]
[gushing] Ah!
-Aha!
-[triumphant music plays]
[Trevor smugly] Yes!
-[shouting]
-[banging]
[exhales]
[bell tolls ominously]
[sighs]
-[flames crackling]
-[mystical music playing]
[sizzling]
[mystical chanting music playing]
[Trevor vocalizing]
Uh.
[ominous music playing]
[music swells]
-[gentle fluttering]
-[eerie music plays]
[closing theme music playing]
-Phew.
-[exciting theme music playing]
[clink]
Right.
[soft droning]
[metallic sliding and thud]
[sighs in frustration]
[Trevor] Right.
One of those.
Good.
-[whirring]
-[music ends]
[contented sigh]
[rattling and chinking]
[Trevor] Cheap.
-[washing machine rumbling]
-[glass tinkling]
Yeah.
-[high pitched] 1513.
-[alarm beeps]
[owl hoots]
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone rings]
-[whispers] Dad.
-[whispers] Darling, everything okay?
You don't have to whisper too, Dad.
Oh yes, right, sorry.
Right.
[clicking and clanging]
[electronic beeping]
[beep]
[electric buzzing]
[Maddy] She actually said
you could take me away.
After your job. She was okay with that?
Yes, couldn't be happier.
There's absolutely nothing
to worry about, darling.
Mum's totally on board and
the job here is going super well.
-[glass clinking]
-[Trevor slurping]
But you know, what we should be thinking
about, is where we're going to go.
And I'm going to send you
something now, darling.
It's a campsite on the Isle of Wight.
And it's got a pool and
table tennis tables and, uh, and it's
just a walk from the beach after a couple
of very short bus rides.
I miss you, Dad.
-I miss you too, sweet pea.
-[emotive music playing]
So much.
-[tense music playing]
-[clicking]
[soft whine]
Here.
Good dog.
[water flushing]
[dramatic music playing]
[burglar 1 whispers] Garage.
Find this.
[click]
-[tense music playing]
-[Trevor] Huh?
Eh?
[water flushing]
Huh.
[dramatic music builds]
-[smack]
-[buzzing]
-[yelps]
-[squirting noise]
[thud]
-[peeling noise]
-[burglar 2 softly] What?
[banging]
[squeak]
[buzzing]
[thud]
[burglar 3] Eric.
We're good to go on the Jag.
[grunting]
-[pop]
-[thud] Oh! Oh!
[buzzing]
[Trevor shouts] Right!
I know you're there!
Come on!
Where are you?
Where have you gone?
I can hear you.
Yes, I can! And I'm going to find you.
[buzzing]
Aha! There you are.
-[smack]
-[thud]
-[piano starts playing]
-Eh.
[Trevor] Where have you gone?
Are you over here somewhere?
I'm going to find you!
And when I find you,
I'm going to kill you!
Where've you gone?
You can't hide forever!
I'm going to get you!
Where are you?
Come here!
I want you to go away!
[softly] Please go away.
[mournfully] Please.
[Trevor high-pitched] 1513. Night setting.
-[beep]
-[alarm beeps]
-[burglar 3] Oh God.
-[tense piano music playing]
-[piano music fades]
-[rattling door]
[closing theme music playing]
[slow intriguing theme music playing]
[buzzing]
[wings fluttering]
[Trevor high-pitched] 1748.
[door unlocks]
Go! Let's go!
[Trevor whistling]
-[indistinct soft muttering]
-[door bell rings]
Oh my goodness.
Oh, no.
-[burglar whispers] We've got to get out.
-[burglar 2] Shut up!
[burglar] Get down!
[door opens]
[brightly] Oh, good morning.
Good morning, Sir.
Sorry to disturb you again.
Um, one of your neighbors reported
an unfamiliar car parked in Heath Grove,
and we've now traced it to the gang of
burglars I mentioned yesterday.
We're hoping somebody
might have seen something.
No. I haven't seen a thing.
And you're sure about that, Sir?
There are three suspects.
Two white males, one Black.
Sorry, officer. There's absolutely no one
in this house apart from me,
I can assure you.
[burglar 1] Stop! What are you doing?
It's not working.
[burglar 2] I've been in here
for eight hours!
[tense music playing]
[female voice] And you'd never seen these
men before?
No.
Even though you were alone in
the house with them for over eight hours?
Er…
You didn't hear them break in.
You didn't hear them moving about.
You didn't notice anything suspicious?
[apologetically] No.
[cars crunching on gravel]
-[door closes]
-[floorboards creak]
Right.
-[spraying]
-[squeaking]
[buzzing]
-[ominous music playing]
-[Trevor intrigued] Ah…
[quirky bustling music playing]
[Trevor mutters]
[whines anxiously]
[mystical music playing]
[whines hopefully]
No, Cupcake.
-I've got to look after you.
-[whines disappointedly]
[Trevor upbeat] Right.
[Trevor] Right.
[Trevor, softly] There.
-[buzzing]
-[epic music playing]
[dramatic crescendo]
[clunk]
[Trevor] Okay.
[pitter patter of Cupcake's claws]
[whispers] Go on, go on.
[music builds]
Yes!
-[soft thud]
-Ha!
[hissing]
Hm.
[hissing fades and dies]
[click]
[death bell tolls]
Yes!
[snoring]
Oh! Oh no!
What?
Cupcake?
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
-[phone rings]
-Oh!
Oh no…
-[phone ringing]
-[birds chirping]
-[sighs]
-What's taking him so long?
-Hello.
-Yeah, uh, we had a call from the police.
Oh. Oh, yes. I was, um…
Yeah, they left a message.
They said there was a break-in.
Is Cupcake all right?
-Uhm…
-[snoring]
She's just having a nap, actually.
Yeah, was anything taken?
Oh, uh, no, it was uh…
Well, they were caught. [chuckles]
The police caught the burglars?
Cupcake must have been terrified.
Can I see her?
Uh… she's out in the garden.
I thought you said she was having a nap.
Oh, yes.
She was having a nap, and now she's out in
the garden. Oh, there she is.
Hello, Cupcake. Hello!
[stiffly] Would you mind getting her,
please? I'd really like to see her.
-Uhm…
-[sharply] Now!
O-kay.
Cupcake.
Cupcake!
Cupcake, come here.
-Come on. Come on. Here we go.
-[snoring]
-Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
-[flapping]
[shouting] Cupcake!
Wake up!
-Meow.
-[phone rings]
[painfully] Oh…
[enthusiastically] Jess, hi!
I'm a bit tied up, actually. Would you--
No, Trevor. I need to know whether this
holiday is happening or not.
I have to work out my
schedule for next week.
Absolutely. Could I pop
you on hold for just a moment?
Do not put me on hold, Trevor. Do not pu--
[groans]
Come on.
Oh, hello.
There's my baby. How's my Cup-cup?
Oh, she's very well. Aren't you Cupcake?
[whining]
I know. I know. Yes, you are. Oh,
look out. What's she seen? Oh!
[thud]
-She's off.
-[snoring]
There she goes.
That cat had better watch out.
Go, Cupcake, go!
Anyway, look, I'll speak to you tomorrow.
-Thanks for calling. Bye.
-No, I--
Search vet! Nearest vet!
-Trevor, I'm still here.
-[sighs]
No, you're not.
-[exasperated sigh]
-[dramatic music playing]
Okay Cupcake. Come on.
I don't feel good about this.
Christian, what are you doing?
This house-sitter's really worrying me.
Yeah, he's worrying me too.
-[rattles doors]
-No… ugh.
-[snoring]
-[door clicks]
[Trevor] There we go.
Gently does it.
[hopeful music playing]
Right.
-Oh, phone!
-[buzzing]
[dramatic music builds]
[closing theme music playing]
-[car engine revving]
-[gears grinding]
-[tires screech]
-[thudding]
[Trevor] No, no, no, no!
[tires screech and engine revs]
Hello? Yes, yes, it is an emergency.
Great, I'll be there in five minutes.
Okay, thank you.
[engine almost stalling]
[engine roars]
-[Trevor] Won't be long Cupcake.
-[Cupcake whimpers]
-[sighs]
-[buzzing]
[suspense thriller music playing]
-[tires screeching]
-[Cupcake yelps]
-[smack]
-[Trevor] Uh!
[frantic buzzing]
-[incoherent uttering]
-[car horn hooting]
[car horn blaring]
-[tires screeching]
-[Cupcake whines]
-[buzzing]
-[car engine rumbling]
[incoherent muttering]
[buzzing]
-[squeak and click]
-Yes!
[van horn honking]
[metal clanging and scraping]
-[tires screech]
-[engine cuts out]
[Trevor grunts, gasps]
Ow! Ah!
[clanging]
-[grunting]
-[tense music playing]
[car engine starting and revving]
[birds chirping serenely]
[car engine revs and backfires]
-[groaning]
-[Cupcake whines]
[car door slams]
[door bell chimes]
-[Trevor] Hello!
-[female voice] Good morning Sir.
[Trevor] Good morning,
I was wondering if you could help.
[car engine revs and backfires]
[birds screeching]
[Trevor groans] Goodness.
-[Cupcake whines]
-[Trevor panting]
Here.
Here we go.
Good girl.
-Stay there.
-[soft whine]
-[tap]
-[grunting]
-[clang]
-[door opens]
[door shuts]
[Trevor] Right.
-[music crescendos]
-[clap]
[soft suspicious music playing]
-Huh?
-[tapping]
[whispers] Where've you gone?
[muffled buzzing]
[gasps]
[loud clanging]
[hysterical incoherent uttering]
You go there.
[muffled buzzing]
Ah! Here!
[raucous grinding]
[clang]
Okay…
-[loud buzz]
-Oh! You!
Right! Come on!
I'll get you… fire you!
[incoherent spluttering]
[shouts] Where are you?
-[mournful piano music playing]
-[buzzing]
[deep breathing] Oh gracious!
[regretfully] Oh no.
Oh no.
-[clang]
-[whimpers] Oh no.
[whimpering]
What have I done?
-[buzzing]
-[tender music playing]
-[clunk]
-[screams]
[loud clang]
[despairing music playing]
[sighs]
[wings fluttering]
[clicking tones]
[narrator] The life of the male
bumble bee isn't always plain sailing.
When the time comes, the colony's female
bees force the males out of the hive.
Ejected from the only home they've ever
known, these solitary bees have no choice
but to live out their days alone.
Homeless, hiveless, friendless.
-[clicking tones]
-[warm music playing]
-[birds chirping]
-[upbeat music playing]
[door creaks open]
[magical music playing]
[banging and sawing]
[grunting]
[buzzing]
[jar lid turning]
-Right.
-[rubbing]
[soft clank]
[rustling]
-[foreboding music playing]
-Eh.
-[buzzing]
-[music swells]
[closing theme music playing]
[airplane engine roaring]
[Nina anxiously] Christian,
he's still not picking up.
[sighs]
[soft grunt]
-[click and slide]
-[grunts]
[optimistic music playing]
-There.
-[buzzing]
[music swells romantically]
[Trevor] That's right.
[bee's wings fluttering]
-Yes!
-[electric buzzing]
-[thunderous explosion]
-[shattering and thud]
[whines]
[intense music playing]
What was that?
-[buzzing]
-[triumphant music playing]
-[screams in disbelief] What?
-[barking]
[thuds]
-[crash]
-[Cupcake whimpers]
-[Cupcake whines]
-[Trevor] Oh no!
[screams in abject frustration]
-[creak]
-Ah…
Christian…
-[Nina] Oh my God…
-[Christian] No!
[bang and shattering]
-[crackling]
-[doors shut]
[Trevor roaring]
[crackling]
-[Trevor screaming]
-[epic disaster music playing]
No!
[Nina] God!
[buzzing]
What are you doing here?
[soft indistinct background talking]
-[judge] The defendant will stand.
-[seat creaks]
Trevor Bingley, on all 14 counts
of wilful neglect,
dangerous driving, criminal damage
and arson, you have been found guilty.
-[gasps]
-Yes! [thud] Yes.
And I hereby sentence you to
the maximum term of three years in prison.
-[soft indistinct muttering]
-[Nina chuckles]
[whines softly]
[judge bangs gavel]
This court is adjourned.
[Maddy whimpers] Dad.
It's okay.
[slam]
-[officer cynically] Enjoy your stay.
-[thud]
[construction sounds]
[Christian] Huh. You can not be serious.
Nine million pounds, is that all?
Uh, well, it would be the largest domestic
insurance settlement for 20 years.
Uh, two million for the Jaguar,
four for the artworks,
and a… further three million
for general damage to the house.
What about my emotional distress?
They tried for my art collection and then
this moron burns down my entire house.
They're lucky I'm not asking for 50. Huh?
Yes.
-[splat]
-[coughing]
-[female voice] There you go.
-Thank you.
-[clunk]
-[soft grind]
[soft sigh]
[inmate] This bloke turns up, right?
This floppy-haired tool,
with this weird Scandi accent…
[plastic knife breaks]
-[inmate] had an E-type Jag, you know.
-[sighs]
[inmate] He pays us to rob this house.
And get this,
it only turns out to be his own house.
It's full of all this art, you know,
Mondrians and Kandinskys or something.
It's all bollocks to me, anyway.
But, you name it, he's got it.
And every single
one was a worthless fake. I kid you not.
Turns out it was all one gigantic
insurance fraud.
[inmate] What?
What are you doing here?
[phone rings]
-Hello?
-Hello. It's Trevor Bingley.
-Trevor who?
-Trevor Bingley.
From, uh, from Housesitters Deluxe.
Uh, in the, uh, fur coat? And the, um…
Oh, yes.
Hello, Sir. How are you doing?
Under the… circumstances.
Well, it's taken a bit of
getting used to, to be honest.
But actually, everyone's
been really friendly.
-All right, Trev?
-Oh.
Oh, hi Dino!
I'll bring your lunch along in a minute.
And the thing is, I've
got something very important to tell you.
-[soft indistinct chatter]
-[slow trendy music playing]
[female voice] It's absolutely gorgeous.
Nina said you got it for a song. 300,000?
Well, they sold it to me as a Sickert,
but I suspected it was actually a Degas.
[chuckles] Christian, darling,
there's someone at the door.
Turns out I was right.
Now I insured it for 15 million.
[chuckles] How do you do it?
-[chuckles]
-[Nina whispers] It's the police.
Okay.
[door clicks]
[apprehensive music playing]
We have some questions, sir,
about suspicious insurance claims
in connection
with burglaries at your house.
What suspicious insurance claims?
That's him. He paid us.
[dramatic music swells]
[male news reader] Having assembled
a collection of worthless fakes,
Kolstad-Bergenbatten
insured it for millions, then paid
a criminal gang to steal it from his own
house, and he pocketed the insurance.
[clanking and creaking]
[female judge] Trevor Bingley,
in recognition of your action,
which led directly to the
imprisonment of a shameless fraudster,
the Crown hereby pardons you
and grants you immediate release.
[pensive music playing]
[sighs]
-[Maddy joyously] Dad!
-[Trevor] Darling!
[Maddy] Ha!
-[Trevor] Thank you. It's amazing.
-[Maddy chuckles]
[Maddy chuckles fondly] Oh, Dad.
[heartwarming music playing]
[chuckles softly]
[swoosh]
[excitedly] Oh!
I can't believe it. I just can't
believe it. We're actually here.
[Trevor sighs excitedly]
Hm.
-[birds chirping]
-[buzzing]
-[tentative theme music playing]
[Trevor gasps]
[Trevor in disbelief] Hey?
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[inhaling sharply]
[sighs]
[fluttering]
-[sighs contentedly]
-[warm music playing]
[Trevor] Here.
There you go.
Hm.
[happy music swells]
-[smack]
-[buzzing]
[incoherent uttering]
[buzzing]
[upbeat music playing]
-[thud]
-[shout]
-[clattering]
-[grunting]
-[buzzing]
-[Trevor] Take that!
[Trevor] Come here! Come on!
Get out!
Ha!
Hello! Oh!
I'm going to get you!