[serene music playing]
Oh!
[soft grunting]
Heh.
Oh…
-[soft beep]
-["Just an Illusion" playing]
Oh.
-[water squirts]
-Ow!
[enjoying] Oh.
[squeaks]
[buzzing]
[screams]
[incoherent muttering]
[buzzing]
[beep and music stops]
-Huh?
-[mysterious music playing]
[music reaches dramatic crescendo]
-[fluttering]
-[Trevor gasps] There you are.
[hairdryer blowing]
[whooshing]
[blows faster and louder]
[bumps and buzzes]
[blowing stops]
-[banging]
-[buzzing]
[Trevor exclaims]
[whispers] Where are you?
[muffled buzzing]
[tense music building]
-[grunt]
-[loud bang, piano wires clang]
Yes!
Ah!
[single piano note plays]
-[piano notes playing]
-[buzzing]
-[muffled buzzing]
-Tsk. [sighs]
[piano starts playing]
[buzzing]
[music stops]
[softly] Yes!
-[buzzing]
-[thud]
[screams]
You!
[screaming] Get out!
Get out!
[screams] Die!
Die!
[rattling]
[satisfied music playing]
[click]
[soft whirring]
[sucking noise]
[rattling]
[gushing] Ah!
-Aha!
-[triumphant music plays]
[Trevor smugly] Yes!
-[shouting]
-[banging]
[exhales]
[bell tolls ominously]
[sighs]
-[flames crackling]
-[mystical music playing]
[sizzling]
[mystical chanting music playing]
[Trevor vocalizing]
Uh.
[ominous music playing]
[music swells]
-[gentle fluttering]
-[eerie music plays]
[closing theme music playing]