-Phew.
-[exciting theme music playing]
[clink]
Right.
[soft droning]
[metallic sliding and thud]
[sighs in frustration]
[Trevor] Right.
One of those.
Good.
-[whirring]
-[music ends]
[contented sigh]
[rattling and chinking]
[Trevor] Cheap.
-[washing machine rumbling]
-[glass tinkling]
Yeah.
-[high pitched] 1513.
-[alarm beeps]
[owl hoots]
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone rings]
-[whispers] Dad.
-[whispers] Darling, everything okay?
You don't have to whisper too, Dad.
Oh yes, right, sorry.
Right.
[clicking and clanging]
[electronic beeping]
[beep]
[electric buzzing]
[Maddy] She actually said
you could take me away.
After your job. She was okay with that?
Yes, couldn't be happier.
There's absolutely nothing
to worry about, darling.
Mum's totally on board and
the job here is going super well.
-[glass clinking]
-[Trevor slurping]
But you know, what we should be thinking
about, is where we're going to go.
And I'm going to send you
something now, darling.
It's a campsite on the Isle of Wight.
And it's got a pool and
table tennis tables and, uh, and it's
just a walk from the beach after a couple
of very short bus rides.
I miss you, Dad.
-I miss you too, sweet pea.
-[emotive music playing]
So much.
-[tense music playing]
-[clicking]
[soft whine]
Here.
Good dog.
[water flushing]
[dramatic music playing]
[burglar 1 whispers] Garage.
Find this.
[click]
-[tense music playing]
-[Trevor] Huh?
Eh?
[water flushing]
Huh.
[dramatic music builds]
-[smack]
-[buzzing]
-[yelps]
-[squirting noise]
[thud]
-[peeling noise]
-[burglar 2 softly] What?
[banging]
[squeak]
[buzzing]
[thud]
[burglar 3] Eric.
We're good to go on the Jag.
[grunting]
-[pop]
-[thud] Oh! Oh!
[buzzing]
[Trevor shouts] Right!
I know you're there!
Come on!
Where are you?
Where have you gone?
I can hear you.
Yes, I can! And I'm going to find you.
[buzzing]
Aha! There you are.
-[smack]
-[thud]
-[piano starts playing]
-Eh.
[Trevor] Where have you gone?
Are you over here somewhere?
I'm going to find you!
And when I find you,
I'm going to kill you!
Where've you gone?
You can't hide forever!
I'm going to get you!
Where are you?
Come here!
I want you to go away!
[softly] Please go away.
[mournfully] Please.
[Trevor high-pitched] 1513. Night setting.
-[beep]
-[alarm beeps]
-[burglar 3] Oh God.
-[tense piano music playing]
-[piano music fades]
-[rattling door]
[closing theme music playing]