-[car engine revving]
-[gears grinding]
-[tires screech]
-[thudding]
[Trevor] No, no, no, no!
[tires screech and engine revs]
Hello? Yes, yes, it is an emergency.
Great, I'll be there in five minutes.
Okay, thank you.
[engine almost stalling]
[engine roars]
-[Trevor] Won't be long Cupcake.
-[Cupcake whimpers]
-[sighs]
-[buzzing]
[suspense thriller music playing]
-[tires screeching]
-[Cupcake yelps]
-[smack]
-[Trevor] Uh!
[frantic buzzing]
-[incoherent uttering]
-[car horn hooting]
[car horn blaring]
-[tires screeching]
-[Cupcake whines]
-[buzzing]
-[car engine rumbling]
[incoherent muttering]
[buzzing]
-[squeak and click]
-Yes!
[van horn honking]
[metal clanging and scraping]
-[tires screech]
-[engine cuts out]
[Trevor grunts, gasps]
Ow! Ah!
[clanging]
-[grunting]
-[tense music playing]
[car engine starting and revving]
[birds chirping serenely]
[car engine revs and backfires]
-[groaning]
-[Cupcake whines]
[car door slams]
[door bell chimes]
-[Trevor] Hello!
-[female voice] Good morning Sir.
[Trevor] Good morning,
I was wondering if you could help.
[car engine revs and backfires]
[birds screeching]
[Trevor groans] Goodness.
-[Cupcake whines]
-[Trevor panting]
Here.
Here we go.
Good girl.
-Stay there.
-[soft whine]
-[tap]
-[grunting]
-[clang]
-[door opens]
[door shuts]
[Trevor] Right.
-[music crescendos]
-[clap]
[soft suspicious music playing]
-Huh?
-[tapping]
[whispers] Where've you gone?
[muffled buzzing]
[gasps]
[loud clanging]
[hysterical incoherent uttering]
You go there.
[muffled buzzing]
Ah! Here!
[raucous grinding]
[clang]
Okay…
-[loud buzz]
-Oh! You!
Right! Come on!
I'll get you… fire you!
[incoherent spluttering]
[shouts] Where are you?
-[mournful piano music playing]
-[buzzing]
[deep breathing] Oh gracious!
[regretfully] Oh no.
Oh no.
-[clang]
-[whimpers] Oh no.
[whimpering]
What have I done?
-[buzzing]
-[tender music playing]
-[clunk]
-[screams]
[loud clang]
[despairing music playing]
[sighs]
[wings fluttering]
[clicking tones]
[narrator] The life of the male
bumble bee isn't always plain sailing.
When the time comes, the colony's female
bees force the males out of the hive.
Ejected from the only home they've ever
known, these solitary bees have no choice
but to live out their days alone.
Homeless, hiveless, friendless.
-[clicking tones]
-[warm music playing]
-[birds chirping]
-[upbeat music playing]
[door creaks open]
[magical music playing]
[banging and sawing]
[grunting]
[buzzing]
[jar lid turning]
-Right.
-[rubbing]
[soft clank]
[rustling]
-[foreboding music playing]
-Eh.
-[buzzing]
-[music swells]
[closing theme music playing]