-[alarm beeping]
-[theme music playing gently]
[Trevor in high-pitched voice] 1748.
[sighs]
Morning, Cupcake.
-Right.
-[soft whine]
Let's get you your special food.
-[Cupcake whimpers excitedly]
-There you go.
[soft thud]
[drawer clicks]
[sighs contentedly]
-[enjoying] Hm.
-[buzzing]
[yoghurt splats on the floor]
[tuts] Oh!
[door bell rings]
Oh, hello, good morning.
-Good morning, Sir. Sorry to disturb you.
-Oh, that's all right.
-Are you the owner of this property?
-[laughs bashfully] Oh, no.
[sing song] No, oh…
[bee buzzes inside his trousers]
[growls] No…
-You're not the property owner?
-[shakily] No, I'm here temporarily…
[spluttering] while, while the owners,
-while the owners are away.
-[fingers crackle]
[sighs and grunts]
-I'm the house-sitter.
-[flapping noise]
[claps]
Okay, well uhm… we had a notification
-of an alarm being activated.
-[shrieks] Ooh!
[covering] Oh! Oh, Really?
Really? [whimpering] Eee, ooo…
An alarm? Right.
Oh, right.
But it was de-set
before we could send someone out.
[grunting]
Uh, so is everything okay?
Oh, yes. I'm fine, thank you. Yes, yes.
Yes, just got a few things to
get on with around the house.
-[whimpering]
-[flapping]
Thank you so much for coming.
-[door thuds]
-[rapid breathing]
[unzipping]
[buzzing]
-Ha.
-[stapler clacks]
[triumphant music playing]
[sliding]
-[buzzing]
-[incoherent uttering]
[tearing noise]
[groans]
-Oh.
-[click]
[getting an idea] Ha…
[wheelbarrow squeaking]
[doors creak]
-[click]
-Yes!
[whoosh of fire]
[soft awkward whimper]
[whoosh of flames]
-[click]
-Ah!
-Ha!
-[soft whine]
-[drawer slides open]
-[clanks]
Good.
[dog paws clack on the floor]
[licking]
[buzzing]
[dramatic music playing]
Ha!
-[slam]
-Yes!
[phone rings]
-[ringtone]
-Oh, hello.
Is everything all right?
[awkwardly] Yes, fine.
It's just that we had a call
from the security company.
They said the alarm had gone off.
Oh, did you? No, no,
nothing to worry about.
Uh, just a little mix-up with the codes.
How's Cupcake? Is she eating her food?
Oh, uh, yes. Yes. She's, she's eating…
[dramatic music builds]
[mournfully] Oh…
What?
Oh, uh, nothing.
[falsely nonchalant]
Nothing, it's all, it's all fine.
[Trevor whispers] No!
-Did something happen?
-Um… no, no, all good here.
-[Cupcake groans and whines]
-[stomach rumbles]
[loud fart]
Oops. Pardon me.
Can I see Cupcake?
Uh, yes. Yes, absolutely.
Um, why don't I jus--
[frustrated] Ugh!
He froze.
[taps]
Oh…
[Cupcake whines, farts]
[sloppy fart]
-[resignedly] Ugh.
-[Cupcake whines]
-[dramatic music playing]
-Right!
[sighs]
[pensively] Hmmm!
-Oh! Oh, dear.
-[Cupcake's stomach gurgles]
[clanks open]
[grunting]
-Ha!
-[buzzing]
[epic freedom music plays]
[wings fluttering]
[determined music playing]
[Trevor panting]
Huh!
-[music intensifies]
-[buzzing deepens]
-[sighs]
-[defeated music playing]
-[rattling]
-Huh?
[buzzing]
[closing theme music plays]