[tense music playing]
[Trevor rattles door]
[soft whimper]
[rattling door handle]
[birds chirping]
[rattling]
[tuts]
[Trevor gasps with realisation]
Cupcake?
-[knocking on glass]
-[Trevor] Cupcake.
[overly cheery] Hello.
[muffled] Come on. Come on!
[whines]
[muffled] Come. Come on! Come on!
Ooh…
[muffled] Come on. Come on!
-[Trevor imitates barking]
-[Cupcake groans]
[birds chirping]
-[knocking on glass]
-[triumphant music playing]
-[cat mews]
-[Cupcake barks]
-[cat screeches]
-[thud, Cupcake whines]
-Cupcake.
-[Cupcake barks]
[Cupcake groans]
[electric beep and slide]
Yes!
Aha!
[grunting]
Oh dear.
[grunts]
-[beep and electric sliding]
-[Trevor yelps] Ow!
[gasps] Oh my goodness!
-[electric door revving]
-[Trevor grunting]
-[cat screeches]
-[Cupcake barks]
-Huh?
-[buzzing]
[Trevor] What?
[tense music builds]
-[crunch]
-[Trevor screams]
-[squelching]
-[Trevor groans]
[repulsed] Urgh!
Pwoar!
Ow!
[gingerly] Oof!
-[grunting and groaning]
-[buzzing]
Right.
[socks squeak]
[buzzing]
Ah!
-[clink]
-[Trevor] Aha!
[whirring]
[metallic clinking and whirring]
-Ahh!
-[buzzing]
Ha! Die!
-[metallic clinking and electric whirring]
-[Trevor whimpering]
[bang]
-[church bell tolls]
-[whispers] Oh no!
[buzzing]
[wings fluttering]
-Where's he gone?
-[buzzing]
[coughs]
[Trevor] I'll get you!
-[doorbell rings]
-Argh!
-[thud]
-[groan]
-[groans]
-[doorbell rings]
[tense music playing]
[radio voice] This is a stolen moped, sir.
[incoherent muttering]
[tuts]
[revelatory music plays]
-[Trevor falsely calm] Oh, hello again.
-We've had a…
[sniffs]
-We've had a tip-off, sir.
-Right.
I don't think this is real fur,
just in case that's what you were…
A tip-off about a gang
of professional burglars, sir,
who we believe might be
operating in this area.
Oh, that's good.
I mean, that you've had a tip-off.
Not that there are burglars.
Burglars, bad.
[oddly] Bad burglars.
We're asking everyone to keep an eye out
for any suspicious behavior.
And inform us immediately.
Absolutely. Well, I'm personally,
uh, very suspicious so uh…
So I'll be sure to…
Well, look, I should probably…
Yes, I'll let you get back to…
Thank you very much. Um, and look,
thank you so much for coming.
I've got my, uh…
-[door clicks]
-[deep sigh]
[phone rings]
[Jess] Right Trevor let's get this sorted.
Oh, Jess. Hi.
Oh my God, what are you wearing?
Oh, this. Well, it's the only thing that
I could find and,
and there was a policeman at the door.
-Why, what have you done this time?
-Nothing.
I got locked out. It wasn't
my fault though. You see there was a bee…
Of course, a bee. Blame it on a bee.
Just like the evil trolley that got you
sacked from Asda.
Or the shredder that attacked
you at the estate agents.
It did attack me.
Trevor, you need to stop obsessing about
stupid little things that
absolutely do not matter.
Not everything is out to get you, okay?
Look, if I rearrange my schedule, will
you swear not to ruin everything again?
You need to focus on Maddy.
You can't let her down, Trevor.
[with feeling] I know. I know.
Just, please concentrate on this holiday.
-For her sake.
-I will, Jess. I really will.
And the bee's gone now, I think, so…
-All right, well, good luck!
-Thank you.
And clean yourself up.
You look like a bloody panda.
-[disconnected phone tone]
-[slow thoughtful music playing]
[hangers clanging]
[thud]
[mischievous music playing]
[buzzing descends the chimney]
[closing theme music playing]