[slow intriguing theme music playing]
[buzzing]
[wings fluttering]
[Trevor high-pitched] 1748.
[door unlocks]
Go! Let's go!
[Trevor whistling]
-[indistinct soft muttering]
-[door bell rings]
Oh my goodness.
Oh, no.
-[burglar whispers] We've got to get out.
-[burglar 2] Shut up!
[burglar] Get down!
[door opens]
[brightly] Oh, good morning.
Good morning, Sir.
Sorry to disturb you again.
Um, one of your neighbors reported
an unfamiliar car parked in Heath Grove,
and we've now traced it to the gang of
burglars I mentioned yesterday.
We're hoping somebody
might have seen something.
No. I haven't seen a thing.
And you're sure about that, Sir?
There are three suspects.
Two white males, one Black.
Sorry, officer. There's absolutely no one
in this house apart from me,
I can assure you.
[burglar 1] Stop! What are you doing?
It's not working.
[burglar 2] I've been in here
for eight hours!
[tense music playing]
[female voice] And you'd never seen these
men before?
No.
Even though you were alone in
the house with them for over eight hours?
Er…
You didn't hear them break in.
You didn't hear them moving about.
You didn't notice anything suspicious?
[apologetically] No.
[cars crunching on gravel]
-[door closes]
-[floorboards creak]
Right.
-[spraying]
-[squeaking]
[buzzing]
-[ominous music playing]
-[Trevor intrigued] Ah…
[quirky bustling music playing]
[Trevor mutters]
[whines anxiously]
[mystical music playing]
[whines hopefully]
No, Cupcake.
-I've got to look after you.
-[whines disappointedly]
[Trevor upbeat] Right.
[Trevor] Right.
[Trevor, softly] There.
-[buzzing]
-[epic music playing]
[dramatic crescendo]
[clunk]
[Trevor] Okay.
[pitter patter of Cupcake's claws]
[whispers] Go on, go on.
[music builds]
Yes!
-[soft thud]
-Ha!
[hissing]
Hm.
[hissing fades and dies]
[click]
[death bell tolls]
Yes!
[snoring]
Oh! Oh no!
What?
Cupcake?
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
-[phone rings]
-Oh!
Oh no…
-[phone ringing]
-[birds chirping]
-[sighs]
-What's taking him so long?
-Hello.
-Yeah, uh, we had a call from the police.
Oh. Oh, yes. I was, um…
Yeah, they left a message.
They said there was a break-in.
Is Cupcake all right?
-Uhm…
-[snoring]
She's just having a nap, actually.
Yeah, was anything taken?
Oh, uh, no, it was uh…
Well, they were caught. [chuckles]
The police caught the burglars?
Cupcake must have been terrified.
Can I see her?
Uh… she's out in the garden.
I thought you said she was having a nap.
Oh, yes.
She was having a nap, and now she's out in
the garden. Oh, there she is.
Hello, Cupcake. Hello!
[stiffly] Would you mind getting her,
please? I'd really like to see her.
-Uhm…
-[sharply] Now!
O-kay.
Cupcake.
Cupcake!
Cupcake, come here.
-Come on. Come on. Here we go.
-[snoring]
-Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
-[flapping]
[shouting] Cupcake!
Wake up!
-Meow.
-[phone rings]
[painfully] Oh…
[enthusiastically] Jess, hi!
I'm a bit tied up, actually. Would you--
No, Trevor. I need to know whether this
holiday is happening or not.
I have to work out my
schedule for next week.
Absolutely. Could I pop
you on hold for just a moment?
Do not put me on hold, Trevor. Do not pu--
[groans]
Come on.
Oh, hello.
There's my baby. How's my Cup-cup?
Oh, she's very well. Aren't you Cupcake?
[whining]
I know. I know. Yes, you are. Oh,
look out. What's she seen? Oh!
[thud]
-She's off.
-[snoring]
There she goes.
That cat had better watch out.
Go, Cupcake, go!
Anyway, look, I'll speak to you tomorrow.
-Thanks for calling. Bye.
-No, I--
Search vet! Nearest vet!
-Trevor, I'm still here.
-[sighs]
No, you're not.
-[exasperated sigh]
-[dramatic music playing]
Okay Cupcake. Come on.
I don't feel good about this.
Christian, what are you doing?
This house-sitter's really worrying me.
Yeah, he's worrying me too.
-[rattles doors]
-No… ugh.
-[snoring]
-[door clicks]
[Trevor] There we go.
Gently does it.
[hopeful music playing]
Right.
-Oh, phone!
-[buzzing]
[dramatic music builds]
[closing theme music playing]