&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life.
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet,
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Alya]
&lrm;Don't blink now, we're live from Paris.
&lrm;Yo, peeps, Alya here
&lrm;bringing you
&lrm;the one and only Ladyblog.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;What is that?
&lrm;[Ladybug squeals]
&lrm;Ladybug in action.
&lrm;Hang on, we're going for a ride.
&lrm;Freak out...
&lrm;This is no ordinary book,
&lrm;it's a 10th-grade history book.
&lrm;And I should know,
&lrm;I've got the very same book.
&lrm;Could Ladybug be a high-school student
&lrm;in real life?
&lrm;I told you from day one, Tikki,
&lrm;I'm a total klutz.
&lrm;What's done is done.
&lrm;We can't change what happened.
&lrm;We can only move forward.
&lrm;Alya mustn't find out who you are.
&lrm;You know how persistent she can be
&lrm;with her blog dedicated to Ladybug.
&lrm;How do we get it back?
&lrm;I'm not cut out for this Ladybug thing.
&lrm;You are the chosen one, Marinette.
&lrm;It will all work out, trust me.
&lrm;Everyone has a past
&lrm;they can learn from.
&lrm;This'll show you why.
&lrm;An exhibition on the pharaoh Tutankhamun?
&lrm;What's that got to do with Alya?
&lrm;Persuade Alya to go
&lrm;and make sure she brings the book.
&lrm;Tell her you found out
&lrm;something about Ladybug.
&lrm;-At the museum?
&lrm;-You'll see.
&lrm;I don't know
&lrm;how I'm gonna convince Alya
&lrm;to go to an Egyptian exhibit
&lrm;much less convince her
&lrm;that I'm not Ladybug.
&lrm;She will be interested,
&lrm;and so will you. Promise.
&lrm;[Alya] Can you believe it?
&lrm;If I find out
&lrm;who this history book belongs to
&lrm;and I figure out
&lrm;Ladybug's true identity.
&lrm;I'm so on this one.
&lrm;You think you can figure out
&lrm;who Ladybug is
&lrm;from a book
&lrm;every high-school student owns?
&lrm;Yep, ours is the only school
&lrm;that uses that book
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;All I gotta do is find out
&lrm;which girl lost her book last week.
&lrm;-There are 43, not counting me.
&lrm;-42...
&lrm;not counting you or me.
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;Yesterday, somebody didn't have
&lrm;her textbook in class.
&lrm;I left it at home.
&lrm;You know I always forget stuff.
&lrm;[questioning hum]
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;Just messing with you.
&lrm;I'll only drop you
&lrm;from my investigation
&lrm;when you bring your book to class.
&lrm;[Alya yells]
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;It's not broken.
&lrm;Hey, I'm OK too.
&lrm;Thanks for asking.
&lrm;[Jalil] I'm sorry.
&lrm;You're in the same grade
&lrm;as Alix, right?
&lrm;I'm her brother, Jalil Kubdel.
&lrm;You're into Tutankhamun too?
&lrm;Doc!
&lrm;[sighs]
&lrm;Weird.
&lrm;So, again, why are we here?
&lrm;It has something to do
&lrm;with Ladybug?
&lrm;-For reals?
&lrm;-Well...
&lrm;Yeah, it's over there.
&lrm;[she hesitates]
&lrm;Hang on, we're going for a ride.
&lrm;[Alya gasps]
&lrm;Freak out.
&lrm;This is no ordinary book,
&lrm;it's a 10th-grade history book.
&lrm;And I should know,
&lrm;I've got the very same book.
&lrm;Could Ladybug be high-school student
&lrm;in real life?
&lrm;What are the odds
&lrm;that we have the same textbook?
&lrm;Maybe we go to the same school.
&lrm;Wouldn't you know her then?
&lrm;[chewing]
&lrm;Why bother yourself with ladies
&lrm;when you could be enjoying this?
&lrm;Ladies smell far better
&lrm;than that cheese
&lrm;and they're better looking.
&lrm;Suit yourself, your loss.
&lrm;My only loss is my appetite.
&lrm;Come on. Tell me what it is.
&lrm;No, cuz it wouldn't be
&lrm;a surprise then...
&lrm;To you or me.
&lrm;[Jalil] I'm telling you, father,
&lrm;it's in the hieroglyphics.
&lrm;Excuse me.
&lrm;There, as you know,
&lrm;the one with the sceptre is
&lrm;Tutankhamun 1.
&lrm;Opposite, is Nefertiti, his princess,
&lrm;with 100 mummies beside them.
&lrm;She died before him.
&lrm;The Sun God, Ra,
&lrm;took her as his Goddess.
&lrm;Yes, I know all that.
&lrm;I'm the director
&lrm;of this exhibition, remember?
&lrm;Then you know Tutankhamun wanted
&lrm;to bring her back to life
&lrm;by offering the Sun God a new wife.
&lrm;This illustrates a ritual he devised.
&lrm;Nobody has ever deciphered it,
&lrm;but I have!
&lrm;It's a magic chant
&lrm;to recite to complete the ritual.
&lrm;I'm sure of it!
&lrm;He reminds me of someone else
&lrm;with crazy ideas...
&lrm;You!
&lrm;You might think
&lrm;my Ladybug theories are crazy
&lrm;but you watch, I'll prove you wrong.
&lrm;Jalil, frescoes like these are
&lrm;often illustrations of a legend.
&lrm;They call it a legend for a reason.
&lrm;That's what everyone thinks
&lrm;but I know it's real.
&lrm;I can prove it.
&lrm;Really?
&lrm;How are you going to do that?
&lrm;I need to get my hands on
&lrm;Tutankhamun's sceptre
&lrm;and recite the spell.
&lrm;Are you serious?
&lrm;Don't even think of touching it.
&lrm;I'd lose my job on the spot.
&lrm;It's a priceless, historical object,
&lrm;not a toy.
&lrm;Dad, we have to try out the spell.
&lrm;What if he had found out
&lrm;how to bring people back to life?
&lrm;Jalil, that's enough.
&lrm;Get your head out of those scrolls,
&lrm;and focus on the real world...
&lrm;this one.
&lrm;There's nothing wrong
&lrm;with living out a fantasy,
&lrm;especially when
&lrm;I can make it a reality.
&lrm;Fly away, my evil Akuma,
&lrm;and transform that young man.
&lrm;[confused sigh]
&lrm;[she squeals]
&lrm;Put that down.
&lrm;I'll show you what
&lrm;I found out about Ladybug.
&lrm;About time.
&lrm;This better be blog worthy.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] Pharaoh,
&lrm;I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;I have endowed you
&lrm;with the power of the ancient gods.
&lrm;You must do me a favour
&lrm;in return for this gift.
&lrm;My precious Nefertiti
&lrm;will come back to life
&lrm;This thing's making my eyes hurt.
&lrm;Look closely. It is in there...
&lrm;[whistle]
&lrm;Hey, you.
&lrm;Tut, give me time.
&lrm;[man whimpers]
&lrm;Hey!
&lrm;Alya, hide!
&lrm;Get out of here, faster.
&lrm;I gotta transform.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;[whispering]
&lrm;O.M.G.
&lrm;Coming to you live, viewers.
&lrm;I'm here before
&lrm;Ladybug or Cat Noir. It's insane.
&lrm;I love the face changes.
&lrm;They'd suit you.
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[alarm rings]
&lrm;You know that's stealing?
&lrm;I'm taking back
&lrm;what rightfully belongs to me.
&lrm;Maybe, if you were the real Pharaoh,
&lrm;which you're not.
&lrm;Look at Ladybug go.
&lrm;If I'm dreaming, don't wake me up.
&lrm;Ladybug waved at me. No way.
&lrm;[Ladybug screams]
&lrm;Sekhmet, give me your strength!
&lrm;How nice of you
&lrm;to hold the door open.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Enjoy your coffin.
&lrm;This is crazy. Keep your eyes peeled.
&lrm;Hiya.
&lrm;[Pharaoh] Your face...
&lrm;Fate has placed you on my path.
&lrm;Come with me!
&lrm;Hey, hands off the threads.
&lrm;I can walk myself.
&lrm;Seriously?
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;[Marinette] Let her go.
&lrm;Hiding behind an innocent bystander?
&lrm;-You're weak.
&lrm;-I'm more powerful than you.
&lrm;Don't forget all the latest
&lrm;behind the scenes are on my blog.
&lrm;That Alya is one brave chick.
&lrm;If by brave you mean
&lrm;bossy, feisty, and bold,
&lrm;yep, that's her.
&lrm;Come on, get us outta here, Cat Noir.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[clunking]
&lrm;How are we going to find them?
&lrm;Alya's live stream on her blog.
&lrm;Hi, Alya here,
&lrm;live blogging from the shoulder
&lrm;of a terrifying villain.
&lrm;Huge scoop to come.
&lrm;Go ahead.
&lrm;I'll join you when
&lrm;my Miraculous is charged up.
&lrm;Hurry, It'll take both of us
&lrm;to defeat him.
&lrm;Hey.
&lrm;On to the next phase.
&lrm;Anubis, bring me mummies!
&lrm;[mummies groan]
&lrm;Soon, we will be together again,
&lrm;my Nefertiti, my long lost love.
&lrm;This'll be a major scoop.
&lrm;Excuse me, Pharaoh,
&lrm;but what exactly is going on?
&lrm;I'm going to carry out the sacred spell,
&lrm;to bring Nefertiti back.
&lrm;Oh... gotcha.
&lrm;You mean the spell on the papyrus?
&lrm;Correct. The 100 mummies
&lrm;and the offering.
&lrm;What offering?
&lrm;To persuade the sun god Ra
&lrm;to give me back my sweet princess.
&lrm;I must give a pure soul in return.
&lrm;Dude, that's hard to come by.
&lrm;I've already found her.
&lrm;You look so much like her.
&lrm;Say what?
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;Hold on, Alya.
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;Oh no, I ran right into
&lrm;one of those time bubbles.
&lrm;[slow motion]
&lrm;I've got to get out of this.
&lrm;Ladybug, this is Alya.
&lrm;I'm the sacrificial offering
&lrm;for the Sun God.
&lrm;Please hurry.
&lrm;Hold on, Alya.
&lrm;[slow motion]
&lrm;I'm nearly there.
&lrm;[Plagg] Do you really think
&lrm;this mumbo jumbo with the sun
&lrm;and mummies is gonna work?
&lrm;[Plagg burps]
&lrm;You have no respect.
&lrm;Your batteries are charged enough.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;Thanks for waiting.
&lrm;No problem.
&lrm;We must find the Akuma and free it
&lrm;before he sacrifices her.
&lrm;I can't see her or Pharaoh.
&lrm;Over there.
&lrm;[Alya struggles]
&lrm;Hey, back up.
&lrm;Who's that goddess chick
&lrm;with black spots on your papyrus?
&lrm;Ladybug, my sworn enemy.
&lrm;My nemesis kept me from carrying out
&lrm;my ritual 5000 years ago,
&lrm;but she won't stop Nefertiti
&lrm;from coming back to me this time.
&lrm;Did you say Ladybug
&lrm;5000 years ago?
&lrm;Everyone does have a past
&lrm;they can learn from.
&lrm;Well, you don't look a day over 3000.
&lrm;Now you know why
&lrm;I'm so much wiser than you.
&lrm;Oh sacred Ra,
&lrm;God of the Sun,
&lrm;I, Pharaoh, offer to thee,
&lrm;a pure soul,
&lrm;This sacrifice
&lrm;for the return of Nefertiti.
&lrm;I bow to you
&lrm;and present this gift with my mummies.
&lrm;We pray to you the safe return
&lrm;of Princess Nefertiti.
&lrm;Awaken, Nefertiti!
&lrm;Awaken!
&lrm;Awaken Nefertiti.
&lrm;Ladybug!
&lrm;We must save her.
&lrm;If he completes the ritual
&lrm;Alya will be gone, forever.
&lrm;What should we do?
&lrm;Hold back the mummies.
&lrm;I'll take on the Pharaoh.
&lrm;Why do I have to deal with them
&lrm;while you go calmly around the back?
&lrm;I'm the only one
&lrm;who can capture his Akuma.
&lrm;And you're the bravest.
&lrm;Sure.
&lrm;I'll just pretend you really think that.
&lrm;[chanting]
&lrm;Awaken, Nefertiti. Awaken.
&lrm;Hey, you bunch of bandages.
&lrm;Shall we wrap this up?
&lrm;Cat Noir!
&lrm;Seize him!
&lrm;Is that really as fast as you can go?
&lrm;[mummies groan]
&lrm;Wait, this looks like a trap!
&lrm;Gotcha.
&lrm;Horus, give me your wings!
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[bleep]
&lrm;Peeps, you've just witnessed
&lrm;another feat from Ladybug.
&lrm;Thanks for saving me.
&lrm;Oh, you're welcome,
&lrm;but it's not over yet, not until...
&lrm;Not until Ladybug destroys
&lrm;the pendant with the Akuma,
&lrm;and turns everything back to normal.
&lrm;I pay attention.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;The pendant... Good eye.
&lrm;[Ayla screams]
&lrm;[he roars]
&lrm;[sigh of relief]
&lrm;Way to go, Ladybug!
&lrm;No!
&lrm;You're not going to win
&lrm;this time, Ladybug!
&lrm;Help me, Ladybug!
&lrm;Crush that insect!
&lrm;[Alya yells]
&lrm;What the...
&lrm;Cat Noir, this way.
&lrm;[Cat Noir giggles]
&lrm;We have to save Alya before
&lrm;she reaches the circle of darkness.
&lrm;[Pharaoh] You won't stop me
&lrm;from bringing Nefertiti back.
&lrm;I'll finish you.
&lrm;Anubis, bring me mummies!
&lrm;Horus, give me your wings!
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;[Pharaoh cackles]
&lrm;[Ladybug screams]
&lrm;Cat Noir, the pendant.
&lrm;That's where the Akuma is.
&lrm;Sekhmet, give me your strength!
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;It's over.
&lrm;Ladybug, save me!
&lrm;Ra, God of the Sun,
&lrm;accept this humble offering
&lrm;and return the princess to me!
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;A Ladybug outfit?
&lrm;That's our last hope?
&lrm;[questioning sigh]
&lrm;This offering isn't good enough
&lrm;for Nefertiti.
&lrm;Hey, thanks a lot.
&lrm;Too late, Ladybug,
&lrm;the ritual has begun.
&lrm;Set Alya free
&lrm;and sacrifice me instead.
&lrm;Wouldn't that be the sweetest
&lrm;revenge 5000 years later?
&lrm;I'm the one who kept
&lrm;Nefertiti from you all these years.
&lrm;It's true that you'd make
&lrm;a much more precious offering
&lrm;than this mortal.
&lrm;Horus, give me wings!
&lrm;Seriously?
&lrm;Excuse you, but I make
&lrm;excellent sacrificing material.
&lrm;Take her Miraculous, the earrings!
&lrm;You win, Pharaoh.
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;You want my Miraculous?
&lrm;-Go get it.
&lrm;-Get it!
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;A toy?
&lrm;You tricked me!
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you,
&lrm;little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;What happened?
&lrm;Thanks, Ladybug,
&lrm;but I still gotta ask
&lrm;how old are you really?
&lrm;Much older than a high-school
&lrm;student, that's for sure.
&lrm;Don't you wanna know
&lrm;how old I am?
&lrm;In a sec, it looks like
&lrm;I'll find out for myself.
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;[Alya giggles]
&lrm;[Alya] Where have you been?
&lrm;You won't believe this,
&lrm;I got mummified.
&lrm;Hope you weren't trying
&lrm;to swap me for Nefertiti. Creepy.
&lrm;What? You were almost sacrificed?
&lrm;Without you, I'd never have found out
&lrm;that Ladybug's 5000 years old.
&lrm;Hey, what are friends for?
&lrm;[Alya] I still don't get it.
&lrm;Why did she have
&lrm;a 10th-grade history book?
&lrm;[hesitantly]
&lrm;She... She probably had to find out
&lrm;what's been going on
&lrm;for the past 50 centuries.
&lrm;You're probably right.
&lrm;It's tough staying in the loop.
&lrm;Hey, Ladybug's textbook, it's gone.
&lrm;[Marinette giggles]
&lrm;You might have gotten away this time
&lrm;but I assure you, Ladybug,
&lrm;someday, wherever you are,
&lrm;I will have your Miraculous,
&lrm;and you'll be nothing,
&lrm;nothing at all!
&lrm;I don't get it.
&lrm;I know I'm not 5000 years old.
&lrm;So who exactly was
&lrm;that Ladybug in the papyrus?
&lrm;Kwamis like me and superheroes
&lrm;like you have always existed.
&lrm;So that wasn't you
&lrm;on the papyrus, either?
&lrm;-What do you think?
&lrm;-You don't look 5000 years old.
&lrm;[Tikki chuckles]
&lrm;Well, I'm not. I'm older than that.
&lrm;I'm the Kwami who has watched over
&lrm;every Ladybug since the beginning.
&lrm;You must have known much less klutzy
&lrm;Ladybugs than me, right?
&lrm;Every Ladybug is different.
&lrm;[sadly]
&lrm;Yeah, that's what I thought.
&lrm;Marinette, you are different,
&lrm;but different as in surprising,
&lrm;unpredictable and endearing,
&lrm;and very talented.
&lrm;-You learn fast.
&lrm;-Really?
&lrm;Yes.
&lrm;[they giggle]
&lrm;You'd better get to sleep.
&lrm;You have that history test tomorrow.
&lrm;Oh yeah,
&lrm;good thing it's on Ancient Egypt.
&lrm;[lively music]