&lrm;In the daytime I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[alarm rings]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Happy birthday!
&lrm;[she stumbles and groans]
&lrm;Happy birthday, Adrien.
&lrm;Plagg, get that filthy camembert
&lrm;out of my face.
&lrm;Don't forget
&lrm;to clean your room after school.
&lrm;Mom, it's Friday.
&lrm;I'm already doing something with Alya.
&lrm;Fine. I'll clean it
&lrm;but don't blame me
&lrm;if I find your private stuff like e-mails,
&lrm;your diary...
&lrm;OK. I'll do it.
&lrm;Have a nice day, sweetie.
&lrm;Happy Birthday! I mean... Have a nice day.
&lrm;Your schedule, Adrien.
&lrm;Thanks, Nathalie.
&lrm;Did my father get back to you
&lrm;about my birthday party?
&lrm;Well... he... doesn't think
&lrm;it'd be a good idea.
&lrm;Of course not.
&lrm;Happy Birthday, Adrien.
&lrm;[Nino] Dude, seriously?
&lrm;Has your dad always been such a downer?
&lrm;Doesn't he remember
&lrm;what it's like to wanna party.
&lrm;No, I'm sure
&lrm;he was a downer back then, too.
&lrm;At least I tried.
&lrm;It's your b'day, dude... insist.
&lrm;You can do it. You can do it.
&lrm;I can do it. I can do it.
&lrm;I'm gonna have a chat with your pops.
&lrm;Don't waste your time,
&lrm;he won't change his mind.
&lrm;I can't do it. I can't do it.
&lrm;[Alya sighs]
&lrm;No you don't girl.
&lrm;You've been stalling all morning.
&lrm;Now's the time.
&lrm;[she squeals]
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;Hey.
&lrm;Wait.
&lrm;Am I seeing what I think?
&lrm;Don't tell me it's Adrien's birthday.
&lrm;[Chloe groans]
&lrm;Do I have to do everything?
&lrm;Seriously, what are you good for?
&lrm;I... I wanted to gift you a make.
&lrm;I mean, gift you a give I made,
&lrm;I mean...
&lrm;Out of the way.
&lrm;Happy Birthday, Adrien.
&lrm;Yeah, thanks, Chloe.
&lrm;[Marinette moans]
&lrm;Did you get my gift?
&lrm;[hesitantly] No.
&lrm;What? Those delivery guys.
&lrm;I bet it was too heavy
&lrm;so they had to get another guy to help.
&lrm;Slackers.
&lrm;I'll make sure you get it by tonight.
&lrm;[she hums]
&lrm;[Nino chuckles]
&lrm;Get back there.
&lrm;Don't be a pushover... literally.
&lrm;[Marinette sighs]
&lrm;-What did you get him?
&lrm;-I didn't... you did.
&lrm;And it better be amazing
&lrm;and it better not be late!
&lrm;[Chloe groans]
&lrm;[Alya] Come on. You can do it.
&lrm;[car horn beeps]
&lrm;Gotta go... Photo shoot.
&lrm;Why can't I just mean what I say?
&lrm;Say what you mean?
&lrm;Exactly.
&lrm;Looks like I've got some business
&lrm;to take care of with Adrien's old man
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;This mailbox won't budge.
&lrm;Ring the bell.
&lrm;Are you kidding? What if Adrien answers?
&lrm;Yes?
&lrm;Hi... I'm in Adrien's class and I...
&lrm;[she mumbles]
&lrm;Did I already say that?
&lrm;Put it in the box.
&lrm;Thank you.
&lrm;I hope he likes it.
&lrm;You signed the note, right?
&lrm;Girl, girl, girl.
&lrm;Who was that?
&lrm;A friend of Adrien's
&lrm;delivering a gift for his birthday.
&lrm;Did you buy one from me?
&lrm;Oh... but... you didn't ask me to.
&lrm;Of course I did!
&lrm;Yes, Mr. Agreste. I'll take care of it.
&lrm;Good.
&lrm;[she sighs with relief]
&lrm;[intercom rings]
&lrm;Yes?
&lrm;[he hesitates] &lrm;Hi...
&lrm;He'll be here in a minute.
&lrm;Adrien's not home yet.
&lrm;I was coming to see you, du... sir.
&lrm;Me?
&lrm;Yeah. I know you don't want Adrien
&lrm;to have a party,
&lrm;but it's his birthday, dude... I mean sir.
&lrm;It's all he wants.
&lrm;No, that's final.
&lrm;But that's messed up.
&lrm;He does well in class,
&lrm;he does what you tell him,
&lrm;photo shoots, fencing, Chinese, piano...
&lrm;Nino, you're here?
&lrm;Anything for my best bud.
&lrm;Show some awesomeness, dude... I mean sir,
&lrm;please.
&lrm;Forget it, Nino. It's fine.
&lrm;[father] Listen, young man,
&lrm;I decide what's best for my son.
&lrm;In fact, I've decided
&lrm;you're a bad influence
&lrm;and you're not welcome here.
&lrm;Leave now!
&lrm;Father, he was just trying
&lrm;to do something cool for me.
&lrm;Goodbye.
&lrm;Nino, wait.
&lrm;I'm sorry. My father he's...
&lrm;pretty stubborn.
&lrm;It's just best to stay out of his way.
&lrm;It's not fair, Adrien... harsh, uncool.
&lrm;Thanks anyway, Nino.
&lrm;[child sobs] But daddy, please.
&lrm;No, it's not playtime.
&lrm;You've chores to do.
&lrm;Adults ruin everything, all the time.
&lrm;Desperate to help his friend
&lrm;but feeling powerless.
&lrm;How frustrating...
&lrm;It won't be long
&lrm;before frustration turns to anger.
&lrm;Fly away, my little Akuma,
&lrm;and evilize him!
&lrm;Hawk Moth is my name,
&lrm;and Bubbler is now yours.
&lrm;I will help you with these horrid adults.
&lrm;All you have to do is get something
&lrm;from Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;[evil voice] Yes, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;[bubbling]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;No more adults means total freedom.
&lrm;This is soooo sweet!
&lrm;[fearful cries]
&lrm;Help!
&lrm;[screams]
&lrm;Perfect.
&lrm;Adrien must have gotten his gift by now?
&lrm;What did you say?
&lrm;I can't wait to get back to school.
&lrm;Mom!
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;Dad!
&lrm;Hawk Moth must have released
&lrm;another Akuma.
&lrm;I've gotta find his newest villain ASAP.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;And now... party time!
&lrm;[Bubbler] Hey, hey, hey,
&lrm;Today's your lucky day, dudes.
&lrm;The adults are taking the day off.
&lrm;Make the most of it.
&lrm;No chores, no homework, no more nagging,
&lrm;just fun, fun, fun.
&lrm;This is the Bubbler's gift to you.
&lrm;Don't worry your parents will come back.
&lrm;I'll see to it.
&lrm;Take care of them in the meantime.
&lrm;Yeah! Go Ladybug!
&lrm;[clock ticks]
&lrm;[sarcastically] Wow, that was a birthday
&lrm;lunch-break to remember. Yay.
&lrm;Nathalie? Father?
&lrm;Yay!
&lrm;Happy birthday!
&lrm;Hey, birthday boy!
&lrm;Guess what? Daddy's gone.
&lrm;While the cat's away, the mice will play.
&lrm;Nino?
&lrm;The Bubbler's brought all your homies
&lrm;for one single sole purpose
&lrm;to ce... le... brate!
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;-Let's get dis party started!
&lrm;-Yeah!
&lrm;[dance music]
&lrm;Come on everybody!
&lrm;I've brought you here to party!
&lrm;So dance...
&lrm;or else you'll join the adults in the sky.
&lrm;[wicked laugh]
&lrm;It won't be long before Ladybug
&lrm;and Cat Noir show up to meet their doom.
&lrm;[wicked laugh]
&lrm;[Plagg] What's your problem? Relax.
&lrm;You're getting the party
&lrm;you always wanted.
&lrm;Nino's been akumatized.
&lrm;I've gotta help him
&lrm;You may never get this chance again.
&lrm;Come on. Let's have a little fun
&lrm;while your father's away.
&lrm;Then we'll save Nino, trap his Akuma,
&lrm;and all will be good.
&lrm;OK. You're right.
&lrm;This might be the first time
&lrm;that I get to do what I want for once.
&lrm;It's you and me, Bubbler.
&lrm;Yeah!
&lrm;Hey, nice party...
&lrm;I guess, since it's my first one.
&lrm;I'm requesting a slow-dance.
&lrm;It's a bit early, isn't it?
&lrm;[Chloe groans]
&lrm;It's for Adrien. His first slow dance...
&lrm;Oh, you know it, girl.
&lrm;[romantic music]
&lrm;Is it me,
&lrm;or does everyone seem a bit weird?
&lrm;Forget about them.
&lrm;Let's go dance. Come on.
&lrm;There's no way this is happening.
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;A record?
&lrm;[she cackles]
&lrm;[funky music]
&lrm;[gasps]
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;Dude, who just hijacked my mix?
&lrm;Yours truly.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Better bug out quick before I change back.
&lrm;Spots off.
&lrm;Marinette!
&lrm;It was an emergency.
&lrm;Yeah, if by emergency you mean jealousy.
&lrm;Once you use your lucky charm,
&lrm;you only have minutes before...
&lrm;I turn back, I know, but I figured...
&lrm;The Bubbler... he's not going anywhere.
&lrm;We've time to get some food
&lrm;to get your energy back.
&lrm;Then, we'll get right back out there.
&lrm;I promise.
&lrm;[dance music]
&lrm;Gotta find a place
&lrm;where I can transform fast.
&lrm;Where have you been, girl?
&lrm;I was scared for you.
&lrm;Me too.
&lrm;I'm sure Ladybug and Cat Noir
&lrm;will save us.
&lrm;They've never failed us.
&lrm;Come with me, I have something for you.
&lrm;I have to do something first.
&lrm;[tauntingly] It's about Adrien.
&lrm;[reluctantly] OK.
&lrm;Marinette, the Bubbler.
&lrm;OK, OK, in a sec.
&lrm;Look... Now you can sign your gift.
&lrm;Yes.
&lrm;Hey, you. Why aren't you having fun?
&lrm;None of your business.
&lrm;Then I'm gonna make it my business.
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;"Love, Marinette"
&lrm;There.
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;We're good. Spots on, Marinette.
&lrm;I can't do it now. Alya's here.
&lrm;[Ayla] What?
&lrm;Hey... Go ahead.
&lrm;I'll meet you in the yard.
&lrm;No! You were right, Tikki.
&lrm;I never should have waited.
&lrm;Hey, Paris! How ya doin'?
&lrm;[crowd groans]
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;[Adrien] Ladybug?
&lrm;Sorry, Bubbler, party's over.
&lrm;Why you gotta be like that?
&lrm;You made all the adults disappear,
&lrm;and now you're imprisoning
&lrm;anyone who isn't having fun.
&lrm;You will not bust up my party!
&lrm;I think I've been a complete idiot.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;Looks like I made it just in time.
&lrm;I had it under control...
&lrm;but thanks.
&lrm;Get their Miraculouses.
&lrm;I want those powers... Now!
&lrm;[he roars]
&lrm;[bubbling]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;[Marinette whimpers]
&lrm;[he laughs wickedly]
&lrm;Give me your Miraculouses
&lrm;before you run out of air.
&lrm;Dream on, Bubbler.
&lrm;Total party-poopers, just like adults.
&lrm;Kids need adults!
&lrm;False. Kids need freedom, fun,
&lrm;let loose and live it up.
&lrm;[Bubbler] Adults are bossy.
&lrm;[Marinette] But adults keep children safe.
&lrm;They care for their kids. They love them.
&lrm;Most adults do anyhow.
&lrm;You must bring the adults back.
&lrm;Nope, never... Know what?
&lrm;Since you care about them so much,
&lrm;why don't you go float with them?
&lrm;[they scream]
&lrm;What do you think you're doing, Bubbler?
&lrm;You're supposed to seize
&lrm;their Miraculouses!
&lrm;Use your Cataclysm.
&lrm;Couldn't you have said that 500 feet ago?
&lrm;We can't stay stuck
&lrm;in this bubble together forever.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;-Shall we see if you land on your feet?
&lrm;-No thanks.
&lrm;Your stick... there!
&lrm;Got it!
&lrm;Hang on!
&lrm;[they yell]
&lrm;Good thing cats aren't afraid of heights.
&lrm;We have to get to his bubble sword.
&lrm;That's where the Akuma is.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;We'd better hurry.
&lrm;Where is everybody?
&lrm;Get out here and party.
&lrm;Sorry to burst your bubble.
&lrm;-Ladybug!
&lrm;-Ladybug! Ladybug!
&lrm;No one wants to party with you anymore,
&lrm;Bubbler.
&lrm;What's wrong with you all guys?
&lrm;Why you gotta be such haters?
&lrm;[he roars]
&lrm;No!
&lrm;Outer space is the next stop
&lrm;for your precious peeps.
&lrm;And they're never coming back!
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;I'm gonna switch back soon. Hurry!
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;Your... plumbing skills gonna help us out?
&lrm;Your aim needs work.
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Is that all you got?
&lrm;Got it.
&lrm;[hissing]
&lrm;[Ladybug] Cat Noir, cover me.
&lrm;Go on!
&lrm;[he roars]
&lrm;[Ladybug] Get out of here, you nasty bug.
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you, little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilize!
&lrm;Gotcha.
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;Who? Dude...
&lrm;Pound it.
&lrm;You can't run forever, Ladybug.
&lrm;And when I catch you, I will crush you.
&lrm;I will destroy you both!
&lrm;Nathalie?
&lrm;Did my son like his gift?
&lrm;[nervously] Actually...
&lrm;I was going to check right away.
&lrm;Good.
&lrm;[sigh of relief]
&lrm;A birthday present... from your father.
&lrm;[happily surprised] Oh... thank you.
&lrm;I mean... please say
&lrm;thank you to my father for me.
&lrm;[Chloe] What do you mean
&lrm;'"Not for a week"?
&lrm;There were no adults to deliver it.
&lrm;So what? Ridiculous, utterly ridiculous.
&lrm;Serves Chloe right.
&lrm;[Adrien] Hey, girls.
&lrm;Hey, that's my scarf.
&lrm;He's wearing my scarf.
&lrm;Hey, dude.
&lrm;Yo, nice scarf, Adrien. Off the chain.
&lrm;Yeah. Can you believe it?
&lrm;My dad got it for me?
&lrm;It's so awesome.
&lrm;He's gotten me a lame pen
&lrm;for 3 years in a row.
&lrm;Wow. I guess anyone can change.
&lrm;Adults can be cool
&lrm;when you least expect it.
&lrm;Speaking of adults, my father said
&lrm;you were a bad influence but...
&lrm;Don't sweat it.
&lrm;We're buds, always n' forever.
&lrm;You've gotta tell him
&lrm;you knitted the scarf.
&lrm;But he seems so happy about his dad.
&lrm;I don't want to spoil it for him.
&lrm;[endearing sigh] Marinette...
&lrm;You're amazing, girl.
&lrm;You know that, right?
&lrm;And someday,
&lrm;Adrien will figure it out too... promise.
&lrm;[school bell rings]