&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life,
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Tikki] Invite him to a movie, then.
&lrm;[Marinette] Right, Tikki.
&lrm;Imagine that.
&lrm;Hey, Adrien. Would you like to...
&lrm;[spluttering]
&lrm;Exactly. I can't help it.
&lrm;Every time I see him,
&lrm;I get all clammy and I feel like fainting.
&lrm;So you have to be blindfolded
&lrm;to have a normal conversation with him?
&lrm;Pretty much.
&lrm;There is a simple solution.
&lrm;It's called a phone.
&lrm;You just need his number.
&lrm;I know who'll have it.
&lrm;I'm sure you've outdone yourself, Theo.
&lrm;It was my honor.
&lrm;I can't wait to meet Ladybug.
&lrm;I hope she signs my photo.
&lrm;I used it as the inspiration
&lrm;for the statue.
&lrm;It's nearly time.
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir
&lrm;should already be here by now.
&lrm;We know improv's not your bag,
&lrm;so stick to this script.
&lrm;The teachers say
&lrm;I don't sound natural when I read
&lrm;Then memorize it. It's pretty simple.
&lrm;You can do it.
&lrm;Just don't improvise, got it?
&lrm;Forget it. It's never gonna work.
&lrm;Too late.
&lrm;It's dialing.
&lrm;[Ayla giggles]
&lrm;Hey, this is Adrien's voicemail,
&lrm;leave a message.
&lrm;It's gone to voicemail.
&lrm;Leave a message. Don't improv'.
&lrm;Hello, Adrien's voicemail...
&lrm;This is Marinette... who...
&lrm;has a message...
&lrm;for you, of course,
&lrm;because it's your phone, so...
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;Call me, see you later, bye.
&lrm;What did you expect?
&lrm;"Hey, hot stuff. It's Marinette.
&lrm;"I'd ask you out
&lrm;"but I've got such a crush on you
&lrm;that the only way to talk to you
&lrm;"is over this stupid phone."
&lrm;Pretty ridiculous, right?
&lrm;To hear your message, press 1.
&lrm;To erase your message, press 2.
&lrm;Hit 2! Hit 2!
&lrm;Message saved. Goodbye.
&lrm;[she sobs]
&lrm;It's not as bad as you think.
&lrm;Ok, it's bad,
&lrm;but you had to tell him one day,
&lrm;some way or another.
&lrm;Think of it this way, no more secrets.
&lrm;The voicemail recorded
&lrm;my whole conversation.
&lrm;-Big deal.
&lrm;-I called him hot stuff.
&lrm;He can't hear that message, Alya.
&lrm;If he does, I'll die of shame.
&lrm;OK, I've an idea.
&lrm;If his phone went to voicemail,
&lrm;it means he's busy.
&lrm;That means you can get to it
&lrm;before he does.
&lrm;I wonder where he'd be?
&lrm;Of course. He's got fencing after school.
&lrm;That's why he didn't pick up.
&lrm;It ends in 22.5 minutes.
&lrm;You're insane.
&lrm;You know that, right?
&lrm;You have one new message.
&lrm;I gotta get a drink. Be right back.
&lrm;Plagg!
&lrm;You pig!
&lrm;[he burps]
&lrm;You have one new message.
&lrm;Move please,
&lrm;so I can check my voicemail.
&lrm;I don't recognize this number.
&lrm;Oh no, we're late!
&lrm;Time to transform, Plagg.
&lrm;[excited yelling]
&lrm;Yeah!
&lrm;Hey, everybody.
&lrm;They're unveiling Ladybug
&lrm;and Cat Noir sculptures today.
&lrm;I totally spaced.
&lrm;Me too.
&lrm;You never mentioned
&lrm;going to the unveiling.
&lrm;I'm not, I mean I am...
&lrm;I mean, I forgot?
&lrm;Listen, about Adrien's cell phone...
&lrm;What if we go after?
&lrm;After the ceremony,
&lrm;his fencing training will be over,
&lrm;and he'll have his phone back by then.
&lrm;Shoot. I gotta cover this event
&lrm;for the Ladyblog.
&lrm;I'm sorry, Marinette.
&lrm;Don't sweat it. I can manage...
&lrm;I think.
&lrm;-You sure?
&lrm;-Yes, yes, I'm sure.
&lrm;Cool, good luck.
&lrm;Stay out of trouble.
&lrm;And don't improv'.
&lrm;[car horn]
&lrm;Isn't Ladybug supposed to be
&lrm;at the unveiling?
&lrm;Yes, but Marinette needs to be
&lrm;at the school first.
&lrm;But it is a ceremony in your honor.
&lrm;And it's my honor that's at stake.
&lrm;I'll be in and out in 5 minutes.
&lrm;We can be at the ceremony in no time.
&lrm;Excuse me Cat Noir,
&lrm;but Ladybug's not here.
&lrm;Don't worry. She'll be here soon.
&lrm;I can handle it for now.
&lrm;I'm the one in charge anyway.
&lrm;I wanted to ask her to sign this photo.
&lrm;She's amazing.
&lrm;She's so brave...
&lrm;And smart...
&lrm;The way she saves everyone.
&lrm;Perhaps we should commence.
&lrm;It might bring her here faster.
&lrm;Just a minute more, Mayor Bourgeois.
&lrm;She is going to come. I can feel it.
&lrm;In there.
&lrm;[Tikki] Oh boy.
&lrm;Which one's his?
&lrm;Call him. His phone will ring.
&lrm;Nice, Tikki.
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;It's only proper for Paris
&lrm;to pay homage to those who protect us.
&lrm;[Mayor] Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;Can I get some photos?
&lrm;[Tikki] Hurry, they're finishing up.
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;Here it is.
&lrm;It's locked!
&lrm;Ta-da!
&lrm;These statues are amazing
&lrm;but one thing's off.
&lrm;I'm actually taller than her.
&lrm;Ladybug didn't show. I just wanted to...
&lrm;express my adoration for her.
&lrm;Let her know that everything I had
&lrm;went into her statue..
&lrm;If she took time to get to know me,
&lrm;she'd see how much we have in common,
&lrm;our devotion to the things we love.
&lrm;Hey, don't mean to burst your bubble,
&lrm;but you know, Ladybug and I,
&lrm;we're a thing, you know.
&lrm;-Really?
&lrm;-Yeah, we're like this.
&lrm;What does Ladybug see in him?
&lrm;[phone bleeps]
&lrm;They're coming. Forget it.
&lrm;I haven't erased it yet.
&lrm;We're out of time.
&lrm;We have to get to the ceremony.
&lrm;That was rough.
&lrm;[Cat Noir whistles]
&lrm;"A thing"?
&lrm;You don't even take love seriously
&lrm;calling it "a thing".
&lrm;You don't deserve her.
&lrm;I do!
&lrm;[evil voice] Disappointed by Ladybug
&lrm;and jealous of Cat Noir,
&lrm;the perfect formula for disaster.
&lrm;Fly away, my little Akuma,
&lrm;and evilize him.
&lrm;Hello, Copycat,
&lrm;I'm Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Once you get rid of Cat Noir,
&lrm;you can take his place,
&lrm;and Ladybug will be yours forever.
&lrm;The very thought of it makes me purr.
&lrm;Where is it?
&lrm;What are you looking at me for?
&lrm;I didn't eat it, I swear.
&lrm;How do you listen to messages...?
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;Adrien's looking for his phone.
&lrm;What if he tracks it?
&lrm;He'll figure out I stole it
&lrm;and I'll spend my life in jail
&lrm;and I'll never get to go
&lrm;to the movies with Adrien.
&lrm;You need to get your priorities in order.
&lrm;I know.
&lrm;Some days it feels impossible
&lrm;to balance being Marinette
&lrm;and being Ladybug.
&lrm;Hey, this is Adrien's voicemail,
&lrm;leave a message.
&lrm;It must still be at the gym.
&lrm;Don't mind me.
&lrm;Just stealing this painting.
&lrm;Go about your business.
&lrm;[alarm rings]
&lrm;Hey!
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;I gotta get this on camera.
&lrm;And in some astonishing news,
&lrm;there's been a theft at the Louvre.
&lrm;Amateur videos show
&lrm;that the thief is none other
&lrm;than the famous hero, Cat Noir.
&lrm;This painting is the cat's meow.
&lrm;The "cat's meow"?
&lrm;Not only is he a fake,
&lrm;he's a terrible fake.
&lrm;Thanks JD. Now for your weather.
&lrm;Of course Adrien owns
&lrm;a super-expensive hi-tech smartphone.
&lrm;I can't even figure out how it works.
&lrm;It would help
&lrm;if you took off those silly mittens.
&lrm;And risk leaving finger prints? No way.
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;Problem fixed?
&lrm;Almost. I haven't erased the message
&lrm;yet but I'm working on it now.
&lrm;No way. You palmed his phone?
&lrm;Yes... No...
&lrm;I mean...
&lrm;I was planning to give it back.
&lrm;Where are you? I could use some help.
&lrm;No can do.
&lrm;I'm waiting for details
&lrm;on the Cat Noir robbery.
&lrm;What? Somebody robbed Cat Noir?
&lrm;No, girl. Didn't you hear?
&lrm;Cat Noir came in and stole the Mona Lisa,
&lrm;in broad daylight.
&lrm;Ladybug's gonna turn up,
&lrm;and I don't wanna miss it.
&lrm;Chill. I'll be over later.
&lrm;OK.
&lrm;Cat Noir is a lot of things,
&lrm;but he's no thief.
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;Tikki, Spots on!
&lrm;Easy, tigers, you've got the wrong cat.
&lrm;That thief's an impostor.
&lrm;I'm the real Cat Noir.
&lrm;Let me check it out.
&lrm;I have a knack for finding clues,
&lrm;you know, animal instincts.
&lrm;Of course. Come with me.
&lrm;Thanks for your help.
&lrm;Hey. I'm the real Cat Noir.
&lrm;I'm way slicker than that guy.
&lrm;Kitty's in the slammer,
&lrm;I repeat, kitty's in the slammer.
&lrm;Mr. Mayor, this is ridiculous.
&lrm;I'm sure there's a simple explanation.
&lrm;Kitty's in the slammer, Ladybug.
&lrm;Don't think you're gonna...
&lrm;Now, now, leave it to the experts.
&lrm;We've got it under control.
&lrm;Thanks for the hospitality
&lrm;but I gotta split.
&lrm;So, I'll say this one more time.
&lrm;You've got the wrong cat!
&lrm;Cat Noir's getting away.
&lrm;If he's so innocent,
&lrm;why is he running away?
&lrm;If you were wrongly imprisoned,
&lrm;wouldn't you?
&lrm;[police sirens]
&lrm;Requesting assistance.
&lrm;We're in pursuit of the suspect.
&lrm;Cat Noir, what's going on?
&lrm;You know I'm innocent, don't you, Bugaboo?
&lrm;Stop calling me Bugaboo. This is serious.
&lrm;I'm gonna find the culprit
&lrm;and save my tail.
&lrm;I'll get back to...
&lrm;[police sirens]
&lrm;Give yourself up, Cat Noir!
&lrm;Aren't you gonna go after him?
&lrm;I'll leave it to the experts.
&lrm;Come on, let's get him.
&lrm;[adrien whistles]
&lrm;If you want my opinion,
&lrm;I'd say the thief was akumatized.
&lrm;That I figured.
&lrm;See that lollypop stick?
&lrm;The sculptor.
&lrm;How did I not see that jealousy coming?
&lrm;Yours or his?
&lrm;[sarcastic laugh] So funny.
&lrm;Gotcha, Copycat.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Cat Noir, where are you?
&lrm;I've found his den.
&lrm;-&lrm;Who?
&lrm;-My copycat.
&lrm;I'm not getting you.
&lrm;If you'd been there this morning,
&lrm;you'd know.
&lrm;Well, tell me where you are.
&lrm;No. This is between me and him.
&lrm;I got myself into this mess,
&lrm;so I'm gonna get myself out of it.
&lrm;Cat? Cat!
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;"Cat's in the bag!"?
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;I don't get what Ladybug sees in you,
&lrm;a fool who so easily falls into my trap.
&lrm;Looking for this?
&lrm;Which one shall I pick up?
&lrm;My one or my one.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Ladybug, hurry, I've caught
&lrm;the imposter at Theo's workshop.
&lrm;I'll be there in 30 seconds.
&lrm;Don't come here, Ladybug, it's a trap!
&lrm;Too late, Cat, Ladybug's on her way,
&lrm;which was my plan all along.
&lrm;She won't be duped. She knows me too well.
&lrm;I know you well, too. And, from now on,
&lrm;she'll love me, not you!
&lrm;Love me?
&lrm;You're right. She loves me.
&lrm;That's why she'll be able
&lrm;to reveal your true identity.
&lrm;Copycat, stop the small talk
&lrm;and get me Cat Noir's Miraculous!
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;[whizzing]
&lrm;There you are.
&lrm;[Ladybug]
&lrm;Cat Noir, he really looks like you.
&lrm;That's because I am me.
&lrm;-Where's his Akuma?
&lrm;-Inside his ring of course.
&lrm;Grab it.
&lrm;Ladybug's doing all the work for us,
&lrm;what sweet irony.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;He even has the same powers as you.
&lrm;Simply amazing, isn't it?
&lrm;If you don't believe I'm Cat Noir,
&lrm;ask him about our love for each other.
&lrm;Have I ever lied to you, Bugagoo?
&lrm;I hope you didn't tell him about us.
&lrm;What?
&lrm;That we're... you know...
&lrm;We made a secret promise.
&lrm;Yes... Of course.
&lrm;We never made a promise,
&lrm;Copycat!
&lrm;I love you, Ladybug.
&lrm;I'm way better than this mangy alley cat!
&lrm;Sorry, liars are losers.
&lrm;Cat Noir may annoy me,
&lrm;but he's never lied to me.
&lrm;Thanks for the compliment... I think.
&lrm;Do it now, take his Miraculous!
&lrm;If I can't have you... then nobody will.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;Let's wrap this up.
&lrm;Lucky Charm!
&lrm;A spoon?
&lrm;What am I supposed to do with this?
&lrm;Excellent job, Milady.
&lrm;Where's his Akuma?
&lrm;Photo in his pocket. Let's make it snappy.
&lrm;[cackling] You're going
&lrm;to change back before me.
&lrm;He's pretty good.
&lrm;Don't rub it in.
&lrm;I told you I was better than him.
&lrm;But I'm better than both of you.
&lrm;-Hey, it's me.
&lrm;-He's lying. I'm the real one.
&lrm;Now you're both annoying me.
&lrm;Show me your ring.
&lrm;How many pads do you have left?
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Cat Noir, scratch attack!
&lrm;Gladly. I love a good cat fight.
&lrm;Time to go Akuma fishing.
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you, little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilize!
&lrm;Gotcha.
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;Nice catch.
&lrm;I'm glad you could tell
&lrm;the real Cat from the fake.
&lrm;Once I figured out
&lrm;which cat really loved me,
&lrm;it was a no-brainer.
&lrm;Better help him out.
&lrm;His crush just got crushed.
&lrm;That makes two of us.
&lrm;What am I doing here?
&lrm;Ladybug?
&lrm;Sorry I couldn't make it
&lrm;this morning, Theo.
&lrm;Can you sign it for me?
&lrm;Of course I can.
&lrm;You've got some real artistry here.
&lrm;You really captured my essence.
&lrm;Thank you, Ladybug.
&lrm;And don't worry,
&lrm;I know about you and Cat Noir, it's OK.
&lrm;Didn't find it.
&lrm;To hear your message, press 1.
&lrm;To erase your message, press 2.
&lrm;Your message has been erased.
&lrm;I'm gonna tell him I found his phone.
&lrm;That'd be a good way to start
&lrm;a conversation, wouldn't it?
&lrm;Then I'll ask him out.
&lrm;That's my girl.
&lrm;[Nino] Maybe you dropped it.
&lrm;Then whoever has it
&lrm;found it in the locker room.
&lrm;[Alya whispers] Do it now.
&lrm;I had it during fencing practice.
&lrm;What in the...?
&lrm;I already looked in here.
&lrm;You need some time off.
&lrm;I know, let's go to the movies.
&lrm;Hey, dudes,
&lrm;mind if a few friends tag along?
&lrm;Sure thing!
&lrm;Yay!