&lrm;In the daytime I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;Welcome to the finals
&lrm;of our Kidz Plus competition
&lrm;announcing the lucky winner
&lrm;to be our new Kidz Plus Weathergirl.
&lrm;[crowd chants] Mireille!
&lrm;Hi.
&lrm;[crowd chants] Aurore! Aurore!
&lrm;We started off with 5,000 contestants,
&lrm;and thanks to our audience at home,
&lrm;we've whittled our talent down
&lrm;to these 2 amazing young ladies.
&lrm;So, let's welcome our fantastic finalists.
&lrm;To my right, Aurore Beauréal!
&lrm;And on my left, Mireille Caquet!
&lrm;Who'll be the lucky winner? Vote now!
&lrm;Type 1 for Aurore, 2 for Mireille.
&lrm;And remember,
&lrm;standard text message rates apply.
&lrm;Come on, Manon. Give that back.
&lrm;But I want to be a fashion designer too.
&lrm;Manon, please.
&lrm;It's not finished.
&lrm;You're going to ruin it.
&lrm;[Manon giggles]
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;I'm voting for Mireille. She's the best.
&lrm;Hey, my phone.
&lrm;[Manon giggles]
&lrm;[frustrated groan]
&lrm;Why did I agree to do this again?
&lrm;[Tikki squeaks]
&lrm;Stay low, Tikki.
&lrm;Don't worry.
&lrm;If you can handle Manon for a day,
&lrm;any villain here on out will be
&lrm;a piece of cake.
&lrm;[doorbell rings]
&lrm;-[Marinette] Alya?
&lrm;-Hey, I got a huge scoop.
&lrm;Guess who's on a photo shoot in the park?
&lrm;Now? Adrien is in the park right now?
&lrm;As we speak.
&lrm;Oh gosh. What...
&lrm;What am I going to say to him?
&lrm;The same thing as usual...
&lrm;-I... I.... Wh...
&lrm;-Stop it.
&lrm;Who's she?
&lrm;I forgot about this little detail.
&lrm;And who's she?
&lrm;Manon, my mom's friend's daughter.
&lrm;I'm babysitting all day.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Oh no, I can't go out.
&lrm;Let me guess,
&lrm;another you-couldn't-say-no favor?
&lrm;No... I just couldn't...
&lrm;say... no.
&lrm;Look, no problem.
&lrm;I'll look after your little detail.
&lrm;[Manon giggles]
&lrm;Thanks, but I'm responsible for her.
&lrm;Besides, I couldn't do that to you,
&lrm;she's...
&lrm;an absolute angel.
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;[Manon giggles]
&lrm;Manon, put that down!
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;Come back.
&lrm;[squealing]
&lrm;[crashing and giggling]
&lrm;[crashing and giggling continues]
&lrm;You're a pushover, Marinette.
&lrm;I babysit my sisters all the time,
&lrm;which makes me an expert
&lrm;in dealing with "angels".
&lrm;Who are you anyway?
&lrm;I'm a mythical unicorn
&lrm;from the world of Reespa,
&lrm;disguised
&lrm;as a totally fabulous human girl.
&lrm;I grant magical wishes
&lrm;but only to little monkeys who behave.
&lrm;[she giggles] No you're not...
&lrm;are you?
&lrm;[they both giggle]
&lrm;[Marinette gasps]
&lrm;OK, let's all go to the park.
&lrm;[Manon] Yay.
&lrm;[cheerfully] OK.
&lrm;This is the moment we've been waiting for!
&lrm;The viewers have made their decision.
&lrm;And the new Kidz Plus Weathergirl is...
&lrm;Mireille!
&lrm;[cheers and applause]
&lrm;She crushed you. Better luck next time.
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;What's the big deal?
&lrm;You only lost by half a million votes.
&lrm;[evil voice]
&lrm;The vibrations are so strong...
&lrm;I can feel
&lrm;the imminent anger and sadness...
&lrm;the moment of weakness of my next victim,
&lrm;such easy prey for my Akuma.
&lrm;[angry sighs]
&lrm;[elevator beeps]
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;[angrily] I should have won.
&lrm;I had the talent, the star looks,
&lrm;everything!
&lrm;But she took everything away from me.
&lrm;They took everything away from me!
&lrm;[fizzing]
&lrm;[she squeals]
&lrm;[evil voice] So correct you are.
&lrm;You should have won, yes.
&lrm;[angrily] I should have won, yes!
&lrm;Stormy Weather,
&lrm;I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;I give you the power to seek revenge
&lrm;on them as my Weathergirl.
&lrm;All you have to do
&lrm;is bring me the Miraculous.
&lrm;Can you do that?
&lrm;Yes.
&lrm;That's my Weathergirl.
&lrm;Show the world
&lrm;who the best Weathergirl really is.
&lrm;[camera clicks]
&lrm;Come on.
&lrm;We'll stroll over there, real cool,
&lrm;as if we just happened to be passing by.
&lrm;-Then what?
&lrm;-Then...
&lrm;I'll invite him for a smoothie
&lrm;after the shoot.
&lrm;Then, we'll get married
&lrm;and live in a beautiful house,
&lrm;have kids, a dog, maybe a cat...
&lrm;No, forget the cat.
&lrm;A hamster, I love hamsters.
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;Let's start with "passing by"
&lrm;and see if we can get to that smoothie.
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;Magnifico, super.
&lrm;I want to see hunger in your eyes.
&lrm;[Marinette]
&lrm;Remember... cool, just be cool.
&lrm;[Alya] We couldn't be more invisible.
&lrm;OK, let's start over.
&lrm;[Marinette gasps and giggles]
&lrm;[photographer chuckles]
&lrm;Did you see that? He waved at me.
&lrm;Yeah, I saw it too.
&lrm;Pretty normal
&lrm;since we're in the same class.
&lrm;[Marinette giggles nervously]
&lrm;[elevator beeps]
&lrm;[wicked laughing]
&lrm;I am Stormy Weather,
&lrm;the only Weathergirl
&lrm;who always gets the forecast right.
&lrm;And, unfortunately for you,
&lrm;there's a freak icy front moving in,
&lrm;right now!
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;Somebody get me out of here!
&lrm;Help! Help!
&lrm;[photographer] Bravo, that's it.
&lrm;Gimme ze smile
&lrm;of when mamma brings spaghetti.
&lrm;OK, now...
&lrm;Oh no, mamma dropped ze spaghetti.
&lrm;Now, eat ze spaghetti off ze floor.
&lrm;Yes, you're angry.
&lrm;[photographer] Show me angry... Yes, yes.
&lrm;Marinette, I want a balloon
&lrm;with Mireille on it.
&lrm;Can I? Can I?
&lrm;Marinette?
&lrm;Marinette!
&lrm;[he groans] Silenzio!
&lrm;Come on.
&lrm;Come on, I'll get you that balloon.
&lrm;No, I wanna go with Marinette.
&lrm;I'll deal with it. I am her babysitter.
&lrm;But what about Adrien?
&lrm;[crowd cheers] Mireille, Mireille!
&lrm;[she cackles]
&lrm;Where's Mireille?
&lrm;[frustrated groan]
&lrm;For all of you who voted for Mireille,
&lrm;I'd advise you to move indoors.
&lrm;It's going to get very blustery.
&lrm;Oh wait... too late.
&lrm;[blustering wind]
&lrm;[crowd gasps and screams]
&lrm;Come on. Let's go back.
&lrm;I wanna go on the merry-go-round.
&lrm;No, no, not right now.
&lrm;I've gotta get back to Adrien.
&lrm;You promised.
&lrm;You aren't going to break
&lrm;your promise, are you?
&lrm;Oh please, not the baby-doll eyes.
&lrm;You know I can't say no to...
&lrm;[caring sigh]
&lrm;[Manon giggles]
&lrm;[angry groan]
&lrm;[child sobs]
&lrm;Here's a new one.
&lrm;[camera clicks]
&lrm;No, no.
&lrm;Ze boy haz eaten too much spaghetti.
&lrm;We needz more energy... more romance.
&lrm;We needz...
&lrm;a girl.
&lrm;You, I need an extra.
&lrm;Who? Me?
&lrm;Si, to pose wiz Mr. Adrien.
&lrm;You don't want me. I...
&lrm;I'm having an allergic reaction
&lrm;to this apple.
&lrm;[speaking with a lisp]
&lrm;I know jutht the perthon.
&lrm;[puffing and panting]
&lrm;They need an extra
&lrm;to pose with Adrien.
&lrm;What? Seriously?
&lrm;Is that boy your boyfriend?
&lrm;What? No... I mean, yes... No.
&lrm;Go on. What're you waiting for?
&lrm;But what about Manon?
&lrm;You take care of Prince Charming,
&lrm;I'll take care of Miss Unicorn.
&lrm;You don't know how to control her anyway.
&lrm;No way! Marinette's my babysitter.
&lrm;Trust me.
&lrm;Unicorns unite.
&lrm;Let's go to Reespa
&lrm;and find some sad village kids
&lrm;and grant them those wishes. Yee-haw!
&lrm;Yee-haw!
&lrm;[Manon giggles]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;Run!
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on! Yeah!
&lrm;[crowd screams]
&lrm;[explosions]
&lrm;Help!
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;[explosions]
&lrm;Plagg? Plagg!
&lrm;I'm not here. I'm sleeping.
&lrm;[excited cry]
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;For your information,
&lrm;I can smell camembert in my sleep.
&lrm;It's one of my many talents.
&lrm;Great, but there's no time
&lrm;to talk cheese.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;Why did I leave Manon?
&lrm;I should have never done that.
&lrm;No, Alya's right.
&lrm;She's in good hands. I must trust her.
&lrm;I'll get you out of here!
&lrm;Let's wire-cut this icy cake.
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;Or not... On to plan B.
&lrm;Don't worry. It will be OK.
&lrm;Where's Marinette?
&lrm;She hasn't forgotten you, Manon.
&lrm;How did you know my name?
&lrm;I... I... Marinette told me.
&lrm;She's coming right back, OK?
&lrm;[Ladybug chuckles]
&lrm;[explosions]
&lrm;Hey, Ice Queen.
&lrm;What's with all the terrorizing?
&lrm;Why don't you pick on someone
&lrm;your own temperature?
&lrm;My name is not Ice Queen,
&lrm;it's Stormy Weather!
&lrm;Listen, I'm feline
&lrm;more generous than usual, today.
&lrm;So cool down, and we'll call it quits. 'K?
&lrm;[blustering wind]
&lrm;[Cat Noir yells]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;I thought cats
&lrm;always landed on their feet.
&lrm;Why thanks, M'Ladybug,
&lrm;but I had it covered.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;No time for your childish charm,
&lrm;Cat Noir, but you're welcome.
&lrm;We should be expecting lightning storms,
&lrm;like, right now!
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[thunder rumbles]
&lrm;[they scream]
&lrm;[exploding]
&lrm;[they groan]
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;You've just won yourself a catfight.
&lrm;Black Ice!
&lrm;[car alarms bleep]
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;[blustering wind continues]
&lrm;[car alarms bleep]
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[explosion]
&lrm;A little Cat Noir
&lrm;will take the wind out of her sails.
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;Wow, kitty-kitty, think before you leap.
&lrm;-You've got a plan?
&lrm;-Just follow my lead.
&lrm;Not you again.
&lrm;[blustering wind]
&lrm;[they scream]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;[they groan]
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[bus bell rings]
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;[bus bell dies out]
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;[Alya sings] Lemonade crunchy ice,
&lrm;hit it once, hit it twice. Freeze!
&lrm;Hey, no fair. You always win...
&lrm;[ice cracks]
&lrm;What was that?
&lrm;It's...
&lrm;It's the big Goblin King.
&lrm;He ate too much and split his shirt.
&lrm;[she roars]
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;[rumbling]
&lrm;Wanna hear a story?
&lrm;You've shown them all
&lrm;who the real winner is, my Weathergirl,
&lrm;but now is the time for you
&lrm;to fulfil your part of the agreement,
&lrm;and here's my plan.
&lrm;Maybe she's got anger issues.
&lrm;Or she failed her driving test.
&lrm;Hello, viewers.
&lrm;Here's the latest forecast
&lrm;for this first day of summer.
&lrm;Looks like Mother Nature
&lrm;had a change in plans.
&lrm;Summer vacation is officially over.
&lrm;Already?
&lrm;But I look so good in a swimsuit.
&lrm;The cat suit will do, thanks.
&lrm;At least now we know where to find her.
&lrm;Prepare for the worst weather ever
&lrm;with 10 ft. snowdrifts.
&lrm;Hey. That girl reminds me of someone.
&lrm;It's her.
&lrm;The Akuma must be in her parasol.
&lrm;In Stormy Weather's world,
&lrm;it's Winter Wonderland, forever!
&lrm;[they roar]
&lrm;It's a recording.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;This is all going
&lrm;wonderfully according to plan.
&lrm;Soon their Miraculous will be mine.
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] Bring them to me!
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[Cat Noir]
&lrm;Frosty the Snowgirl's getting away.
&lrm;Do I hear a damsel in distress?
&lrm;[Ladybug]
&lrm;Some of us don't have night vision.
&lrm;No need to bug out. Just trust me.
&lrm;Then the cyclops monster picked
&lrm;the princess up and said,
&lrm;"Look into my eye."
&lrm;[Manon giggles]
&lrm;Then she stuck a finger right in it.
&lrm;As soon as she took a bite
&lrm;of the cursed potato,
&lrm;the poor princess
&lrm;fell into a deep, deep sleep.
&lrm;[creaking]
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;[fearfully] Hurry up, Ladybug.
&lrm;[Ladybug] OK, I think I can manage to...
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Duck!
&lrm;[Ladybug]
&lrm;I'll follow your lead on this one
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;You airheads, you fell right into my trap.
&lrm;The time is now. Bring me the Miraculous!
&lrm;There's no way out! Party's over, fools.
&lrm;We're just...
&lrm;[he chuckles]
&lrm;We're just getting started, Stormy.
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;A bath towel? What do I do with this?
&lrm;Great. We're about to be obliterated
&lrm;but... at least we'll be dry.
&lrm;Just hold your whiskers.
&lrm;Hey!
&lrm;So what's the plan?
&lrm;My arm's starting to get cramp.
&lrm;See that sign? Check it out.
&lrm;Alright!
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;Hey, Coldilocks,
&lrm;is that all you've got?
&lrm;[she squeals]
&lrm;Get out of here, you nasty bug.
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you, little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilize!
&lrm;Gotcha.
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous, Ladybug!
&lrm;[sparkling]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[hissing]
&lrm;And after defeating
&lrm;the three-headed dragon...
&lrm;with taekwondo...
&lrm;the princess kissed
&lrm;her Prince Charming and...
&lrm;They lived happily ever after?
&lrm;[hesitantly] Sure...
&lrm;until they had little monkeys
&lrm;like you who drove them crazy.
&lrm;[Manon chuckles]
&lrm;[she gasps] What am I doing up here?
&lrm;[together] Pound it.
&lrm;Someday, your Miraculous will be all mine.
&lrm;I don't care how many enemies I need
&lrm;to throw at you to win,
&lrm;but I will be victorious!
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Hey, there's the photographer
&lrm;and Adrien waiting for you.
&lrm;It's not too late?
&lrm;Come on, Marinette,
&lrm;you saved Manon
&lrm;and the whole world for that matter.
&lrm;Have some fun.
&lrm;[Manon] Marinette!
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;I know what your secret is.
&lrm;Wh... What secret?
&lrm;Ladybug is your best friend.
&lrm;That's how you always know
&lrm;what the other one's gonna do.
&lrm;[relieved sigh]
&lrm;Can I have a lollipop? Can I?
&lrm;-Can I? Can I?
&lrm;-No, Manon. I've something to do.
&lrm;Alya, you'll watch her, yeah?
&lrm;I'm ready for the photo shoot.
&lrm;Wait. Who iz zat... angel?
&lrm;[photographer giggles] Angel... magnifico.
&lrm;[Marinette sighs]
&lrm;[photographer giggles]