&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life.
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;The Stonebeings are all over Paris.
&lrm;For now, they're showing
&lrm;no signs of movement.
&lrm;Police have cordoned off the areas.
&lrm;We won't stop until
&lrm;we get these people back to normal
&lrm;but we're not making much headway.
&lrm;Paris is relying
&lrm;on our new guardian angels,
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir to save us.
&lrm;Our lives depend on them.
&lrm;I know how upsetting and scary this is
&lrm;but don't worry,
&lrm;we've got 2 superheroes
&lrm;looking out for Paris.
&lrm;We have to show them we're not scared
&lrm;because we trust them.
&lrm;But what if Ladybug fails?
&lrm;Then, I'd come and save you.
&lrm;Superbaker to the rescue!
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;Thanks, Superdad.
&lrm;[clock chimes] What's he doing?
&lrm;Adrien?
&lrm;You didn't see him leave?
&lrm;If anything happens to him,
&lrm;you'll be responsible!
&lrm;[Plagg] You're a strange kid.
&lrm;Who'd want to be at school
&lrm;when he could stay at home?
&lrm;You don't get it. I've had enough
&lrm;of being shut up at home.
&lrm;I wanna make friends,
&lrm;go to a normal school like everyone else.
&lrm;[Plagg groans] I think I'm feeling weak.
&lrm;You know what's strange?
&lrm;You eating this smelly camembert cheese
&lrm;and that I have to smell like it 24/7.
&lrm;That's strange.
&lrm;If you want to transform into a superhero,
&lrm;then stinky cheese is the deal, my friend.
&lrm;"Ladyblog: bringing you all the news
&lrm;about the coolest superhero, Ladybug."
&lrm;How awesome is that?
&lrm;Check out the number of views.
&lrm;But why do you trust Ladybug so much?
&lrm;All these Stonebeings...
&lrm;She'll handle them.
&lrm;What if she's not cut out
&lrm;to be a superhero like people think?
&lrm;What're you talkin' about?
&lrm;Oh, wait.
&lrm;I know what this is about.
&lrm;You're scared, but don't be.
&lrm;I've seen her with my own two eyes,
&lrm;Ladybug is a true superheroine.
&lrm;She'll protect us all.
&lrm;I believe in her.
&lrm;[Alix] You don't remember?
&lrm;[Juleka] You went totally ballistic.
&lrm;It was so cool.
&lrm;You were out to crush me.
&lrm;Sorry, I wasn't myself.
&lrm;Once a monster, always a monster.
&lrm;Don't let the door hit you on the way out.
&lrm;[evil voice]
&lrm;Yes, feel the burn of those words.
&lrm;Lose your temper, Ivan.
&lrm;Your Akuma awaits you.
&lrm;[dull ring]
&lrm;[Nathalie] Adrien!
&lrm;Your father will be furious.
&lrm;[Adrien] Say you were too late,
&lrm;please.
&lrm;How could you say that?
&lrm;You're the Stoneheart.
&lrm;[sarcatic] So I'm the one
&lrm;who broke Sabrina's dad's arm?
&lrm;Just because your footage
&lrm;of those lame heroes was on TV,
&lrm;you don't have to get
&lrm;so high and mighty.
&lrm;You little...
&lrm;Look out, she's angry.
&lrm;She's going to split her underwear
&lrm;and turn into a huge monster.
&lrm;[Adrien] Hey, Chloe.
&lrm;Adrikins, you came!
&lrm;[excited chattering] I know him!
&lrm;[excited muttering] He's so handsome!
&lrm;I'll handle it.
&lrm;You should tell Mylene how you feel.
&lrm;I don't know what you're talking about.
&lrm;Come on, I saw how you look at her.
&lrm;No, no negative emotions.
&lrm;What I mean is... be positive.
&lrm;I'm sure she likes you too.
&lrm;[whispering] Go talk to her.
&lrm;I'm no good with words.
&lrm;Who needs words?
&lrm;You could draw her a picture,
&lrm;send her flowers...
&lrm;I could write her a song?
&lrm;That's a great idea.
&lrm;Who wouldn't want
&lrm;a love song written for her?
&lrm;Go for it, Ivan, and stay positive.
&lrm;[he chuckles]
&lrm;The negative emotions are fading.
&lrm;Can I have your autograph?
&lrm;Can I have an autograph? I'm a huge fan.
&lrm;This is your seat, Adrikins.
&lrm;I saved it for you,
&lrm;right in front of me.
&lrm;Thanks, Chloe.
&lrm;Hey... Adrien.
&lrm;[suspiciously] You're friends with Chloe?
&lrm;Hey, what's that all about?
&lrm;The brats who sat here yesterday
&lrm;need some attitude adjustment.
&lrm;I'm just commanding
&lrm;a bit of respect, that's all.
&lrm;Think that's really necessary?
&lrm;You've got a lot to learn
&lrm;about school culture, Adrikins.
&lrm;Watch the master.
&lrm;Alya, wouldn't you like to be a superhero
&lrm;and fight monsters and villains?
&lrm;Totally. I'm not scared of anyone. Why?
&lrm;No reason.
&lrm;[Alya gasps]
&lrm;What are you doing?
&lrm;I...
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;OK, I get it.
&lrm;Good job, you 3. Very funny.
&lrm;No, no. I was trying to take it off.
&lrm;Really?
&lrm;You're friends with Chloe, right?
&lrm;Why do people keep saying that?
&lrm;See what I mean about respect?
&lrm;I know I've seen him somewhere before.
&lrm;[gasping] Of course.
&lrm;He's the son of fave' designer,
&lrm;Gabriel Agreste!
&lrm;Daddy's boy,
&lrm;teen supermodel and Chloe's buddy?
&lrm;[scoffing] Forget it.
&lrm;Why not tell her it was Chloe?
&lrm;I've known Chloe since I was a kid.
&lrm;She's not perfect
&lrm;but I can't throw her under the bus.
&lrm;She's my only friend.
&lrm;I'm Nino. It's time for you to make
&lrm;some new friends.
&lrm;I'm going to be late.
&lrm;[she shrieks] Ivan...
&lrm;you scared me.
&lrm;I made this for you.
&lrm;[heavy metal music]
&lrm;[singing loudly] Mylene, be serene!
&lrm;[higher pitch] Be serene...!
&lrm;[evil voice] Yes...
&lrm;I've been waiting for this.
&lrm;You know the way, evil Akuma.
&lrm;Track down your prey.
&lrm;Fly away, and evilise him!
&lrm;This is your 2nd chance,
&lrm;Stoneheart and now you have extra help.
&lrm;No-one will stop you
&lrm;capturing your loved one,
&lrm;but I'll need something in return.
&lrm;[thudding]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;[Miss Bustier] Agreste, Adrien?
&lrm;You say present.
&lrm;Present!
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;-Bourgeois, Chloe?
&lrm;-Present.
&lrm;Bruel, Ivan?
&lrm;[roaring] Present!
&lrm;[roaring] Mylene?
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;Let go of me, Ivan.
&lrm;I'm not Ivan anymore. I'm Stoneheart.
&lrm;Why are you doing this?
&lrm;So you and I can be together, forever!
&lrm;[Chloe whimpers]
&lrm;Daddy, the monster is back.
&lrm;You!
&lrm;Please, my hair.
&lrm;[Mylene] Put us down, Ivan.
&lrm;Let's follow him.
&lrm;Oh no, you go.
&lrm;I'm finding a place to hide.
&lrm;You're gonna miss Ladybug in action.
&lrm;You and Ladybug will be
&lrm;better off without me.
&lrm;If you say so.
&lrm;Wait, your bag.
&lrm;My first day and I didn't
&lrm;make it past roll call.
&lrm;A day off? I like the sound of that.
&lrm;No, no. We've got homework to do.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;You've no idea who you're dealing with.
&lrm;My daddy, the mayor, will bring in
&lrm;the army and the entire cavalry.
&lrm;Don't forget the superheroes!
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Oh no, my bad.
&lrm;Super-incompetent, you mean.
&lrm;You wanted the cavalry?
&lrm;Here it is!
&lrm;[Mylene] No!
&lrm;Seize him!
&lrm;[Mylene] Watch out!
&lrm;[Mylene] Ivan,
&lrm;where are we going?
&lrm;To deliver a message.
&lrm;We'll be brought together forever.
&lrm;This lovey-dovey stuff makes me sick.
&lrm;Don't worry, little monster,
&lrm;I'll take care of you too.
&lrm;Ladybug,
&lrm;I need help.
&lrm;What's she waiting for?
&lrm;[Alya screams]
&lrm;Let go, you rock-head!
&lrm;Help!
&lrm;-I need Ladybug.
&lrm;-I knew you'd come around.
&lrm;I'm still not sure I'm up for this
&lrm;but Alya's in danger.
&lrm;I can't do nothing.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;You can't stay here. It's too dangerous.
&lrm;Cat Noir, extend it!
&lrm;[Ladybug] Sorry I was late.
&lrm;Have I ever told you
&lrm;you turn my world upside down?
&lrm;You're quite a joker.
&lrm;But your timing needs work.
&lrm;We gotta go.
&lrm;Aren't we gonna take care of them?
&lrm;No, if we want to save them all
&lrm;then we go to the source...
&lrm;that one.
&lrm;I demand my daughter's safe return.
&lrm;Daddy!
&lrm;You're welcome to her!
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;I promise to be nice, be polite and...
&lrm;-I didn't promise.
&lrm;-What?
&lrm;My little princess.
&lrm;We're clear to attack!
&lrm;Wait, don't attack. You'll make it worse.
&lrm;I've a new plan.
&lrm;Leave it to the pros.
&lrm;You already failed once.
&lrm;He's right.
&lrm;Had I captured the Akuma the 1st time,
&lrm;this wouldn't have happened.
&lrm;I knew I wasn't the one for this job.
&lrm;No. He's wrong.
&lrm;Without you, she wouldn't be here.
&lrm;Without us, they won't make it.
&lrm;We'll prove it.
&lrm;Trust me on this, OK?
&lrm;OK.
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;[coughing and spluttering]
&lrm;[weak groan]
&lrm;People of Paris,
&lrm;listen carefully...
&lrm;I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Hawk moth?
&lrm;[evil voice] Ladybug, Cat Noir,
&lrm;give me
&lrm;the Ladybug earrings and the cat ring now!
&lrm;You've done enough damage
&lrm;to these innocent people.
&lrm;Nice try, but we know who the bad guy is.
&lrm;Let's not reverse the roles.
&lrm;You turned these
&lrm;innocent victims into villains.
&lrm;Hawk Moth, no matter how long it takes,
&lrm;we will find you
&lrm;and you'll hand us your Miraculous!
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;[Hawk Moth groans]
&lrm;[Ladybug yells]
&lrm;Let me make this promise.
&lrm;Whoever wants to harm you,
&lrm;Cat Noir and I will do
&lrm;all we can to keep you safe.
&lrm;Yes!
&lrm;Whoever she is beneath that mask
&lrm;I love that girl.
&lrm;That's the problem with superheroes,
&lrm;they're too... heroic!
&lrm;Stoneheart, they're trying to take
&lrm;your loved one away.
&lrm;Snatch their Miraculouses,
&lrm;they'll be powerless against you.
&lrm;OK, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;[Mylene] Help me!
&lrm;You'll never take Mylene from me!
&lrm;[Stoneheart] Come to me, my Stonebeings!
&lrm;We're surrounded.
&lrm;What now? We can't attack him.
&lrm;But we know where the Akuma is.
&lrm;[Cat Noir] In the fist he's got Mylene in.
&lrm;So, he's in love with her...
&lrm;That's it!
&lrm;We don't separate them,
&lrm;we bring them closer together.
&lrm;They're made each other,
&lrm;they just don't know it.
&lrm;I don't get it,
&lrm;but I guess I better trust you.
&lrm;Something tells me
&lrm;this is how it'll be in future.
&lrm;[helicopters hum]
&lrm;Help! I'm scared of heights!
&lrm;It'll be alright!
&lrm;[Stoneheart roars]
&lrm;How will you get them even closer?
&lrm;By using our powers!
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;A parachute?
&lrm;What do I do with this?
&lrm;[Cat Noir yells]
&lrm;You know what you're doing?
&lrm;We'll find out soon enough.
&lrm;His hand... get ready!
&lrm;[kissing]
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;Home run!
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you, little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;[they yell]
&lrm;Cat Noir, take care of Ivan!
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;[sigh of relief]
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;[Cat noir amazed] Are you seeing this?
&lrm;Yeah, it's beautiful and amazing, it's...
&lrm;miraculous!
&lrm;This is just the beginning, Ladybug.
&lrm;You may have won this battle
&lrm;but I will win the war!
&lrm;I will get your Miraculouses,
&lrm;I will get the absolute power,
&lrm;and then, my secret dream will come true!
&lrm;I think you two need to talk.
&lrm;I...I...
&lrm;It may help if you read
&lrm;the lyrics to Ivan's song.
&lrm;It's beautiful.
&lrm;It's a shame you can't hear them
&lrm;when you scream...
&lrm;I mean sing.
&lrm;It was scary, wasn't it?
&lrm;Is that why you left?
&lrm;I'm sorry. I'll be gentle.
&lrm;They're made for each other.
&lrm;Like us two.
&lrm;[bleeping] See that?
&lrm;Time to split. See you soon, Cat Noir.
&lrm;Can't wait, Milady.
&lrm;By the time I biked to the Eiffel Tower,
&lrm;it was all over. I'm way bummed.
&lrm;You'll get your scoop eventually.
&lrm;You're right. next target,
&lrm;"Ladybug: An Exclusive Interview."
&lrm;Sounds exciting.
&lrm;Oh, wait, even better,
&lrm;"Finding out
&lrm;who's really under that mask!"
&lrm;Good luck with that one.
&lrm;You disobeyed me.
&lrm;You see that school?
&lrm;Yes, Father.
&lrm;You will never,
&lrm;I say never, go back there again,
&lrm;-Father...
&lrm;-&lrm;without your bodyguard.
&lrm;He'll drop you off and pick you up.
&lrm;Nathalie will organise your schedule.
&lrm;You'll continue music, Chinese,
&lrm;fencing and your photo shoots.
&lrm;Thank you, Nathalie,
&lrm;Thank you, father.
&lrm;No, wait.
&lrm;[Chloe] You're in
&lrm;the wrong seat.
&lrm;Go on, get lost.
&lrm;All that's necessary
&lrm;for the triumph of evil
&lrm;is that good people do nothing.
&lrm;What's that supposed to mean?
&lrm;It means I'm not putting up
&lrm;with your crud anymore,
&lrm;neither is anyone else.
&lrm;So take your attitude and go and get lost.
&lrm;[laughing]
&lrm;Good job.
&lrm;You wanna make friends, right?
&lrm;Talk to Marinette about the gum.
&lrm;What should I say?
&lrm;Just be yourself.
&lrm;Hey.
&lrm;[she huffs]
&lrm;I just want you to know
&lrm;I was only trying to get the gum off,
&lrm;I swear.
&lrm;I've never been to school before.
&lrm;I've never had friends.
&lrm;It's all sort of new to me.
&lrm;[romantic music]
&lrm;[thunder rumbles]
&lrm;See you tomorrow.
&lrm;[romantic music]
&lrm;[stammering] See you tomorrow...
&lrm;[chuckling] Why am I stammering?
&lrm;Hey. I think I might have an idea.
&lrm;First day of school
&lrm;and we already have two love-birds.
&lrm;[puffing] Whatever, she's just a friend.
&lrm;A friend.
&lrm;[romantic music]
&lrm;[Waizze] Excellent choice, master.
&lrm;Those two are made for each other.