&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl, with a normal life,
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Nooroo] &lrm;Many centuries ago,
&lrm;magic jewels with extraordinary
&lrm;powers were created,
&lrm;these were the Miraculous.
&lrm;Throughout history, heroes have used them
&lrm;for the good of the human race.
&lrm;Two of these Miraculous
&lrm;are more powerful than the others,
&lrm;the earrings of the Ladybug
&lrm;with power of creation,
&lrm;and the ring of the Black Cat,
&lrm;which grants the power of destruction.
&lrm;According to legend,
&lrm;whoever controls both these jewels
&lrm;will achieve absolute power.
&lrm;I want that absolute power, Nooroo.
&lrm;I must have those Miraculous.
&lrm;But nobody knows where they are.
&lrm;I found you though, my little Nooroo.
&lrm;Your Miraculous,
&lrm;remind me of its powers again.
&lrm;The moth brooch allows you
&lrm;to give someone a superpower
&lrm;and to make them your follower.
&lrm;And, when it comes
&lrm;to luring superheroes,
&lrm;what could be better
&lrm;than creating supervillains?
&lrm;But master, the Miraculous
&lrm;aren't meant for evil purposes.
&lrm;I must have this absolute power!
&lrm;Your Miraculous is in my control.
&lrm;I am your master now!
&lrm;And you must obey me.
&lrm;Yes, master.
&lrm;Nooroo...
&lrm;dark wings, rise!
&lrm;From this day on,
&lrm;I shall be known as... Hawk Moth.
&lrm;[evil cackling]
&lrm;Master, master.
&lrm;[chanting] Master, master...
&lrm;Chanting... it's part of the treatment.
&lrm;Master, master.
&lrm;Thank you for coming.
&lrm;See you next week.
&lrm;Master, the Moth Miraculous,
&lrm;I felt its aura.
&lrm;I thought it was lost forever.
&lrm;But master, it's a negative aura.
&lrm;I fear it's in the hands of a dark power.
&lrm;We must find Nooroo and his Miraculous.
&lrm;If it's in the wrong hands,
&lrm;there's no telling what evil
&lrm;will come upon the world.
&lrm;Time to transform! Wayzz...
&lrm;[bones crack]
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;Master, be reasonable, you are...
&lrm;Still young, I'm only 186.
&lrm;But you're right, Wayzz.
&lrm;I can no longer do it alone.
&lrm;We'll need some help.
&lrm;[alarm rings] Marinette!
&lrm;Your alarm's going off.
&lrm;You'll be late for your first day.
&lrm;Got it, mom.
&lrm;Coming...
&lrm;-I bet Chloe is in my class again.
&lrm;-Four years in a row?
&lrm;-Is that possible?
&lrm;-Definitely. Lucky me.
&lrm;Don't say that.
&lrm;It's the start of a new year.
&lrm;I'm sure everything will be just fine.
&lrm;[he hums French national anthem]
&lrm;Dad, these are so awesome!
&lrm;Glad you like 'em.
&lrm;Thanks, dad, they'll love them.
&lrm;You're the best.
&lrm;We're the best.
&lrm;Thanks to your amazing designs.
&lrm;Thanks.
&lrm;See you tonight.
&lrm;[bell tinkles]
&lrm;[she yelps]
&lrm;[horn beeps]
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;Thank you, miss. What a disaster.
&lrm;I'm no stranger to disaster.
&lrm;Besides, there's still a few left.
&lrm;Delicious.
&lrm;[bell rings] No, I'm late!
&lrm;Have a nice day, sir.
&lrm;[school bell rings]
&lrm;Thank you very much, young lady.
&lrm;Nino, why don't you sit
&lrm;at the front this year?
&lrm;Marinette Dupain-Cheng.
&lrm;Here we go again.
&lrm;That's my seat.
&lrm;But Chloe, this has always been my seat.
&lrm;Not anymore. New school year, new seats.
&lrm;So go and sit beside
&lrm;that new girl over there?
&lrm;-But...
&lrm;-Adrien's arriving today,
&lrm;and since that's his seat,
&lrm;this is going to be my seat. Get it?
&lrm;Who's Adrien?
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;Can you believe
&lrm;she doesn't know who he is?
&lrm;What planet do you live on?
&lrm;He's only a famous model.
&lrm;And I am his best friend. He adores me.
&lrm;Go on, move.
&lrm;Who elected you Queen of Seats?
&lrm;Look, Sabrina,
&lrm;we've got a little do-gooder this year.
&lrm;What you gonna do,
&lrm;shoot beams at me with your glasses?
&lrm;Wouldn't you like to know?
&lrm;C'mon.
&lrm;Sorry, sorry, sorry.
&lrm;Everyone got a seat?
&lrm;[Alya] Chillax, girl. No biggie.
&lrm;I wish I could handle Chloe like you do.
&lrm;You mean like Majestia.
&lrm;"All that is necessary
&lrm;"for the triumph of evil is
&lrm;that good people do nothing."
&lrm;That girl over there is evil,
&lrm;and we're the good people.
&lrm;-We can't let her get away with it.
&lrm;-Easier said than done.
&lrm;She likes to make my life miserable.
&lrm;Because you let her, girl.
&lrm;You need more confidence.
&lrm;-Marinette.
&lrm;-Alya.
&lrm;For those who don't know me,
&lrm;I'm Miss Bustier.
&lrm;I'll be your teacher this year.
&lrm;He should be here by now.
&lrm;[car approaches]
&lrm;[car tires screech]
&lrm;Adrien, please reconsider.
&lrm;You know what your father wants.
&lrm;This is what I want to do.
&lrm;[old man groans]
&lrm;Thank you, young man.
&lrm;I want to go to school
&lrm;like everybody else.
&lrm;What's wrong with that?
&lrm;Please don't tell father.
&lrm;[bell rings] If you who have PE,
&lrm;meet Mr. D'Argencourt at the stadium.
&lrm;The rest can go to the library.
&lrm;[Ivan] Kim!
&lrm;-Ivan, what are you doing?
&lrm;-It's Kim!
&lrm;I'm so gonna...
&lrm;Ivan!
&lrm;Go to the principal's office.
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;Negative emotions. This is perfect.
&lrm;Just what I need.
&lrm;Anger, sadness...
&lrm;Burn a hole into his heart,
&lrm;my horrible Akuma.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Fly away, my little Akuma,
&lrm;and evilise him!
&lrm;[door opens]
&lrm;Hasn't anyone ever taught you to knock?
&lrm;Go on, out you go. Let's try it again.
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;[Mr. Damocles] Go on, knock.
&lrm;Stoneheart, I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;I give you the power to seek revenge.
&lrm;OK, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;[bubbling]
&lrm;Well, come on in.
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;[rumbling]
&lrm;[screams]
&lrm;[Alya] Come on.
&lrm;[banging] Did you hear that?
&lrm;[roaring] Kim!
&lrm;Hello, police? Get me the army!
&lrm;What's going on? He had Ivan's voice?
&lrm;It's as if he's been transformed
&lrm;into a real-life supervillain.
&lrm;GPS, check, battery, check,
&lrm;I'm so outta here.
&lrm;Where are you going?
&lrm;When there's a supervillain,
&lrm;a superhero's not far behind.
&lrm;I'm not missing this.
&lrm;[screeching of tires]
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;Who was 1st President of the 5th Republic?
&lrm;People think it was De Gaulle
&lrm;but it was René Coty
&lrm;before the first elections.
&lrm;Excellent, Adrien.
&lrm;Give me a minute would you, Nathalie?
&lrm;Yes, sir.
&lrm;You are not going to school.
&lrm;I've already told you.
&lrm;But...
&lrm;I want you here
&lrm;so I can keep an eye on you
&lrm;not in that dangerous world.
&lrm;It's not dangerous.
&lrm;I'm always stuck here.
&lrm;Why can't I go out and make friends?
&lrm;You're not everyone else,
&lrm;you're my son.
&lrm;Continue.
&lrm;We can stop for today if...
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;[police sirens]
&lrm;[thudding]
&lrm;[Roger] Ready?
&lrm;[Roger] Fire!
&lrm;All Parisians, stay at home
&lrm;until the situation's under control.
&lrm;As incredible as it seems,
&lrm;Paris is being attacked by a supervillain.
&lrm;The police are struggling
&lrm;to control the situation.
&lrm;Be confident.
&lrm;The strong arm of the law will crash...
&lrm;I mean, the other arm.
&lrm;I hate first days at school.
&lrm;What's this doing here?
&lrm;Help, it's a giant bug!
&lrm;A mouse... a bug-mouse.
&lrm;Everything's OK. Don't be scared!
&lrm;Bug-mouse talks!
&lrm;No way. Like the genie in the lamp.
&lrm;I met him once, so he grants wishes,
&lrm;I'm way more personable.
&lrm;Plagg, nice to meet you.
&lrm;Swanky.
&lrm;[chomping] Don't touch that!
&lrm;Come back here.
&lrm;It's so shiny. Can you eat this?
&lrm;[chomping] No, you can't. What about this?
&lrm;Marinette, I know everything
&lrm;seems a bit strange...
&lrm;OK, if you feel safer.
&lrm;What are you?
&lrm;How do you know my name?
&lrm;I'm a Kwami, and my name is Tikki.
&lrm;Now, just let me explain.
&lrm;[chomping]
&lrm;[yelping]
&lrm;I still don't know why you're here.
&lrm;I'm a Kwami. I grant powers.
&lrm;Yours is the power of destruction. Got it?
&lrm;Good. Got anything to eat? I'm starving.
&lrm;My dad's pranking me, right?
&lrm;Wait, he has no sense of humour.
&lrm;He must never know I exist
&lrm;or anyone for that matter.
&lrm;Mom! Dad!
&lrm;No, no, no.
&lrm;I'm your friend, Marinette.
&lrm;You must trust me.
&lrm;You're the only one
&lrm;who can stop Stoneheart.
&lrm;Do you think they'll be up to it, master?
&lrm;I only got it wrong once.
&lrm;It will not happen again.
&lrm;At least I hope not.
&lrm;This has to be a mistake.
&lrm;The only superpower
&lrm;I could have is super-awkwardness.
&lrm;I know. Alya would know.
&lrm;I think she would. She loves superheroes.
&lrm;She'd totally be up for it. Ask her.
&lrm;Marinette, you're the chosen one.
&lrm;I'm stuck here. I can't even go to school.
&lrm;What good's a superhero
&lrm;imprisoned in his own house?
&lrm;No good.
&lrm;That's why it's all going to change,
&lrm;if you're willing to change.
&lrm;OK, so all I do
&lrm;is break the object
&lrm;where that thingy is?
&lrm;It's called an Akuma,
&lrm;which you must capture.
&lrm;Got it. Capture it.
&lrm;What's that charm thing?
&lrm;Your lucky charm, it's your super-power.
&lrm;This is all going too fast.
&lrm;I won't be able to pull this off.
&lrm;Trust yourself, Marinette.
&lrm;Just say "Spots on".
&lrm;Spots on?
&lrm;What's happening?
&lrm;"Claws out", that's how you transform.
&lrm;Got it.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;Wait, I haven't finished...
&lrm;Too cool.
&lrm;How does this thing come off?
&lrm;Tikki? If you can hear me,
&lrm;I want my normal clothes back.
&lrm;I'm not going anywhere.
&lrm;Stoneheart is heading to
&lrm;the Montparnasse tower.
&lrm;Alya?
&lrm;[Sabine] Marinette, did you get home OK?
&lrm;Yeah, mom, just super.
&lrm;Marinette? You in here?
&lrm;[Sabine] Tom, we'd better call the school.
&lrm;OK, I have special powers.
&lrm;And apparently this amazing
&lrm;super yoyo thingy.
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;I'm getting the hang of this.
&lrm;[whistling]
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;[they groan]
&lrm;-Hey, nice of you to drop in.
&lrm;-Sorry, I didn't do it on purpose.
&lrm;I bet you're the partner
&lrm;my Kwami told me about.
&lrm;I'm... Cat Noir.
&lrm;Yeah, Cat Noir... And you?
&lrm;I'm...
&lrm;Madly clumsy, I'm so clumsy.
&lrm;No sweat, Clumsy-girl. I'm learning too.
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;-Wait, where are you going?
&lrm;-To save Paris, right?
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;Trust yourself, trust yourself.
&lrm;[whizzing]
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;[thudding] Kim!
&lrm;So, who's the wuss now?
&lrm;[Rose screams]
&lrm;It's not nice to pick on
&lrm;people smaller than you.
&lrm;I guess you're talking about yourself.
&lrm;Everything's going to plan.
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir's Miraculous
&lrm;have been activated.
&lrm;Here they come to save the day
&lrm;and now my supervillain will destroy them.
&lrm;Where are you, partner?
&lrm;I can't.
&lrm;I'm not going to be able to do it.
&lrm;[Alya gasps]
&lrm;What are you waiting for?
&lrm;The world is watching!
&lrm;Animal cruelty? How shameful.
&lrm;Yes!
&lrm;Sorry I took so long.
&lrm;It's cool, Wonderbug.
&lrm;Let's kick his rocky behind.
&lrm;Wait. He gets bigger with every attack.
&lrm;-We have to do something different.
&lrm;-What?
&lrm;I don't know.
&lrm;Let's use our powers.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;Apparently, I destroy whatever I touch.
&lrm;I don't need a superpower for that.
&lrm;[Ladybug] No, don't!
&lrm;Cool, it's just you and me.
&lrm;Time to rumble, soon-to-be rubble.
&lrm;Wait!
&lrm;I guess I only get one shot
&lrm;to use my power.
&lrm;And you only have 5 minutes
&lrm;before you change back.
&lrm;Didn't your Kwami explain?
&lrm;I guess I was too excited.
&lrm;Well, up to me?
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;[Cat Noir sarcastically] Super power.
&lrm;My Kwami said I must break the object
&lrm;where the Akuma is hiding.
&lrm;He's made out of stone.
&lrm;His hand, it's closed.
&lrm;He never opens it.
&lrm;It's like Russian dolls,
&lrm;the object is hidden in his fist.
&lrm;What's your plan?
&lrm;This.
&lrm;[Ladybug] Don't resist, trust me.
&lrm;[yelling] This girl's crazy!
&lrm;[Ladybug] Catch me if you can.
&lrm;And now...
&lrm;Alya, the tap!
&lrm;This girl is awesome.
&lrm;She's crazy awesome.
&lrm;What's going on? What am I doing here?
&lrm;You were incredible, Miss...Bug Lady.
&lrm;You did it.
&lrm;We both did it.
&lrm;Pound it!
&lrm;[Bleeping]
&lrm;You should go.
&lrm;Our identities must remain secret.
&lrm;Farewell, milady,
&lrm;let's do this again soon.
&lrm;Not too soon I hope.
&lrm;"You haven't got the guts
&lrm;to tell Mylene you love her. Wuss!"
&lrm;Kim wrote it. He makes fun of me.
&lrm;You shouldn't get so upset about this.
&lrm;There's no shame
&lrm;in telling someone you love them.
&lrm;How do you know my name, Miss?
&lrm;Uncanny, amazing, spectacular.
&lrm;Will you be protecting Paris?
&lrm;How did you get your powers?
&lrm;Did you get stung
&lrm;by a radioactive ladybug?
&lrm;I've got a ton of questions, Miss...?
&lrm;Ladybug, call me Ladybug.
&lrm;Ladybug...
&lrm;Super awesome.
&lrm;Thanks to this amateur footage,
&lrm;Parisians now know who their heroes are.
&lrm;I did it, Tikki.
&lrm;You see, you were up to it.
&lrm;[Sabine] Marinette, dinner!
&lrm;We will be organising
&lrm;a huge celebration in honour of
&lrm;our city's new protectors,
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;Ladybug, her name is Ladybug.
&lrm;[revolted] What is this?
&lrm;Seriously? My personal chef made it.
&lrm;If you expect me to get my energy back,
&lrm;I need to eat something more... delicate.
&lrm;OK, what?
&lrm;[Sabine] Oh my!
&lrm;Just as Paris is about to
&lrm;celebrate our new superheroes,
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir,
&lrm;a new wave of panic has hit the capital
&lrm;as people are turned into stone monsters.
&lrm;It's simply unbelievable.
&lrm;Camembert cheese, fantastic.
&lrm;All he eats is camembert.
&lrm;which means I'll smell like stinky cheese.
&lrm;The Stonebeings are still like statues.
&lrm;Police are perplexed. What will happen?
&lrm;Will they come to life?
&lrm;Plagg, what's going on? We defeated him.
&lrm;Did you capture the akuma?
&lrm;What's that got to do
&lrm;with the other Stonebeings?
&lrm;An Akuma can multiply
&lrm;that's why it must be captured.
&lrm;If Ivan becomes negative again,
&lrm;the Akuma will turn him back
&lrm;into Stoneheart.
&lrm;He'll use the Stonebeings as his army.
&lrm;So that means this is all my fault?
&lrm;I knew it.
&lrm;I'm not cut out to be a superhero.
&lrm;I'll keep messing up.
&lrm;Keep calm. It was your first time.
&lrm;You'll capture Stoneheart's Akuma
&lrm;and do it successfully.
&lrm;I can't. I told you, I'm clumsy.
&lrm;I create disaster all the time.
&lrm;I'll make things worse for everyone.
&lrm;Cat Noir's better off alone, I'm quitting.
&lrm;I can't do anything without Ladybug?
&lrm;Only Ladybug can capture Akumas
&lrm;and repair damage
&lrm;caused by a supervillain.
&lrm;If Cat Noir can't capture
&lrm;the Akumas, find another Ladybug.
&lrm;I'm not cut out to be Ladybug.
&lrm;I'm sorry, Tikki.
&lrm;No, don't...
&lrm;Tikki?
&lrm;I'm really sorry, Tikki.
&lrm;Ivan has a sensitive heart.
&lrm;It won't be long
&lrm;before anger and sadness strike again.
&lrm;and the Stonebeings will come alive.
&lrm;Then we'll see how long
&lrm;you remain hidden, Ladybug.
&lrm;Once I have your Miraculous,
&lrm;you will be powerless against me.
&lrm;Everyone will be powerless
&lrm;against me!
&lrm;I will have
&lrm;absolute power!
&lrm;[cackling]