&lrm;In the daytime I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life.
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Marinette] Here I am, milady.
&lrm;Glad to see you, Cat Noir.
&lrm;Of course you are, I'm the cat's meow.
&lrm;[she chuckles]
&lrm;- He shouldn't say that.
&lrm;- No?
&lrm;[cough]
&lrm;This is no time to goof around, Cat Noir.
&lrm;We've gotta capture
&lrm;the baddies' Akumas before...
&lrm;Actually, what do the baddies want?
&lrm;We want to win.
&lrm;Yeah, but win what?
&lrm;I dunno. What do they usually want?
&lrm;Depends...
&lrm;Lady Wi-Fi wanted to reveal
&lrm;Ladybug's identity.
&lrm;Evillustrator wanted revenge
&lrm;on a girl for mocking him.
&lrm;Then, there was Rogercop...
&lrm;But the evil Hawk Moth
&lrm;who makes them bad
&lrm;wants to take Ladybug's
&lrm;and Cat Noir's jewels,
&lrm;their Miraculouses.
&lrm;And what would happen
&lrm;if he did take them?
&lrm;The bad guys... would win.
&lrm;I know.
&lrm;I know what the bad guys want.
&lrm;We want the Miraculous,
&lrm;then we'll win, forever and ever!
&lrm;I'm gonna get your Miraculous,
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;You... you..
&lrm;goodie-two-shoeses!
&lrm;You'll be super-duper sorry.
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;You won't get our Miraculouses.
&lrm;Yeah?
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir have won again!
&lrm;No fair. You always win.
&lrm;[she cries]
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir always win.
&lrm;And the bad guys always lose.
&lrm;But you never let me play
&lrm;with Ladybug and Cat Noir!
&lrm;Don't cry.
&lrm;Of course you can play with them.
&lrm;I'll even let you borrow one of them.
&lrm;[Mrs. Chamack] I'm back.
&lrm;Have you been good?
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;Mommy! Marinette didn't let me win.
&lrm;She didn't play fair and square.
&lrm;Manon, you can't always expect to win.
&lrm;Yes you can.
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir always win.
&lrm;Well, you're right there
&lrm;but they're superheroes.
&lrm;You'll win next time, Manon.
&lrm;Now give the doll back to Marinette.
&lrm;[angrily] No! I wanna keep her!
&lrm;I told her she could borrow it.
&lrm;That's sweet of you,
&lrm;but she already has so many toys
&lrm;I wouldn't know where to put it.
&lrm;[she gasps] No!
&lrm;Look what you've done.
&lrm;Give it to me.
&lrm;[Manon sobs]
&lrm;[mother sighs] I'm sorry, Marinette.
&lrm;It's nothing. I can sew it up again.
&lrm;It's no problem.
&lrm;Thank goodness.
&lrm;Come on, Manon, say goodbye.
&lrm;I... want... that... doll!
&lrm;No. You can play with it here, next time.
&lrm;Come on, Manon,
&lrm;be a good girl and say goodbye.
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;[sulkily] Goodbye.
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;Hi, Alec.
&lrm;Didn't I leave it for you
&lrm;on my desk at the station?
&lrm;I left my bag up there, Mommy.
&lrm;Go quickly.
&lrm;It's not there?
&lrm;I think our heroes are in need
&lrm;of a little TLC.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Manon, what...?
&lrm;I left my bag.
&lrm;Can I have Ladybug?
&lrm;[she sighs] You heard what your mom said.
&lrm;She won't know if I hide it.
&lrm;Sorry, but I have to sew her up.
&lrm;Pretty please.
&lrm;Please, please, not the baby-doll eyes.
&lrm;[she whimpers]
&lrm;[sighing] Ok, you can borrow Lady Wi-Fi.
&lrm;Can I have the Ladybug doll?
&lrm;Hold on, Alec.
&lrm;Hurry, Manon!
&lrm;[mother] We have to stop by the station!
&lrm;Coming, Mommy!
&lrm;She sure had you wrapped
&lrm;around her little finger.
&lrm;What? No she...
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;You know, Tikki,
&lrm;I can't say no to those...
&lrm;[Tikki] Baby-doll eyes?
&lrm;Just be glad no baddies have them.
&lrm;You'd be rendered powerless.
&lrm;[Manon] Here I am, baddy.
&lrm;[pretend fighting]
&lrm;[triumphantly] I saved Paris again!
&lrm;No! No fair!
&lrm;You always win!
&lrm;Sorry, Alec, it must be in the studio.
&lrm;No sweat.
&lrm;Can you watch Manon?
&lrm;I won't be lon...
&lrm;Where are you hiding,
&lrm;Ladybug?
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;This is one of Marinette's dolls.
&lrm;You took it, after I specifically
&lrm;told you not to.
&lrm;But, but Marinette wanted me to have it.
&lrm;You disobeyed me.
&lrm;I told you they were to stay there.
&lrm;You won't need it anymore.
&lrm;No, Mommy, please don't.
&lrm;I'm not happy about this.
&lrm;Wait for me here.
&lrm;[frustrated sigh]
&lrm;[she huffs]
&lrm;I didn't steal that doll!
&lrm;I... want... that... doll!
&lrm;[satisfied sigh]
&lrm;What could be more pure
&lrm;than an innocent child's emotions,
&lrm;especially anger?
&lrm;I love it.
&lrm;Fly away, evil Akuma,
&lrm;and commiserate
&lrm;with this frustrated child.
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;The movie starts soon.
&lrm;Or we can buy your book
&lrm;and go to the next one.
&lrm;Either way.
&lrm;[she gasps] Marinette, 9 o'clock.
&lrm;There isn't one at 9.
&lrm;Not that 9 o'clock, this 9 o'clock.
&lrm;Adrien.
&lrm;Come on!
&lrm;[she squeals]
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;[Marinette] Sorry.
&lrm;[fluttering]
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;[evil voice] Puppeteer, I'm Hawk Moth.
&lrm;From now on, you can control anyone.
&lrm;Even Ladybug and Cat Noir?
&lrm;Yes, as long as you possess their dolls.
&lrm;And I can win?
&lrm;Yes, you will be able to win.
&lrm;But in return,
&lrm;you must do something for me.
&lrm;Bring you their Miraculouses.
&lrm;I know!
&lrm;What a smart little girl you are.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Wanna play a game?
&lrm;Help!
&lrm;I gotta get
&lrm;those Ladybug and Cat Noir dolls.
&lrm;I... want... those... dolls!
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;I'm sure I left it here.
&lrm;Where is it?
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Here it is.
&lrm;Sorry, Alec.
&lrm;Here's the file you need.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;I wonder where he gets off.
&lrm;Maybe he's going to the same movie.
&lrm;How cool would that be?
&lrm;But wait!
&lrm;Then he might think
&lrm;we're following him, like stalkers.
&lrm;Me? A stalker?
&lrm;Although I would follow him.
&lrm;I wouldn't really stalk him.
&lrm;[groaning] Who am I kidding?
&lrm;[Alya giggles] Who are you talking to?
&lrm;He's waving.
&lrm;Oh no, now what are we gonna do?
&lrm;Wave back.
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;OK, Lady Wi-Fi,
&lrm;come to life!
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;What's going on?
&lrm;Alya!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Marinette,
&lrm;gimme those Ladybug and Cat Noir dolls!
&lrm;Lady Wi-Fi?
&lrm;No! I'm Puppeteer.
&lrm;And I want... those... dolls, now!
&lrm;Puppeteer? The dolls?
&lrm;I don't have them, they're at home.
&lrm;Why do you want them, Puppeteer?
&lrm;Because you said I could have them.
&lrm;Then mommy said "No!"
&lrm;So giv'em to me now!
&lrm;Or you'll be super-duper sorry.
&lrm;Manon.
&lrm;I want Ladybug
&lrm;and Cat Noir's Miraculouses.
&lrm;To win... forever and ever.
&lrm;Manon, this isn't a game!
&lrm;Excuse me, Sir.
&lrm;There's a... a cat loose on the train.
&lrm;What? Thanks kiddo.
&lrm;[Plagg] Cat?
&lrm;Plagg, We have to transform.
&lrm;Just when we'd lost your bodyguard.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;What about the movie?
&lrm;The buttery popcorn!
&lrm;Tikki, I have to transform.
&lrm;That was Lady Wi-Fi.
&lrm;Did she say anything?
&lrm;I'm not sure,
&lrm;but... her voice belonged to
&lrm;a girl I babysit.
&lrm;It's as if she was controlling my friend,
&lrm;Alya,
&lrm;I mean Lady Wi-Fi, from a distance.
&lrm;This is so weird.
&lrm;What was all that about dolls?
&lrm;I've got some dolls
&lrm;she likes to play with.
&lrm;Your dolls? OK, where do you live?
&lrm;- 12, rue Gotlib.
&lrm;- I'll take care of it.
&lrm;I don't like the idea of Cat Noir
&lrm;rummaging around in my room.
&lrm;Just say the words.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[Ladybug] Hey, kitty!
&lrm;Up here!
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[Ladybug] Puppeteer! Such a shame.
&lrm;It's really not nice to steal
&lrm;from your babysitter.
&lrm;Breaking and entering are grounds
&lrm;for a time out.
&lrm;I'll get your Miraculouses,
&lrm;you goodie-two-shoeses.
&lrm;There's only one goodie-two-shoes here,
&lrm;and I'm not her.
&lrm;Freeze!
&lrm;Remember how
&lrm;we defeated her last time?
&lrm;Take out the Wi-Fi.
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Gotcha.
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] Nice move, Puppeteer.
&lrm;Good girl.
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] Now take her Miraculous!
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;[she gasps and groans]
&lrm;Looks like you've lost your signal, Wi-Fi
&lrm;Where's the Akuma?
&lrm;I want those dolls, Lady Wi-Fi!
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;- Did you get her Akuma?
&lrm;- She didn't have one.
&lrm;How come?
&lrm;She's controlled by Puppeteer,
&lrm;she must have it.
&lrm;Right. Lady Wi-Fi's just a puppet.
&lrm;Tell me you got my doll.
&lrm;Sorry... only this one.
&lrm;We better find her
&lrm;before she takes control of me.
&lrm;Your ring.
&lrm;You're about to turn back.
&lrm;Don't let her make me her puppet.
&lrm;I like to be in command.
&lrm;You mean second in command.
&lrm;Call me when you're back in business.
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;Yes? What? Ladybug?
&lrm;Where are you?
&lrm;At the TV station.
&lrm;Is Manon there?
&lrm;Yes, she's playing downstairs.
&lrm;Is everything okay?
&lrm;Yes, just don't move.
&lrm;I'll be right there.
&lrm;I'm gonna use these dolls
&lrm;to beat Ladybug fair and square.
&lrm;[Plagg] What? I'm savouring my cheese.
&lrm;Can you savour it faster?
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;She's still here.
&lrm;I need you all outside.
&lrm;No, I want to find my daughter.
&lrm;I'll bring her back, Mrs. Chamack.
&lrm;It'll help me more if I know you're safe.
&lrm;Evillustrator,
&lrm;come to life!
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;[he growls]
&lrm;Rogercop, come to life!
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Have you found her?
&lrm;At the TV station.
&lrm;Got it!
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;I'm OK. I'm not a puppet.
&lrm;Let's find the Akuma
&lrm;before that changes.
&lrm;Sorry.
&lrm;On three.
&lrm;One... two...
&lrm;three!
&lrm;Cat Noir, come to life!
&lrm;No!
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Cat Noir, no!
&lrm;Use Cat Noir to seize Ladybug's doll.
&lrm;Then you'll have won everything
&lrm;and Ladybug will be defeated.
&lrm;[together] Gimme that ladybug doll!
&lrm;I'm gonna get your Miraculous!
&lrm;Not so fast, rug rat.
&lrm;The Akuma must be in there.
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;Stop her!
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;Sorry, Cat Noir.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;One against five.
&lrm;That's not very fair and square.
&lrm;This is the moment I've been waiting for.
&lrm;Your time is up, Ladybug.
&lrm;You're doomed!
&lrm;The Ladybug doll!
&lrm;Get it!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Thanks, Evillustrator. Now, the doll.
&lrm;Is this what you want? Say pretty please.
&lrm;The doll. She got away with it.
&lrm;Get her!
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Where did she go?
&lrm;First I have to get rid of them,
&lrm;then Puppeteer.
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;If you want this doll so badly,
&lrm;come and get it.
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;I'm faster than you.
&lrm;You're going to lose, Ladybug.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[child gasps]
&lrm;Gimme that doll. It's mine!
&lrm;[child screams]
&lrm;I'll get you Ladybug.
&lrm;You'll be super-duper sorry.
&lrm;Now you're alone...
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Where is she?
&lrm;Now I'm the winner.
&lrm;Drop that doll, Manon!
&lrm;I'm not Manon, I'm Puppeteer.
&lrm;Luck charm!
&lrm;A power strip?
&lrm;[Puppeteer] You've lost, Ladybug!
&lrm;There may be 4 of you,
&lrm;but I'm twice as dangerous.
&lrm;[he roars]
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;[Rogercop groans]
&lrm;Ladybug...
&lrm;Freeze!
&lrm;Come to li...
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[whistling]
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you, little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;[gasps]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;What happened?
&lrm;You were a puppet
&lrm;but you didn't do anything foolish.
&lrm;Good, and Ladybug,
&lrm;FYI, you can pull
&lrm;my heart strings any day.
&lrm;I liked you better
&lrm;when you sounded like a 5-year-old.
&lrm;[angrily] No!
&lrm;This cannot be happening!
&lrm;[he groans angrily]
&lrm;[gasping] Manon!
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;Thank you, Ladybug. Thank you.
&lrm;It's time I bug out.
&lrm;[Marinette] I'm sorry about what happened,
&lrm;Mrs. Chamack.
&lrm;I shouldn't have given her
&lrm;the doll after you said no.
&lrm;Manon can be pretty persuasive.
&lrm;Yeah, with her...
&lrm;Baby-doll eyes? Yes, I know.
&lrm;See you later, then. Kiss, Manon.
&lrm;[chuckling]
&lrm;Bye, mommy.
&lrm;See you later, Mrs. Chamack.
&lrm;Bye-bye.
&lrm;I wanna play with Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;I've a better idea.
&lrm;Why don't we go to the zoo?
&lrm;But I want to play with the dolls.
&lrm;Pretty please.
&lrm;Don't even try it, Manon.
&lrm;I love the zoo.
&lrm;I'm ready.
&lrm;[giggling]