&lrm;In the daytime I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life&lrm;.
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;Agent Smith, it's too dangerous.
&lrm;We must evacuate!
&lrm;You're suggesting we run... Officer Jones?
&lrm;After it devoured my family, my friends,
&lrm;even my beloved dog, Sniffles?
&lrm;Never! I won't run... I no longer fear it.
&lrm;I'm going to face it...
&lrm;[shrieking] Cut!
&lrm;Sorry, Mylene.
&lrm;Mylene, that's like the 10th take,
&lrm;and it's only the 1st scene.
&lrm;[Alix] 14th actually, but who's counting?
&lrm;I'm sorry.
&lrm;I'm gonna do better
&lrm;on the next take, I promise.
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;[Rose] Anyone want tea?
&lrm;You're in the special forces.
&lrm;You don't get freaked out.
&lrm;I know but...
&lrm;that monster mask
&lrm;is so realistic and scary.
&lrm;Just big old me, Mylene.
&lrm;Nothing to be scared of.
&lrm;He doesn't even need a mask.
&lrm;What a bratty snob.
&lrm;Put the mask back on.
&lrm;You're playing a monster.
&lrm;Mylene, we need you to stay in character.
&lrm;I need to sing my happy song.
&lrm;It always makes me feel better.
&lrm;♪ Smelly wolf, smelly wolf
&lrm;Stinky breath and slimy... ♪
&lrm;And the Oscar for
&lrm;best pathetic scaredy-cat,
&lrm;afraid of its own shadow goes to
&lrm;[cackling] Mylene!
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;Chloe, seriously?
&lrm;Yeah, so what?
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;Mylene!
&lrm;Anyone going after her?
&lrm;Mylene, wait!
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;Don't listen to them. It's easy to judge
&lrm;when they're not in front of the camera.
&lrm;You're awesome.
&lrm;Come back, I'll roar more quietly.
&lrm;Here, it's from my favourite band,
&lrm;The Zombie Skull Crushers.
&lrm;Wow.
&lrm;That's really sweet of you, Ivan,
&lrm;but they're right,
&lrm;I can't act to save my life.
&lrm;[sobbing] Excuse me.
&lrm;[sobbing continues]
&lrm;[evil voice] A film shoot... Oh yes.
&lrm;So many emotions,
&lrm;some fake, yet others very... very real.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Fly away, my evil Akuma,
&lrm;and overpower this young,
&lrm;misunderstood artist.
&lrm;Epic, Chloe, just epic!
&lrm;What do we do without our lead actress?
&lrm;Who needs her? She was totally lame.
&lrm;[Ivan] You're lame!
&lrm;Mylene's crying her eyes out
&lrm;thanks to you.
&lrm;[Chloe] Me, lame?
&lrm;Hey, everyone chill out.
&lrm;You're right.
&lrm;[whispering] Chloe is lame.
&lrm;But fighting won't bring Mylene back.
&lrm;I'm the producer and I'll do all I can
&lrm;to finish filming tonight.
&lrm;The deadline
&lrm;for the Short Film Festival is
&lrm;tomorrow in precisely 26 hours,
&lrm;15 minutes and...
&lrm;13 seconds from now.
&lrm;Thank you, Max.
&lrm;We still have editing, post-sound,...
&lrm;Who's gonna take Mylene's part?
&lrm;Me, of course.
&lrm;You haven't read the script.
&lrm;Of course I have...
&lrm;The first scene anyway.
&lrm;It ends with a kiss
&lrm;between Agent Smith and Officer Jones.
&lrm;[she shrieks]
&lrm;You wrote that?
&lrm;Hold up.
&lrm;I didn't write that.
&lrm;I wrote it. It was just a little tweak
&lrm;to move the story forward.
&lrm;What? You edited my script
&lrm;without even telling me?
&lrm;That's low!
&lrm;[she growls] You mean our script.
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;-Juice?
&lrm;-Thanks, Rose.
&lrm;Who cares who wrote what?
&lrm;We've got to film this thing right?
&lrm;She's right.
&lrm;We can only use the school until 6pm sharp
&lrm;which leaves us 9 hours, 12 minutes
&lrm;and 12 seconds, 11, 10, 9, 8...
&lrm;[Max counts down]
&lrm;Adrien and Chloe kissing
&lrm;cannot happen... No way!
&lrm;It makes no sense story-wise anyway.
&lrm;The main character's...
&lrm;Hold on.
&lrm;We can't just let Mylene leave.
&lrm;It's wrong.
&lrm;We all chose her to play
&lrm;the lead female role
&lrm;and we're all in this movie together.
&lrm;She needs our support.
&lrm;I'm gonna find her and bring her back.
&lrm;Always trying to save the day,
&lrm;aren't you, Marinette?
&lrm;Good luck finding the filthy hole
&lrm;that scaredy-cat's hiding in.
&lrm;[Marinette growls]
&lrm;Why are you so intimidated
&lrm;and scared all the time?
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;[evil voice] Horrificator, I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Up until now, you have felt fear.
&lrm;From now on, you will cause fear.
&lrm;And after you've shown them
&lrm;how they make you feel,
&lrm;you'll do something for me in return.
&lrm;[evil voice] Yes, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;[bubbling]
&lrm;[Marinette] Mylene!
&lrm;Mylene?
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;[Alya] Marinette!
&lrm;Did you find Mylene?
&lrm;No.
&lrm;You'd better come ASAP.
&lrm;There's some serious lip-puckering
&lrm;about to get going on.
&lrm;Time for you to use
&lrm;your scare tactics, Horrificator...
&lrm;and thrive!
&lrm;Horrificator, take 15.
&lrm;Action!
&lrm;I'm not scared
&lrm;of that Horrificator thingy,
&lrm;Officer Whatever-your-name-is.
&lrm;Now kiss me.
&lrm;Cut!
&lrm;Marinette, what gives?
&lrm;We're in the middle of a shoot
&lrm;and I'm the director, FYI.
&lrm;I say "cut," no-one else, comprende?
&lrm;And I'm the producer.
&lrm;Mylene's supposed to be the star.
&lrm;We're out of time.
&lrm;And for what I can see, Mylene is MIA.
&lrm;From the top.
&lrm;Here we go again.
&lrm;Agent Smith doesn't need
&lrm;a man in her life.
&lrm;Sniffles just got munched on.
&lrm;Do you wanna finish this film or not?
&lrm;Let's make Agent Smith a nurse instead.
&lrm;That'll fix everything.
&lrm;Sorry, but how exactly?
&lrm;I don't know
&lrm;but I'll look amazing in a uniform.
&lrm;We're not rewriting
&lrm;the script again!
&lrm;"Alya" is not going on those credits!
&lrm;[Chloe] Nobody cares!
&lrm;[Ayla] What?
&lrm;Everyone calm down.
&lrm;This movie's a team effort.
&lrm;Your nurse idea is perfect, Chloe.
&lrm;Of course it is because it's mine.
&lrm;But Chloe, you don't have a uniform.
&lrm;Which is why
&lrm;that idea was never believable.
&lrm;You should go to the nurse's office
&lrm;and try on some uniforms.
&lrm;[fingers click] Kim, Max, come!
&lrm;You've been promoted
&lrm;to wardrobe and bodyguard.
&lrm;Nice going, Miss Producer,
&lrm;now we have no lead again.
&lrm;Yeah, but now we've got rid of Chloe.
&lrm;And now what?
&lrm;We go find Mylene. She's here somewhere.
&lrm;I told you, tick-toc, there's no time.
&lrm;-We need a lead, now!
&lrm;-Marinette can do it.
&lrm;What? No! I can't act. I'm the producer.
&lrm;But you wanna kiss Adrien, don't you?
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;Yes, but not like this.
&lrm;A nurse's uniform, how brilliant am I?
&lrm;Even that dimwit,
&lrm;Marinette, liked the idea.
&lrm;[swishing]
&lrm;I'm only doing this as a favour.
&lrm;When Mylene returns
&lrm;she'll have her role back.
&lrm;Of course she will, chill out.
&lrm;And just think, after tonight,
&lrm;you'll finally have kissed Adrien.
&lrm;[Marinette squeals]
&lrm;Hey, wait a minute.
&lrm;Marinette never likes my ideas,
&lrm;I think you've all been duped.
&lrm;You guys take care of the uniform
&lrm;just in case.
&lrm;-Did you hear something?
&lrm;-No, what?
&lrm;Totally unbelievable.
&lrm;What's that?
&lrm;I said...
&lrm;It's got to be believable.
&lrm;Don't worry. You'll do fine.
&lrm;Ready to roll? Camera...
&lrm;Horrificator, take 16.
&lrm;Action!
&lrm;I'm not scared of that monster,
&lrm;Officer Jones.
&lrm;Cut! I knew it.
&lrm;What did I say about people saying "cut"?
&lrm;Well played, Marinette.
&lrm;All that speech on working together,
&lrm;Then you stab me in the back!
&lrm;Your stupid movie won't get
&lrm;into the festival if I'm not in it
&lrm;because my daddy
&lrm;is one of the judges!
&lrm;[horrific screaming]
&lrm;Did you hear that?
&lrm;If this is one of your silly ploys
&lrm;to get rid of me
&lrm;you can forget it, besides...
&lrm;[horrific screaming]
&lrm;I definitely heard that.
&lrm;We'd better scope this out.
&lrm;A snack for the road?
&lrm;Hey! Anybody here? Kim? Max?
&lrm;Where are you?
&lrm;I saw the same pink goo in the bathroom.
&lrm;That's Kim's.
&lrm;They've vanished.
&lrm;Or they're playing a sick joke.
&lrm;We should tell Principle Damocles
&lrm;what's going on.
&lrm;Nino, come on, stop filming.
&lrm;No way. This is just getting good.
&lrm;Looks like it's time
&lrm;to bring in the alter ego.
&lrm;Yo, Adrien, where you going?
&lrm;I left Officer Jones's jacket.
&lrm;She'll probably wear it in all the scenes.
&lrm;[snarling]
&lrm;[splodging]
&lrm;Time to transform, Plagg.
&lrm;What are you doing?
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;They'll think I've disappeared too.
&lrm;[Plagg] And you say I stink of camembert.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[knocking] Mr Damocles? Sir?
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[Rose] Even Principle Damocles is missing.
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;Anyone seen Agent Smith?
&lrm;I mean, Marinette.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Oh on. This is Marinette's phone.
&lrm;[grunting]
&lrm;Quick, check the windows.
&lrm;Crazy.
&lrm;We're trapped. I'm calling daddy.
&lrm;Dudes, phones never work in horror movies.
&lrm;-No bars.
&lrm;-No coverage.
&lrm;Told you so. Boo-ya!
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Is everything OK?
&lrm;Ladybug in my movie, this is legit.
&lrm;And on my Ladyblog.
&lrm;We've got to evacuate the building, OK?
&lrm;No...
&lrm;That's easier said than done.
&lrm;Double legit!
&lrm;I tried to cut through it
&lrm;but it's totally indestructible.
&lrm;So we're trapped inside for now.
&lrm;Stay put and try to relax.
&lrm;Let's take a stroll.
&lrm;We know Hawk Moth's taken
&lrm;another victim in this school.
&lrm;There's one way to get rid of
&lrm;this goo and free everyone...
&lrm;capture that Akuma.
&lrm;Exactly,
&lrm;I love it when you read my mind.
&lrm;We'd better find this thing first
&lrm;and its prisoners.
&lrm;Wow, you did it again.
&lrm;Don't mind me.
&lrm;Finding missing peeps,
&lrm;solving a mystery,
&lrm;with Cat Noir and Ladybug!
&lrm;This movie's gonna be so swank.
&lrm;Stay together, right behind us.
&lrm;You too, Spielberg.
&lrm;[snarling]
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;[he squeals]
&lrm;Absorb their fear,
&lrm;Horrificator, feed on it!
&lrm;It will give you strength.
&lrm;And soon enough,
&lrm;you'll be giving me strength too.
&lrm;We're better off on our own
&lrm;than with the others.
&lrm;Why stay with them
&lrm;when we can hide on our own?
&lrm;There!
&lrm;Anyone recognise that shoe?
&lrm;That's Adrien's shoe.
&lrm;That's weird, there's no pink slime.
&lrm;Yes, there is.
&lrm;[snarling]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;Everybody, run!
&lrm;Awesome.
&lrm;So awesome.
&lrm;[she chuckles]
&lrm;[disgusted sigh]
&lrm;What's your name, Drool-ator?
&lrm;Cat's aren't afraid
&lrm;of slimy toads like you.
&lrm;We'd better find that Akuma.
&lrm;I see nothing but miles of slime.
&lrm;Help!
&lrm;Fear, it's fear
&lrm;that gives it its strength.
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;[fearful cries]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;It's taken Nath' and Alix.
&lrm;The more people are scared of it
&lrm;the more powerful it gets.
&lrm;By defeating fear, we defeat it.
&lrm;First we've got to get out
&lrm;of this sticky situation
&lrm;before it dries.
&lrm;[she squeals]
&lrm;Did you see how it left Ivan alone?
&lrm;Yeah, what's that all about?
&lrm;I think the monster is Mylene.
&lrm;Where are Sabrina and Chloe?
&lrm;We'll find them...
&lrm;If we can find a way out.
&lrm;It's a good thing
&lrm;I come up with brilliant ideas.
&lrm;No-one's gonna get through that barricade.
&lrm;We can relax
&lrm;and let them do the hard work.
&lrm;[Sabrina yelps]
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;We're too late.
&lrm;But look,
&lrm;we can track the monster.
&lrm;[Nino giggles]
&lrm;Oh, yeah, I'm so amped!
&lrm;-Turn you amp down, will you?
&lrm;-My bad.
&lrm;Their fear will make you powerful enough
&lrm;to defeat Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;Get their Miraculouses!
&lrm;Anybody here?
&lrm;Ladybug, it's me,
&lrm;Chloe Bourgeois!
&lrm;Don't worry, we'll get you out.
&lrm;Well hurry up already!
&lrm;Is everyone here?
&lrm;[muffled] Yes!
&lrm;-Mr Damocles?
&lrm;-Present.
&lrm;-Alix? Nathaniel?
&lrm;-Yeah!
&lrm;Adrien?
&lrm;Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
&lrm;[relieved sigh]
&lrm;What about Marinette?
&lrm;Yeah, we've got everyone.
&lrm;They won't budge.
&lrm;Get us out!
&lrm;Calm down. We'll get you out.
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;OK, now this is getting scary.
&lrm;Lucky Charm!
&lrm;Guitar strings, are you kidding me?
&lrm;Guitar, music... Mylene's song.
&lrm;That's it. Enough is enough.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;OK, we're all going to sing.
&lrm;Sing? So that's your plan.
&lrm;The only way is to get
&lrm;your fear under control.
&lrm;Do you all know Smelly Wolf?
&lrm;Seriously? Smelly Wolf?
&lrm;Care to join us?
&lrm;OK, everyone,
&lrm;1, 2, 3, 4,
&lrm;♪ Smelly wolf, smelly wolf ♪
&lrm;♪ Trapped in a stinky hut ♪
&lrm;♪ Smelly wolf, smelly wolf
&lrm;I'm gonna kick your... ♪
&lrm;Stinky breath and slimey drool ♪
&lrm;♪ Smelly wolf, smelly wolf
&lrm;You're just a silly... ♪
&lrm;[calm growl]
&lrm;Wow, it's working.
&lrm;[excited squeaks]
&lrm;[purring]
&lrm;That's the button I gave Mylene.
&lrm;That's where the Akuma is.
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you, Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;Pound it!
&lrm;[Nino] Awesome.
&lrm;You don't scare me, Ladybug!
&lrm;I'll destroy you in the end,
&lrm;someday, somehow... I'll destroy you!
&lrm;What do you think, Mr Mayor?
&lrm;Off the hook right?
&lrm;We didn't make the cut.
&lrm;He said the monster
&lrm;was a horrible replica, no joke!
&lrm;Don't worry,
&lrm;this is how all movie directors start.
&lrm;Yeah, even if that final kiss
&lrm;wasn't quite what we expected.