&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life.
&lrm;But there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;Yes, I'm in the middle
&lrm;of something important.
&lrm;What do you want?
&lrm;What? This is unacceptable!
&lrm;The sample garment doesn't match.
&lrm;All you had to do
&lrm;was follow a pattern, imbeciles.
&lrm;What am I supposed to do?
&lrm;The show is in 3 days.
&lrm;No, he's completely useless.
&lrm;Call my assistant, Nathalie.
&lrm;She'll give you some other names.
&lrm;He hides stuff
&lrm;behind the painting of mom?
&lrm;[Plagg]
&lrm;I love dirty secrets.
&lrm;[Plagg excitedly]
&lrm;Yes, go, go on.
&lrm;I can't.
&lrm;My dad will be angry.
&lrm;I don't know the code,
&lrm;and I have fencing class.
&lrm;[Plagg]
&lrm;You party-pooper.
&lrm;Plagg, no!
&lrm;[Plagg]
&lrm;My my, what have we got here?
&lrm;A book on Tibet, a hotel flyer,
&lrm;a load of old junk.
&lrm;Come on! Where's the good stuff?
&lrm;[Plagg]
&lrm;I've seen this book before.
&lrm;But who cares? I'm famished.
&lrm;I need camembert!
&lrm;Why does my dad keep
&lrm;this in a safe?
&lrm;[gasping] Hawk Moth?
&lrm;Why is a monster
&lrm;in a book of superheroes?
&lrm;[Plagg] Cheese! Didn't you hear me?
&lrm;[footsteps]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[approaching footsteps]
&lrm;Adrien, you're going to be late.
&lrm;I was looking for my homework.
&lrm;Silly me.
&lrm;[Rose] Can you believe it?
&lrm;Lila knows Prince Ali?
&lrm;She even flew in his private jet.
&lrm;Why did Jagged Stone write a song
&lrm;about Lila and not me?
&lrm;Lila knows all
&lrm;the Hollywood directors.
&lrm;She said she'd mention me
&lrm;to Mr Besielberg.
&lrm;-Lila?
&lrm;-Yeah,
&lrm;she just started here.
&lrm;She gave me an interview.
&lrm;Ladybug saved her life once.
&lrm;Who is this girl?
&lrm;What's she doing next to my love?
&lrm;Lila's got the most incredible life.
&lrm;And now she's going here.
&lrm;She's totally awesome.
&lrm;What? Don't say that.
&lrm;This is super-bad.
&lrm;What if he falls for her?
&lrm;I've never flown in a jet.
&lrm;Nobody's written a song about me
&lrm;and I don't know anyone in Hollywood.
&lrm;He'll forget I exist!
&lrm;Where are they going?
&lrm;Alya, we've gotta stop them.
&lrm;You need to chill out.
&lrm;My Ladyblog had the most hits ever
&lrm;after that interview.
&lrm;What's going on?
&lrm;Has this girl hypnotized everyone?
&lrm;Are you jealous, Marinette?
&lrm;Me? Jealous?
&lrm;No way.
&lrm;Where is she?
&lrm;Marinette, Adrien's book!
&lrm;I need a closer look.
&lrm;Why are you
&lrm;so concerned about his book? Hide!
&lrm;Now we can do our homework.
&lrm;It's more fun doing it together.
&lrm;[gasping] What's that?
&lrm;Nothing, just stories about...
&lrm;superheroes.
&lrm;[seductively] I love superheroes.
&lrm;No, it's already too late!
&lrm;[questioning sighs]
&lrm;Ladybug?
&lrm;[Adrien sighs]
&lrm;She's amazing.
&lrm;A girl doesn't need to wear
&lrm;a costume to be amazing, you know?
&lrm;I don't know...
&lrm;So, you've got
&lrm;a soft spot for the bug?
&lrm;Me?
&lrm;No, not at all.
&lrm;You know,
&lrm;I happen to be friends with Ladybug.
&lrm;Really?
&lrm;We can chat about it but not here.
&lrm;Let's meet in the park after school.
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;[she yelps]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[sigh of relief]
&lrm;[phone vibrates]
&lrm;I gotta go.
&lrm;I've got a lesson in 58 seconds.
&lrm;So... the park?
&lrm;Sure.
&lrm;A vixen superheroin...?
&lrm;Interesting.
&lrm;[Tikki gasps] Marinette.
&lrm;I know. I've gotta talk to Adrien
&lrm;before he meets Lila.
&lrm;He has to know she's a thief.
&lrm;No. You can't say anything.
&lrm;I need to check out the book first.
&lrm;If it's what I think, we have to get it.
&lrm;I don't get it.
&lrm;Why do we need it?
&lrm;I'll explain when I'm sure.
&lrm;We mustn't let Lila out of our sight.
&lrm;Ladybug and me? We're like this.
&lrm;Liar.
&lrm;[Tikki] There. She's coming out.
&lrm;[Tikki sighs] We're too far away.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Hi.
&lrm;Oh no! He's already here.
&lrm;She dumped the book in the bin.
&lrm;What a brat.
&lrm;-I'll get it.
&lrm;-No.
&lrm;I have to get it.
&lrm;You take care of Adrien.
&lrm;Tikki...
&lrm;[Adrien]
&lrm;So you do know Ladybug, for real?
&lrm;This is the book, Marinette.
&lrm;Not only did Ladybug save my life,
&lrm;we've become close friends.
&lrm;We've something special in common.
&lrm;It's what I wanted to tell you about.
&lrm;I'm the descendant
&lrm;of a vixen superheroine, Volpina.
&lrm;Volpina?
&lrm;I read about her in my book.
&lrm;Of course she's in it.
&lrm;She's one
&lrm;of the most important superheroes,
&lrm;and more powerful than Ladybug.
&lrm;Ladybug doesn't even make the top 10.
&lrm;My grandma gave me this necklace.
&lrm;[Tikki] She's good, really good.
&lrm;You've got your book.
&lrm;I can't lose Adrien.
&lrm;Time to transform!
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;Are you telling me
&lrm;this is a... Miraculous?
&lrm;Hey, Lila. How's it going?
&lrm;Long time no see.
&lrm;I saw your interview.
&lrm;Awesome job.
&lrm;Sure, I remember when I saved your life
&lrm;We've been good friends
&lrm;ever since, practically BFFs.
&lrm;Actually, when did I save your life?
&lrm;I don't recall.
&lrm;Yes, of course, now I remember...
&lrm;Never!
&lrm;And we're not friends either.
&lrm;Miss Show-off was trying
&lrm;to impress you and everyone else.
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;So you're not a descendant
&lrm;of a superhero?
&lrm;More like a super-liar.
&lrm;How dare you!
&lrm;Wait... Lila...
&lrm;What was that all about?
&lrm;I mean... weren't you a bit harsh?
&lrm;I don't put up with lies
&lrm;especially when they're about me.
&lrm;What is with you, Ladybug?
&lrm;I may have gone overboard,
&lrm;but at least I'm not dealing
&lrm;with her anymore.
&lrm;My chances with Adrien... Gone!
&lrm;I hate you, Ladybug.
&lrm;[she growls]
&lrm;Jealousy, deceit,
&lrm;and the desire to be a superhero.
&lrm;This young lady is my perfect prey.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Fly, my evil little one,
&lrm;and akumatise her!
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Volpina... I am Hawk Moth!
&lrm;I'm giving you the power of illusion.
&lrm;From now on your lies will come to life.
&lrm;Gain Ladybug and Cat Noir's trust
&lrm;and convince them you're a superhero.
&lrm;Then, betray them
&lrm;and bring me their Miraculous!
&lrm;It would be my pleasure, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;[bubbling]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;Code red!
&lrm;[Ladybug gasps]
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;[squawking]
&lrm;[cooing]
&lrm;I am Volpina,
&lrm;the only superhero Paris needs.
&lrm;[cheering] Volpina, Volpina!
&lrm;[chanting] Volpina, Volpina!
&lrm;Volpina?
&lrm;-We've got a new partner.
&lrm;-Isn't it weird?
&lrm;A superhero appearing out of nowhere?
&lrm;[Cat Noir] At least she got the job done.
&lrm;I could have stopped the meteorite.
&lrm;Hey, relax.
&lrm;I'm just saying she seems awesome.
&lrm;Hey, glad you dropped in.
&lrm;I need a hand. Come on.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[Cat Noir] I can't believe it,
&lrm;it's Hawk Moth, in the flesh.
&lrm;He never shows up.
&lrm;Something big is going on.
&lrm;We can take him down
&lrm;but it'll take all of us.
&lrm;We better make the most of our talents.
&lrm;Count on us.
&lrm;Very nice to meet you, Cat Noir.
&lrm;Cool outfit.
&lrm;Why thanks. You too.
&lrm;[gagging]
&lrm;First the meteorite,
&lrm;now Hawk Moth appearing,
&lrm;on the same day?
&lrm;Isn't that unusual?
&lrm;Why would you say that?
&lrm;I was asking Cat Noir.
&lrm;I'm finding you unusual today,
&lrm;everything OK?
&lrm;I'm fine, just fine.
&lrm;Volpina, what's your Miraculous?
&lrm;My necklace.
&lrm;-What power does it give you?
&lrm;-Flight and super-strength.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;He's getting away!
&lrm;Ladybug, go left. Cat Noir, go right.
&lrm;I'll come from... behind.
&lrm;No! I'll go right,
&lrm;Cat Noir from behind,
&lrm;and you... go left.
&lrm;Fine.
&lrm;-No difference to me.
&lrm;-Good.
&lrm;[Volpina roars]
&lrm;Can you chill out?
&lrm;She's one of us.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;He's running right into my trap.
&lrm;Where did he go?
&lrm;I'll take him.
&lrm;Good, now that other one.
&lrm;Where did he go?
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;I wouldn't move an inch if I were you.
&lrm;Don't worry,
&lrm;I don't want to be your friend.
&lrm;But now we won't be able to say
&lrm;you don't know me.
&lrm;Lila?
&lrm;You'll call me Volpina!
&lrm;You're not a superhero.
&lrm;You're one of Hawk Moth's victims.
&lrm;Everyone thinks I'm a superhero,
&lrm;including Cat Noir.
&lrm;So you won't be able
&lrm;to call me a liar anymore,
&lrm;because everyone will think
&lrm;you're the liar.
&lrm;Volpina, take Ladybug's Miraculous,
&lrm;her earring. Now!
&lrm;Before I get rid of you,
&lrm;you're going to give me
&lrm;your Miraculous.
&lrm;Never!
&lrm;Do you really think
&lrm;you've got a choice, Ladybug?
&lrm;Either you give me the Miraculous
&lrm;or the building goes down!
&lrm;You wouldn't.
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;Stop!
&lrm;[rumbling]
&lrm;It's an illusion,
&lrm;like the meteorite, like Hawk Moth.
&lrm;That's your power, isn't it?
&lrm;[Ladybug] Illusion, lies,
&lrm;Of course.
&lrm;[popping]
&lrm;[she roars]
&lrm;[whizzing]
&lrm;Of course.
&lrm;Is Volpina with you?
&lrm;No, I can't find Hawk Moth either.
&lrm;He was never there.
&lrm;What? But we saw him?
&lrm;That's Volpina's power.
&lrm;She creates illusions.
&lrm;Hawk Moth wasn't real.
&lrm;What are you saying?
&lrm;She's not a superhero.
&lrm;She was akumatised by Hawk Moth.
&lrm;-I don't get it. Why?
&lrm;-&lrm;I think it's my fault.
&lrm;I ruined her chances
&lrm;with a guy she likes.
&lrm;Lila?
&lrm;She's going to his house.
&lrm;I'll send the address, meet me there.
&lrm;You got it.
&lrm;I think I know the way.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Wouldn't Cat Noir be more useful?
&lrm;If Volpina's got a thing for me,
&lrm;I can make her see sense.
&lrm;You think you can take down Volpina...
&lrm;without me?
&lrm;Hide, Plagg. She's coming.
&lrm;Adrien,
&lrm;Hey. Who are you?
&lrm;You remember this necklace?
&lrm;I didn't know how to tell you
&lrm;but this way you can see I'm not lying,
&lrm;I am a superhero.
&lrm;-Lila?
&lrm;-You can call me Volpina.
&lrm;I'm sorry about the park earlier.
&lrm;Ladybug's jealous
&lrm;because she's not as powerful as me.
&lrm;You'll see Ladybug isn't just
&lrm;a figment of your imagination.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;What is he doing?
&lrm;No time to hang around.
&lrm;See what I mean?
&lrm;She's jealous of me... of you, of us.
&lrm;But this time
&lrm;you won't ruin our date, Ladybug.
&lrm;Excuse me but it wasn't really a date...
&lrm;I mean, it could've become one, right?
&lrm;[Cat Noir] No need to get angry.
&lrm;Excuse us,
&lrm;I need a chat with Super-liar.
&lrm;You! Stop thinking
&lrm;your illusions are reality.
&lrm;[Plagg] So, was I right, or was I right?
&lrm;Come on. Claws out!
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Sorry.
&lrm;I had trouble finding the place.
&lrm;Illusions?
&lrm;Cat Noir, she's taken Adrien!
&lrm;-It's an illusion.
&lrm;-How are you so sure?
&lrm;My feline sixth sense. It's legendary.
&lrm;Really? You don't say. Adrien's gone!
&lrm;I'm not gonna try to get outta this.
&lrm;[she cackles]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Give me your Miraculous now,
&lrm;or I will.
&lrm;I thought you loved him.
&lrm;Not as much as seeing you two defeated.
&lrm;No hard feelings.
&lrm;It's a bluff. It's an illusion.
&lrm;You wanna bet on that?
&lrm;[humming]
&lrm;No!
&lrm;Don't do it, Ladybug.
&lrm;[she growls]
&lrm;There she is!
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;I've got an idea to take down Volpina.
&lrm;-With a chocolate ice-lolly?
&lrm;-Trust me.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;[crumbling]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[Ladybug] Trapped, like a fox.
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;Your days are over, Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;-Lila?
&lrm;-Ladybug?
&lrm;I totally overreacted
&lrm;and never should have spoken
&lrm;to you like that. I'm sorry.
&lrm;Forget it, Ladybug, you were right,
&lrm;we'll never be friends.
&lrm;[Cat Noir] That hurts.
&lrm;She's still angry...
&lrm;You're not done with Volpina yet, Ladybug.
&lrm;You haven't seen the last of her!
&lrm;There's one problem
&lrm;Where's Adrien?
&lrm;Everything's back to normal,
&lrm;so he must be back at home.
&lrm;I should check.
&lrm;No! I'll go.
&lrm;You're about to change back.
&lrm;[bleeping] So are you.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;No arguing. I'll take care of it.
&lrm;[he sighs] That stubbornness.
&lrm;It's so... so...
&lrm;irresistible.
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;Adrien?
&lrm;Are you there?
&lrm;Can I come in?
&lrm;This is Ladybug.
&lrm;Is everything OK?
&lrm;Yeah. Needed a shower
&lrm;-after all the excitement.
&lrm;-OK...
&lrm;Sure.
&lrm;-Sorry, I'll be off then.
&lrm;-Thank you.
&lrm;[they sigh]
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;This book could have been
&lrm;my connection to Adrien
&lrm;without my mask for once.
&lrm;But I get it,
&lrm;I'm not gonna be returning it.
&lrm;I'm sorry, Marinette,
&lrm;but its information is invaluable.
&lrm;Information? But it's all in code.
&lrm;Someone's been looking
&lrm;for it for a long time.
&lrm;He knows how to decipher it.
&lrm;What's so special about this book?
&lrm;It contains all the secrets
&lrm;of the Miraculous powers.
&lrm;It's dangerous in the wrong hands.
&lrm;He needs it back.
&lrm;I don't get it, Tikki.
&lrm;Tell me what's going on. Who is he?
&lrm;The Great Guardian.
&lrm;I think the time has come
&lrm;for you to meet him.
&lrm;Did you take my book?
&lrm;[chewing] Of course not.
&lrm;If he finds out
&lrm;it'll be worse than dealing
&lrm;with Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Hello, Ladybug.