&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life.
&lrm;But there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[sigh of relief] That was close.
&lrm;What you did for Alya
&lrm;was very cool, Marinette
&lrm;You think?
&lrm;I'd have liked to do more but...
&lrm;[Sabine] &lrm;Marinette, Alya's here!
&lrm;[Alya] &lrm;Don't worry, I'll just head up.
&lrm;She didn't wait long
&lrm;to tell me the big news.
&lrm;Hide, Tikki, quick.
&lrm;Girl, you will not believe
&lrm;what just happened to me!
&lrm;Ladybug saved some workers
&lrm;from a villain.
&lrm;Millions of reporters
&lrm;were waiting to interview her.
&lrm;And that's when it happened!
&lrm;[reporter]
&lrm;Please, Ladybug, just a few words.
&lrm;Hey, are you Alya
&lrm;the girl with the blog about me?
&lrm;The Ladyblog?
&lrm;Y-Yeah.
&lrm;I like your work.
&lrm;It's awesome. Keep it up.
&lrm;Your earring, Ladybug.
&lrm;Thanks. Better get going. Bug out.
&lrm;That was super...
&lrm;Cool, right?
&lrm;Ladybug knows me. My blog!
&lrm;She thinks it's awesome,
&lrm;awesome!
&lrm;Yeah, that's... awesome.
&lrm;Let me grab my laptop.
&lrm;You're right, Tikki.
&lrm;I think it made her a little happy.
&lrm;-Can I see the video?
&lrm;-OK, but fast.
&lrm;[she squeals]
&lrm;You thought I was going to drop it.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[Tikki] Video deleted!
&lrm;Tell me I didn't just do that.
&lrm;You didn't just do that.
&lrm;OK, you did.
&lrm;At least you didn't drop it.
&lrm;I really screwed up this time.
&lrm;Alya's gonna kill me.
&lrm;It's not the end of the world.
&lrm;Alya will understand.
&lrm;She is your best friend.
&lrm;You're right.
&lrm;[cheerful muttering]
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;-On second thoughts...
&lrm;-Who are you talking to?
&lrm;To... to a pigeon.
&lrm;Say hello to Alya, Jacques.
&lrm;Say bye-bye, Jacques. Come down.
&lrm;You've got visitors.
&lrm;What's the name of the play is,
&lrm;Mr. Haprele?
&lrm;It's...
&lrm;It's called, "The Mime's
&lrm;Extraordinary Adventures"
&lrm;starring the most talented
&lrm;awesome actor and mime.
&lrm;Come on now...
&lrm;My father!
&lrm;Give it up for Fred Haprele.
&lrm;Thank you. Thank you, Mylene.
&lrm;Well, congratulations.
&lrm;She must be very proud.
&lrm;All I need is my hat
&lrm;to complete my costume.
&lrm;Here it is.
&lrm;Thank you, Marinette,
&lrm;saving me at the last minute.
&lrm;[Marinette giggles]
&lrm;I don't think
&lrm;Mylene was exaggerating at all.
&lrm;Thank you.
&lrm;I fixed the tear in it.
&lrm;I also sewed the pocket
&lrm;on the inside.
&lrm;That's perfect.
&lrm;Thanks to you,
&lrm;I'll have my good luck charm
&lrm;with me all the time.
&lrm;A photo of my daughter.
&lrm;Oh, dad.
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;Hello...
&lrm;[shouting] &lrm;Where are you?
&lrm;-I had to get my hat.
&lrm;-&lrm;I need you now!
&lrm;I know.
&lrm;The bus leaves in half an hour.
&lrm;I'll be there.
&lrm;That was the play's director.
&lrm;She's nervous about the premiere.
&lrm;She's ready to blow a fuse.
&lrm;I better get going.
&lrm;-See you tonight, girls.
&lrm;-We can't wait.
&lrm;Love you, dad.
&lrm;What's his excuse this time?
&lrm;He said had to get his hat
&lrm;from a repair shop.
&lrm;Well, he's a convincing actor.
&lrm;Actually, he is a great actor,
&lrm;but he makes excuses for being late...
&lrm;For falling asleep during rehearsals.
&lrm;for leaving early,
&lrm;for missing parts of his costume.
&lrm;Come on, Sarah,
&lrm;when are you going to wake up?
&lrm;But it's up to you
&lrm;if you want the show to suffer.
&lrm;Look, you're his understudy.
&lrm;Be ready to replace him
&lrm;just in case, okay?
&lrm;I won't let you down, Sarah.
&lrm;Thanks.
&lrm;[he chuckles]
&lrm;Thanks, I gotta go.
&lrm;I want to change before the show.
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;Hey, that's my ringtone.
&lrm;[Marinette giggles nervously]
&lrm;Gimme.
&lrm;It's my mom, I'll call her back.
&lrm;Mylene, you wanna see a cool video?
&lrm;No!
&lrm;You wouldn't want her to be late
&lrm;for her dad's show.
&lrm;Marinette's right, I gotta go.
&lrm;OK, I'll go with you
&lrm;and show you on the way.
&lrm;Wait, your bag's open.
&lrm;All good. See ya.
&lrm;-Bye.
&lrm;[sigh of relief]
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;Sarah, I'm early. I'm around the corner.
&lrm;No, it's Chris.
&lrm;Sarah asked me to call you
&lrm;about a location change.
&lrm;The bus is picking us up
&lrm;in 10 minutes at the Louvre.
&lrm;That's on the other side of town.
&lrm;Yes, but it's closer
&lrm;to the Eiffel Tower.
&lrm;Well... OK.
&lrm;Luckily, I'll just make it on time.
&lrm;Thanks for telling me.
&lrm;Sure, see you there.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[Alya] I'm off this way.
&lrm;OK, see you.
&lrm;Wait, I have to show you
&lrm;my awesome vid...
&lrm;Where's my phone?
&lrm;You stole Alya's phone?
&lrm;I... I borrowed it.
&lrm;Look, all I need to do is
&lrm;transform into Ladybug
&lrm;and film myself doing
&lrm;the exact same thing.
&lrm;Then I'll give it back.
&lrm;I don't know.
&lrm;Maybe it's better to come clean now.
&lrm;You might be digging a bigger hole.
&lrm;I can handle this.
&lrm;Fine, but don't say I didn't warn you.
&lrm;[phone vibrates]
&lrm;-Hi, Mylene.
&lrm;-&lrm;Do you have Alya's phone?
&lrm;Alya's phone?
&lrm;Got it. The silly girl dropped it.
&lrm;[Alya] &lrm;I'm here too.
&lrm;Hi, Alya. You're on speaker-phone?
&lrm;OK, I'll give it to you at the show.
&lrm;See ya.
&lrm;Don't look at me like that.
&lrm;It'll all work out,
&lrm;I think.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;We have to go for dress rehearsals.
&lrm;Wait any longer and you'll be
&lrm;jeopardising the production.
&lrm;You're right, Chris. Let's go.
&lrm;You'll take Fred's place.
&lrm;I definitely won't let you down.
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Where are they?
&lrm;Excuse me, have you seen a bus
&lrm;with a poster on it for "The Mime"?
&lrm;[phone vibrates]
&lrm;He's got a nerve calling now.
&lrm;I wouldn't give him the time of day.
&lrm;-&lrm;Sarah, where are you?
&lrm;-You never turned up.
&lrm;I'm on time... at the Louvre.
&lrm;What? Why would we meet there?
&lrm;I-I thought
&lrm;the meeting place changed.
&lrm;Fred, I don't want to hear
&lrm;you lame excuses.
&lrm;-But Chris...
&lrm;-I don't care.
&lrm;It's not just this excuse,
&lrm;there's always an excuse.
&lrm;Enough is enough.
&lrm;Chris will be the lead tonight.
&lrm;At least I can count on him.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;An actor who misses his premiere.
&lrm;Now that's a tragedy.
&lrm;Go, my evil Akuma.
&lrm;Let's hand this actor
&lrm;the role of a lifetime!
&lrm;Okey-dokey, here we go.
&lrm;[cat meows]
&lrm;Hey, are you Alya
&lrm;the girl with the blog about me?
&lrm;[meowing]
&lrm;Hey! No!
&lrm;Get away!
&lrm;That is so gross.
&lrm;Cats are nothing but trouble.
&lrm;[sobbing] What did I do?
&lrm;You're going to be
&lrm;so disappointed in me.
&lrm;Mime,
&lrm;I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;I'm giving you the power
&lrm;to make whatever you gesture
&lrm;come to life.
&lrm;Destroy this premiere performance.
&lrm;You may be a mime
&lrm;but they can't silence you!
&lrm;However, in return,
&lrm;you must bring me back Ladybug's
&lrm;and Cat Noir's Miraculouses.
&lrm;So, shall we get on with the show?
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[clinking]
&lrm;[he gasps and screams]
&lrm;[siren wails]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Are you OK?
&lrm;Looks like Mylene's dad's hat.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Mr Haprele?
&lrm;If you're ticked off.
&lrm;We can talk about it.
&lrm;Or not.
&lrm;[arrows whistle]
&lrm;[Nathalie] &lrm;Yes, sir, understood.
&lrm;I'm sure he'll understand, sir.
&lrm;My dad's flaking, isn't he?
&lrm;Let me guess,
&lrm;something came up.
&lrm;Yes, but he reserved
&lrm;the best seats in the house.
&lrm;As usual, the best money can buy.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Get out and hide.
&lrm;I'll cover you.
&lrm;[romantic music]
&lrm;[arrows whistle]
&lrm;We've gotta transform now.
&lrm;I thought I was a spectator,
&lrm;not a performer.
&lrm;-What about the show?
&lrm;-No time.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[clicking]
&lrm;[clinking]
&lrm;Grab her Miraculous, her earrings, now!
&lrm;[rope creaks]
&lrm;Keep your hands to yourself.
&lrm;It's OK, I've got this.
&lrm;My pleasure, Cat Noir.
&lrm;[clinking]
&lrm;Apparently, not seeing is believing.
&lrm;We can't let him go like that.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[car door opens and shuts]
&lrm;[car starts]
&lrm;No, wait!
&lrm;-There, I did it.
&lrm;-I wish you did.
&lrm;When he started miming the car,
&lrm;the bars disappeared.
&lrm;Hey, wait.
&lrm;Nice ride
&lrm;but I'd have made it a convertible.
&lrm;[car accelerates]
&lrm;He's one of the actors
&lrm;and he's after that bus.
&lrm;Where is he going?
&lrm;We've gotta stop him.
&lrm;-Hit the brakes.
&lrm;-What brakes?
&lrm;[screams]
&lrm;[tires screech]
&lrm;Not bad for driving an invisible car
&lrm;but they'll never believe
&lrm;we saved their lives.
&lrm;[clicking]
&lrm;[motorbike revs up]
&lrm;He's off again.
&lrm;We've got to catch up with the bus.
&lrm;What are you doing?
&lrm;Good thing you have friends
&lrm;in high places.
&lrm;-Hold on.
&lrm;-I could've done this.
&lrm;-We're the Cat and Bug team.
&lrm;-Bug and Cat team.
&lrm;Drop me off there.
&lrm;Get ready.
&lrm;-Where's the Akuma?
&lrm;-In his hat.
&lrm;-How do you know?
&lrm;-I have hidden talents.
&lrm;[engine accelerates]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[sword clinks]
&lrm;-Distract him.
&lrm;-Gotcha!
&lrm;Meow.
&lrm;[he gasps] Fred?
&lrm;The Miraculous. Grab her earring!
&lrm;-Grab his hat.
&lrm;-Look out!
&lrm;[chainsaw whirrs]
&lrm;[grinding]
&lrm;-We have to get them to safety.
&lrm;-Can I lend a paw?
&lrm;Yeah, cover me.
&lrm;Hurry up, Milady.
&lrm;[tapping]
&lrm;Stop.
&lrm;What's happening?
&lrm;An actor has been akumatised,
&lrm;and he seems to have it in
&lrm;for your troupe.
&lrm;Fred?
&lrm;[arrows whistle]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;Stay inside.
&lrm;We'll get this under control.
&lrm;I know why he's after us.
&lrm;I stole his role
&lrm;but he can have it back,
&lrm;I don't care anymore.
&lrm;Just keep us safe.
&lrm;What do you mean?
&lrm;You didn't steal it, he lost it.
&lrm;Not exactly,
&lrm;I have to tell you something.
&lrm;His Miraculous, I want his ring!
&lrm;I don't know why you're so violent
&lrm;but I don't think Mylene would approve.
&lrm;[bleep]
&lrm;That's what I call "silent but deadly".
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;A shoe box? Great.
&lrm;There better be explosive boots in there.
&lrm;Of course,
&lrm;we have to make him really angry.
&lrm;Blow his fuse!
&lrm;Isn't he angry enough?
&lrm;You're good at annoying people.
&lrm;Do your thing.
&lrm;Hey...
&lrm;That is true.
&lrm;Gotta borrow these.
&lrm;A box, a magnifying glass,
&lrm;some light, and voilà!
&lrm;A homemade projector. Hey, Mime!
&lrm;Nice poster, don't you think?
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;Yes! Remember he can only mime
&lrm;one thing at a time.
&lrm;So he's cornered.
&lrm;Good thinking, Milady.
&lrm;Thanks.
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you, Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise.
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;[he gasps] Yes!
&lrm;What happened? How did I get here?
&lrm;POUND IT!
&lrm;I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
&lrm;I'm sorry too.
&lrm;I was so desperate to perform
&lrm;that I lied to you.
&lrm;[bleeping] Your earrings.
&lrm;Better get going.
&lrm;Shame, I could have been
&lrm;your date to the play.
&lrm;-Just you and me.
&lrm;-Thanks, but I have other plans.
&lrm;The show's not over yet, Ladybug.
&lrm;You just wait.
&lrm;There's still a last act to come
&lrm;when you least expect it.
&lrm;Got it!
&lrm;[Adrien] Hey.
&lrm;You're here, cool.
&lrm;I thought I'd end up alone.
&lrm;[Alya] Did you bring my phone?
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;I don't know which I liked more,
&lrm;the show or Adrien.
&lrm;Give him a call
&lrm;and ask him out to a movie.
&lrm;Speaking of calling
&lrm;I've something to tell you.
&lrm;I... accidentally erased
&lrm;your Ladybug video,
&lrm;then I dropped your phone in a bin,
&lrm;and now it stinks,
&lrm;like really really bad...
&lrm;and I'm sorry, so so sorry.
&lrm;I know that video meant a lot.
&lrm;I'm a lame friend.
&lrm;[she giggles] Chillax, lady.
&lrm;If anyone knows
&lrm;about your legendary clumsiness,
&lrm;it's me, your BFF.
&lrm;So... You're not angry?
&lrm;Well... you should have come clean
&lrm;and told me, but no, we're cool.
&lrm;Besides, I'd already uploaded it
&lrm;to my blog.
&lrm;I'm so lucky
&lrm;to have a friend like you.
&lrm;So you probably don't care
&lrm;about my surprise.
&lrm;Screw up or no screw up,
&lrm;you know I love surprises.
&lrm;Ok. You see that theatre?
&lrm;There's something inside for you,
&lrm;on the stage.
&lrm;Hello, Alya right?
&lrm;Last time, I was in a hurry.
&lrm;I've got more time now
&lrm;if you want to interview me.
&lrm;[she gasps] No? Seriously?
&lrm;Do I? Do I!
&lrm;Have a seat.
&lrm;You don't know me but FYI, this is like
&lrm;the biggest moment of my life.
&lrm;Alya's lucky to have you
&lrm;as a friend too.
&lrm;-Well? Show me!
&lrm;-Only after I've put it on my blog.
&lrm;-I'm not gonna lose this video.
&lrm;-Hey!
&lrm;[giggling]