&lrm;In the daytime I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;You have one day to work
&lrm;on a fashion piece of your own design.
&lrm;In ten hours, your presentation
&lrm;will be judged
&lrm;by the great fashion designer
&lrm;Gabriel Agreste,
&lrm;the father of our student Adrien.
&lrm;Adrien will model the winning design.
&lrm;And now, this year's theme: derby hats.
&lrm;Derby hats?
&lrm;[Marinette] Derby hat?
&lrm;Derby hat? Derby hat?
&lrm;I don't have any derby hat design.
&lrm;I've got top hats, caps, two-horned hats.
&lrm;A beret? I'm your girl.
&lrm;A sombrero? No problemo. But a derby?
&lrm;It won't even matter,
&lrm;I'll probably make a fool of myself,
&lrm;trip on my derby, collapse on Mr. Agreste,
&lrm;give him a concussion
&lrm;and Adrien will hate me.
&lrm;I'll never be a great fashion designer.
&lrm;My life is over!
&lrm;For a derby hat?
&lrm;Let me see your sketch pad.
&lrm;There must be something in here.
&lrm;Forget it, I'll probably mess
&lrm;everything up in the end.
&lrm;[Adrien] Wow, Alya! Awesome designs.
&lrm;I didn't know you had such skills.
&lrm;Thanks, but I can't take the credit.
&lrm;These sick designs belong to Marinette.
&lrm;Off the chain, right?
&lrm;You're super talented.
&lrm;You have a good chance of winning.
&lrm;Well... um... yeah, I like designs that...
&lrm;go upwards?
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;While stopping?
&lrm;I mean... thanks?
&lrm;Sure. Good luck, maybe I'll be wearing
&lrm;your derby at father's next photo shoot.
&lrm;You gotta get a grip next time.
&lrm;Did you hear?
&lrm;He thinks you can win.
&lrm;Did you hear how impressed Adrien was?
&lrm;Of course I heard.
&lrm;Her? Win the contest? As if.
&lrm;Adrien will convince his father
&lrm;to award me the winner.
&lrm;I'm sure he will, Chloe.
&lrm;You're a born champion.
&lrm;Yours is sure to be the best.
&lrm;Yeah, it is.
&lrm;As soon as I can get my hands
&lrm;on this sketch pad.
&lrm;[Alya] Nine hours until show time.
&lrm;Yikes! I'm off to my secret garden
&lrm;of inspiration.
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;I'm okay, I'm okay.
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;The time has come for us
&lrm;to find our next victim,
&lrm;my wicked little Akumas,
&lrm;and to prey upon Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;Their Miraculouses must be mine.
&lrm;It's hard to be creative under pressure.
&lrm;You save the world under pressure.
&lrm;Designing a hat is a piece of cake.
&lrm;A cake derby hat,
&lrm;stylish and tasty.
&lrm;[pigeons coo]
&lrm;[cooing]
&lrm;[Mr. Ramier] Happy day, happy day.
&lrm;Splendid is the afternoon.
&lrm;Edgar, you fancy one.
&lrm;Fantastic. Dazzling performance.
&lrm;Scram, winged rats.
&lrm;How many times do you need
&lrm;to be told Mr. Ramier?
&lrm;No... feeding... the pigeons!
&lrm;It's forbidden.
&lrm;They'll leave their waste everywhere!
&lrm;Who's going to feed my poor pigeons?
&lrm;Mr. Ramier, you're banned
&lrm;from every park in Paris.
&lrm;Leave or I'll call the authorities.
&lrm;Wait, I'm the authorities.
&lrm;Get out!
&lrm;I almost feel sorry for that man.
&lrm;[Tikki] What a unique character.
&lrm;He was like a human bird.
&lrm;All he needed was a feather jacket
&lrm;to complete the look.
&lrm;A feather jacket?
&lrm;Nice thinking, Tikki.
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] &lrm;Poor Mr. Ramier.
&lrm;The feeling of injustice.
&lrm;Such easy prey for my Akuma.
&lrm;Fly away, my little Akuma,
&lrm;and evilize him.
&lrm;Mr. Pigeon, I'm Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Neither this police officer
&lrm;nor any other park keeper
&lrm;should stop you from taking care
&lrm;of your friends.
&lrm;What would Paris be without pigeons?
&lrm;What would pigeons be without you?
&lrm;[evil laugh]
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;[mad cooing]
&lrm;Yes!
&lrm;-That's a derby.
&lrm;-Thanks, Tikki.
&lrm;We're so awesome!
&lrm;We?
&lrm;Sorry, you're so awesome.
&lrm;When are we... you going to make the hat?
&lrm;And ruin these nails? Of course not.
&lrm;Daddy will pay someone.
&lrm;Ouch!
&lrm;-What are you looking for?
&lrm;-A feather.
&lrm;I don't have a feather for the hat.
&lrm;It has to have one.
&lrm;Yes!
&lrm;Sorry, Mr. Officer, Sir.
&lrm;[flapping]
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;Come on, can't we go any faster?
&lrm;[Driver] Sorry, we have a situation.
&lrm;You need to get off.
&lrm;This is weird.
&lrm;[car horns]
&lrm;[Announcer] &lrm;Pigeons took over Paris.
&lrm;This is a matter of major concern
&lrm;for authorities.
&lrm;I've just been told that a "Mr. Pigeon"
&lrm;is making an announcement.
&lrm;Oh dreary day for Parisians.
&lrm;[he coos]
&lrm;Sorry to ruffle your feathers,
&lrm;but Paris now belongs to pigeons.
&lrm;Flap-flap!
&lrm;[he coos]
&lrm;[Marinette] Paris needs us.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;Yeah!
&lrm;[loud cooing]
&lrm;This is weirder than weird.
&lrm;Birds of a feather flock together.
&lrm;[he sneezes]
&lrm;I'm allergic to feathers.
&lrm;-That's helpful.
&lrm;-Tell me about it.
&lrm;[he begins to sneeze]
&lrm;There's another problem.
&lrm;The park keepers are vanishing.
&lrm;What? We have to track down Mr. Pigeon.
&lrm;But how?
&lrm;I don't know where we can find him
&lrm;but he can find us.
&lrm;[whistling]
&lrm;[humming]
&lrm;Act natural or he'll never show up.
&lrm;What? I am acting natural.
&lrm;[cooing]
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;Job well done, buddy-boy.
&lrm;Pigeons will reign supreme.
&lrm;Power to the pigeons!
&lrm;[triumphant cooing]
&lrm;Where is he?
&lrm;He should have been here by now.
&lrm;[flapping]
&lrm;[Adrien sneezes]
&lrm;What the...
&lrm;[he sneezes]
&lrm;[Cat Noir]
&lrm;Where's that bird brain Mr. Pigeon?
&lrm;He's gotta be here.
&lrm;If you want to give Paris
&lrm;to the pigeons for good,
&lrm;you must rid the city of those two pests.
&lrm;[cooing]
&lrm;I feel like birdseed all of a sudden.
&lrm;[they both gasp]
&lrm;Any bright ideas?
&lrm;You're the cat,
&lrm;don't you eat these things?
&lrm;Look.
&lrm;[Mr. Pigeon coos]
&lrm;Chirpy day! I'm so ruthless.
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] Excellent.
&lrm;Take their Miraculouses.
&lrm;Your Miraculouses. Give them to me
&lrm;or face the wrath of my feathered friends.
&lrm;[cooing]
&lrm;[banging]
&lrm;On the count of three,
&lrm;my pigeons will open fire.
&lrm;You can save your sorry skins
&lrm;by handing me your Miraculous. One, two...
&lrm;Cat Noir, the bars.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[creaking]
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;[Cat Noir]
&lrm;Well, well, the pigeon is a chicken.
&lrm;Me? I'm not flying away.
&lrm;I'm just killing two birds with one stone.
&lrm;[he coos]
&lrm;[flapping and yelling]
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;[mocking yell]
&lrm;[mocking cooing]
&lrm;Merry Christmas!
&lrm;I'm not done with you yet.
&lrm;[mad cooing]
&lrm;[beeping]
&lrm;I've got to go
&lrm;before my identity is revealed.
&lrm;You wouldn't want
&lrm;to let the cat out the bag.
&lrm;Ha, ha, very funny.
&lrm;Ladybug, Cat Noir,
&lrm;I'm in great danger of losing money
&lrm;if my guests leave Paris.
&lrm;Get rid of those pigeons.
&lrm;Before we do, I have an urgent need.
&lrm;An urgent need? I see.
&lrm;Head to the Royal Suite.
&lrm;There's paper in there.
&lrm;Perhaps you'd prefer a litter tray?
&lrm;No need for litter.
&lrm;But could I have some camembert?
&lrm;Sorry, emergency.
&lrm;[knocking]
&lrm;-How do you like your camembert?
&lrm;-Runny.
&lrm;[knocking]
&lrm;-Unpasteurized Saint-Claquos.
&lrm;-Thanks.
&lrm;[beeping]
&lrm;[Plagg screams]
&lrm;The exhaustion. My poor aching body.
&lrm;I can't move a muscle.
&lrm;[Adrien] You wanna bet?
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;My gooeyness...
&lrm;Eat up, Ladybug needs help.
&lrm;I can get a much better view from up here.
&lrm;They're flying in the same direction.
&lrm;Better follow them.
&lrm;[Elevator beeps]
&lrm;-Ready when you are.
&lrm;-Let's go.
&lrm;That's where Mr. Pigeon keeps
&lrm;the park keepers.
&lrm;The Grand Palais.
&lrm;[he begins to sneeze]
&lrm;My pigeon radar is on alert.
&lrm;Either your radar's on the brink
&lrm;or the park keepers are unattended.
&lrm;Let's set the cat among the pigeons.
&lrm;Hold up, kitty. It's too easy.
&lrm;I've got a plan.
&lrm;[Mr. Pigeon] Perfect timing.
&lrm;We're ready to greet them.
&lrm;They're going to fall right into my trap.
&lrm;It won't be long
&lrm;before you get your Miraculouses.
&lrm;I can't wait, my dear Pigeon.
&lrm;[Ladybug] If we destroy that bird call,
&lrm;we'll capture the Akuma.
&lrm;You open the window,
&lrm;I grab him and you snag the bird call.
&lrm;Early bird gets the worm.
&lrm;[he sneezes loudly]
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;So much for the element of surprise.
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;[cooing]
&lrm;[yelling and cooing]
&lrm;Diddle-dee-dee, come closer.
&lrm;I have a bone to "peck" with you.
&lrm;I'd be honored.
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;[Agent] Get us out of here.
&lrm;[evil giggle]
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;A coin? What am I supposed
&lrm;to do with that?
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;You can't buy yourself out of here.
&lrm;Cat Noir!
&lrm;[Ladybug] Snack time, pigeons.
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;My bird call. No!
&lrm;Cat Noir, grab it.
&lrm;[he sneezes]
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;-Yes.
&lrm;-Ouch.
&lrm;[desperate cooing]
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you, little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilize.
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;[twinkling]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;What happened? Where am I?
&lrm;Pound it.
&lrm;Wretched pigeons, wretched Ladybug!
&lrm;I'll destroy every one of you.
&lrm;[he roars]
&lrm;I have less than an hour.
&lrm;[busy signal rings]
&lrm;Where is that girl?
&lrm;Hello, Mr. Damocles,
&lrm;I am Mr. Agreste's assistant.
&lrm;Hello Miss.
&lrm;Pardon me, but where is Mr. Agreste?
&lrm;I'm here.
&lrm;Ah...
&lrm;Hello Mr. Agreste, welcome to our school.
&lrm;Adrien, take Nathalie around.
&lrm;There's Mr. Agreste. He's coming this way.
&lrm;They have poured their hearts
&lrm;and souls into their projects.
&lrm;Where have you been? You got your hat?
&lrm;Yep, here.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;-What?
&lrm;-But it's the same as Chloe's.
&lrm;What?
&lrm;Hi, Mr. Agreste, I'm Chloe Bourgeois.
&lrm;You know my father, the Mayor.
&lrm;That thieving little brat!
&lrm;-Shall I take care of it?
&lrm;-I think I can handle this.
&lrm;Turn the tablet to Miss Bourgeois's hat.
&lrm;Is this a joke?
&lrm;No fair!
&lrm;Marinette copied my design.
&lrm;It's scandalous!
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;I apologize for the situation.
&lrm;But I can prove
&lrm;that this derby hat is mine.
&lrm;Go ahead.
&lrm;Everything is handmade
&lrm;from the embroidery
&lrm;to the weaving and the stitching.
&lrm;Done by myself.
&lrm;And there's an element
&lrm;that only a true designer knows about.
&lrm;I signed mine.
&lrm;[Chloe cries]
&lrm;Exquisite creation.
&lrm;You have the laboring hands
&lrm;of a hat maker, Miss...
&lrm;Marinette.
&lrm;Congratulations, Miss Marinette.
&lrm;You're the winner.
&lrm;Thank you, thank you, thank you.
&lrm;Adrien will wear your derby.
&lrm;Awesome job, Marinette.
&lrm;[he starts to sneeze]
&lrm;[he sneezes loudly]
&lrm;[sniffing]
&lrm;I'm allergic to feathers.
&lrm;[he sneezes]
&lrm;Gesundheit.
&lrm;Thanks.
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;[giggling]