&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life,
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret?
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Marinette]
&lrm;"Dear diary, guess what?
&lrm;"I nearly transformed back
&lrm;"revealing my true identity to Cat Noir."
&lrm;Weren't you meeting Alya after school
&lrm;to research your term paper?
&lrm;Oh no, I'm late... again!
&lrm;[bell rings]
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[video game music]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;-What's that noise?
&lrm;-Hide, Tikki.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[video game music]
&lrm;[Kim] Come on, Max.
&lrm;[Kim] Use the kitty paw.
&lrm;What's going on?
&lrm;[she hushes her]
&lrm;Try-outs for the Paris Ultimate
&lrm;Mecha Strike 3 Tournament.
&lrm;The school sends
&lrm;the 2 students with the highest scores.
&lrm;Actually, the try-outs are for a partner
&lrm;to team up with Max.
&lrm;Why Max?
&lrm;[Kim] Cus he's unbeatable.
&lrm;He's got the highest APM over anyone.
&lrm;-APM?
&lrm;-Actions per minute.
&lrm;This tournament is his life.
&lrm;He's been grinding all year.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[Max sighs]
&lrm;[Miss Bustier] Adrien's in the lead.
&lrm;[Kim] What happened, Max?
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;[Max sighs]
&lrm;Awesome job, we'll make a killer combo.
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;Let me get this straight.
&lrm;If someone beats Max's score,
&lrm;they'll team up with Adrien?
&lrm;No-one can beat Max,
&lrm;or rather Max and Adrien.
&lrm;It's a slam dunk, they're our dream team.
&lrm;[Marinette squeals]
&lrm;I see where you're going with this.
&lrm;[excitedly] Just imagine...
&lrm;teaming with Adrien.
&lrm;Are you insane, girl?
&lrm;This is about stepping up
&lrm;and representing,
&lrm;not snuggling up and snogging.
&lrm;This is serious business.
&lrm;Seriously, Alya,
&lrm;you think I'd go through with it?
&lrm;I think we have our champions...
&lrm;[Marinette] Wait!
&lrm;[nervously] Is it too late to try out?
&lrm;Well, the library is closing
&lrm;in 5 minutes but...
&lrm;[determined sigh]
&lrm;[Alya sighs]
&lrm;Oh boy.
&lrm;[excitedly] Adrien's joypad.
&lrm;Is she serious? There's no way.
&lrm;Unless the player
&lrm;has a particular motivation.
&lrm;The rules are elementary.
&lrm;You battle each other's robot...
&lrm;Please... Every time you win,
&lrm;you loot his items and gain XP,
&lrm;which upgrades your mech'.
&lrm;I'm not a newb' thanks.
&lrm;[video game music]
&lrm;[he sighs] Sounds like you know enough.
&lrm;Let's see if it's enough.
&lrm;[Kim] This'll be fun.
&lrm;[Scoffing] Seriously?
&lrm;How can you spend
&lrm;so much time in front of a screen?
&lrm;I know. As if.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[Kim] Come on, Max. You can do it.
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;And now, quarter circle
&lrm;plus kick and flying hyper-storm.
&lrm;Triple-hit combo,
&lrm;Marinette style, boo-ya!
&lrm;[Marinette cheers] I win.
&lrm;What? I can't believe it.
&lrm;She... she beat him.
&lrm;Beat him? She pulverised him.
&lrm;The king's been knocked off his throne.
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;[Kim] Max, come on.
&lrm;I accept this defeat.
&lrm;I relinquish my position.
&lrm;Congratulations, Marinette,
&lrm;and Adrien.
&lrm;Max, wait.
&lrm;[sad music]
&lrm;Look, I'm fine. I lost fair and square,
&lrm;but if you don't mind,
&lrm;I'd like some solitude.
&lrm;So, Marinette and Adrien
&lrm;will represent the school
&lrm;at the Ultimate Mecha Strike 3 Tournament.
&lrm;Good luck.
&lrm;I guess I'll be coming over to practice
&lrm;with my new partner.
&lrm;See you later.
&lrm;[dreamily] See... ya.
&lrm;[romantic music]
&lrm;You gotta win.
&lrm;You'll be representing the school,
&lrm;not just hanging out with Adrien.
&lrm;Adrien.
&lrm;Brother.
&lrm;[Max] This is a travesty,
&lrm;an unequivocal travesty.
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] A competition,
&lrm;I know you like that, my little Akumas.
&lrm;Where there's a winner, there's a loser.
&lrm;[mysterious music]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Fly away, my little Akuma,
&lrm;and evilise him.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;I should be the one
&lrm;going to that tournament.
&lrm;I worked so hard for it.
&lrm;This is inconceivable.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Gamer, I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;I'll help you win
&lrm;the tournament of your life,
&lrm;but in return, you must help me
&lrm;achieve my high score.
&lrm;Absolutely, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Game on!
&lrm;Now they'll see who's
&lrm;the greatest gamer in Paris.
&lrm;[evil growling]
&lrm;[bubbling]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;[excitedly] Training with Adrien, Adrien!
&lrm;There are other ways
&lrm;to spend time with Adrien.
&lrm;What do you mean?
&lrm;You know Max wanted
&lrm;to be in that tournament.
&lrm;He's been training all year.
&lrm;You're right.
&lrm;All I could think of was Adrien.
&lrm;Hey, Adrien's coming to my house.
&lrm;[gasping] Adrien's coming... to my house!
&lrm;This is a total disaster. I have to...
&lrm;clean my room!
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;That's what
&lrm;I've been trying to tell you.
&lrm;All this... is not...
&lrm;happening!
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Calm down, Marinette,
&lrm;you still have time.
&lrm;He won't show up right now.
&lrm;[bell rings]
&lrm;[mother] Marinette!
&lrm;Someone's here to see you.
&lrm;[panicking] Coming!
&lrm;Marinette and I are finalists
&lrm;in the Paris Ultimate
&lrm;Mecha Strike 3 tournament.
&lrm;No way!
&lrm;Well, she did learn from the best.
&lrm;Tom style, boo-ya!
&lrm;She never told us
&lrm;about this tournament.
&lrm;We were paired up today.
&lrm;You two are a pair?
&lrm;I'm not surprised.
&lrm;She talks a lot about you.
&lrm;[Marinette] Mom!
&lrm;[nervously] Come up, Adrien.
&lrm;Very nice to meet you.
&lrm;[romantic music]
&lrm;[endearing sighs]
&lrm;[woman] Bye, see you next week.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Gamer, it's time to get to the next level
&lrm;and show everyone who's best.
&lrm;No time like the present.
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[video game music]
&lrm;[they giggle]
&lrm;-Sorry,
&lrm;-No, you go.
&lrm;I'LL USE THE OTHER ONE.
&lrm;[nervous giggles]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;-Your parents seem nice.
&lrm;-Yeah, they are but sometimes...
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[she shrieks]
&lrm;Sometimes what?
&lrm;[knocking]
&lrm;Everything OK?
&lrm;Just in case you were hungry...
&lrm;No, thanks, we're training.
&lrm;Well, maybe you can use a few tips,
&lrm;dad style.
&lrm;Thanks, but no thanks.
&lrm;[irritated] Papa.
&lrm;Sometimes they're a little nosey.
&lrm;[endearing sighs]
&lrm;[nervous giggle]
&lrm;Where were we?
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;I'll soon be at level 2.
&lrm;My skills are indisputable.
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;I am unstoppable!
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Excellent.
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[gamer cackles]
&lrm;[Adrien growls]
&lrm;Wow! We won again thanks to you.
&lrm;[nervously]
&lrm;Yeah... Yes, we did.
&lrm;We? That was practically all you.
&lrm;You're amazing, Marinette.
&lrm;I guess you wouldn't even need me.
&lrm;I'm so lame compared to you.
&lrm;[hesitantly] No, no... I...
&lrm;No, you're so good.
&lrm;I mean... I'm the one who's not good.
&lrm;I mean... I'm lucky, that's all.
&lrm;[knocking]
&lrm;Anyone want cookies,
&lrm;hot from the oven?
&lrm;[Adrien gasps] We're trying to work.
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;Actually, you know what?
&lrm;I've got a secret.
&lrm;This is why I win.
&lrm;Are you messing with me?
&lrm;Try playing a match with it.
&lrm;[door opens]
&lrm;How about a salmon and spinach pie?
&lrm;Tell me what you think.
&lrm;[Marinette groans]
&lrm;A little snack wouldn't hurt.
&lrm;[she hesitates and chuckles]
&lrm;I'm really sorry.
&lrm;I can't get anything done
&lrm;with my parents around.
&lrm;[gulping] It's OK.
&lrm;Your dad makes great pies.
&lrm;[hesitating] Yeah... so shall we go back?
&lrm;Let's see if it works.
&lrm;[thudding]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Is this a publicity stunt
&lrm;for the tournament?
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[gamer] Well, well...
&lrm;Marinette,
&lrm;let's see who's victorious this time.
&lrm;It doesn't look like it.
&lrm;[whirring]
&lrm;Look out!
&lrm;We'd better get outta here.
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Game over, Marinette.
&lrm;How does he know my name?
&lrm;Max!
&lrm;He really did want
&lrm;to be in the tournament.
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;Game over.
&lrm;Not yet.
&lrm;Here comes a new challenger.
&lrm;Cat Noir, hey!
&lrm;Over here!
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;I heard you
&lrm;really ticked off the final boss.
&lrm;It doesn't give him extra
&lrm;points to transform everyone.
&lrm;Wait, I left Adrien at the park.
&lrm;We have to go back.
&lrm;[he hesitates]
&lrm;Don't worry, he's not in danger.
&lrm;He'll be fine. You'll be safe here.
&lrm;I'll take care of everything.
&lrm;Arch, leap and do a barrel-roll.
&lrm;He's always so over the top.
&lrm;If ever there was a game to win,
&lrm;this is it.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[lively music continues]
&lrm;[whirring]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Get away from here, as far as you can!
&lrm;[screams] Hurry!
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Hey, tin can, over here!
&lrm;My calculations indicate
&lrm;that your system's about to crash.
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;[whizzing]
&lrm;[gamer groans]
&lrm;You're the one crashing, robot.
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;He's a robot from Ultimate Mecha Strike.
&lrm;I know. And it's nearly at level 3,
&lrm;4 is the highest.
&lrm;-Wait, you know that game?
&lrm;-Of course.
&lrm;See? You and me, it was meant to be.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[whirring]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;I think our problem got
&lrm;a whole lot bigger.
&lrm;[cheerfully] Level 3.
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;If you want to be the most
&lrm;powerful robot,
&lrm;you must capture Ladybug
&lrm;and Cat Noir's Miraculouses.
&lrm;Then it really will be game over.
&lrm;Those Miraculouses are mine.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[whizzing]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;We have to stop him
&lrm;before he destroys Paris.
&lrm;THE STADIUM!
&lrm;[whizzing]
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Where's Clunky got to?
&lrm;[thud]
&lrm;[they yell]
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;Attack him with your Cataclysm power,
&lrm;It might shock him.
&lrm;My pleasure. Two can play this game.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[agonising cry] No!
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;Smack-down, Cat Noir.
&lrm;Cat Noir style, boo-ya!
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Check out that loot!
&lrm;System crash, Gamer!
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;You've forgotten the rules.
&lrm;I saved my last level.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[Ladybug sighs]
&lrm;Re-spawn!
&lrm;Not the old spawn point glitch again.
&lrm;Did you see him press his glasses?
&lrm;I bet the Akuma's in there.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[Marinette] We've levelled up too.
&lrm;I don't have long left.
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;I'll man it, you shoot.
&lrm;-Why do you get to man it?
&lrm;-Wanna flip for it?
&lrm;[whirring]
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;OK, you man it, I'll fire.
&lrm;Look out. Here he comes.
&lrm;[smashing]
&lrm;[fizzing]
&lrm;Don't let it go to your head.
&lrm;Hawk booster!
&lrm;[worried cry]
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Round 2, Gamer.
&lrm;[he growls]
&lrm;Pyramissiles!
&lrm;Force-field, Cat Noir!
&lrm;Got it! Force-field activated.
&lrm;[rumbling]
&lrm;Catsabre.
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Pyradrill!
&lrm;[whizzing]
&lrm;[grinding]
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;[fizzing]
&lrm;He's powerful.
&lrm;He took out our force-field.
&lrm;We'll have to do without.
&lrm;Ladybombs!
&lrm;Laser wall!
&lrm;[whizzing]
&lrm;[Ladybug] Ladyhelix!
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Kitty-punch!
&lrm;[bombs whistle]
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Ear thunder!
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;-He's anticipating our attacks.
&lrm;-Watch out!
&lrm;[thudding]
&lrm;[clunking]
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Gamer-fire!
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[Ladybug groans]
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;Today, I'll be victorious.
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[Cat Noir roars]
&lrm;Catouken!
&lrm;[clunking]
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;I am the strongest player in the world.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;How do we beat him
&lrm;if we can't catch him?
&lrm;We have to jam the system.
&lrm;Tatsukitty!
&lrm;Catoukin!
&lrm;Gamer Crusher!
&lrm;Shoryubug!
&lrm;Catoukin!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;[clunking]
&lrm;We must get inside.
&lrm;Go. You're boss.
&lrm;Take control, I'll be right back.
&lrm;Right back? Where you going?
&lrm;It's just us two, Gamer.
&lrm;What...?
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Graffiti? Spray-paint? Arts and crafts?
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;Bingo.
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[she hums]
&lrm;[he growls]
&lrm;You won't get away with this.
&lrm;[rumbling]
&lrm;Game over, Gamer.
&lrm;Game over for you too, Akuma.
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;[twinkling]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[sighs of relief]
&lrm;What am I doing here?
&lrm;POUND IT!
&lrm;Such pitiful insolence!
&lrm;The moment you challenged me
&lrm;was the moment you sealed your fate!
&lrm;This battle is not yet over.
&lrm;[stadium speaker] &lrm;Remember,
&lrm;the high score to beat is 245,000.
&lrm;So gamers, hit those consoles. Game on!
&lrm;After all you've done,
&lrm;now you want to pull out?
&lrm;But I feel so bad for Max.
&lrm;And well... it just wouldn't be right.
&lrm;You're doing the right thing,
&lrm;but you don't get the chance
&lrm;to play with Adrien every day.
&lrm;Max... I thought about this a lot...
&lrm;And now, representing
&lrm;the Francois Dupont high school!
&lrm;I think you should be playing tonight.
&lrm;What?
&lrm;Don't get me wrong, I love gaming,
&lrm;but it's not my heart and soul.
&lrm;This is your baby.
&lrm;It's your tournament, Max.
&lrm;I won't take that away from you.
&lrm;Dudes, make up your minds.
&lrm;They're waiting for you.
&lrm;I insist.
&lrm;How can I thank you?
&lrm;By winning... with her.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;You're way better than me.
&lrm;You belong on the team.
&lrm;Win it for the school.
&lrm;[Adrien] I know you can do it.
&lrm;Go on, dudes, they're waiting.
&lrm;[Marinette hesitates]
&lrm;No... but... I...
&lrm;Only with you.
&lrm;[cheering] Let's show 'em who's gold!
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;[happy music]