&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life,
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet,
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;Help!
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[laughing]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[Marinette gasps]
&lrm;Oh, Super-Nathan, you're my hero.
&lrm;It was nothing.
&lrm;- I love you.
&lrm;- I love you too.
&lrm;Nathaniel!
&lrm;What are you drawing?
&lrm;Wh-Wh...
&lrm;This is why you are failing science.
&lrm;I'm sorry.
&lrm;Go to the principal's office
&lrm;and show him that chicken scratch!
&lrm;Then you'll be really sorry.
&lrm;[gasps]
&lrm;[Marinette gasps]
&lrm;Look Sabrina,
&lrm;it's him as a superhero.
&lrm;Look who he's saving,
&lrm;It's Marinette.
&lrm;He's totally crushing
&lrm;on you, Marinette.
&lrm;Give me that.
&lrm;Enough, Nathaniel, go!
&lrm;[evil voice]
&lrm;Artists can be so emotional.
&lrm;I love it.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Fly to him, my little Akuma.
&lrm;Draw him into our evil web.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Are you tired of having
&lrm;your creative spirit crushed?
&lrm;Evillustrator, I'm your friend
&lrm;and patron of the arts.
&lrm;I'm here to offer you support
&lrm;but I don't give this power for free.
&lrm;I've some items that need retrieving.
&lrm;Just tell me what you want.
&lrm;[bubbling]
&lrm;The next particle physics
&lrm;presentation group is
&lrm;Nino, Adrien, and Alya.
&lrm;[enviously]
&lrm;So lucky.
&lrm;And Sabrina, Chloe, and Marinette.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;So unlucky.
&lrm;Can't you add her to another group?
&lrm;We work better on our own.
&lrm;This is a group presentation,
&lrm;not pairs. Deal with it.
&lrm;[bell rings]
&lrm;I hate dealing with it.
&lrm;Could we trade groups?
&lrm;And deal with
&lrm;that twosome of terror? Sorry.
&lrm;But I promise to talk all about you.
&lrm;You're the best!
&lrm;[Chloe] Forget it, Sabrina.
&lrm;I've no time for dumb projects.
&lrm;Besides, now you have Marinette
&lrm;to help you.
&lrm;OK, that's fine.
&lrm;We'll do the work. Don't worry.
&lrm;[Marinette] &lrm;What?
&lrm;Is everything OK?
&lrm;It's fine, Marinette.
&lrm;Why can't you help with the project?
&lrm;None of your business, nosey.
&lrm;Actually, since I'm part of
&lrm;this group, it is.
&lrm;It's OK. You and I will do
&lrm;all the research and the writing
&lrm;then Chloe can present it.
&lrm;That way it's equal.
&lrm;That's not equal at all.
&lrm;Is that how you two work?
&lrm;Yeah, ever since grade school
&lrm;when I started doing Chloe's homework.
&lrm;We've been BFFs ever since.
&lrm;You got a problem with that?
&lrm;Come on, Sabrina.
&lrm;Sabrina, Chloe's
&lrm;taking advantage of you.
&lrm;You don't have to do what she says.
&lrm;That's not how a best friend acts.
&lrm;[Chloe] Not only am I
&lrm;Sabrina's best friend,
&lrm;I'm her only friend.
&lrm;So she better do what I say,
&lrm;cuz without me, she has nothing.
&lrm;I'd rather have no friends
&lrm;than be friends with you.
&lrm;Whatever. I've more important things
&lrm;to do.
&lrm;My hair's a mess and Jean-Claude
&lrm;promised to work his magic.
&lrm;Later.
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Marinette!
&lrm;I can't believe you stood up to Chloe.
&lrm;It was so amazing.
&lrm;Well... yeah...
&lrm;What are friends for?
&lrm;I'm super excited to hang out with you
&lrm;and have a new friend
&lrm;who helps with the project
&lrm;We'll have the best time together.
&lrm;We'll do the presentation
&lrm;and tell the truth about Chloe, OK?
&lrm;[uncertainly]
&lrm;Sounds... great.
&lrm;Yay! I'll see you
&lrm;in the library, bestie.
&lrm;[Chloe huffs]
&lrm;What do you mean you're not doing it?
&lrm;Marinette's right. I-I'm not your slave.
&lrm;I never actually said that.
&lrm;But Marinette didn't buy
&lrm;a super cute beret.
&lrm;And I did.
&lrm;Perhaps I could lend it to you.
&lrm;Are you trying to bribe her
&lrm;into staying your friend...
&lrm;with a hat?
&lrm;[excitedly]
&lrm;A really, really adorable hat.
&lrm;That would look fantastic on me.
&lrm;No, excuse me,
&lrm;but you are trying to steal
&lrm;my friend from me
&lrm;with homework!
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;My hair!
&lrm;[violent blowing]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[Chloe] No, not the hair!
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;[frightened screaming]
&lrm;No! Stop!
&lrm;Run and hide!
&lrm;[Ladybug squeals]
&lrm;I got wind you were being blown away
&lrm;by a hairy situation.
&lrm;Fewer puns, more action!
&lrm;[Ladybug yells]
&lrm;That guy looks pretty sketchy.
&lrm;[they groan]
&lrm;Where did he go?
&lrm;I don't know
&lrm;but he sure illustrates his point.
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Chloe, this Evillustrator,
&lrm;he's targeting you specifically.
&lrm;Any idea why?
&lrm;No, everyone adores me.
&lrm;Yeah, because you're so adorable.
&lrm;Yay! Ladybug said I'm adorable.
&lrm;I totally need a picture of us together.
&lrm;[Ladybug huffs]
&lrm;That was unpleasant.
&lrm;I look great, but your smile's wonky.
&lrm;Let's take another.
&lrm;[Ladybug groans]
&lrm;Sorry, I'm a little camera shy.
&lrm;- Someone's got a fan.
&lrm;- Yeah, great.
&lrm;What's the deal?
&lrm;Why are you acting weird?
&lrm;You gotta admit that
&lrm;having her worship you is awesome.
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;Seriously?
&lrm;I'm over this. Let's go.
&lrm;Are you kidding?
&lrm;What if he attacks her again?
&lrm;Fine, you stay. Later.
&lrm;What do you mean, later?
&lrm;You want to protect her,
&lrm;so you don't need me.
&lrm;So... later!
&lrm;[Chloe]
&lrm;Ladybug, text me, OK?
&lrm;[cry of pain]
&lrm;Hey!
&lrm;Sorry, Tikki, Chloe just fires up
&lrm;this little red bug.
&lrm;Well, simmer down.
&lrm;A hot head won't get you anywhere.
&lrm;It's hard to keep my cool...
&lrm;especially in school.
&lrm;Oh my gosh, Sabrina, the project!
&lrm;Look like you have a new BFF.
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;[footsteps]
&lrm;[worried cry]
&lrm;[Marinette gasps]
&lrm;It's you... from the library.
&lrm;What are you doing here?
&lrm;I wanted to see you.
&lrm;[confused]
&lrm;OK.
&lrm;But why did you attack Chloe?
&lrm;Chloe is cruel and selfish.
&lrm;Can't argue with that.
&lrm;[nervously]
&lrm;Are you... going to hurt me?
&lrm;You? You're Marinette.
&lrm;You're beautiful, sweet and perfect.
&lrm;I could never hurt you.
&lrm;[embarrassed]
&lrm;Wow, that's very... flattering...
&lrm;Thank you.
&lrm;[nervously]
&lrm;I just came to ask...
&lrm;It's my birthday today and...
&lrm;would you wanna come to my party?
&lrm;Oh... actually...
&lrm;it's not really the best night.
&lrm;I've got a presentation to work on
&lrm;and I have to call my friend
&lrm;so we can meet and...
&lrm;Please. It'll just be you and I.
&lrm;[romantic music]
&lrm;Oh, my gosh.
&lrm;[awkwardly]
&lrm;That's...me
&lrm;You like it?
&lrm;[hesitantly]
&lrm;I love it.
&lrm;So much that I'll be at your party...
&lrm;on one condition.
&lrm;Anything for you.
&lrm;You can't hurt Chloe anymore.
&lrm;I can't bear violence.
&lrm;For you, and only you.
&lrm;Meet you next to Notre-Dame
&lrm;at sunset.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;What are you thinking, Marinette?
&lrm;I'm thinking
&lrm;poor Nathaniel has a crush on me,
&lrm;and his alter ego, the Evillustrator,
&lrm;is gonna get crushed by Ladybug.
&lrm;But how is Ladybug going to
&lrm;crush this crush
&lrm;when you're going on the date
&lrm;with him as Marinette?
&lrm;Maybe some cool cat needs
&lrm;to crash the party.
&lrm;[Chloe whines]
&lrm;Sabrina is so selfish
&lrm;making me do this project myself.
&lrm;[whining]
&lrm;My brain hurts.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Hey...
&lrm;Cat Noir, are you any good
&lrm;at particle physics?
&lrm;This cat's got
&lrm;particle physics in the bag.
&lrm;Great.
&lrm;Sit, kitty.
&lrm;Now, make it sounds
&lrm;purr-fect for my presentation.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;See that? I made a cat joke.
&lrm;I can be funny.
&lrm;[sarcastically]
&lrm;Yeah... hilarious.
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;You can't just fly off
&lrm;and then make cat calls, Ladybug.
&lrm;Sorry, that wasn't cool,
&lrm;but you can leave Chloe.
&lrm;I need you to protect this girl.
&lrm;Her name's Marinette.
&lrm;Cute, isn't she?
&lrm;The Evillustrator is in love with her.
&lrm;He won't harm Chloe
&lrm;if Marinette comes to his party.
&lrm;While he's distracted,
&lrm;you take him down.
&lrm;What about you?
&lrm;I'm going on a secret mission.
&lrm;I'll catch you later. Can you handle it?
&lrm;[he chuckles]
&lrm;It'll be a cinch.
&lrm;You're out of danger.
&lrm;So, see ya... Later.
&lrm;[angrily]
&lrm;Later? What about my presentation?
&lrm;[she growls]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Sabrina...
&lrm;you scared me.
&lrm;Sorry, I was just waiting for you.
&lrm;Did you get my messages?
&lrm;Yes... Yes I did.
&lrm;And I was totally going to call you.
&lrm;You were?
&lrm;[excitedly]
&lrm;I knew you would... Eventually.
&lrm;So I did your geography homework.
&lrm;[surprised]
&lrm;You didn't have to.
&lrm;Since you're my new best friend,
&lrm;it's the least I can do.
&lrm;Thanks but I can't accept it.
&lrm;Really?
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;OK, but just this once.
&lrm;Great.
&lrm;So, you wanna work on
&lrm;the project tonight?
&lrm;I'm so sorry Sabrina.
&lrm;I've something really important to do.
&lrm;Something important, really?
&lrm;That's fascinating.
&lrm;You know who else uses that excuse?
&lrm;[hesitating]
&lrm;No...
&lrm;Chloe. I'm beginning to see
&lrm;how similar you two are.
&lrm;You expect me to do all the work,
&lrm;like she did. Right?
&lrm;No...I-I don't, really. It's just...
&lrm;I can't believe I did
&lrm;your geography homework for you.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;I thought I was going to have to
&lrm;save you from her claws.
&lrm;Get it? Claws.
&lrm;I haven't even introduced myself.
&lrm;I'm Cat Noir.
&lrm;Yeah, I know.
&lrm;You save the day all the time
&lrm;and stuff. I'm Marinette.
&lrm;Why are you here?
&lrm;That birthday-boy date
&lrm;of yours is bad news.
&lrm;[she mimics him]
&lrm;But you're safe with me.
&lrm;That puts my mind at ease.
&lrm;But I am going to need help.
&lrm;Care to assist a superhero?
&lrm;What about Ladybug?
&lrm;Aren't you a duo?
&lrm;She's busy.
&lrm;[she mimics him]
&lrm;So you get to be my Ladybug.
&lrm;[sigh of repulsion]
&lrm;Cat Noir and I
&lrm;fighting crime together? Amazing.
&lrm;What do I do?
&lrm;Just get his pencil away from him.
&lrm;I'll take care of the rest.
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;What a lovely little scene
&lrm;you're setting,
&lrm;but I don't get distracted, boy.
&lrm;I just want Marinette to love me.
&lrm;[angrily]
&lrm;And I want the Miraculous. So get it!
&lrm;Or else...
&lrm;[throbbing]
&lrm;[fearfully]
&lrm;OK, I will, I will.
&lrm;[Marinette]
&lrm;Happy birthday.
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;[shyly]
&lrm;Marinette.
&lrm;Thanks for accepting to come.
&lrm;- It's so beautiful.
&lrm;- You like it?
&lrm;Well hold on.
&lrm;I'm just getting started.
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;Come on, you've gotta be kidding.
&lrm;Sorry...
&lrm;I didn't mean to startle you.
&lrm;I can't draw in the dark.
&lrm;Voilà!
&lrm;You're so talented.
&lrm;So why would you want
&lrm;to use your power to hurt people.
&lrm;Not all people, just Chloe.
&lrm;And I won't do it again.
&lrm;You were true to your promise
&lrm;so I'll be true to mine.
&lrm;I actually draw a little too.
&lrm;I'm not as good as you, of course.
&lrm;I'm sure you're great.
&lrm;Can I draw you something special
&lrm;for your birthday?
&lrm;[surprised]
&lrm;That would be amazing.
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;Marinette, give my pencil back.
&lrm;I need to draw something... now.
&lrm;No... I'm keeping it.
&lrm;Cat Noir, now!
&lrm;Marinette?
&lrm;You're working with him?
&lrm;I'm so stupid.
&lrm;I thought you liked me
&lrm;but you're just like Chloe.
&lrm;Teasing me, mocking me,
&lrm;leading me on!
&lrm;Come on, seriously?
&lrm;Why is everyone
&lrm;comparing me to Chloe?
&lrm;And I'm taking back my promise.
&lrm;Chloe's going to get
&lrm;a lesson she'll never forget.
&lrm;We've been penned in, literally.
&lrm;[Marinette gasps]
&lrm;Cat Noir, put your stick like this,
&lrm;then extend it.
&lrm;- Great thinking.
&lrm;- Yeah, I'm a genius.
&lrm;Gotta go.
&lrm;A superhero's work is never done.
&lrm;Damsels in distress,
&lrm;ladies in waiting...
&lrm;I've more saving to do.
&lrm;You can thank me later.
&lrm;Me thank him?
&lrm;He should be thanking me.
&lrm;We'd still be trapped
&lrm;if it wasn't for me.
&lrm;[Tikki]
&lrm;Speaking of which...
&lrm;He needs help saving Chloe.
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;I'm so sorry, Miss,
&lrm;but after what happened
&lrm;in the Library,
&lrm;I couldn't work on my project.
&lrm;It would have been too traumatic.
&lrm;Just look what it's done to my hair.
&lrm;[sobbing suddenly stops]
&lrm;Who's going to believe that?
&lrm;Even a stupid hairdryer
&lrm;couldn't make me look bad.
&lrm;[door rumbles]
&lrm;Cat Noir, is that you?
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;Chloe, where are you?
&lrm;Are you hiding?
&lrm;That is so cute.
&lrm;You're playing hide and seek.
&lrm;In the closet?
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;[he chuckles]
&lrm;I win, Chloe. I found you.
&lrm;My designer dresses, my heels...
&lrm;You're a monster!
&lrm;You like to walk all over people
&lrm;but you don't like it
&lrm;when others trample on you,
&lrm;do you, Chloe?
&lrm;Do you?
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;Oops, broke your heel,
&lrm;better watch your ankles.
&lrm;Look what the cat dragged in.
&lrm;No cat dragged me anywhere,
&lrm;Cat Noir.
&lrm;I flew in all on my own.
&lrm;What was the secret mission?
&lrm;If I told you, it wouldn't be a secret.
&lrm;This is what's known as
&lrm;the final showdown.
&lrm;The thing is if you knew her,
&lrm;you wouldn't bother saving her.
&lrm;She's the real baddie!
&lrm;It's not true. Everybody adores me.
&lrm;Look out!
&lrm;[she whimpers]
&lrm;The light...
&lrm;- He can't draw in the dark.
&lrm;- Got it.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[crumbling]
&lrm;Here, kitty,
&lrm;a ball and chain to play with.
&lrm;Hey!
&lrm;Sadly, those who get in my way
&lrm;get erased.
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[she whimpers]
&lrm;[ring bleeps]
&lrm;No, no, no...!
&lrm;[Hawk Moth]
&lrm;Cat Noir's Miraculous,
&lrm;take it, take it now!
&lrm;Before you go,
&lrm;you have something I want.
&lrm;Ladybug,
&lrm;this cat doesn't have 9 lives.
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;A bouncy ball?
&lrm;Just try and stop me with that,
&lrm;little lady.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;Gladly.
&lrm;[bouncing and smashing]
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;Hurry!
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you,
&lrm;little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[bubbling]
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;Where am I?
&lrm;POUND IT!
&lrm;[angrily]
&lrm;No!
&lrm;Their Miraculouses were
&lrm;practically mine, and they will be!
&lrm;Once I have them all in my grasp,
&lrm;I will have absolute power!
&lrm;[Ayla]
&lrm;What happened when Ladybug
&lrm;and Cat Noir turned up?
&lrm;To be honest,
&lrm;they only made matters worse.
&lrm;They came barrelling in
&lrm;and started smashing things,
&lrm;throwing balls around.
&lrm;Balls?
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;I hope you had a good time
&lrm;taking care of that thing...
&lrm;I'm really sorry, Sabrina,
&lrm;but I can meet you today
&lrm;to work on the project.
&lrm;Too late. Chloe and I are
&lrm;doing the project together.
&lrm;You mean you're doing it.
&lrm;Of course,
&lrm;after all she's been through.
&lrm;[Marinette groans]
&lrm;Nice new beret.
&lrm;I know. Chloe lent it to me.
&lrm;She really is my BFF.
&lrm;Chloe!
&lrm;Your geography homework's ready.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;Hey, I heard about
&lrm;your adventures with Cat Noir.
&lrm;- Were you scared?
&lrm;- Me, scared?
&lrm;It was a dream...
&lrm;I mean you're a dream...
&lrm;I mean in your dreams.
&lrm;[sighing]
&lrm;This is a nightmare.
&lrm;[uncertainly]
&lrm;OK...
&lrm;So what about Cat Noir,
&lrm;was he awesome?
&lrm;Sure, yeah,
&lrm;but not as awesome as you,
&lrm;because you're
&lrm;the most awesome of awesome.
&lrm;So... that's a yes?
&lrm;[bell rings]
&lrm;Do you realise
&lrm;you just blabbered on to Adrien
&lrm;about how you think he's awesome?
&lrm;He touched me.
&lrm;I'll never wash my jacket again.
&lrm;Girl, you have got to get
&lrm;better control of your emotions.