&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life,
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet,
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Chloe huffs] This is rubbish.
&lrm;I don't have a thing to wear.
&lrm;This one is way too pink,
&lrm;those are so last season,
&lrm;those ones didn't cost enough
&lrm;and these are never in season.
&lrm;I hate all of these!
&lrm;[smashing]
&lrm;Is someone there?
&lrm;[humming]
&lrm;Anybody?
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[cackling] Hey, wait!
&lrm;Come back, shoes.
&lrm;[sobbing] It's not true, I love you.
&lrm;[sad sigh]
&lrm;Look at Chloe.
&lrm;[snoring]
&lrm;That girl's a wreck.
&lrm;Maybe she misses her BFF.
&lrm;Sabrina has been absent
&lrm;since yesterday.
&lrm;[hushing]
&lrm;What is it, Chloe?
&lrm;Someone pulled my hair.
&lrm;I didn't do it, Mrs M.
&lrm;It wasn't her!
&lrm;It's... it's some...
&lrm;invisible, mystical being,
&lrm;like a leprechaun or a unicorn,
&lrm;without the horn.
&lrm;[laughter]
&lrm;Quiet, everyone. Eyes on your papers!
&lrm;[gasping] It's happening again.
&lrm;Chloe, sit down.
&lrm;I can't. My purse is beating me up.
&lrm;Chloe, don't run in the classroom!
&lrm;Get back to your seat.
&lrm;Compose yourself, Miss Bourgois.
&lrm;[laughter]
&lrm;[Chloe screams]
&lrm;[whispering]
&lrm;We've gotta get outta here.
&lrm;Miss, I have to go to the restroom.
&lrm;Thank you.
&lrm;So do I, please.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Somebody seems to have it in for Chloe.
&lrm;The hard part is finding out who doesn't.
&lrm;[phone bleeps]
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;[phone vibrates]
&lrm;[phones ring]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Something strange is going on.
&lrm;Time to transform!
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;Damaging my daughter's reputation is like
&lrm;soiling the reputation of
&lrm;the Mayor of Paris, which is me.
&lrm;An attack on Chloe is an attack on Paris.
&lrm;We'll find the culprit, you have my word.
&lrm;Chloe, my darling,
&lrm;we've got special guests.
&lrm;[excited] Ladybug!
&lrm;I knew you'd save me,
&lrm;considering we're good friends.
&lrm;[Mayor] I had to make an emergency call
&lrm;to all the big designers.
&lrm;Can you imagine my daughter
&lrm;wearing department-store clothing?
&lrm;How humiliating!
&lrm;[camera clicks]
&lrm;[frustrated groan]
&lrm;Have you had any run-ins
&lrm;with anyone lately?
&lrm;I never have run-ins with anyone.
&lrm;Everybody loves me.
&lrm;Really?
&lrm;Not even with your closest friends?
&lrm;Sabrina?
&lrm;[puffing] Impossible.
&lrm;She adores me. I'm her idol.
&lrm;She's safe here with the doors locked.
&lrm;This enemy may be invisible
&lrm;but it can't go through walls.
&lrm;I'm sure you'll make
&lrm;my life perfect again,
&lrm;like it was before.
&lrm;Is something up?
&lrm;She's hiding something.
&lrm;Whatever you tell us stays in this room.
&lrm;She did have a run-in with someone.
&lrm;[lift beeps] Miss Chloe and Sabrina
&lrm;like to impersonate Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;I was playing the part
&lrm;of Big Mustachio that day.
&lrm;Big Mustachio?
&lrm;One of Chloe's ideas.
&lrm;Big Mustachio wants all Parisians
&lrm;to have heinous moustaches.
&lrm;What a hairy situation?
&lrm;Please, go on.
&lrm;[Mrs Chamack] Thank you for this interview
&lrm;about your new album, Mr Stone.
&lrm;Can you tell us how...
&lrm;Jagged Stone?
&lrm;Ladybug,
&lrm;what are you doing here?
&lrm;When I heard you were here,
&lrm;I knew you'd want to see me.
&lrm;I had to come say hello.
&lrm;Well, you did right.
&lrm;What's the deal with your hair?
&lrm;I... the old hair was so drab.
&lrm;This colour is amazing.
&lrm;Don't you think?
&lrm;I've got a few minutes to spare.
&lrm;I'm sure you'd jump at the chance
&lrm;to interview me?
&lrm;Hey, wait.
&lrm;I thought you here to say hi to me.
&lrm;And I did.
&lrm;Now, where were we?
&lrm;She pretended she was me?
&lrm;How often does that happen?
&lrm;She idolises you.
&lrm;Chloe, I've found Big Mustachio.
&lrm;Chloe? But...
&lrm;You're not Ladybug. You're a fake!
&lrm;[Chloe huffs] No, I'm not.
&lrm;I'm Ladybug, look.
&lrm;[Chloe huffs] But, Chloe...
&lrm;How was I supposed to know?
&lrm;That's the problem!
&lrm;You never know anything!
&lrm;That crocodile
&lrm;has a larger brain than you!
&lrm;Get out!
&lrm;I never want to see you again.
&lrm;Mademoiselle does argue
&lrm;with her friend Sabrina at times.
&lrm;I'd say that it's...
&lrm;"the norm",
&lrm;but it was different this time.
&lrm;Sabrina came back the next day.
&lrm;Sabrina who?
&lrm;I don't know any Sabrina.
&lrm;But of course you do, Chloe, it's me...
&lrm;your BFF.
&lrm;You should talk to her. She's right here.
&lrm;I don't see anyone.
&lrm;She must be invisible.
&lrm;As far as I'm concerned
&lrm;she doesn't even exist.
&lrm;This invisible person,
&lrm;it's Sabrina.
&lrm;Who's been akumatised by Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Impossible. She's too weak
&lrm;to do something so bold,
&lrm;especially to me.
&lrm;You're wrong.
&lrm;You've been a great help to us. Thanks.
&lrm;It won't be easy
&lrm;to find someone we can't see.
&lrm;We'll just have to wait
&lrm;for her to find us.
&lrm;And we have an advantage.
&lrm;She doesn't know we're onto her.
&lrm;And now I do, Ladybug.
&lrm;It's time to fulfil
&lrm;our agreement, Vanisher.
&lrm;Cat Noir and Ladybug are at your mercy.
&lrm;Take their Miraculouses
&lrm;and bring them to me!
&lrm;They'll never see me coming, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;The flower... it...
&lrm;[gust of wind]
&lrm;Look out, Ladybug!
&lrm;If it really is you, Sabrina,
&lrm;then I'll be the one to take you down.
&lrm;You didn't get my costume.
&lrm;Now, you'll have to face me.
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;How handy.
&lrm;Looking for me Sabrina?
&lrm;I'm right here. Come on!
&lrm;Oh no, seriously? You need to leave!
&lrm;If you stop this ridiculousness right now,
&lrm;I might let you be my BFF again.
&lrm;[Vanisher]
&lrm;You've got no friends left, Chloe.
&lrm;And you'll never have any ever again!
&lrm;I'll make sure of that.
&lrm;You don't scare me. Everybody loves me.
&lrm;This isn't a game, Chloe.
&lrm;[Ladybug squeals] It's over, Ladybug.
&lrm;Not yet, Vanisher.
&lrm;Just because you see me,
&lrm;doesn't mean you'll defeat me.
&lrm;Look who's come to the rescue.
&lrm;You stay here, don't move!
&lrm;Hey! This concerns me too, you know.
&lrm;Her Akuma's in her bag.
&lrm;Wait, Ladybug,
&lrm;I don't think that's where it is.
&lrm;So you wanna fight after all, Chloe?
&lrm;-Can you handle this?
&lrm;-With pleasure, Milady.
&lrm;Wait! The Akuma must be
&lrm;in the designer pin I got her.
&lrm;It's on her sweater, such an ugly sweater.
&lrm;It was a gift from me.
&lrm;I won't tell you again.
&lrm;You need to leave.
&lrm;You're putting us all in danger.
&lrm;Got it?
&lrm;Why aren't you listening? It's in her pin.
&lrm;That's better.
&lrm;Your days are over, Akuma.
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;[cracking]
&lrm;I knew it.
&lrm;So, who was right then?
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you, little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;Inconceivable! I was so close!
&lrm;[he roars]
&lrm;What happened?
&lrm;What am I doing here?
&lrm;Oh no, it's the brooch Chloe gave me.
&lrm;Why didn't you listen to Chloe?
&lrm;She was trying to help.
&lrm;First, because she put us in danger,
&lrm;and second, she lied to us earlier.
&lrm;I won't listen to a liar.
&lrm;You're calling me a liar?
&lrm;How dare you!
&lrm;I was your hugest fan but not anymore.
&lrm;You don't deserve my devotion!
&lrm;We're live.
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir
&lrm;just defeated Vanisher.
&lrm;Here they are.
&lrm;Ladybug,
&lrm;Is it true you two are very close?
&lrm;I'm through with you, Ladybug!
&lrm;A betrayed Ladybug worshipper...
&lrm;Just what I need to recover
&lrm;from the defeat of Vanisher.
&lrm;This... is... perfect.
&lrm;Fly away, my little Akuma,
&lrm;and evilise her!
&lrm;[she sobs]
&lrm;Antibug, I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Ladybug has let you down.
&lrm;I want her downfall, too.
&lrm;So, shall we defeat Ladybug together?
&lrm;You can count on me, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;There will only be one heroine in Paris,
&lrm;me, Antibug!
&lrm;Cat Noir and I are an unstoppable team.
&lrm;[Chloe blows a kiss]
&lrm;Your time is up, Ladybug.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Excuse me, I've gotta go. Bug out.
&lrm;Thank you, Ladybug.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;If it weren't for me,
&lrm;you wouldn't have defeated Vanisher.
&lrm;And now, I'm going to defeat you!
&lrm;Chloe?
&lrm;Wrong, super-wrong.
&lrm;I am Antibug.
&lrm;We've got an emergency.
&lrm;I'm about to change back.
&lrm;Go, I can take care of her.
&lrm;Look at that.
&lrm;She's nothing without Cat Noir.
&lrm;We'll meet again soon, trust me.
&lrm;It's just you and me, Antibug!
&lrm;I love a good cat fight.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;I don't have any food for you, Tikki.
&lrm;Don't worry, Marinette.
&lrm;You'll find something.
&lrm;I'll try.
&lrm;Ladybug has disappeared.
&lrm;How will Cat Noir get out of this alone?
&lrm;This is all my fault.
&lrm;You don't have to do everything yourself.
&lrm;There's no harm in listening to others.
&lrm;You're right,
&lrm;but first we have to help Cat Noir.
&lrm;We'll find some food at the hotel.
&lrm;[radio crackles]
&lrm;OK... OK...
&lrm;[gasping] Cat Noir!
&lrm;[Antibug giggles]
&lrm;-Hurry up, Tikki.
&lrm;-I'm eating as fast as I can.
&lrm;Aren't you tired
&lrm;of playing second fiddle to Ladybug?
&lrm;And aren't you tired of copying Ladybug?
&lrm;Keep it up, Antibug.
&lrm;Cat Noir is the perfect bait.
&lrm;Team up with me, Cat Noir.
&lrm;Never! Not with a fake like you.
&lrm;Ladybug and I are a team.
&lrm;Let's hope she shows up soon.
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;I know you can hear me, Ladybrat,
&lrm;wherever you are.
&lrm;If you want to keep Cat Noir alive,
&lrm;give me your Miraculous.
&lrm;And if you refuse,
&lrm;take a good look at Cat Noir,
&lrm;because this will be the last
&lrm;time you see him.
&lrm;I'm going to count to ten.
&lrm;One...
&lrm;Can you make it 20?
&lrm;[Chloe] Two...
&lrm;I need more time.
&lrm;Go save Cat Noir.
&lrm;But I can't transform.
&lrm;You are Ladybug,
&lrm;with or without the costume.
&lrm;I think I'd know if I was able to...
&lrm;Three...
&lrm;I'm giving you advice.
&lrm;Now take it,
&lrm;don't make the same mistake twice.
&lrm;Got an idea.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Four...
&lrm;Cat Noir and I,
&lrm;we're an unstoppable team.
&lrm;Ladybug?
&lrm;[sigh of relief]
&lrm;[Marinette gasps]
&lrm;Ladybug.
&lrm;Cat Noir and I,
&lrm;we're an unstoppable team.
&lrm;So, you think
&lrm;you're so smart, do you?
&lrm;Show yourself, bug-face.
&lrm;Ready for round 2?
&lrm;It worked!
&lrm;-I'm fit to go, Marinette.
&lrm;-Yes!
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;[Chloe] Bad kitty,
&lrm;come get your leash back.
&lrm;Sorry, I don't take orders
&lrm;from a mere copycat.
&lrm;Nice yoyo. Mine's better.
&lrm;What kept you?
&lrm;I think the Akuma's in the yoyo.
&lrm;-I think it's in her earrings.
&lrm;-Why?
&lrm;She was wearing them
&lrm;when she was akumatised,
&lrm;and her yoyo was destroyed.
&lrm;Pretty good advice...
&lrm;[bell rings] For a cat.
&lrm;Thanks.
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;Anti-charm!
&lrm;A bag of marbles? What do I do with this?
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;What? You're going to defeat me
&lrm;with marbles? Child's play!
&lrm;That's your downfall.
&lrm;You're so quick to judge.
&lrm;-Over to you!
&lrm;-Got it!
&lrm;[Antibug screams]
&lrm;I'll take that.
&lrm;[pigeons coo]
&lrm;See? You're nothing without your Cat Noir.
&lrm;Cat Noir and I are a team.
&lrm;If you take me on, you take him on too.
&lrm;It's not my problem you have no friends.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Take her Miraculous before it's too late!
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[cracking]
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you,
&lrm;little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous ladybug!
&lrm;What am I doing here?
&lrm;Pound it!
&lrm;Ladybug?
&lrm;Chloe...
&lrm;I'm really sorry.
&lrm;I should have taken your advice.
&lrm;Well, in that case...
&lrm;I might reconsider.
&lrm;Reconsider what?
&lrm;I might just have to stay
&lrm;your most devoted fan after all.
&lrm;Yeah... well...
&lrm;Thanks... I suppose.
&lrm;In that case,
&lrm;let me offer you some advice.
&lrm;you should work things out
&lrm;with your friend, Sabrina.
&lrm;Well, since it's coming from Ladybug...
&lrm;Thanks for your advice, Cat Noir.
&lrm;Course, we're a team, aren't we?
&lrm;[romantic music]
&lrm;[Ladybug] Unstoppable.
&lrm;Bug out!
&lrm;[school bell rings]
&lrm;Hey, here's Antibug.
&lrm;And Vanisher.
&lrm;Now all we need
&lrm;is Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;Well? What are you doing? Sit down.
&lrm;Did you see that?
&lrm;Chloe smiled nicely... kind of.
&lrm;I think she's actually happy
&lrm;to have Sabrina back.
&lrm;Weirdly, I think the feeling's mutual.
&lrm;And put it on your sweater.
&lrm;It'll make it less horrible.
&lrm;Thank you, Chloe.
&lrm;Yeah, yeah, show me your gratitude later,
&lrm;class is starting.
&lrm;I think they'll always be BFFs,
&lrm;in their own way.
&lrm;I still prefer our way.