&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life.
&lrm;But there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Mrs. Bustier]
&lrm;Thanks to Mr. Bourgeois,
&lrm;we're able to have
&lrm;our work experience day
&lrm;at the Grand Paris Luxury Hotel.
&lrm;You will all get hands-on experience
&lrm;with a job at the hotel.
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;You'll be graded on your effort
&lrm;which will affect
&lrm;whether you pass or fail.
&lrm;[chuckling]
&lrm;[Adrien gasps awkwardly]
&lrm;Do you have Marinette
&lrm;and Alya on your list?
&lrm;Doesn't look like it.
&lrm;I bet I know who helped daddy
&lrm;make the assignments.
&lrm;She gets to spend
&lrm;an entire day with Adrien.
&lrm;This is gonna be
&lrm;the worst... day... ever.
&lrm;There must be an oversight.
&lrm;[Chloe]
&lrm;Daddy!
&lrm;Thank you, sweetie.
&lrm;Yes, Alya, you'll be...
&lrm;sorting trash at the dumpster.
&lrm;And Marinette,
&lrm;who will be...
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[excited cry]
&lrm;[rock music]
&lrm;Hey, that's...
&lrm;Excuse me, this is a luxury hotel,
&lrm;[Fang snarls]
&lrm;not a zoo.
&lrm;Daddy!
&lrm;That's Jagged Stone,
&lrm;the rock star.
&lrm;He's sold millions of albums,
&lrm;he's very famous and he's very rich.
&lrm;Mr. Stone,
&lrm;welcome to the Grand Paris Hotel.
&lrm;I am Major Bourgeois,
&lrm;owner of this establishment,
&lrm;the most luxurious in all of Paris.
&lrm;How might we serve you?
&lrm;How d'you think?
&lrm;I'm not here to admire your lobby.
&lrm;Jagged wants
&lrm;your most luxurious suite.
&lrm;Fang better get a real bathtub,
&lrm;not a tiny water hole
&lrm;like the hotel across the street.
&lrm;We have everything you need,
&lrm;Mrs. Fang,
&lrm;even a state-of-the-art
&lrm;fitness centre.
&lrm;Fang is my crocodile.
&lrm;[Fang pants]
&lrm;Mr. Stone, we have all you require
&lrm;[stammering]
&lrm;for your... F-Fang.
&lrm;Would he... enjoy a bubble bath?
&lrm;Crocodiles don't like bubble baths,
&lrm;it dries their scales out.
&lrm;[snarling]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[snarling]
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;No, not him again.
&lrm;Remember me, Mr. Stone?
&lrm;Vincent Asa.
&lrm;Just one photo
&lrm;to show everyone we're best buds.
&lrm;Please, I'm your biggest fan.
&lrm;I know. You've been
&lrm;to my last 36 shows
&lrm;but we are not friends.
&lrm;There, look into the lens.
&lrm;[camera clicks]
&lrm;Didn't you hear him?
&lrm;You still haven't got it, have you?
&lrm;No... photos!
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;Good reflexes.
&lrm;Don't let me see you
&lrm;near Mr. Stone again.
&lrm;Next time you won't get
&lrm;your camera back.
&lrm;[angry sigh]
&lrm;I sense brewing anger
&lrm;and frustration...
&lrm;perfect fodder
&lrm;for my evil little Akumas.
&lrm;It won't be long, now.
&lrm;[mysterious music]
&lrm;Fly away, my little Akuma,
&lrm;and evilise him!
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Pixelator, I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;I'm giving you the power to capture
&lrm;your hero's smile, forever,
&lrm;but in return, you'll need to do
&lrm;some capturing for me as well.
&lrm;Yes, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Yes, yes.
&lrm;[exhausted sigh]
&lrm;Mr. Bourgeois, you haven't told Marinette
&lrm;what she'll be doing.
&lrm;Yes, of course, Marinette...
&lrm;Gofer...
&lrm;I've got a job for you already.
&lrm;Gofer, what's that?
&lrm;I'm guessing
&lrm;it's as bad as trash duty.
&lrm;Mr. Stone needs a new pair
&lrm;of shades for tonight's gig.
&lrm;Red, white and blue,
&lrm;with two Eiffel Towers.
&lrm;-Can you get that?
&lrm;-Of course we can.
&lrm;Marinette is our gofer,
&lrm;she'll take care of it.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;It's an employee who "goes for"
&lrm;anything a customer needs,
&lrm;anything at all!
&lrm;So go ahead,
&lrm;go for it.
&lrm;[nervous giggle]
&lrm;These should do.
&lrm;Now I can get back
&lrm;and hang with Adrien.
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;And Chloe.
&lrm;These aren't even close
&lrm;to what Mr. Stone wants.
&lrm;What do you mean?
&lrm;There's some red and white,
&lrm;and 2 Eiffel towers.
&lrm;I'm just saying it's better
&lrm;to do it right the first time.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Meow.
&lrm;-Where are the Eiffel Towers?
&lrm;-Here.
&lrm;This is a joke, right?
&lrm;Are you trying to ruin my career?
&lrm;But Mr. Stone,
&lrm;the glasses you want don't exist.
&lrm;Do I look like I care?
&lrm;Just get me those sunglasses!
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;Great.
&lrm;Now I'll have to spend
&lrm;even more time away from Adrien.
&lrm;That's what I tried telling you,
&lrm;just do it right the first time.
&lrm;Yeah, you're right Tikki.
&lrm;I get it now.
&lrm;Those sunglasses exist somewhere,
&lrm;get creative.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Of course.
&lrm;Failed as a gofer already?
&lrm;Not surprised.
&lrm;Don't let the door hit you
&lrm;on the way out.
&lrm;Excuse me, sir, can I help you?
&lrm;Look into the lens.
&lrm;Photo finished.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Look what the cat dragged in.
&lrm;Let me handle this, Adrien.
&lrm;Watch and learn.
&lrm;Excuse me!
&lrm;You can't be a guest at this hotel.
&lrm;My father only allows in
&lrm;important celebrities, like me.
&lrm;Well, then, I'm Pixelator,
&lrm;your number one fan.
&lrm;Moi&lrm;? You're flattering me.
&lrm;Keep going.
&lrm;A photo of you, sweet Miss?
&lrm;Chloe, of course.
&lrm;Look out!
&lrm;Look into the lens, Miss.
&lrm;-What the...?
&lrm;-What just happened?
&lrm;I think we've been like... digitised.
&lrm;What do you mean digitised?
&lrm;I don't know
&lrm;but I don't think it's good.
&lrm;Well, I can fix this.
&lrm;Leave it to me.
&lrm;Daddy?
&lrm;Daddy!
&lrm;[Marinette]
&lrm;Where did I put them?
&lrm;Voila!
&lrm;But they're pink.
&lrm;They won't be after.
&lrm;These will be the most amazing
&lrm;or the ugliest pair of shades
&lrm;in shades' history.
&lrm;Mrs. Bustier is grading me
&lrm;on effort, right?
&lrm;Don't worry,
&lrm;I'm sure Jagged will love them.
&lrm;Or hate them.
&lrm;[Chloe huffs]
&lrm;I still can't get through.
&lrm;How can there be no reception?
&lrm;[phone bleeps]
&lrm;Ridiculous!
&lrm;It just goes on forever.
&lrm;No door, no walls, nothing.
&lrm;You mean we're stuck here
&lrm;Just...
&lrm;Just us two?
&lrm;No, there's gotta be a way out.
&lrm;[Chloe sighs]
&lrm;I hope.
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Adrien? Chloe?
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;I bet they've gone somewhere fun.
&lrm;And now I'm here all alone
&lrm;without Adrien.
&lrm;Snap out of it.
&lrm;Let's just focus on getting
&lrm;Mr. Stone his glasses, OK?
&lrm;-Jagged Stone?
&lrm;-What?
&lrm;Look into the lens.
&lrm;I'll get them to Mr. Stone.
&lrm;Can't you deliver them now?
&lrm;He's... resting.
&lrm;Who likes having
&lrm;his belly scratched?
&lrm;Daddy's little Fang?
&lrm;OK, no problem,
&lrm;Just trying to do
&lrm;the job right this time.
&lrm;-Got it.
&lrm;-Thank... you.
&lrm;I hope Mr. Stone likes them.
&lrm;Hard work always pays off.
&lrm;Who are you?
&lrm;Look into the lens.
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Hey there,
&lrm;time for your photo shoot.
&lrm;How did you get in here?
&lrm;What photo shoot?
&lrm;Fang, attack!
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;See you later, alligator.
&lrm;What? Fang? Fang!
&lrm;Who are you?
&lrm;I'm Pixelator,
&lrm;your biggest fan, Mr. Stone.
&lrm;Can I call you Jagged?
&lrm;-No!
&lrm;-I want to immortalize you, Jagged.
&lrm;I'll be your one and only fan.
&lrm;You will belong to me for eternity.
&lrm;Now, look into the lens.
&lrm;So you're Ladybug.
&lrm;I've heard such pathetic
&lrm;things about you.
&lrm;Look into the lens.
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[Jagged Stone yells]
&lrm;[angry groan]
&lrm;Where did they go?
&lrm;If you want Jagged,
&lrm;you must find Ladybug.
&lrm;I don't have time
&lrm;to deal with this Ladybug.
&lrm;Yes you do.
&lrm;[Hawk Moth]
&lrm;Plenty of time!
&lrm;OK, OK.
&lrm;[Pixelator]
&lrm;Tell me what to do.
&lrm;[Hawk Moth]
&lrm;I demand an excellent photo
&lrm;of Ladybug with her Miraculous.
&lrm;[Hawk Moth]
&lrm;I want those powers!
&lrm;So listen very carefully.
&lrm;I can't stay here, I'm performing.
&lrm;You'll get to do your gig.
&lrm;You'll even wear awesome shades.
&lrm;[She chuckles]
&lrm;While I catch Pixelator, stay here.
&lrm;No-one would think to look here.
&lrm;Ladybug, is this safe?
&lrm;This is a school.
&lrm;Yes, Pixelator would never imagine
&lrm;his idol would hang out at school.
&lrm;I mean... isn't school awesome?
&lrm;This is ridiculous.
&lrm;I don't have time for this.
&lrm;First, I get hijacked
&lrm;by this crazed fan,
&lrm;then, I'm attacked
&lrm;by a super-weirdo...
&lrm;Wait, what do you know
&lrm;about this crazed fan?
&lrm;He's come to every one
&lrm;of my shows this year.
&lrm;He's sent me stacks of letters,
&lrm;gone through my trash,
&lrm;he even followed my mother
&lrm;to her weekly bingo night.
&lrm;-How creepy.
&lrm;-Not really.
&lrm;It's just a bunch
&lrm;of elderly ladies having fun.
&lrm;[She groans]
&lrm;Vincent... Asa.
&lrm;Got his address.
&lrm;You're not leaving me here, are you?
&lrm;I mean...
&lrm;isn't... school awesome?
&lrm;Daddy! Daddy!
&lrm;Plagg, I've gotta find
&lrm;some way to transform.
&lrm;Come on, what's the rush?
&lrm;[Angry sigh]
&lrm;Fine, if you insist.
&lrm;At least find me some cheese.
&lrm;I'm gonna see
&lrm;if there's a way out.
&lrm;Don't go anywhere,
&lrm;could be dangerous.
&lrm;Dangerous?
&lrm;Not scared, are you?
&lrm;Scared? &lrm;Moi&lrm;? As if. No way.
&lrm;[He chuckles]
&lrm;[Screeching]
&lrm;The Champs-Elysées... perfect.
&lrm;May the photo shoot begin.
&lrm;Amateur.
&lrm;This isn't creepy at all.
&lrm;What?
&lrm;[Chloe screams]
&lrm;Ladybug?
&lrm;What are you two doing in there?
&lrm;Ladybug, remember me?
&lrm;Your biggest fan.
&lrm;Please get us out of here.
&lrm;It's terrible in here.
&lrm;I mean...
&lrm;only when you're not around.
&lrm;[Man]
&lrm;Over here, Ladybug.
&lrm;[Woman]
&lrm;Help, Ladybug.
&lrm;Help!
&lrm;What happened?
&lrm;It's terrible.
&lrm;This man, he... took a photo of us
&lrm;and we ended up trapped in here.
&lrm;While innocently strolling
&lrm;the Champs-Elysées.
&lrm;I sure hope
&lrm;Cat Noir's there already.
&lrm;Excuse me, sir. Sir?
&lrm;Care for an interview
&lrm;to spread the villain's voice?
&lrm;[Pixelator]
&lrm;I will continue my photo shoot
&lrm;until Jagged Stone turns up.
&lrm;Where are you Jagged?
&lrm;Your biggest fan awaits.
&lrm;All I want is one photo.
&lrm;Otherwise, soon the people of Paris
&lrm;will be nothing but memories.
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;This is terrible.
&lrm;I've gotta do what Pixelator says.
&lrm;Surely you can't be serious?
&lrm;It's dangerous out there.
&lrm;Who cares?
&lrm;Jagged Stone can't turn down
&lrm;a TV appearance.
&lrm;Imagine what it would do
&lrm;for my career?
&lrm;Got an itchy trigger finger, eh?
&lrm;[together]
&lrm;Yeah!
&lrm;I was expecting you, Ladybug.
&lrm;Look into the lens.
&lrm;[He chuckles]
&lrm;I have a proposition to make.
&lrm;If you free those innocent people,
&lrm;I'll organise a photo shoot
&lrm;with Jagged Stone.
&lrm;No! Don't listen to her.
&lrm;She's trying to trick you.
&lrm;Why should I believe you?
&lrm;You have no choice.
&lrm;I'm the only one
&lrm;who knows where Jagged is.
&lrm;How about I free half now
&lrm;and the rest
&lrm;after the photo shoot? Deal?
&lrm;OK, deal.
&lrm;[Under her breath]
&lrm;Yeah, right.
&lrm;[Nino gasps]
&lrm;Dude!
&lrm;[Nino]
&lrm;You scared me.
&lrm;Fill in for me, will you?
&lrm;What do you think
&lrm;I have been doing?
&lrm;I think someone's been akumatised.
&lrm;The question is,
&lrm;where's the Akuma?
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;I kept my part of the deal,
&lrm;now bring me Jagged!
&lrm;Pixelator, I know your Akuma's
&lrm;inside your glasses!
&lrm;Stop wasting time.
&lrm;[Bystander]
&lrm;Yeah, go, Cat Noir!
&lrm;Thanks for dropping in.
&lrm;Not very handy, I see.
&lrm;What about our deal?
&lrm;I told you she'd betray you.
&lrm;Capture them!
&lrm;I want their Miraculous!
&lrm;Together!
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;No, not again.
&lrm;When the cat's away,
&lrm;the mice will play.
&lrm;Ready to become immortalised?
&lrm;Can't wait to live it up.
&lrm;Look into the lens.
&lrm;Hey, Pixelator,
&lrm;I heard you wanted my photo.
&lrm;[Pixelator]
&lrm;Jagged?
&lrm;It's about time you showed up.
&lrm;Get out of here, Mr. Stone!
&lrm;It's me you wanted
&lrm;all this time, right?
&lrm;Well, here I am, in the flesh.
&lrm;Look into the lens.
&lrm;Wait, wrong side.
&lrm;This isn't my best angle.
&lrm;No, wait, the lightings wrong.
&lrm;Does my nose look big?
&lrm;This is better.
&lrm;Hurry up, already!
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;[Gasping]
&lrm;A powder compact?
&lrm;-I think I'm ready.
&lrm;-Stop moving!
&lrm;Look into the lens!
&lrm;Don't do it, Mr. Stone!
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;Yes!
&lrm;[Pixelator]
&lrm;Come on,
&lrm;open your eyes.
&lrm;Batter up!
&lrm;What?
&lrm;[Gasping]
&lrm;How did...
&lrm;Next time, I assure you,
&lrm;it won't be a photo finish.
&lrm;I won't stop Ladybug.
&lrm;I'll destroy you!
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you,
&lrm;little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;[Gasping]
&lrm;What happened?
&lrm;Where am I?
&lrm;[together]
&lrm;Pound it!
&lrm;Thank you for this
&lrm;work-experience day, Mr. Bourgeois.
&lrm;I'm sure we'll all remember it
&lrm;for a long time.
&lrm;So will I.
&lrm;[Discreet coughing]
&lrm;I almost forgot.
&lrm;Jagged Stone's giving
&lrm;a concert tonight.
&lrm;I'm giving tickets to those
&lrm;who showed the most effort.
&lrm;Ri... diculous! Utterly ridiculous!
&lrm;Good evening, Paris!
&lrm;It's my first live concert... ever.
&lrm;It's amazing!
&lrm;Yeah, amazing.
&lrm;This song is for
&lrm;the girl who saved my life,
&lrm;this one's for you, Ladybug.
&lrm;[Piano music]