&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette.
&lrm;just a normal girl
&lrm;with a normal life,
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet,
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Marinette] &lrm;You'll see Tikki,
&lrm;with this app, I'll say it just fine.
&lrm;Welcome to my home.
&lrm;My name is Marinette.
&lrm;[in Chinese]
&lrm;Welcome to my home.
&lrm;My name is Marinette.
&lrm;[in poor Chinese]
&lrm;Welcome to my home.
&lrm;My name is Marinette.
&lrm;No, that's not right.
&lrm;[in Chinese]
&lrm;Welcome to my home.
&lrm;My name is Marinette.
&lrm;Good job, Marinette.
&lrm;I'm so nervous.
&lrm;Do you think he'll like them?
&lrm;Of course, they're fine.
&lrm;They can't be "fine"
&lrm;they have to be perfect.
&lrm;My mom's uncle is
&lrm;a famous Chinese chef.
&lrm;He's very particular
&lrm;so things have to be just right.
&lrm;[doorbell rings]
&lrm;That's him.
&lrm;Hide, Tikki.
&lrm;[in Chinese]
&lrm;Hello.
&lrm;Welcome, Mari. You're at 'nette's.
&lrm;[stammering]
&lrm;Welcome to Marinette's.
&lrm;You're Chinese.
&lrm;No, no, in Mandarin.
&lrm;[in poor Chinese]
&lrm;Welcome to my ho... home...
&lrm;Welcome to my home.
&lrm;My name is Marinette.
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;This is so lame.
&lrm;[app in Chinese]
&lrm;Welcome to my home.
&lrm;My name is Marinette.
&lrm;[app groans]
&lrm;This is so lame.
&lrm;Alya, help me.
&lrm;I don't know what to do
&lrm;with my mom's uncle.
&lrm;I don't think I can pull this off.
&lrm;Chill out, Marinette.
&lrm;I got a solution. Hang tight.
&lrm;[call disconnects]
&lrm;You're amazing. What solution?
&lrm;[doorbell]
&lrm;Hey, Marinette.
&lrm;Adrien!
&lrm;What... What are you...
&lrm;Alya said you need someone
&lrm;who speaks Chinese.
&lrm;Here I am,
&lrm;translator at your service.
&lrm;No? I mean, yes!
&lrm;[phone alert]
&lrm;Where's Alya?
&lrm;[Adrien in Chinese]
&lrm;Is this your first time in Paris?
&lrm;[in Chinese]
&lrm;No, but I last visited 30 years ago.
&lrm;You speak perfect Chinese.
&lrm;[in Chinese]
&lrm;Thanks, Cheng Sifu.
&lrm;[in English]
&lrm;My English very bad.
&lrm;I didn't think you spoke English.
&lrm;Me neither.
&lrm;No, not good. My English not good.
&lrm;[Alec]
&lrm;In the World's Greatest Chef
&lrm;the best chefs in the world
&lrm;will blow your minds
&lrm;with their creations.
&lrm;Cheng Sifu!
&lrm;I'm honoured
&lrm;to have you on our final show.
&lrm;You'll have the chance to defeat
&lrm;all of the chefs
&lrm;who have competed this far.
&lrm;Only one will be named
&lrm;the World's Greatest Chef.
&lrm;The winner's dish will be
&lrm;the new special
&lrm;on Le Grand Paris's
&lrm;restaurant menu.
&lrm;Tell us, Cheng Sifu,
&lrm;what dish are you serving today?
&lrm;[Adrien speaks Chinese]
&lrm;My dish is Celestial Soup.
&lrm;We've heard so much about it.
&lrm;And now we'll get to try it.
&lrm;Shall I come with you?
&lrm;No, thank you, Adrien.
&lrm;Cooking needs no words.
&lrm;Thanks, Adrien.
&lrm;Sorry for bothering you for nothing.
&lrm;I thought
&lrm;he couldn't speak English.
&lrm;No problem.
&lrm;It was awesome to practice
&lrm;my Chinese with the Sifu.
&lrm;The Sifu?
&lrm;It means "master".
&lrm;He's a great master.
&lrm;Well, look who it is.
&lrm;My favourite person,
&lrm;Marinette Dupain-Cheng.
&lrm;Seriously, does your great uncle
&lrm;expect to win with a soup?
&lrm;It's not even a main dish.
&lrm;Can't he make sushi
&lrm;like everyone else?
&lrm;Japanese people make sushi.
&lrm;Cheng Sifu is Chinese.
&lrm;And he's not "like everyone else."
&lrm;He's the best chef in the world.
&lrm;His soup is legendary.
&lrm;Well, I despise soup.
&lrm;So what?
&lrm;Didn't you know? I'm on the jury.
&lrm;Your uncle will not get my vote.
&lrm;Yeah? He doesn't need
&lrm;your vote to win.
&lrm;The other judges have
&lrm;better taste than you.
&lrm;Silly me. You have no taste.
&lrm;Look at your clothes.
&lrm;Don't talk about me like that!
&lrm;You've made a big mistake.
&lrm;You really stood up for Cheng.
&lrm;He would have appreciated that.
&lrm;I'm not sure.
&lrm;I don't think he likes me.
&lrm;No, you're wrong.
&lrm;No, I swear.
&lrm;He ripped up the bouquet I gave him.
&lrm;Cheng Sifu isn't just a chef,
&lrm;he's an artist.
&lrm;He said he was gonna put
&lrm;flowers in his soup.
&lrm;He improvises
&lrm;on fateful things that happen.
&lrm;The flowers must be yours.
&lrm;So... you think
&lrm;he actually likes me?
&lrm;Totally.
&lrm;He's shown you great respect,
&lrm;in his own special way.
&lrm;[Chinese music]
&lrm;[Chinese music continues]
&lrm;Mister Cheng?
&lrm;Marinette's looking for you outside.
&lrm;Let's see if the judges
&lrm;enjoy your uncle's soup
&lrm;after this, Marinette Dupain-Cheng.
&lrm;Marinette wasn't there.
&lrm;No speak Japanese. See ya.
&lrm;Our panel of gourmets
&lrm;is made up of
&lrm;André Bourgeois, mayor of Paris
&lrm;and owner of this luxury hotel
&lrm;his daughter, Chloe,
&lrm;representing her generation,
&lrm;rock star, Jagged Stone
&lrm;and his crocodile, Fang,
&lrm;and finally, the divine head chef
&lrm;of this very hotel,
&lrm;Marlena Cesaire
&lrm;and yours truly, Alec.
&lrm;It's time to determine the fate
&lrm;of the famous Celestial Soup.
&lrm;Let's get tasting!
&lrm;What is this?
&lrm;I don't think it would fare well
&lrm;with our guests.
&lrm;I'll give it 3.
&lrm;Seeing as it seems unappetizing,
&lrm;I'll pass on the tasting
&lrm;but I'll still give it a 0.
&lrm;[spluttering]
&lrm;It's like kissing the singer
&lrm;from the Zombeats... Negative 0.
&lrm;I'm sorry, but it's inedible.
&lrm;I give it one 1.
&lrm;[sighing]
&lrm;I... I...
&lrm;I don't understand.
&lrm;I never put these ingredients in.
&lrm;Someone sabotage soup.
&lrm;Sorry, Chan Sifu,
&lrm;I'm giving you a 0 too.
&lrm;Your score is 0.8 out of 10,
&lrm;the lowest so far.
&lrm;Your Celestial Soup will not be
&lrm;in the hotel's menu.
&lrm;And you will not be named
&lrm;World's Greatest Chef!
&lrm;This isn't right.
&lrm;I'm sure this is Chloe's doing.
&lrm;I'd like to say you're wrong
&lrm;but I know her only too well.
&lrm;Uncle Cheng,
&lrm;I'm sure it's not your fault.
&lrm;I'm sure Chloe's behind this.
&lrm;It was actually because of me.
&lrm;I provoked her.
&lrm;Shame is on Celestial Soup.
&lrm;I shall never be
&lrm;World's Greatest Chef.
&lrm;No, uncle Cheng!
&lrm;It's horrible
&lrm;to lose face in China.
&lrm;We'll wait for him downstairs.
&lrm;A great artist was wronged today.
&lrm;I can feel it.
&lrm;I can hear his heart
&lrm;screaming out for revenge.
&lrm;Fly, my little Akuma,
&lrm;and evilise him!
&lrm;Victory never tasted so good.
&lrm;Marinette was right.
&lrm;It was that evil brat!
&lrm;No respect for Cheng Sifu.
&lrm;Kung Food, I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Those who tasted your soup
&lrm;will become your servants.
&lrm;The one who wronged you
&lrm;will pay dearly.
&lrm;I will show I am
&lrm;greatest chef in the world!
&lrm;[tummy rumbles]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;My guts are killing me.
&lrm;I'm feeling quite uncomfortable.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;You have eaten my soup.
&lrm;You become my servants!
&lrm;At your command, master.
&lrm;Grab the girl!
&lrm;Wait! Calm down.
&lrm;I'm the mayor's daughter, remember?
&lrm;Daddy?
&lrm;Kung Food make new Brat Soup.
&lrm;[Chloe]
&lrm;But I don't like soup!
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Perfect!
&lrm;Soon Ladybug and Cat Noir
&lrm;will show up to meet their doom.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Get out! Hurry!
&lrm;Not polite to leave table
&lrm;without permission.
&lrm;Cut off exits!
&lrm;-What's that?
&lrm;-Caramel?
&lrm;It tastes good but it's indestructible.
&lrm;We're trapped.
&lrm;My uncle's upstairs.
&lrm;Don't worry. I'll go find him.
&lrm;Thanks...
&lrm;I'll... look for a way out.
&lrm;[Kung Food]
&lrm;You will taste Kung Food's soup.
&lrm;Everybody become my servant.
&lrm;And I become
&lrm;World's Greatest Chef!
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Uncle?
&lrm;I shouldn't have riled up Chloe!
&lrm;I've gotta save my uncle.
&lrm;You'll do it, Marinette,
&lrm;I'm sure you will.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;You didn't happen to pick up
&lrm;a little piece
&lrm;of camembert, did you?
&lrm;Cheese comes after the meal.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;-Cat Noir?
&lrm;-Ladybug?
&lrm;I don't know about you
&lrm;but I'm hungry.
&lrm;Let's go eat then.
&lrm;Who are those two?
&lrm;They're Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;They've come to stop you.
&lrm;Add them to your recipe!
&lrm;Surprise ingredients?
&lrm;Delicious!
&lrm;-You, capture them.
&lrm;-Yes, master Kung Food.
&lrm;Brat Soup more powerful
&lrm;with superhero flavour.
&lrm;[Chloe]
&lrm;I will not eat your soup!
&lrm;Foolish girl. You are not eating soup.
&lrm;You are soup!
&lrm;Help! Let me down.
&lrm;Don't worry.
&lrm;You will be let down soon.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;It's jammed.
&lrm;Ladybug, Cat Noir,
&lrm;you soon be ingredients
&lrm;in Kung Food's soup
&lrm;but first,
&lrm;you taste today's special.
&lrm;Seafood Appetisers.
&lrm;Jagged Stone!
&lrm;Seafood? This "scampi" happenin'.
&lrm;Can you carry a "tune-a"?
&lrm;Look out!
&lrm;That's not very rock 'n' roll.
&lrm;Rock is one thing, soup is another.
&lrm;When I'm done with you,
&lrm;you'll be mince-meat.
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;Good job.
&lrm;No time to lose.
&lrm;Chloe may be the main dish.
&lrm;We better not wait to find out.
&lrm;Let me out!
&lrm;This Brat Soup will be
&lrm;Kung Food's masterpiece.
&lrm;Must you tie me up
&lrm;above this foul liquid?
&lrm;My clothes will stink.
&lrm;Soup not greasy at all.
&lrm;Soup very well-balanced.
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;-Let me outta here.
&lrm;-Bad sous-chef!
&lrm;You, do me justice!
&lrm;Yes, master.
&lrm;Ladybug, come on.
&lrm;It's just you and me together.
&lrm;We could go places.
&lrm;Yeah, like up.
&lrm;Yeah, we've nowhere to go but up.
&lrm;You spoke too soon.
&lrm;The electricity between us
&lrm;caused a short-circuit.
&lrm;You wish. More like us getting
&lrm;ourselves into a sticky mess.
&lrm;[lift beeps]
&lrm;Royal hotpot,
&lrm;with its giant smoked sausages.
&lrm;Looks like a food-fight.
&lrm;I prefer my sausages with mash.
&lrm;Welcome to the world-famous
&lrm;Suite 36 of this hotel.
&lrm;If we're not careful,
&lrm;we'll be the mash.
&lrm;You're no competition, Ladybug.
&lrm;Time to pick up the bill, Kung Food.
&lrm;Grab Cat Noir's Miraculous.
&lrm;His ring, bring it to me.
&lrm;Do it now!
&lrm;Wrong superhero, Bourgeois!
&lrm;I bet you don't know how to do this.
&lrm;Really, Ladybug?
&lrm;Nice work, Milady.
&lrm;Shall we go find the head chef?
&lrm;Pea-brain! Useless!
&lrm;My recipe not perfect
&lrm;without those two.
&lrm;Capture them! And don't mess up,
&lrm;or you end up in soup.
&lrm;[together]
&lrm;Yes, master.
&lrm;My hair is ruined.
&lrm;Do you know
&lrm;how long it took to style it?
&lrm;That won't be a problem soon.
&lrm;Ladybug, help me!
&lrm;We're almost there.
&lrm;This fighting has made me hungry.
&lrm;Kung Food is generous.
&lrm;No need to choose
&lrm;between cheese and dessert.
&lrm;You get both.
&lrm;[lift beeps]
&lrm;Watch this spectacular demonstration
&lrm;of the famous Flying Cakes.
&lrm;Our guests seem to have
&lrm;a few tricks up their sleeves
&lrm;but how will they fair
&lrm;against the Stinky Cheese Bomb?
&lrm;These cheese stings your eyes.
&lrm;[Alec laughs]
&lrm;You're no match for my... Hey!
&lrm;It's about time
&lrm;for second course.
&lrm;[Chloe whimpers]
&lrm;Temperature is just right.
&lrm;Time to add main ingredient.
&lrm;No, no, no, no!
&lrm;No!
&lrm;Ladybug? What took you so long?
&lrm;Wait till I tell everyone...
&lrm;Oops.
&lrm;No! My Brat Soup
&lrm;will be so flavourless.
&lrm;You're more honourable than this,
&lrm;Cheng Sifu.
&lrm;I am not Cheng Sifu. I am Kung Food,
&lrm;the greatest chef in world!
&lrm;Nobody will stop me
&lrm;from finishing my Brat Soup!
&lrm;Get back, Chloe.
&lrm;I take care of you two myself!
&lrm;Cat Noir,
&lrm;the Akuma must be in his hat.
&lrm;Try to grab it.
&lrm;It burns!
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Like it spicy?
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;A check?
&lrm;It's gonna be a steep one.
&lrm;Think you can beat me
&lrm;with a piece of paper?
&lrm;You've been trying to defeat us
&lrm;with sausages and cheese
&lrm;without any luck.
&lrm;Cat Noir, destroy his bag.
&lrm;Got it.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;Your days are over, Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;This evil dinner was almost perfect.
&lrm;Revenge is a dish
&lrm;that's best served cold
&lrm;so watch yourself because
&lrm;I'll be ready to strike again!
&lrm;Could you teach me
&lrm;how to make Celestial Soup?
&lrm;With pleasure, Marinette.
&lrm;Cooking needs no words.
&lrm;Seriously? Still making soup?
&lrm;I told you I hate soup.
&lrm;Do you think
&lrm;the jury will approve?
&lrm;Didn't your father
&lrm;kick you off the jury?
&lrm;No, he didn't.
&lrm;I... I... I resigned.
&lrm;I think Cheng and Marinette
&lrm;have it covered.
&lrm;Let's let the real jury decide.
&lrm;Ridiculous!
&lrm;Utterly ridiculous!
&lrm;Cheng Sifu, your Celestial Soup
&lrm;received the highest marks,
&lrm;making you the final winner!
&lrm;And it will be the "Mayor's Special"
&lrm;on the restaurant menu
&lrm;of my prestigious hotel.
&lrm;Rock 'n' roll!
&lrm;I can't wait to get home
&lrm;and write a song about soup.
&lrm;Thank you
&lrm;but no longer Celestial Soup,
&lrm;now called Marinette Soup.
&lrm;[in Chinese]
&lrm;Thank you.
&lrm;You're welcome.
&lrm;Come stand next to your uncle,
&lrm;the World's Greatest Chef.
&lrm;[cheering]