&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl
&lrm;with a normal life,
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Italian accent]
&lrm;Alright!
&lrm;Look at the camera.
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;Perfect.
&lrm;[Italian accent]
&lrm;Say spaghetti!
&lrm;[together]
&lrm;Spaghetti!
&lrm;I'm gonna be in a photo with Adrien.
&lrm;Right... cus it's a class photo
&lrm;and you're in class with Adrien.
&lrm;Amazing, isn't it?
&lrm;Oh... my... gosh.
&lrm;What if we're in the same row together?
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;Girl, you're too funny.
&lrm;Just smile and whatever happens,
&lrm;don't forget to breathe.
&lrm;At least you know
&lrm;you'll be in the photo.
&lrm;No Juleka, I'm telling you,
&lrm;you're not jinxed.
&lrm;This time it'll work out.
&lrm;I can feel it... right here.
&lrm;What's this about being jinxed?
&lrm;[sighing]
&lrm;Ever since I was little,
&lrm;every time someone takes
&lrm;a photo of me
&lrm;something always goes very wrong.
&lrm;You're wrong, Juleka, you'll see.
&lrm;Sure. We'll do all we can
&lrm;to make sure it goes right.
&lrm;Don't forget to smile.
&lrm;Thank you, kids,
&lrm;you've been wonderful.
&lrm;OK, time to flash
&lrm;your pearly whites.
&lrm;You, sit on the front bench.
&lrm;Quickly please.
&lrm;I've 16 other classes to shoot.
&lrm;[chattering]
&lrm;Look Sabrina,
&lrm;they're up front in the baby seats.
&lrm;Go on, rug rats,
&lrm;don't forget to take your thumbs
&lrm;out of your mouths.
&lrm;[photographer]
&lrm;Next row...
&lrm;You, you, you, you and you.
&lrm;Go sit in the rear bench.
&lrm;Wait just a minute.
&lrm;I should be in the middle row,
&lrm;next to Adrien,
&lrm;in the centre, look,
&lrm;we're the same size.
&lrm;No, go stand in the back row
&lrm;behind the rest.
&lrm;How dare you put me behind the rest?
&lrm;-Do you know who my father is?
&lrm;-Is he a photographer?
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;No...
&lrm;-He's...
&lrm;-Bummer,
&lrm;I really need an assistant.
&lrm;Now hurry up or I'll put you
&lrm;up front with "the babies".
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;You boys, go stand in the middle.
&lrm;It's no big deal, Chloe.
&lrm;As long as
&lrm;we're all on the same photo.
&lrm;Perfect!
&lrm;You guys are awesome.
&lrm;Now stop squirming
&lrm;and let's get this photo shot.
&lrm;Excuse me, sir.
&lrm;You forgot Juleka.
&lrm;Sorry, my bad.
&lrm;Go stand in the middle,
&lrm;next to that blond boy.
&lrm;You'll be right in the centre.
&lrm;All eyes will be on you.
&lrm;No more jinxed class photos.
&lrm;This isn't right.
&lrm;Something's wrong.
&lrm;Course it's not working.
&lrm;I'm in the wrong spot.
&lrm;You... move over here, will ya?
&lrm;Let's see.
&lrm;Excuse me, do we have a problem?
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;It doesn't matter where I put him,
&lrm;it throws the picture out of whack.
&lrm;My spot is unacceptable!
&lrm;That's right, Juleka.
&lrm;Don't let her push you out the way.
&lrm;Miss Bourgeois, behave yourself.
&lrm;Nobody asked you, loudmouth.
&lrm;This isn't gym class, Chlo'.
&lrm;You, over here...
&lrm;You, here.. and you... here.
&lrm;There, perfect.
&lrm;No... it isn't.
&lrm;It's not perfect at all.
&lrm;I'm totally not next to Adrien.
&lrm;Chloe, we still have
&lrm;16 classes to photograph.
&lrm;Go ahead, Vincent.
&lrm;Say spaghetti.
&lrm;[together]
&lrm;Spaghetti.
&lrm;[moaning]
&lrm;I don't believe it.
&lrm;I'm sorry,
&lrm;I have to fetch another battery.
&lrm;Nobody move!
&lrm;-Can I go to the bathroom?
&lrm;-Yes, Juleka, but hurry.
&lrm;Miss Bustier, he said nobody move.
&lrm;It's an emergency, Sir.
&lrm;Make sure she...
&lrm;[whispering]
&lrm;doesn't come back.
&lrm;Miss Bustier,
&lrm;I need to go too.
&lrm;[she chuckles]
&lrm;We're back in business.
&lrm;[Chloe giggles]
&lrm;What are you doing?
&lrm;Where's Juleka?
&lrm;How did you get here?
&lrm;Who cares?
&lrm;At last I'm in the right spot.
&lrm;Flash me your best smiles.
&lrm;It's the last time we're doing this.
&lrm;[Chloe giggles]
&lrm;Wait!
&lrm;Thanks, kids.
&lrm;Wait, please, sir,
&lrm;we have to re-do the photo.
&lrm;-Why?
&lrm;-Because Juleka's not in it.
&lrm;Jula who?
&lrm;Juleka, the tall one
&lrm;with purple streaks.
&lrm;[together]
&lrm;Yeah. Where'd she go?
&lrm;Didn't she go to the bathroom?
&lrm;Mr. Damocles,
&lrm;don't we need to be go to lunch?
&lrm;And aren't you paying
&lrm;the photographer by the hour?
&lrm;Yes, no time to re-take it.
&lrm;Class, move along. Hurry up.
&lrm;OK, lunch break.
&lrm;[Rose]
&lrm;Juleka?
&lrm;Juleka? Jule...
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;Poor, sweet Juleka.
&lrm;I missed the photo, didn't I?
&lrm;Yeah, one of Chloe's tricks.
&lrm;Why should I expect it
&lrm;to be different?
&lrm;Nobody ever hears me or sees me.
&lrm;I'm invisible... even in photos.
&lrm;Don't say that, Juleka.
&lrm;It's not true.
&lrm;Forget it.
&lrm;As long as Chloe's in the picture,
&lrm;she'll find a way
&lrm;to keep me out of it.
&lrm;No, wait, Juleka!
&lrm;Really, Rose, forget it.
&lrm;Forget me.
&lrm;Poor girl,
&lrm;feeling so lonely and ignored.
&lrm;How terrible it must be
&lrm;to feel you don't even exist.
&lrm;Come here, my little friend.
&lrm;Fly away, my evil Akuma,
&lrm;and give this transparent soul
&lrm;a voice and a vision!
&lrm;Juleka's been locked
&lrm;in the bathroom.
&lrm;She really does have
&lrm;the "class photo jinx".
&lrm;Of course, I should have known
&lrm;Chloe was behind this.
&lrm;We have to break the curse, Rose.
&lrm;-We can ask the photographer.
&lrm;-He won't want to.
&lrm;Unless... If the photo disappeared,
&lrm;they'll have to shoot another one...
&lrm;with Juleka.
&lrm;You're a genius.
&lrm;But why would the photo disappear?
&lrm;You find Juleka,
&lrm;I'll take care of the rest.
&lrm;She's not ruining
&lrm;my photo next to Adrien.
&lrm;Think of something, fast.
&lrm;Reflekta, I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;From now on,
&lrm;you will be the only one people see.
&lrm;No-one will ever ignore you again.
&lrm;However, you must do me a favour
&lrm;in return... when the time comes.
&lrm;Yes, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;[Marinette]
&lrm;So...
&lrm;the camera stays
&lrm;in the principal's office
&lrm;during lunch break.
&lrm;I refuse to be part of this.
&lrm;There's no time.
&lrm;We must break the "class photo jinx"
&lrm;before the photographer leaves.
&lrm;[Marinette]
&lrm;OK.
&lrm;There must be
&lrm;another way, Marinette.
&lrm;[footsteps approach]
&lrm;I knew this wasn't a good idea.
&lrm;Hello!
&lrm;What? Who? Who are you?
&lrm;Nobody has ever noticed me,
&lrm;but those days are over.
&lrm;From now on,
&lrm;everybody will notice me,
&lrm;because everyone will look like me.
&lrm;Time to get a new look.
&lrm;Soon there'll be nothing
&lrm;but Reflektas everywhere.
&lrm;No need to panic.
&lrm;Who doesn't love
&lrm;an extreme makeover?
&lrm;Nobody leaves here!
&lrm;Soon, all of Paris will
&lrm;look like me,
&lrm;including Miss Chloe Bourgeois.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Beautiful.
&lrm;It won't be long before Ladybug
&lrm;and Cat Noir show up to show their face.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Chloe Bourgeois?
&lrm;Have you seen Chloe Bourgeois?
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;It's blocked.
&lrm;Yo, check it!
&lrm;Cat Noir's gonna save us.
&lrm;OK, change of plan.
&lrm;Help us, Cat Noir.
&lrm;I can't stand being in this body.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[Reflekta]
&lrm;Much better!
&lrm;I hate cats.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;My ring, my Miraculous... it's gone.
&lrm;His Miraculous,
&lrm;you should have taken it
&lrm;before you transformed him!
&lrm;Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
&lrm;[she cackles]
&lrm;Where is Chloe Bourgeois!
&lrm;I know you're in here, Marinette.
&lrm;Come out, now!
&lrm;Hide, Tikki.
&lrm;Caught red handed,
&lrm;Marinette Dupain-Cheng.
&lrm;The principal will love
&lrm;my video of you snooping around.
&lrm;[Sabrina giggles]
&lrm;Stop or the photo disappears,
&lrm;which would be a shame.
&lrm;You look so good next to Adrien.
&lrm;-No!
&lrm;-Hand it over, Chloe.
&lrm;Give me that card.
&lrm;Give me back my phone.
&lrm;Give it me or I'll keep your phone.
&lrm;You can keep it,
&lrm;I'll buy another one.
&lrm;[Reflekta shouts]
&lrm;Chloe! Where are you?
&lrm;What was that?
&lrm;Hey!
&lrm;Don't just stand there, go get her!
&lrm;Where's that pea-brain?
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;There you are, at last.
&lrm;Chloe Bourgeois!
&lrm;Who are you?
&lrm;Take a good look,
&lrm;I'm your future face.
&lrm;Gross.
&lrm;What in the...
&lrm;Do you realise
&lrm;how much my outfit cost?
&lrm;You should thank me.
&lrm;You look much better like this.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[Marinette gasps]
&lrm;Time to transform, Tikki.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;You won't get rid of me
&lrm;by locking me in the bathroom.
&lrm;[Ladybug gasps]
&lrm;Juleka?
&lrm;Juleka, stop this now!
&lrm;I'm not the Juleka
&lrm;nobody notices anymore.
&lrm;Now, I am the unmistakable Reflekta!
&lrm;Before you transform Ladybug,
&lrm;take her Miraculous, the earrings.
&lrm;I'm sure you'll love
&lrm;your new image, Ladybug.
&lrm;Thanks, but no thanks.
&lrm;I prefer the one I've got.
&lrm;You sure? Ask Cat Noir.
&lrm;I'm sure he loves his new look.
&lrm;My powers might be gone
&lrm;but I can't stand by and do nothing.
&lrm;Who invented these things?
&lrm;If you want
&lrm;your faces back, listen.
&lrm;Heard of safety in numbers?
&lrm;Soon, like everyone else,
&lrm;you'll look just like me!
&lrm;But first,
&lrm;I'm going to take
&lrm;your earrings as a trophy.
&lrm;Time to face off!
&lrm;Catch her!
&lrm;[Mob yells]
&lrm;You're no match for me, Ladybug.
&lrm;This will all be over soon for you!
&lrm;[Rose]
&lrm;Are you going to help us?
&lrm;[Nino]
&lrm;We want our faces back.
&lrm;Don't worry, I'll figure it out.
&lrm;Yeah, these shoes kill, milady.
&lrm;Cat Noir?
&lrm;Excuse us. Out of the way.
&lrm;Cat Noir... is it really you?
&lrm;Of course.
&lrm;Can't you tell by my swagger?
&lrm;Am I still the cat's meow?
&lrm;I... don't know what to say.
&lrm;How about a thank you?
&lrm;Sorry Cat Noir, but you...
&lrm;you just don't look yourself.
&lrm;But... thank you.
&lrm;You're welcome.
&lrm;In case you forgot,
&lrm;we've gotta de-akumatise Reflekta.
&lrm;We? Your powers are gone.
&lrm;Are you gonna throw
&lrm;your shoes at her?
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;Who just saved you?
&lrm;I have to find Reflekta.
&lrm;You'd slow me down.
&lrm;Maybe, but you know...
&lrm;sometimes I do have ideas.
&lrm;Ok, yeah, sorry... And?
&lrm;Taking on Reflekta
&lrm;face to face isn't the best idea
&lrm;unless you want a facelift too.
&lrm;You're right.
&lrm;And that gives me an idea.
&lrm;Where we headed?
&lrm;To the TV station.
&lrm;Here goes.
&lrm;Watch your nails.
&lrm;Your jokes are so lame.
&lrm;You haven't just lost your body,
&lrm;you've lost
&lrm;your sense of humour too.
&lrm;[French accordion music]
&lrm;People of Paris.
&lrm;Reflekta is not invincible.
&lrm;You can help.
&lrm;Just put on a disguise.
&lrm;Then I'll spot the real Reflekta
&lrm;and bring her down.
&lrm;Everybody must look like me.
&lrm;Even you, Mr. Mayor.
&lrm;Remember, put on a disguise.
&lrm;You're no match for Ladybug.
&lrm;Now why would you say that
&lrm;when she's just given away
&lrm;her secrets?
&lrm;Ladybug will save us.
&lrm;Ladybug won't be saving anybody.
&lrm;Don't let Ladybug
&lrm;get away this time
&lrm;or I'll remove your powers!
&lrm;I'm relying on you all.
&lrm;[Cat Noir]
&lrm;And cut.
&lrm;Got it.
&lrm;Sorry but isn't your plan
&lrm;a bit complicated?
&lrm;It's not my real plan.
&lrm;The real plan is
&lrm;now that Reflekta knows
&lrm;we're at the TV station,
&lrm;she'll come to get us.
&lrm;And fall into our claws.
&lrm;You mean, into your nails.
&lrm;[Marinette giggles]
&lrm;Still not funny.
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;The Akuma has to be
&lrm;in her bracelet.
&lrm;Check mate, Reflekta.
&lrm;This isn't the real one.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[mayor]
&lrm;I'm sorry.
&lrm;She promised she'd change me back
&lrm;if I tricked you.
&lrm;Mayor Bourgeois?
&lrm;Look out!
&lrm;I've already been changed
&lrm;so I'm safe.
&lrm;Thanks, Cat Noir.
&lrm;Go ahead, use that charm of yours.
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;A camera?
&lrm;OK?
&lrm;Cat Noir,
&lrm;Turn off the lights, quick.
&lrm;Over here, Reflekta.
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you,
&lrm;little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;-You were awesome, Cat Noir.
&lrm;-And with those shoes on too.
&lrm;They should be illegal.
&lrm;Where... where am I?
&lrm;[together]
&lrm;Pound it!
&lrm;Could you take this girl
&lrm;back to school, please?
&lrm;Yes, of course, Ladybug.
&lrm;Thank you.
&lrm;See you later, Cat Noir.
&lrm;Bug out.
&lrm;You might have pulled
&lrm;it off today, Ladybug,
&lrm;but everything isn't always
&lrm;as it seems.
&lrm;Watch out Ladybug,
&lrm;I'll destroy you
&lrm;when you least expect it.
&lrm;You were right, Tikki.
&lrm;Stealing this was wrong.
&lrm;You won't erase the photo?
&lrm;No, I've got another idea
&lrm;which I think you'll approve of.
&lrm;That's my girl.
&lrm;Here, you can have this back.
&lrm;Ready?
&lrm;Hey, you dropped this.
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;Grazie.
&lrm;I know you're busy
&lrm;but a girl wasn't
&lrm;in the photo you took.
&lrm;Can we do it again?
&lrm;Well... I'm already running late,
&lrm;with everything
&lrm;that's been going on and...
&lrm;Mr. Damocles.
&lrm;I understand but...
&lrm;could you do it after school?
&lrm;We could do it in the park.
&lrm;Well...
&lrm;We want an awesome photo
&lrm;by the best photographer.
&lrm;Please.
&lrm;Well, when you put it that way,
&lrm;OK!
&lrm;OK, we're all good here.
&lrm;Ready?
&lrm;This was a good idea, Marinette.
&lrm;Thanks, Adrien.
&lrm;Like I'd want to be part
&lrm;of their stupid photo anyway.
&lrm;Ridiculous... utterly ridiculous.
&lrm;The "class photo curse" is broken.
&lrm;Thank you, Marinette.