&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl
&lrm;with a normal life,
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet,
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;Welcome.
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir
&lrm;have saved Paris once again.
&lrm;Mr. Duparc was akumatised into
&lrm;the Magician of Misfortune,
&lrm;threatening to make
&lrm;the Eiffel Tower vanish.
&lrm;[sneezing]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[shivering]
&lrm;Tikki,
&lrm;you don't look well.
&lrm;I need you to take me to a doctor.
&lrm;But where will I find
&lrm;a doctor for kwamis?
&lrm;I know a healer.
&lrm;I'll tell you where to go.
&lrm;What will I tell him?
&lrm;You're a secret.
&lrm;He'll ask questions.
&lrm;And I know someone else
&lrm;who'll ask a lot of questions,
&lrm;my teacher,
&lrm;about why I'm late again.
&lrm;Tikki, can I take you to the healer
&lrm;right after school?
&lrm;Thank you.
&lrm;Combustion is a high-temperature
&lrm;exothermic redox chemical reaction
&lrm;between a fuel and an oxidant,
&lrm;usually atmospheric oxygen.
&lrm;Today, Prince Ali,
&lrm;of the Kingdom of Atchoo,
&lrm;will do the honours
&lrm;during his Parisian visit
&lrm;by hosting a toy fundraiser
&lrm;for Paris Children's Hospital.
&lrm;He's so gorgeous,
&lrm;and with a heart of gold.
&lrm;I'm going to write him a letter
&lrm;professing my adoration
&lrm;and utmost respect.
&lrm;Marinette, what's your excuse this time?
&lrm;Locked yourself
&lrm;in the bathroom again?
&lrm;No, of course not.
&lrm;I had to... take my dog... to the vet,
&lrm;because he... ate a wool sweater.
&lrm;Thank you, Rose,
&lrm;the class doesn't need
&lrm;extra refreshing.
&lrm;I thought someone had
&lrm;a tuna sandwich,
&lrm;but it turns out
&lrm;it's Rose's perfume.
&lrm;Ate a sweater?
&lrm;Using your phone
&lrm;during school hours is forbidden.
&lrm;Take your things
&lrm;and go to the principal's office.
&lrm;Watch what happens when you play
&lrm;with flammable substances
&lrm;in a chemistry lab.
&lrm;To make sure you remember,
&lrm;I'll quiz you on lab safety,
&lrm;again.
&lrm;Dude!
&lrm;You two are made for each other.
&lrm;You're both always late.
&lrm;As he missed class, it'd be sweet
&lrm;if some lady could lend him
&lrm;her notes so he can get up to speed?
&lrm;You're right...
&lrm;Oh, you mean for me
&lrm;to give him my notes?
&lrm;No, I can't, I...
&lrm;Your excuses don't work on me.
&lrm;[Tikki sneezes]
&lrm;[sneezing]
&lrm;I think I'm getting sick.
&lrm;Then don't breathe on him.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;[Tikki sneezes]
&lrm;I'm not feeling too good.
&lrm;Don't worry, Tikki,
&lrm;it'll just take...
&lrm;[Tikki groans]
&lrm;You OK? Nothing broken?
&lrm;Yeah... I'm fine.
&lrm;Marinette...
&lrm;Sabrina,
&lrm;what's Prince Ali doing today?
&lrm;A toy drive
&lrm;at the Children's Hospital.
&lrm;What kind of stuffed animal is this?
&lrm;Who left this here?
&lrm;The prince will never have seen
&lrm;one like this before.
&lrm;And when he sees me,
&lrm;Prince Ali will forget
&lrm;all about those sick kids.
&lrm;Did I hear you say Prince Ali?
&lrm;Not to you.
&lrm;Prince Ali's staying
&lrm;at Chloe's dad's hotel.
&lrm;The only hotel fit for a prince
&lrm;and I'll be the first to meet him.
&lrm;Please, could you give him
&lrm;a special letter?
&lrm;No prob.
&lrm;That is so sweet of you
&lrm;to do that for me.
&lrm;You thought I was serious?
&lrm;You think I want to
&lrm;get anywhere near this fish funk?
&lrm;[Marinette] Tikki?
&lrm;Chloe, wait up! That's my...
&lrm;Not anymore. Finders keepers.
&lrm;Tikki.
&lrm;Now there's a broken-hearted
&lrm;princess if ever I saw one.
&lrm;Every rose has its thorns.
&lrm;Fly away, my little Akuma,
&lrm;and evilise her!
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Princess Fragrance, I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Your perfume is now
&lrm;your secret weapon.
&lrm;No-one will be able to resist it,
&lrm;especially Prince Ali.
&lrm;All I want from you,
&lrm;are Ladybug and Cat Noir's Miraculous.
&lrm;I'm coming, my prince.
&lrm;Hello, I'm in Chloe's class.
&lrm;I really have to see her.
&lrm;Are you a friend?
&lrm;A friend of Chloe's?
&lrm;You must be kidding.
&lrm;I mean, we're in the same class.
&lrm;If you're not a friend,
&lrm;then I can't.
&lrm;Yes, I'm a friend of Chloe's.
&lrm;We're BFFs.
&lrm;Chloe doesn't have any friends.
&lrm;Does that mean...
&lrm;you're not letting me in?
&lrm;No.
&lrm;Got a pizza for Chloe Bourgeois.
&lrm;It's usually sushi.
&lrm;Top floor, imperial suite.
&lrm;Yes, yes, yes.
&lrm;[lift beeps]
&lrm;Here's a gift for the sick children,
&lrm;Prince.
&lrm;It's nothing, really.
&lrm;Stop flattering me.
&lrm;No.
&lrm;There, that's better.
&lrm;[lift beeps]
&lrm;Chloe!
&lrm;Wait!
&lrm;Pizza?
&lrm;Don't get that peasant food near me.
&lrm;Wait! It has truffles
&lrm;and caviar on it,
&lrm;for spoilt brats like you.
&lrm;I've come to see Prince Ali.
&lrm;What is going on today?
&lrm;Do you have an appointment?
&lrm;No need. I'm his princess.
&lrm;And I'm a monkey's uncle.
&lrm;That's no way so speak
&lrm;to a princess!
&lrm;[singing]
&lrm;At your service, Princess Fragrance.
&lrm;A thousand times better.
&lrm;Now,
&lrm;where is my wonderful Prince Charming?
&lrm;We can't keep him waiting.
&lrm;In honour of your presence
&lrm;here in Paris, Your Highness,
&lrm;I've taken it on myself
&lrm;to organise a fireworks display
&lrm;on the Seine River.
&lrm;They will be displayed
&lrm;from this barge.
&lrm;Thank you...
&lrm;How do we say in your language?
&lrm;Totally awesome!
&lrm;We'll see if it fits in
&lrm;with his schedule.
&lrm;We have little time for festivities.
&lrm;His Highness
&lrm;has many responsibilities.
&lrm;[Chloe coughs]
&lrm;[Chloe hums]
&lrm;Prince Ali, allow me to introduce you
&lrm;to my own princess. Chloe.
&lrm;[questioning sigh]
&lrm;Prince, I've brought you
&lrm;a special stuffed toy
&lrm;for the sick children.
&lrm;I've never seen one like this.
&lrm;It's very kind of you.
&lrm;You're flattering me.
&lrm;It is so kind of me though,
&lrm;isn't it?
&lrm;Yes, I say that.
&lrm;You did not hear me?
&lrm;[cameras click]
&lrm;Nadia Chamack, don't be bemused
&lrm;it's just &lrm;The News&lrm;.
&lrm;Anything to say
&lrm;about your official Parisian visit?
&lrm;[Prince Ali]
&lrm;I'm happy to be here.
&lrm;Prince Ali, where is...
&lrm;that smell coming from?
&lrm;Like rotten fish.
&lrm;[gagging]
&lrm;What? That's not me.
&lrm;It is me!
&lrm;[singing]
&lrm;At your service, princess fragrance.
&lrm;Who are you?
&lrm;I'm Princess Fragrance.
&lrm;I've come just for you.
&lrm;In just a spritz,
&lrm;you'll be my Prince Ali.
&lrm;This is bad.
&lrm;What or who is that? Plagg?
&lrm;Plagg?
&lrm;There's trouble in Paris.
&lrm;I'm still chewing.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[mayor]
&lrm;Prince, this way.
&lrm;We're safe.
&lrm;It's a reinforced door.
&lrm;So much chaos.
&lrm;How is one supposed to stick
&lrm;to a schedule around here?
&lrm;What is that?
&lrm;[hissing]
&lrm;Get back!
&lrm;[singing]
&lrm;My prince, my prince,
&lrm;smell the fragrance of my eternal love.
&lrm;[vacuum cleaner]
&lrm;[Princess Fragrance]
&lrm;Seriously?
&lrm;Who are you?
&lrm;Looks like you're powerless now.
&lrm;No!
&lrm;There are two of them now. Run!
&lrm;[singing]
&lrm;You can't escape my perfume.
&lrm;[humming]
&lrm;[Princess Fragrance]
&lrm;Get them.
&lrm;[singing]
&lrm;At your service, Princess Fragrance.
&lrm;[Chloe]
&lrm;He's under the spell.
&lrm;Shut the door.
&lrm;-But it's your father.
&lrm;-Who cares?
&lrm;Shut it now!
&lrm;[servant]
&lrm;At your service.
&lrm;[singing]
&lrm;Come into my arms,
&lrm;my sweet prince.
&lrm;[Cat Noir gags]
&lrm;Can we get some fresh air in here?
&lrm;No-one will take my prince away!
&lrm;Emergency evacuation.
&lrm;Everybody down.
&lrm;It's much too dangerous
&lrm;for the prince.
&lrm;[Cat Noir]
&lrm;You're right...
&lrm;safety first.
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;[cry of joy]
&lrm;My prince!
&lrm;Tikki, please be OK.
&lrm;Can we open the windows?
&lrm;This fish smell
&lrm;is even too much for a cat.
&lrm;[Tikki sneezes]
&lrm;We've 9 minutes
&lrm;to get to the hospital,
&lrm;we're on a strict schedule.
&lrm;No way we can go
&lrm;go to the hospital now.
&lrm;We gotta get Prince Ali
&lrm;out of Paris.
&lrm;My prince, fancy seeing you here,
&lrm;what luck.
&lrm;The windows!
&lrm;I'll take you to the Pont des Arts
&lrm;where we'll seal our love.
&lrm;Cat Noir is down.
&lrm;It won't be long
&lrm;before Ladybug shows up too
&lrm;and meets her doom.
&lrm;[evil laugh]
&lrm;No. Where's Tikki?
&lrm;Tikki?
&lrm;Tikki, I was so worried.
&lrm;Marinette...
&lrm;You're worse than I thought.
&lrm;We need to get help.
&lrm;[Tikki]
&lrm;We have no time.
&lrm;You need to transform.
&lrm;I'll be OK.
&lrm;[coughing]
&lrm;I'm not making
&lrm;the same mistake twice.
&lrm;We've got to get you
&lrm;to the healer, now.
&lrm;[Chinese gong rings]
&lrm;Is she gonna be OK?
&lrm;One who burns with impatience
&lrm;can never eat hot porridge.
&lrm;What has this got to do with eating?
&lrm;Silence, please.
&lrm;Reading energies...
&lrm;What type of cat did you say?
&lrm;Cat?...
&lrm;rare hairless flying species
&lrm;from the Kingdom of Atchoo.
&lrm;I won one in a zoo tap-dancing
&lrm;contest when I was in... Atchoo.
&lrm;I see, unusual.
&lrm;Yes, yes, very.
&lrm;[gong rings]
&lrm;We are finished.
&lrm;Your cat's health has been restored.
&lrm;[Tikki mumbles]
&lrm;Thank you so much.
&lrm;You're a real magician, sir.
&lrm;How did you do that?
&lrm;Ancient Chinese secret.
&lrm;Just like yours.
&lrm;Tikki, I'm so sorry.
&lrm;You were so sick and...
&lrm;I don't know
&lrm;what I'd do without you.
&lrm;You wouldn't be Ladybug, for one.
&lrm;I know, but I mean...
&lrm;Tikki, you're more
&lrm;than just my kwami to me.
&lrm;I know.
&lrm;The Pont des Arts bridge,
&lrm;That's where they're headed.
&lrm;I heard it in the car.
&lrm;Hurry, we've no time to lose.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;I can't wait for us
&lrm;to be together forever.
&lrm;Servant, love padlock, please.
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;This will lock our love forever,
&lrm;my prince.
&lrm;[singing]
&lrm;At your service, Princess Fragrance.
&lrm;[Princess Fragrance]
&lrm;My padlock!
&lrm;Not so fast,
&lrm;royal pains in the neck.
&lrm;[angry growling]
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] Use Cat Noir
&lrm;to get Ladybug's Miraculous.
&lrm;Servants, attack!
&lrm;And take her earrings!
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;Snap out of it, Cat Noir.
&lrm;It's me, Ladybug.
&lrm;[singing]
&lrm;Give me your Miraculous.
&lrm;Who needs a padlock
&lrm;to secure our love
&lrm;when I can put everyone
&lrm;under my spell
&lrm;and make Paris our kingdom?
&lrm;[hissing]
&lrm;I'd better do something
&lrm;before this whole thing
&lrm;blows up in my face.
&lrm;Watch what happens when you play
&lrm;with flammable substances...
&lrm;Can't hit me.
&lrm;Missed.
&lrm;Yeah!
&lrm;Nice of you to drop in.
&lrm;[singing]
&lrm;Give me you Miraculous.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[fizzing]
&lrm;[loud explosion]
&lrm;This city's not for us.
&lrm;Too many people want to bother us.
&lrm;Let's go far away from here,
&lrm;my prince, very far.
&lrm;Leaving so soon?
&lrm;The party just got started!
&lrm;You? You are ruining everything!
&lrm;So now I'll ruin you!
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;A balloon?
&lrm;What do I do with this?
&lrm;You can't escape, Ladybug
&lrm;It's over!
&lrm;What the...?
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you,
&lrm;little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;What am I doing here?
&lrm;And where's Ladybug?
&lrm;The schedule's a complete disaster.
&lrm;We're going to be late
&lrm;for everything.
&lrm;Where's the Prince?
&lrm;Wait a minute... where am I?
&lrm;[Prince Ali]
&lrm;How did I get here?
&lrm;[Rose gasps]
&lrm;Prince Ali?
&lrm;And who are you?
&lrm;Never mind, I'll leave you
&lrm;with your biggest fan.
&lrm;Bug out!
&lrm;You know how you're always helping
&lrm;sick children?
&lrm;I want you to know
&lrm;that you are the most
&lrm;kind-hearted person
&lrm;I have ever met.
&lrm;Really?
&lrm;Prince Ali!
&lrm;You're safe.
&lrm;Aren't you glad I'm safe too?
&lrm;Shall we continue
&lrm;where we left off?
&lrm;No, thank you.
&lrm;I have a special event
&lrm;at the hospital with Miss Rose.
&lrm;Let us go quickly
&lrm;before my chaperone locates me.
&lrm;Bye, Chloe.