&lrm;In the daytime I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Marinette]
&lrm;"Leo, your heart's gonna roar."
&lrm;Wow, roar.
&lrm;FYI, Marinette's never gonna
&lrm;fall in love with a statue.
&lrm;You know I'm no good with the ladies,
&lrm;especially this one all of a sudden.
&lrm;Do I go up to her and crack a joke?
&lrm;Shoot her a compliment?
&lrm;Invite her to the zoo? Play it serious?
&lrm;Nino, you're over-thinking this.
&lrm;Invite her to the zoo? Seriously?
&lrm;Well, they have a cool new exhibit.
&lrm;Listen, just be yourself, man.
&lrm;Easy for you to say,
&lrm;Mr. Front-Cover-Teen-Model.
&lrm;I'm not that cool.
&lrm;You're cool too, dude,
&lrm;or you wouldn't be my best bud.
&lrm;Invite her to the zoo.
&lrm;She'll say yes, I promise.
&lrm;What if I act like a moron
&lrm;or she kisses me or thinks I'm lame?
&lrm;OK, I got your back.
&lrm;[chuckling]
&lrm;[students chatter]
&lrm;-He's such a...
&lrm;-Smart, hot, swave spell-binder.
&lrm;All the above.
&lrm;-So sorry... right, Nino?
&lrm;-S-Sorry.
&lrm;[together] -Sorry.
&lrm;Sorry about that.
&lrm;How could we make it up to you?
&lrm;Any ideas, Nino?
&lrm;[Nino murmurs]
&lrm;How about we all check out the zoo?
&lrm;They have a new...
&lrm;T-T-They've got a new panther.
&lrm;Awesome idea, right, Marinette?
&lrm;You love animals.
&lrm;Yeah, I'm really into zoonimals.
&lrm;I mean... anizools, I mean zoonimals.
&lrm;Cool, say after school, four o'clock?
&lrm;Nino, sound good?
&lrm;Cool, four o'clock.
&lrm;Four! Four o'clock.
&lrm;[dazed] Yeah.
&lrm;Earth to Marinette.
&lrm;Do you realise the guy
&lrm;you're crazy about asked you out?
&lrm;[dazed] Yeah.
&lrm;Wait... What? No!
&lrm;Not like this. Not today.
&lrm;I haven't washed my hair.
&lrm;I'm not wearing my lucky socks.
&lrm;Help me Alya.
&lrm;I can't do this alone.
&lrm;How did you do that?
&lrm;-Like I said, just be yourself.
&lrm;-Right.
&lrm;Sure... If I could be yourself.
&lrm;Myself don't work that way.
&lrm;Don't be ridiculous, of course you can.
&lrm;When you're alone with Marinette...
&lrm;What? Alone?
&lrm;No, dude, you're coming too.
&lrm;You can't leave me alone, no way.
&lrm;OK, Nino. What are friends for?
&lrm;[crackling] &lrm;One, two, one, two, testing.
&lrm;Do you read me?
&lrm;I can hear you.
&lrm;but I don't think I can do it.
&lrm;Of course you can. Just be yourself.
&lrm;Remember the last time I did that?
&lrm;Just be yourself, Marinette.
&lrm;[nervous giggle]
&lrm;Hey! What are you doing in here?
&lrm;Get out!
&lrm;Fine, just be yourself
&lrm;but look where you're going.
&lrm;Where are you, love of my life?
&lrm;How can he be the love of your life
&lrm;if you can't even talk to him?
&lrm;Tikki, stay hidden.
&lrm;I'm gonna talk to him.
&lrm;You'll see. I will talk to him.
&lrm;That's right, girl, way to be motivated.
&lrm;Yeah.
&lrm;There they are.
&lrm;Hi, Marinette.
&lrm;False alarm.
&lrm;Hi, Kim, Max, what are you doing?
&lrm;We heard the new panther's here.
&lrm;I wanna see who's strongest.
&lrm;Wanna come?
&lrm;-Target at ten o'clock.
&lrm;-No!
&lrm;I mean,
&lrm;thanks but no thanks.
&lrm;I'm waiting for someone. Go ahead.
&lrm;OK. Maybe see you later.
&lrm;Yeah, later.
&lrm;Where's Adrien?
&lrm;I don't know.
&lrm;Hey, Nino. Isn't Adrien with you?
&lrm;Say you'll be better off
&lrm;without me.
&lrm;We'll be better off without me.
&lrm;This is turning out to be
&lrm;more interesting than I thought.
&lrm;Turn up the volume.
&lrm;Without him, I mean.
&lrm;We don't need him to hang out at the zoo.
&lrm;Of course we do, dumbo.
&lrm;Of course we do, dum...
&lrm;I mean, wasn't he meant to come?
&lrm;Do you wanna wait?
&lrm;Tell her you want to be alone with her.
&lrm;-Not yet.
&lrm;-What?
&lrm;You're right. We'll wait.
&lrm;No. What are you talking about?
&lrm;Don't wait, I'm not coming.
&lrm;Look what Daddy's brought you.
&lrm;Only the finest for my baby.
&lrm;Wow! Look at the size
&lrm;of that piece of meat.
&lrm;Typical diet for a feline
&lrm;requiring the strength to run at 60mph.
&lrm;60mph? Is that all?
&lrm;I thought they ran faster than that.
&lrm;I bet I could beat it.
&lrm;Impossible.
&lrm;No human could compete with my panther.
&lrm;Yeah? Where did your cat come
&lrm;at the county athletics?
&lrm;I came first.
&lrm;You can't compare yourself
&lrm;to my panther, kiddo.
&lrm;No need.
&lrm;I'm obviously the better looking one.
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;Hey, kitty. How about a little race?
&lrm;Last one's a rotten egg.
&lrm;Let's see. With a 6ft per second wind
&lrm;and the sun at 45 degrees...
&lrm;You wouldn't be a rotten egg,
&lrm;you'd be lunch.
&lrm;Your friend's right. Now leave.
&lrm;She needs to eat in peace.
&lrm;You're stressing her out.
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;Stressed out are we, Miss Panthy?
&lrm;It's a wild animal, dude.
&lrm;[roar]
&lrm;Leave now
&lrm;or I'll have you kicked out of the zoo.
&lrm;[mockingly] Come on, Max.
&lrm;Let's leave that poor kitty alone
&lrm;with its angry babysitter.
&lrm;[chuckling]
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;[evil voice]
&lrm;Unleashing the animal in each of us.
&lrm;I like that idea.
&lrm;Go ahead, my little evil Akuma,
&lrm;fly off and take control
&lrm;of that zoo keeper.
&lrm;He's sure taking his time, isn't he?
&lrm;He's not coming, is he?
&lrm;Repeat after me.
&lrm;Yes, he is but first I wanted to...
&lrm;Yes, he is
&lrm;but first I wanted to...
&lrm;tell you that I love you.
&lrm;tell you that I...
&lrm;I... love a girl
&lrm;but don't know how to tell her.
&lrm;What are you doing?
&lrm;You do? Well, I can help you with that.
&lrm;You could?
&lrm;You? Give expert advice on love?
&lrm;Can't wait to hear it.
&lrm;[mockingly] Can't wait to hear it.
&lrm;What?
&lrm;Can't wait to hear...
&lrm;about this lucky girl.
&lrm;[nervously] Yeah.
&lrm;-Tell her, It's you.
&lrm;-It's youuu...
&lrm;[Nino] uuur...
&lrm;...your best friend Alya.
&lrm;What?
&lrm;Alya? Awesome.
&lrm;No! No! It's not awesome.
&lrm;I can fix a date for you.
&lrm;Say what! Seriously?
&lrm;You didn't even ask me!
&lrm;No way. Nino's like a brother to me.
&lrm;No! End of discussion.
&lrm;-He'll be so sad.
&lrm;-What did you say?
&lrm;I said...
&lrm;it'll be sad not to tell her.
&lrm;Animan,
&lrm;I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;I offer you the power to seek revenge...
&lrm;for a small price.
&lrm;[evil voice] Yes, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;Hey, kiddo, still up for a race?
&lrm;Go ahead, I'll give you a head start.
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;He's mine.
&lrm;This whole date thing with Nino
&lrm;is not happening!
&lrm;[screaming] He's coming!
&lrm;[Nino screams]
&lrm;[elephant trumpets]
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;We'd better ditch this place.
&lrm;Why didn't you listen to Alya?
&lrm;I couldn't help it.
&lrm;I didn't want Nino to be sad.
&lrm;We'll deal with that later.
&lrm;It's time to transform.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;We've got to do something.
&lrm;[sigh]
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;You lost, kiddo.
&lrm;What do you think of panthers now?
&lrm;[whimpering] That panthers are the best.
&lrm;What do you think about ladybugs?
&lrm;And another black cat?
&lrm;I think I'm higher on the food chain.
&lrm;Animan, take their jewels.
&lrm;their Miraculouses.
&lrm;Bring them to me!
&lrm;If you value your life,
&lrm;get out of here now.
&lrm;Cat Noir,
&lrm;the Akuma must be inside his bracelet.
&lrm;You hold him. I'll grab the bracelet.
&lrm;[roaring] Attack!
&lrm;We need to get them back in their cages.
&lrm;Really?
&lrm;I'm sure they won't put up a fight.
&lrm;We'd better split up.
&lrm;What the...?
&lrm;Stay put, you'll be safe.
&lrm;Hey, what's up?
&lrm;[Ladybug] There are too many.
&lrm;We can't capture them all.
&lrm;What are we gonna do?
&lrm;Back to plan A.
&lrm;If we can destroy his bracelet,
&lrm;I can capture the Akuma.
&lrm;-Everything will go back to normal.
&lrm;-Good idea.
&lrm;-But it's unbreakable.
&lrm;-He didn't break it.
&lrm;-How did he get away?
&lrm;-I don't know.
&lrm;We'd better find Kim...
&lrm;I mean that boy, before he does.
&lrm;Over there.
&lrm;[Kim whimpers]
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;It's down to the two of us, kiddo.
&lrm;[Animan] And then there was one.
&lrm;You're not getting away this time.
&lrm;Quick,
&lrm;hide in the first place you come to.
&lrm;You'll never get me.
&lrm;[bubbling]
&lrm;[eagle screams]
&lrm;-Now we know how it got away.
&lrm;-Where's Kim?
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Good job, kitty.
&lrm;[sobbing] Help! Rescue me, please.
&lrm;It's OK. Come this way.
&lrm;[snarling]
&lrm;He's safe here.
&lrm;Panthers can't open doors.
&lrm;But what if he morphs
&lrm;into a smaller animal, like a mouse?
&lrm;Right...
&lrm;but we have an advantage over him.
&lrm;We know where to find his prey.
&lrm;He'll sniff him eventually
&lrm;but it's bought us some time.
&lrm;[bear groans]
&lrm;[he screams]
&lrm;We must stop Animan
&lrm;before Paris becomes a jungle.
&lrm;[Ladybug] Follow me.
&lrm;Hi, mo... madam.
&lrm;But you're...
&lrm;You're Ladybug.
&lrm;Yeah, exactly.
&lrm;This is a special news flash.
&lrm;Animals are invading Paris.
&lrm;The police are hard at work
&lrm;trying to contain the situation.
&lrm;Stay indoors and remain calm.
&lrm;Mayor Bourgeois will...
&lrm;You're safe here.
&lrm;Can I borrow this?
&lrm;Sure.
&lrm;Come on, Cat Noir.
&lrm;Lock the doors and windows.
&lrm;We'll do the rest. You'll be safe.
&lrm;Thanks, da... sir,
&lrm;for all your help.
&lrm;You're welcome, Ladybug.
&lrm;And voilà.
&lrm;What's that stuff?
&lrm;Air freshener. It'll cover our scents.
&lrm;Thanks, I always wanted
&lrm;to smell like an ocean breeze.
&lrm;Could we capture him in this?
&lrm;Only until he turns into something bigger.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Would that be big enough?
&lrm;Yes, but how do we get him inside?
&lrm;He's coming.
&lrm;[eagle screams]
&lrm;It's working. He's sniffing out Kim.
&lrm;[sniffing]
&lrm;[he giggles]
&lrm;Follow me.
&lrm;[eagle screams]
&lrm;A ladybug? Smart choice.
&lrm;Couldn't he have chosen a slower animal?
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;[snarling]
&lrm;Where's the button for the doors?
&lrm;Of course,
&lrm;there's no key.
&lrm;Take his Miraculous, the ring, the ring!
&lrm;The transformations are tiring him out.
&lrm;It'll be easier to get his Akuma.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[explosion]
&lrm;It's not exactly a cage but... it'll do.
&lrm;I don't think he can "bear"
&lrm;to listen to that noise.
&lrm;You're too much to bear.
&lrm;Now we wait.
&lrm;Ready to free the Akuma?
&lrm;It's working.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;Since when do extinct animals count?
&lrm;T-Rex might be extinct
&lrm;but it's still an animal.
&lrm;I know some other animals that will soon
&lrm;be extinct, the cat and the ladybug!
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;A car jack?
&lrm;Too bad he doesn't have a flat tire.
&lrm;Look how small his front arms are.
&lrm;So he can't play basketball.
&lrm;What are you getting at?
&lrm;Climb on top of him
&lrm;where he can't get you.
&lrm;While you're distracting him
&lrm;I'll floor him.
&lrm;Sounds like a plan.
&lrm;I can be very distracting.
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;[Cat Noir] It's gonna be tight.
&lrm;[Cat Noir yells]
&lrm;It's weird we didn't need this.
&lrm;What does it mean?
&lrm;I guess it means we rock as a team.
&lrm;Wait!
&lrm;I know what to do.
&lrm;Ladybug!
&lrm;Enjoy your meal!
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;No!
&lrm;You'll pay for this!
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you,
&lrm;little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;-Pound it?
&lrm;-Ladybug!
&lrm;That was a wild ride.
&lrm;[they chuckle]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Woops.
&lrm;Better take off.
&lrm;See you next time, Cat Noir.
&lrm;-What happened to me?
&lrm;-Everything's OK.
&lrm;Go back to the zoo
&lrm;to check on your animals.
&lrm;You ruined everything, Ladybug.
&lrm;This is not how it was supposed to end!
&lrm;But, I promise you,
&lrm;one day it will be me
&lrm;at the top of the food chain
&lrm;and you'll be nothing!
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;No, I forgot about Alya.
&lrm;She's gonna be so mad.
&lrm;Imagine if she knew
&lrm;you shut her up in the cage with Nino.
&lrm;[phone continues]
&lrm;Yeah, she'd kill me.
&lrm;Guess I'll take mad.
&lrm;Listen Alya, I'm sorry about earlier.
&lrm;I shouldn't have told Nino
&lrm;I'd set up a date.
&lrm;I wasn't thinking.
&lrm;I'll explain everything to him
&lrm;so don't worry.
&lrm;Do you forgive me?
&lrm;[they giggle]
&lrm;Thanks, Nino.
&lrm;Do you want one?
&lrm;What's he doing here?
&lrm;Ladybug shut us
&lrm;in the same cage all afternoon.
&lrm;Turns out, we've tons in common.
&lrm;You know, the girl I've a crush on...
&lrm;Oh, yeah.
&lrm;Actually, it was you.
&lrm;That's what I thought
&lrm;but after being with Alya,
&lrm;We don't have to give her all the details.
&lrm;My bad.
&lrm;The funniest part
&lrm;was that Nino was being coached
&lrm;-by Adrien.
&lrm;-Adrien was there?
&lrm;Yeah, lol.
&lrm;Alya tells me
&lrm;you're crushin' on some dude.
&lrm;He doesn't know who,
&lrm;pinkie swear because...
&lrm;I don't make decisions for other people.
&lrm;If you want I can make it happen.
&lrm;-That is if I know the dude.
&lrm;-Nino!
&lrm;Fine, forget I said anything.
&lrm;But if I can help...
&lrm;[Alya] Nino!