&lrm;In the daytime I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[peaceful music]
&lrm;[Mrs. Bustier]
&lrm;I'm pleased with your assignments.
&lrm;Some of you have stepped up.
&lrm;I do appreciate it.
&lrm;Let's move on to the next assignment.
&lrm;Is Marinette still in the girls' room?
&lrm;I don't know, Miss.
&lrm;[bell rings]
&lrm;I want you to read chapter three
&lrm;of "France: The First Thousand Years".
&lrm;Then answer this simple questionnaire.
&lrm;See to it that Marinette receives it.
&lrm;It's Marinette, leave a message.
&lrm;Marinette?
&lrm;Have you seen Marinette?
&lrm;No.
&lrm;[humming]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[whispering]
&lrm;Chloe's Ladybug?
&lrm;Marinette, ring me ASAP.
&lrm;We gotta talk.
&lrm;- Nino, wait!
&lrm;- Yeah?
&lrm;Come, I need your help.
&lrm;- So...
&lrm;- Shhh.
&lrm;It's Marinette. Leave a message.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;I hate when she goes AWOL.
&lrm;Where is that girl?
&lrm;Adrien's the exact same way.
&lrm;You get sly when Mr. Control-Freak
&lrm;is your Daddy-o.
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;[TV announcer]
&lrm;Once again
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir have saved Paris.
&lrm;I think I've just sniffed out
&lrm;who the real Ladybug is!
&lrm;[Nino sighs]
&lrm;Chloe.
&lrm;[laughing]
&lrm;Chloe? Seriously?
&lrm;She's too self-absorbed
&lrm;to save the world.
&lrm;You are cray-cray, Lady.
&lrm;[Alya] I am so not, you'll see.
&lrm;Time flies when you're saving
&lrm;the world. Day's already over.
&lrm;I missed an entire half a day of school
&lrm;and of seeing Adrien!
&lrm;Whoever is behind all this
&lrm;is keeping us on our toes.
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;You don't have any toes.
&lrm;Alya brought back your schoolbag.
&lrm;- Hey, mom.
&lrm;- You seem so forgetful these days.
&lrm;You need some extra exercise
&lrm;for that growing brain of yours.
&lrm;Good idea, mom. I'll start tomorrow.
&lrm;Ladybug saved Paris from destruction,
&lrm;but who's gonna save me
&lrm;from my homework?
&lrm;What's this?
&lrm;"Call me, I know
&lrm;who the real ladybug is."
&lrm;No way. You think she knows?
&lrm;I doubt it. Alya always jumps
&lrm;to conclusions too fast.
&lrm;[Tikki]
&lrm;But just in case.
&lrm;No worries. I got it covered.
&lrm;[beeping]
&lrm;Dang. No signal.
&lrm;Sorry, Miss.
&lrm;Cell tower maintenance.
&lrm;No signal for the next hour.
&lrm;Try again later.
&lrm;Let's finish your homework.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;Hey there. Hi.
&lrm;You look totally fab. No, not you.
&lrm;It's still a month from Halloween.
&lrm;If she's a superhero,
&lrm;then I'm the Wizard of Oz.
&lrm;I'm telling you she's Ladybug.
&lrm;Can you prove it?
&lrm;What time is it?
&lrm;School starts in...
&lrm;An hour ago!
&lrm;Don't mess up your lines.
&lrm;[he groans and giggles]
&lrm;[he stutters]
&lrm;Ladybug! Look over there.
&lrm;[questioning sigh]
&lrm;What kind of lame joke is this?
&lrm;Wh-What I meant was...
&lrm;did you see Ladybug yesterday?
&lrm;Isn't she amazing?
&lrm;I wonder who she really is.
&lrm;Up too late DJing, Nino?
&lrm;Obviously, you didn't get
&lrm;your beauty sleep.
&lrm;[camera click]
&lrm;Chloe!
&lrm;Alya's looking in your locker.
&lrm;That's a lie, I so was not.
&lrm;Give it back!
&lrm;[he giggles]
&lrm;Who's the little liar now?
&lrm;She's guilty of invasion
&lrm;of privacy. I have proof!
&lrm;What? All I did
&lrm;was take a measly photo.
&lrm;I'm sorry, there's no policy
&lrm;on invasion of privacy.
&lrm;Then breaking and entering.
&lrm;I didn't break into her locker.
&lrm;It was open.
&lrm;Nothing was stolen?
&lrm;Only my very soul.
&lrm;My locker is my secret garden.
&lrm;He who enters uninvited
&lrm;burglarizes my inner being.
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;Right. An hour of detention, Alya.
&lrm;Are my ears failing me?
&lrm;One miserable hour of detention
&lrm;to a heinous criminal?
&lrm;Sabrina.
&lrm;The rules state
&lrm;that any student guilty of theft
&lrm;shall be suspended one week.
&lrm;Yes, but she hardly stole...
&lrm;I'm not sure that my father would agree.
&lrm;[principal]
&lrm;Well...
&lrm;now let's not bother your father,
&lrm;the Honorable Mayor,
&lrm;with a minor locker situation.
&lrm;[he hesitates]
&lrm;What I mean is...
&lrm;[clearing his throat]
&lrm;You're suspended for a week.
&lrm;That is so unfair, I'm gonna
&lrm;protest this on the school blog.
&lrm;[Chloe hums]
&lrm;The school blog is suspended as well.
&lrm;[angrily]
&lrm;She's no superhero!
&lrm;She's super-psycho!
&lrm;[evil voice]
&lrm;School life...
&lrm;Such a science experiment.
&lrm;A Petri dish of cultivating secrets,
&lrm;lies and betrayal.
&lrm;A thriving vivarium
&lrm;for my evil little Akumas.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Fly way, my little Akuma
&lrm;and evilize her.
&lrm;I'm late, I'm so, so late.
&lrm;[Marinette pants]
&lrm;[Alya pants]
&lrm;[Alya sighs]
&lrm;It's Marinette, leave a message.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[Hawk Moth]
&lrm;Lady Wifi,
&lrm;I heard that you're seeking
&lrm;to unmask Ladybug.
&lrm;I'd like to help you
&lrm;if you help me, too.
&lrm;I'll expose the lies of anyone
&lrm;who covers up the truth.
&lrm;Sign me up.
&lrm;-Where is she?
&lrm;-She's been suspended.
&lrm;What!
&lrm;Marinette,
&lrm;would you come late discreetly?
&lrm;Sorry...
&lrm;What happened?
&lrm;Accused of breaking
&lrm;into Chloe's locker...
&lrm;I mean Ladybug's locker.
&lrm;What!
&lrm;Marinette, go to the principal's office!
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;What are you talking about?
&lrm;Alya says Chloe is Ladybug, bro.
&lrm;She is crazy.
&lrm;[tinkle]
&lrm;Mr. Damocles?
&lrm;Sir?
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[stuttering]
&lrm;[fizzing]
&lrm;I'm Lady Wifi,
&lrm;Revealer of the Truth.
&lrm;Your principal would like to share
&lrm;a tidbit with you.
&lrm;So, Mr. Damocles,
&lrm;is it true you wrongly suspended
&lrm;a student named Alya?
&lrm;Yes, it is.
&lrm;So you were biased, unfair,
&lrm;totally unjust?
&lrm;Yes, I was.
&lrm;Oh no, Alya.
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;You're going to fight your best friend.
&lrm;No, I'm gonna save my best friend.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;Yeah!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Now, I'll be taking you to meet the girl
&lrm;who's been hiding
&lrm;behind the Ladybug mask.
&lrm;[Damocles yells]
&lrm;Stay connected.
&lrm;[Mrs. Bustier]
&lrm;Everyone go directly home, now.
&lrm;Don't forget to read chapters 4 and 5.
&lrm;If Chloe is Ladybug,
&lrm;Lady Wifi is gonna head
&lrm;for her house.
&lrm;It also means
&lrm;you have a crush on Chloe.
&lrm;[Plagg giggles]
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[Chloe yells]
&lrm;What? This can't be.
&lrm;[Ladybug]
&lrm;Who's being sneaky now?
&lrm;Oh, Ladybug... but...
&lrm;You don't actually believe
&lrm;she's the real Ladybug.
&lrm;Yeah, of course not.
&lrm;Who would believe
&lrm;she's the original Ladybug?
&lrm;She's just a diehard fan.
&lrm;A copy... cat.
&lrm;Right.
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Hello?
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;Well, hello there, Ladybug.
&lrm;[Chloe yells]
&lrm;We've got Wifi.
&lrm;Well, well, so my hunch
&lrm;was correcto-mundo.
&lrm;Everyone thinks Ladybug masks
&lrm;a little angel.
&lrm;Think again, people.
&lrm;[Lady Wifi] The real Ladybug is
&lrm;Chloe Bourgeois, everyone.
&lrm;Who are you?
&lrm;[mumbling]
&lrm;I thought you were Ladybug.
&lrm;Sorry to bust your news story.
&lrm;Next time double-check your facts.
&lrm;You'll be sorry.
&lrm;[Chloe yells]
&lrm;Alya?
&lrm;Alya's been disconnected.
&lrm;I'm Lady Wifi.
&lrm;Newsflash. Ladybug,
&lrm;let's find out who you really are.
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;Follow me.
&lrm;[Cat Noir] What's the plan?
&lrm;Her powers come from her phone.
&lrm;In the basement, there's no service.
&lrm;[Cat Noir]
&lrm;No service, no power. Nice one.
&lrm;We have to go lower.
&lrm;[Lady Wifi] I've got you, Ladybug.
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;Get ready.
&lrm;What do you do
&lrm;when you're not Ladybug?
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;We're a bit busy right now.
&lrm;[fast footsteps]
&lrm;She's back in the hotel.
&lrm;[Cat Noir] She locked the doors.
&lrm;You realize we might know
&lrm;each other in real life?
&lrm;[Ladybug] I doubt it. It's locked.
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Not this one.
&lrm;[Ladybug] Get ready for an ambush.
&lrm;One, two, three!
&lrm;So much for the ambush.
&lrm;[Ladybug] Follow me.
&lrm;Where is she hiding?
&lrm;And what's up with all these phones?
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;How now brown cow?
&lrm;I thought it was you she was after.
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;[Lady Wifi] You can't get me.
&lrm;Yes, I can.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;No, no, no.
&lrm;Hold on in there, Ladybug!
&lrm;Of course, the service elevator.
&lrm;[banging]
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;Who is Ladybug?
&lrm;Is she a superhero or a super-weirdo?
&lrm;How can we trust the girl
&lrm;when we have no idea who she is?
&lrm;We have the right to know.
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;Why doesn't it come off?
&lrm;Because it's magic?
&lrm;[beeping]
&lrm;[Cat Noir]
&lrm;You're out of minutes, Lady Wifi.
&lrm;How romantic.
&lrm;Tomcat's come to save his lovebug.
&lrm;I am not his lovebug.
&lrm;We'll come back to that later.
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[Plagg shivers]
&lrm;Oh, my ring.
&lrm;[Plagg pants]
&lrm;So chilly in here.
&lrm;[Adrien]
&lrm;Where is it? I could use help.
&lrm;[Lady Wifi]
&lrm;What am I gonna do with both of you?
&lrm;[Hawk Moth]
&lrm;Get her to use her lucky charm.
&lrm;She'll switch back,
&lrm;her identity will be revealed
&lrm;and the Miraculous will be mine.
&lrm;If you don't get him out fast,
&lrm;he'll soon be slush.
&lrm;[she cackles]
&lrm;Good luck with your cat-popsicle.
&lrm;I have other news to cover.
&lrm;[police sirens]
&lrm;[Mayor] Come on!
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;[Lady Wifi]
&lrm;What's up, peeps?
&lrm;Listen everyone. I present you
&lrm;with an award-winning news story.
&lrm;[banging and panting]
&lrm;I'll get you out, Cat Noir.
&lrm;[shivering]
&lrm;Take your time.
&lrm;Ladybug is about to drop the bomb
&lrm;on her real identity.
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;This better be some lucky box.
&lrm;[clinking]
&lrm;Of course, the microwaves.
&lrm;Gotcha. Gotcha!
&lrm;Come on, micro-thingies,
&lrm;jam the signal.
&lrm;[fizzing]
&lrm;[shivering]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;You OK, Cat Noir?
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;You used your lucky charm.
&lrm;There's not much time.
&lrm;Exactly.
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Zap open the door.
&lrm;We can't, the microwave's busted.
&lrm;[whispering]
&lrm;Here's what we'll do.
&lrm;Got it.
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;What is she up to?
&lrm;Don't let my Miraculous get away.
&lrm;Right.
&lrm;I'll jam the wifi antenna.
&lrm;Good luck.
&lrm;[elevator beeps]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[buzzing]
&lrm;Here you are.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;Nice idea, kitty-cat
&lrm;but I won't let you
&lrm;cut me off so easily.
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Hurry, Cat Noir.
&lrm;No!
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;Lost the signal.
&lrm;Give me that phone!
&lrm;[evil laugh]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you,
&lrm;little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilize!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;What?
&lrm;Pound it!
&lrm;Ladybug, wow... and Cat Noir!
&lrm;Can I get a quick interview?
&lrm;I'll grab my phone.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Gotta go.
&lrm;You've only got a minute.
&lrm;So... No, where did they go?
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Stay. I won't tell anyone
&lrm;who you are, cat's honor.
&lrm;Nobody must know who we really are,
&lrm;not even us.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;[Tikki sighs]
&lrm;That was close.
&lrm;Tell me about it.
&lrm;[comic music]
&lrm;You were about to know
&lrm;who your love is.
&lrm;What were you thinking?
&lrm;That's the thing.
&lrm;I wasn't thinking. I followed my heart.
&lrm;Your mask will fall one day, Ladybug.
&lrm;Then you'll have to hand over
&lrm;your precious Miraculous.
&lrm;[Tikki]
&lrm;Is that true? You're gonna tell him?
&lrm;Is that what your heart says?
&lrm;Your heart tells you one thing,
&lrm;but a superhero listens to her head.
&lrm;[Alya] Got it!
&lrm;My new smartphone puts
&lrm;the old one to shame.
&lrm;Just look at these pics.
&lrm;What's with all these photos
&lrm;of Adrien?
&lrm;Well... with a mask and a costume...
&lrm;doesn't he look like Cat Noir?
&lrm;Are you out of your mind?
&lrm;He's tons more legit than Cat Noir.
&lrm;I happen to think
&lrm;that Cat Noir is pretty slick.
&lrm;Stop taking photos of Adrien...
&lrm;unless you give them to me.
&lrm;-Give it back!
&lrm;-No.
&lrm;Come on, what if you drop it?
&lrm;You're so clumsy.
&lrm;[they giggle]
&lrm;[cheerful music]
&lrm;[lively music]