&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life,
&lrm;but there's something
&lrm;that no-one knows yet,
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir
&lrm;saved Paris again.
&lrm;And yet again, I hope I have time
&lrm;to finish my magic box.
&lrm;[Tikki]
&lrm;What's it for?
&lrm;To lock up my diary and secrets.
&lrm;[Tikki]
&lrm;Every secret?
&lrm;You write everything in there?
&lrm;Well... yeah. Why?
&lrm;First, what if someone finds out
&lrm;you're Ladybug?
&lrm;And two, what if
&lrm;someone finds out your ladybag?
&lrm;Not gonna happen. Try it.
&lrm;Hey!
&lrm;It works.
&lrm;Mr. Bourgeois was re-elected
&lrm;as mayor of Paris for the 4th term.
&lrm;Here, we see him with his daughter.
&lrm;Look at Chloe.
&lrm;acting as if she were the mayor.
&lrm;Which reminds me,
&lrm;class elections are tomorrow!
&lrm;What's bad about that?
&lrm;Chloe is running for class rep,
&lrm;the person who cares about herself
&lrm;more than students.
&lrm;Well, maybe you should run.
&lrm;I totally would
&lrm;but I've enough to do
&lrm;with Ladybug and my schoolwork.
&lrm;But if you believe in something,
&lrm;you have to try.
&lrm;It's better to fail trying
&lrm;than not trying.
&lrm;Maybe.
&lrm;Don't underestimate yourself.
&lrm;Mr. D'Argencourt,
&lrm;Bourgeois's opponent,
&lrm;and a fencing instructor
&lrm;at Françoise Dupont school,
&lrm;was pummelled in the polls,
&lrm;with the least number
&lrm;of votes in Paris history.
&lrm;I'm gonna be late for school, again.
&lrm;See? This is what I'm talking about.
&lrm;[teacher] Chloe is running
&lrm;for class representative.
&lrm;Sabrina will be her deputy.
&lrm;Any other candidates?
&lrm;- Yes, Kim?
&lrm;- N-Nothing.
&lrm;I'm sorry. I...
&lrm;The bus...
&lrm;[coughing]
&lrm;Dry throat.
&lrm;Chloe is running again.
&lrm;She's been class rep
&lrm;since kindergarten.
&lrm;[gasping] Why don't you run?
&lrm;You'd be an awesome rep.
&lrm;No can do. My blog is a full-time job.
&lrm;[teacher] Alright,
&lrm;I'll give you
&lrm;until the end of lunch to decide.
&lrm;[Chloe] Or I'll tell everyone.
&lrm;[chattering]
&lrm;What did Chloe say this time?
&lrm;She offered to go on a date you?
&lrm;She said she'd tell everyone
&lrm;I'm afraid of spiders.
&lrm;She said I'd get kicked out
&lrm;of Scrapbooking Club.
&lrm;And you know I love all that
&lrm;colourful paper and gluing.
&lrm;I don't care about running.
&lrm;What's your excuse?
&lrm;[hesitantly] Well, I'm ... really busy.
&lrm;With what, oversleeping?
&lrm;Well, no... but...well...
&lrm;I guess I would run if no one else did.
&lrm;Do any new candidates
&lrm;want to run against Chloe?
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;[sigh] No.
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;Chloe and Sabrina are the only candidates,
&lrm;so there's no vote. Chloe, Sabrina...
&lrm;I'll run!
&lrm;Wonderful! Develop your campaign
&lrm;and have a speech ready
&lrm;for tomorrow when we vote.
&lrm;[chattering]
&lrm;Let's hear the scoop on your campaign.
&lrm;How are you gonna represent?
&lrm;Represent?
&lrm;I have no idea.
&lrm;I can't believe I raised my hand.
&lrm;Way to go, Marinette.
&lrm;You spoke from the heart.
&lrm;It was truly authentic.
&lrm;[gasping] Oh... thanks.
&lrm;When you win, can we get new chairs?
&lrm;Ours are so hard I can't think.
&lrm;Maybe pink ones!
&lrm;Could we listen to music in the library?
&lrm;[mumbling] You know... I... you know.
&lrm;[nervous laugh] Sure, Juleka.
&lrm;Adrien!
&lrm;Can Marinette count on your vote?
&lrm;Sure, depending on her speech.
&lrm;Better get cracking then.
&lrm;I've watched how my daddy wins elections.
&lrm;I'm going to follow in his footsteps.
&lrm;I know just how to win.
&lrm;By having the best campaign?
&lrm;Whatever!
&lrm;The secret to winning
&lrm;is ruining your opponent's reputation.
&lrm;Softer chairs...
&lrm;music in library,
&lrm;whatever Juleka said.
&lrm;I'm writing down all the issues.
&lrm;I just have to get it all in my speech.
&lrm;I'm proud of you. I'm sure you'll win.
&lrm;You'll be an awesome rep.
&lrm;They're relying on me to defeat Chloe,
&lrm;even Adrian, do you realise that?
&lrm;[phone vibrates]
&lrm;- &lrm;Marinette, battles on.
&lrm;- Why?
&lrm;Chloe invited everyone
&lrm;to her campaign launch.
&lrm;She's got Jagged Stone coming.
&lrm;Seriously? Jagged Stone my favourite star.
&lrm;I love him!
&lrm;[groaning] As does everyone else.
&lrm;She's trying to buy votes with autographs.
&lrm;Not if I have anything to say about it.
&lrm;Meet you there.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[bell rings]
&lrm;I'm going in, Chloe.
&lrm;- Hello.
&lrm;- Hi, there.
&lrm;Marinette borrowed my math book
&lrm;but I need it back.
&lrm;She isn't here.
&lrm;I've got customers to attend to.
&lrm;Go on up if you don't mind.
&lrm;I'd be glad to, thanks.
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;Wow, Mr. D'Argencourt.
&lrm;You're on fire. That was some attack.
&lrm;It ought to be. This manoeuvre
&lrm;was developed by my ancestor,
&lrm;- Darkblade.
&lrm;- Darkblade?
&lrm;Darkblade conquered Paris
&lrm;and ruled over it with an iron fist
&lrm;until he was overthrown
&lrm;by a wealthy Frenchman
&lrm;who used gold to buy
&lrm;the loyalties of the people.
&lrm;Not long ago, my ancestors' flag
&lrm;was waving above Paris.
&lrm;Is that why you ran
&lrm;in the election, to seek revenge?
&lrm;Par le fer.
&lrm;Who dost we have hither?
&lrm;Nadia Chamack.
&lrm;Don't be bemused, it's just The News.
&lrm;Do you have anything to say about
&lrm;your "landslide defeat"?
&lrm;Hey, you. How did you get in here?
&lrm;- &lrm;Time to go.
&lrm;- Get back here.
&lrm;Here endeth the lesson.
&lrm;[evil voice] A loser and an utter failure,
&lrm;the perfect candidate
&lrm;to lobby my own campaign.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Fly away, my evil little Akuma,
&lrm;and take control of this defeated fighter.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Mr. D'Argencourt, someone said
&lrm;"You're stuck in the dark ages."
&lrm;What do you have to say to that?
&lrm;Poisonous wretch.
&lrm;Stop thou venomous questions?
&lrm;Be gone, you pain in the neck!
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] Darkblade,
&lrm;in return for these powers,
&lrm;capture Ladybug's
&lrm;and Cat Noir's Miraculouses.
&lrm;When the flag of mine ancestors
&lrm;flies once again upon City Hall,
&lrm;then to thee I shall be indebted.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Anything y-you'd like to say
&lrm;about your transformation
&lrm;- into a...
&lrm;- Darkblade,
&lrm;the Lord of Paris.
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Thou shalt become mine knights.
&lrm;Soon mine army shalt be
&lrm;immense and unstoppable.
&lrm;We shalt take City Hall
&lrm;and reclaim the throne
&lrm;from Bourgeois, the usurper.
&lrm;[Plagg] That's some medieval madness.
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;What a great beast
&lrm;to join our conquest.
&lrm;[chanting]
&lrm;PAR LE FER! PAR LE FER!
&lrm;[D'Argencourt]
&lrm;Let us to battle, knights!
&lrm;PAR LE FER!
&lrm;The people chose Bourgeois over you.
&lrm;Thy peoples matter not to me.
&lrm;D'Argencourt was defeated,
&lrm;not Darkblade.
&lrm;En garde!
&lrm;Chloe,
&lrm;I'm in. What am I looking for?
&lrm;Anything,
&lrm;as long as it's totally embarrassing.
&lrm;Wait... I have one just like this.
&lrm;How about... a ball of yarn?
&lrm;Or a screwdriver.
&lrm;No, dingbat, a disgusting photo of her,
&lrm;or some tacky clothing.
&lrm;Dig around a bit.
&lrm;[gasping] How about her diary!
&lrm;Wow, you can actually do something
&lrm;when you put my mind to it.
&lrm;[shrieking]
&lrm;Sabrina? Sabrina!
&lrm;Welcome all,
&lrm;to the launch
&lrm;of Chloe's electoral campaign.
&lrm;And a special thank you
&lrm;to world-famous popstar
&lrm;Jagged Stone for endorsing her
&lrm;If you vote for me,
&lrm;you'll get free tickets
&lrm;to Jagged's next concert.
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;[angrily] You got an autograph?
&lrm;Yeah. Got you one, too.
&lrm;Sorry, couldn't help myself.
&lrm;No, I'm not falling for it.
&lrm;But I'll forgive you if you vote for me.
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;How did I not see that coming?
&lrm;Take him.
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;Not a minute to be wasted.
&lrm;City Hall awaits us!
&lrm;City Hall?
&lrm;You go first. I'll catch up.
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;What took you?
&lrm;You better have her diary.
&lrm;I did... sorta.
&lrm;What's that?
&lrm;When I grabbed the diary,
&lrm;this crazy box closed on my hand.
&lrm;And I'm supposed to believe you?
&lrm;[angry sigh] Why do I bother?
&lrm;Do you realise you're being bribed?
&lrm;Concert tickets are awesome,
&lrm;but they won't solve our problems.
&lrm;What's your campaign then?
&lrm;Well... I'm...
&lrm;I think cushions are
&lrm;more realistic than new chairs.
&lrm;Your cushion could be pink.
&lrm;I'll see about music in the library,
&lrm;using headphones.
&lrm;Remarkable.
&lrm;You actually sound like a class rep.
&lrm;Too bad you have no chance of winning.
&lrm;A word?
&lrm;My diary! What were you...?
&lrm;If you don't pull out,
&lrm;all your secrets will be revealed.
&lrm;Don't! I mean... What secrets?
&lrm;We'll find out,
&lrm;as soon as I get my hands on a chainsaw.
&lrm;Oh ye, oh ye!
&lrm;Darkblade shalt speak now.
&lrm;Listen or be imprisoned!
&lrm;Henceforth,
&lrm;my flag shalt fly over thy kingdom.
&lrm;Bourgeois, pathetic knave,
&lrm;come hither and do battle!
&lrm;What did he say?
&lrm;Basically, he's gonna bust you up.
&lrm;Ask my secretary for an appointment.
&lrm;[cackling] Bow down to Darkblade
&lrm;or feel the wrath of mine sword!
&lrm;PAR LE FER! PAR LE FER!
&lrm;[charging]
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;Take him!
&lrm;Do you only know heavy metal?
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;[Cat Noir laughs]
&lrm;Ouch. Cat Noir, hurry.
&lrm;[knights groan]
&lrm;Nice warmup.
&lrm;Par le fer!
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;Is that the sound of crazed fans?
&lrm;I can get them under control.
&lrm;[awful singing]
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;Behold, a minstrel.
&lrm;Guys, guys, I know you love me,
&lrm;but no reason to fight over it.
&lrm;Are you the usurper's champion?
&lrm;Say what?
&lrm;- No!
&lrm;- What are we gonna do?
&lrm;- The doors, quickly!
&lrm;- Quit, Chloe.
&lrm;[Darkblade]
&lrm;Kneel before thy flag of Darkblade.
&lrm;Bow down before mine eyes.
&lrm;Cloe, what should we do?
&lrm;What would a class rep do?
&lrm;Well, if you vote for me
&lrm;I'll give you an answer... tomorrow.
&lrm;But we can't wait that long.
&lrm;Then tough luck. Ask someone else.
&lrm;[lively music] Tikki, we need to talk.
&lrm;What are you going to do?
&lrm;Cat Noir needs Ladybug,
&lrm;but the students need me too.
&lrm;Trust your instincts.
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;[thudding]
&lrm;[Marinette]
&lrm;Lock the doors
&lrm;and the windows.
&lrm;Quickly!
&lrm;Nino, Juleka, Rose,
&lrm;Mylene, Alya come with me.
&lrm;Good job, girl.
&lrm;Now there's a future class rep
&lrm;in the making.
&lrm;Well, I was going to say
&lrm;the exact same thing.
&lrm;Sabrina, Ivan, Kim,
&lrm;go and lock the doors.
&lrm;Charge!
&lrm;Barricade the entrance.
&lrm;[thudding]
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;[Nino] Hurry.
&lrm;[thudding]
&lrm;- I hope Cat Noir's OK.
&lrm;- Time to retreat.
&lrm;Sir, we have to go.
&lrm;This way.
&lrm;I'll catch up.
&lrm;I'll close all the windows.
&lrm;They should be safe now.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Back off, tin cans.
&lrm;Cat Noir, over here.
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;Sorry, I was busy
&lrm;doing damage control inside.
&lrm;I was managing just fine
&lrm;but it's always nice to see you.
&lrm;Column formation!
&lrm;[grunting]
&lrm;[crashing]
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;Strike!
&lrm;Cursed colourful acrobats.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;Pull!
&lrm;[shouting]
&lrm;Why the roof?
&lrm;- Some of them anyway.
&lrm;- The flag.
&lrm;Tallyho!
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Once mine coat of arms flies here,
&lrm;I shalt reign supreme.
&lrm;- The Akuma's in his sword.
&lrm;- How do we get it?
&lrm;By getting close to him.
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[she roars]
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;Cat Noir!
&lrm;Don't let him get his banner!
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;Villains. Thou impress me not.
&lrm;By the blade of darkness, I declare
&lrm;all peoples of this kingdom
&lrm;are henceforth mine!
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;Bow to King Darkblade!
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;[dramatic music continues]
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Soon thou shalt join my army,
&lrm;you venomous insect.
&lrm;Not... so... fast! &lrm;En garde!
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Soon Ladybug and Cat Noir
&lrm;will meet their doom.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;We'll be turned into knights.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;PAR LE FER!
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[confused] OK?
&lrm;[questioning sigh]
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;Let's hope he's ticklish.
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;Not this time.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[laughing]
&lrm;[she roars]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you, Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;[twinkling]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[bubbling]
&lrm;[confused sigh]
&lrm;POUND IT!
&lrm;[he gasps] Gotta take off. See ya.
&lrm;Our duel is not over, my dear Ladybug.
&lrm;At the end of our battle,
&lrm;I will rule!
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Great job.
&lrm;You proved you can be
&lrm;both Ladybug and class rep.
&lrm;It wasn't easy
&lrm;but I'm glad I tried,
&lrm;If I hadn't
&lrm;I'd never have known I could do it!
&lrm;Where were you?
&lrm;- Hiding under a rock?
&lrm;- Very funny.
&lrm;I got... transformed into a knight.
&lrm;So did I. What a 'knightmare".
&lrm;Now this is all over,
&lrm;I want my personal items back.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;What are you talking about?
&lrm;Yes, please take it off.
&lrm;Thank you.
&lrm;Got an explanation, Chloe?
&lrm;I told you I never took her diary.
&lrm;I'm offended at you accusing me.
&lrm;Then how did you know
&lrm;my diary was in here?
&lrm;[gasps]
&lrm;Well... I...
&lrm;Sabrina told me. It was all her idea.
&lrm;So uncool.
&lrm;Now we know nobody will vote for Chloe.
&lrm;You're gonna be our new class rep.
&lrm;Not so fast.
&lrm;See? She's undependable.
&lrm;She's already giving up.
&lrm;No, I'm not. I want to be voted in fairly
&lrm;not because
&lrm;you don't want to vote for Chloe
&lrm;but because you believe in me.
&lrm;I won't make promises I can't keep,
&lrm;I won't get you everything you want,
&lrm;but I am resourceful,
&lrm;and I know how to prioritise.
&lrm;I'm good at listening and multi-tasking.
&lrm;Representing you all is what I believe in
&lrm;and I believe in myself.
&lrm;So vote for Marinette
&lrm;for class representative.
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;What are you doing?
&lrm;Are you out of your mind?
&lrm;[groaning] What are you good for?
&lrm;By majority vote,
&lrm;Marinette is the new class representative
&lrm;and Alya will be her deputy.
&lrm;You'll be able to do your blog
&lrm;and be deputy.
&lrm;We can do anything
&lrm;if we put our minds to it.
&lrm;I'm with you, girl.
&lrm;[chuckling]
&lrm;[happy music]