&lrm;In the daytime I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;Well? With or without?
&lrm;[hesitantly] With?
&lrm;You're sure it's not better without?
&lrm;Either way, you look perfect.
&lrm;It's not every day you celebrate
&lrm;your 20th wedding anniversary.
&lrm;[father] Marinette! Can you come here?
&lrm;Well?
&lrm;Well what?
&lrm;My moustache, I groomed it.
&lrm;Is it too short? Should I shave it off?
&lrm;Is it crooked?
&lrm;You look perfect, dad...
&lrm;Except for one thing.
&lrm;Thanks, sweetheart.
&lrm;No problem, dad.
&lrm;You're going to be late.
&lrm;Mrs. Chamack is coming to pick up
&lrm;her Eiffel Tower cake
&lrm;in 30 minutes. I'm depending on you.
&lrm;Yeah, yeah, no sweat, piece of cake.
&lrm;[questioning sigh]
&lrm;Married 20 years...
&lrm;pretty cool isn't it, Tikki?
&lrm;Time flies when you're having fun.
&lrm;Not when you're doing homework.
&lrm;[Tikki chuckles]
&lrm;Hey.
&lrm;They're Marinette's parents,
&lrm;a chick I hang out with.
&lrm;Yes, I remember.
&lrm;They make the best bread in Paris.
&lrm;Couldn't you have made
&lrm;more effort to dress nicely?
&lrm;What d'you mean? I took off my cap.
&lrm;But this is a special day.
&lrm;Well, it's only a birthday.
&lrm;[he tuts] No...
&lrm;This is a special birthday.
&lrm;This family heirloom was made
&lrm;by an ancestor many years ago.
&lrm;It's been passed down
&lrm;through the generations,
&lrm;on the fifteenth birthday, and today,
&lrm;it's your turn to inherit it.
&lrm;It's sweet, but I've already got a watch,
&lrm;synched to my phone.
&lrm;Sometimes, there's more to things
&lrm;than meets the eye.
&lrm;Let's just say our ancestor was...
&lrm;[twinkling]
&lrm;ahead of his time.
&lrm;Of course, I'd understand
&lrm;if you'd rather me buy you
&lrm;a new pair of rollerblades.
&lrm;No, dad, I'm stoked.
&lrm;It's awesome, thank you.
&lrm;[her phone rings]
&lrm;Are your friends waiting?
&lrm;Yeah, but I don't want
&lrm;to bail on you, it's cool.
&lrm;No, no, go ahead.
&lrm;Now take good care of it.
&lrm;Yeah.
&lrm;Come on, Marinette, you can do it.
&lrm;Just remember the formula.
&lrm;Think, Marinette.
&lrm;I might be able to if you weren't
&lrm;distracting me.
&lrm;Hey, Alya. What's up?
&lrm;The what?
&lrm;The bet between Alix and Kim?
&lrm;No, of course I didn't forget.
&lrm;I've made the banner.
&lrm;I know everyone's counting on me.
&lrm;In five minutes?
&lrm;No sweat. I'm on my way already.
&lrm;Be right there.
&lrm;But you have to wait for Mrs. Chamack.
&lrm;I've 20 minutes before she arrives.
&lrm;I told them I'd do the banner.
&lrm;They're counting on me.
&lrm;Besides, Adrien will be there.
&lrm;You'll never make it to Trocadéro
&lrm;in five minutes, it's too far.
&lrm;Not too far for Ladybug.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;That's beautiful.
&lrm;Impressive, Marinette.
&lrm;You've picked the wrong side.
&lrm;Alix hasn't even shown up.
&lrm;Probably too chicken
&lrm;to race an athlete like me.
&lrm;[Alix] Spoke too soon, Kim.
&lrm;Your ridiculous bets are over.
&lrm;I'm gonna leave you in the dust, meathead.
&lrm;You're no match for me.
&lrm;My neck's bigger than your thigh.
&lrm;Is that a good thing?
&lrm;Let's review the official rules.
&lrm;Two laps around the fountains,
&lrm;approximately 500 yards.
&lrm;The first over the line is the victor.
&lrm;If Kim wins, Alix will relinquish
&lrm;her rollerblades to him.
&lrm;If Alix wins,
&lrm;Kim will be prohibited
&lrm;from making any dares
&lrm;for the rest of the school year.
&lrm;We're through with those stupid dares.
&lrm;-Yeah, that's right!
&lrm;-No more dares!
&lrm;On your marks.
&lrm;Get set...
&lrm;Hold up!
&lrm;[he groans, the crowd giggles]
&lrm;Forfeiting already?
&lrm;Hold on to this, Alya.
&lrm;I don't want to drop it.
&lrm;Hold on, girl. I can't. I...
&lrm;Guard it with your life.
&lrm;It's a family heirloom.
&lrm;But...
&lrm;Marinette, take this.
&lrm;I gotta record the race for my blog.
&lrm;On your marks.
&lrm;Get set.
&lrm;Go!
&lrm;But she asked you to look after it.
&lrm;I've gotta hold the banner.
&lrm;Need any help?
&lrm;Wh...? Yep, thanks,
&lrm;Gotta be careful,
&lrm;even if you are amazing...
&lrm;At... holding things... in your hands.
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;Last lap.
&lrm;Amazing at holding things?
&lrm;Adrikins? Whatcha got there?
&lrm;Some super-old case or something?
&lrm;Careful, it's Alix's.
&lrm;If it's Alix's, it's probably worthless.
&lrm;Give it back to Adrien, Chloé.
&lrm;Yeah!
&lrm;I call a rematch.
&lrm;That false start threw me off.
&lrm;Did you do this?
&lrm;I had to record the race,
&lrm;so I gave it to Marinette.
&lrm;She had the banner
&lrm;so she gave it to Adrien.
&lrm;Then Chloé snatched it and dropped it.
&lrm;Then you skated over it.
&lrm;My old man gave me this for my birthday.
&lrm;This watch is totally a family heirloom.
&lrm;It was an accident.
&lrm;We didn't mean any harm.
&lrm;As if... I totally had nothing
&lrm;to do with this.
&lrm;You're all to blame!
&lrm;[she sobs]
&lrm;Alix, wait!
&lrm;-Marinette, what about the cake?
&lrm;-There's still time. Hide.
&lrm;[evil voice] Such disappointment,
&lrm;frustration, and negativity.
&lrm;How it fills my heart with exhilaration.
&lrm;Fly away, my little Akuma and evilize her.
&lrm;Bon appetit.
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;It's Mrs. Chamack.
&lrm;-Hello.
&lrm;-Hi, I'm at the bakery,
&lrm;-but it's closed. I need my cake now.
&lrm;-I know you do.
&lrm;My daughter's home.
&lrm;She must be upstairs.
&lrm;I'll phone her now.
&lrm;Maybe we could fix it.
&lrm;This watch was sick, one of a kind.
&lrm;It can't be fixed!
&lrm;There has to be a way
&lrm;to get it back to how it was.
&lrm;Like, how?
&lrm;Go back in time and change the future?
&lrm;When you figure out how, lemme know!
&lrm;[phone rings]
&lrm;Oh no, this can't be good.
&lrm;Hello, dad.
&lrm;Timebreaker, I'm Hawk Moth.
&lrm;I'm granting you the power to retaliate
&lrm;against the people who've wronged you,
&lrm;and to go back in time
&lrm;to restore the future.
&lrm;But you must do me a favor in return
&lrm;when the time is right.
&lrm;You got it, Hawk Moth.
&lrm;Mrs. Chamack is outside
&lrm;waiting for her cake.
&lrm;I gotta go. Can't keep her waiting.
&lrm;She was listening to music.
&lrm;Run!
&lrm;Stop, Alix! What are you doing?
&lrm;The name's Timebreaker now.
&lrm;I'm going back in time to save my watch,
&lrm;using you punks to do it.
&lrm;Go back in time?
&lrm;What did you do? Why is he fading?
&lrm;I needed his energy.
&lrm;He was a pain anyway with all those bets.
&lrm;He deserves to disappear forever,
&lrm;and so do you.
&lrm;We've got to transform, now.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;Yeah!
&lrm;Time out, Timebreaker.
&lrm;Please, help me.
&lrm;I'm messed up, please, please,
&lrm;No!
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Sweet, Rose,
&lrm;always thinking of others before yourself.
&lrm;One minute.
&lrm;I gotta destroy her Akuma
&lrm;before everyone disappears.
&lrm;Where's is that Cat?
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[she cackles]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;One and a half minutes.
&lrm;You won't be able to stop me
&lrm;where I'm going, Ladybug.
&lrm;Lemme guess,
&lrm;we're playing tag and you're it?
&lrm;Exactly!
&lrm;Don't let her touch you.
&lrm;Missed me. Just a second too late.
&lrm;No!
&lrm;Well she wastes no time, does she?
&lrm;The more people she freezes,
&lrm;the more minutes she gets
&lrm;to go back in time.
&lrm;Those kids are goners
&lrm;if we don't get that Akuma.
&lrm;Keep your hands to yourself.
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] Now, Timebreaker,
&lrm;grab her Miraculous,
&lrm;her earring!
&lrm;Cat Noir, No!
&lrm;Wow, six minutes in one go.
&lrm;Musta been those nine lives.
&lrm;Gotta go, the past is waiting.
&lrm;Timebreaker, the Miraculous!
&lrm;Take his ring before he disappears!
&lrm;Go ahead and try.
&lrm;Chill out, Hawk Moth, I have a sick plan.
&lrm;[Ladybug squeals]
&lrm;Wh-What just happened?
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;Go, Alix, yeah!
&lrm;We've gone back in time, haven't we?
&lrm;Watcha got there?
&lrm;Careful, it's Alix's.
&lrm;What is this?
&lrm;Some super-old case or something?
&lrm;If it's Alix's, it's probably worthless.
&lrm;Give it back to Adrien, Chloé.
&lrm;My watch!
&lrm;Chloé, put the watch down!
&lrm;No!
&lrm;Ladybug, this time it's your fault!
&lrm;I need more energy.
&lrm;I've gotta go further back in time.
&lrm;Ladybug, it's all Ladybug's fault!
&lrm;[evil voice] Could this be possible?
&lrm;Do I see double vision in my future?
&lrm;Or should I say "double villain"?
&lrm;Fly away, my devilish Akuma,
&lrm;and join this troubled soul.
&lrm;Everyone, get out of here!
&lrm;Don't let her touch you!
&lrm;Time to transform.
&lrm;[Marinette] Who are you?
&lrm;I don't have time to explain,
&lrm;but I'm you,
&lrm;from a few minutes in the future.
&lrm;She's right.
&lrm;I can feel it.
&lrm;She is you... from the future.
&lrm;Crazy!
&lrm;I know it seems unbelievable
&lrm;but trust me.
&lrm;I mean trust... yourself.
&lrm;And dad's gonna call me,
&lrm;I mean you, in two minutes.
&lrm;He won't be happy because Mrs. Chamack
&lrm;is waiting at the bakery.
&lrm;The cake... But I... I still have...
&lrm;Time? That's what I thought.
&lrm;She'll be early.
&lrm;Just leave now and take care of the cake.
&lrm;Don't worry, Ladybug can handle this.
&lrm;How do I get myself
&lrm;into these crazy situations?
&lrm;Cat Noir, I can't explain now
&lrm;but we've gotta capture
&lrm;Timebreaker's Akuma.
&lrm;Your life depends on it.
&lrm;Which life? I've got nine.
&lrm;I'm serious!
&lrm;The Akuma's in her rollerblades.
&lrm;[Ladybug] We've gotta release it.
&lrm;Am I seeing double?
&lrm;Another thing
&lrm;I don't have time to explain.
&lrm;The energy from these two
&lrm;will be enough for us to go farther back.
&lrm;I want my watch back. Let's do it.
&lrm;Whatever you do, don't let them touch you.
&lrm;Get the Miraculous, Timebreaker!
&lrm;If we were faster,
&lrm;they'd be no match for us.
&lrm;Then let's stock up on more energy first.
&lrm;Then we'll destroy them.
&lrm;Oh, hold on, here she comes now.
&lrm;It's fine, thanks.
&lrm;It's all good.
&lrm;Sorry again for making you wait.
&lrm;[Tikki] Mission accomplished.
&lrm;You mean Mission 1 accomplished.
&lrm;Time for Mission 2.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;Yeah!
&lrm;We've got enough speed.
&lrm;Let's go hardcore on Ladybug and Cat Noir.
&lrm;Once we get their energy,
&lrm;we'll have enough to go back together.
&lrm;And get our watch!
&lrm;I thought we were chasing them.
&lrm;[they yell]
&lrm;Hey, need a hand?
&lrm;Thanks!
&lrm;They're insane on their rollerblades.
&lrm;Unstoppable on the ground.
&lrm;So... what if they're not on the ground?
&lrm;Two Ladybugs? I'm in heaven.
&lrm;We'd better go back now.
&lrm;There'll be less of them.
&lrm;I'm down.
&lrm;Don't fail me this time!
&lrm;[together] They're planning
&lrm;to go back in time again.
&lrm;[together] Lucky charm!
&lrm;[together] Any ideas?
&lrm;While you figure it out,
&lrm;I'll try to buy some time.
&lrm;Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
&lrm;Of course.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;Let's freeze her.
&lrm;[panicked cries]
&lrm;We're going too fast! We can't stop!
&lrm;[they yell]
&lrm;Now!
&lrm;[together] No more evil-doing for you,
&lrm;little Akuma.
&lrm;[together] Time to de-evilize!
&lrm;[together] Gotcha.
&lrm;[together] Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;[together] Miraculous ladybug!
&lrm;[together] Pound it.
&lrm;Here, I think this is yours.
&lrm;Sweet!
&lrm;How did you fix it? Thank you.
&lrm;I shouldn't have given it
&lrm;to someone else to look after.
&lrm;It was my responsibility, my bad.
&lrm;Responsibility isn't something
&lrm;to be taken lightly. I should know.
&lrm;You're totally right.
&lrm;I'll be more careful next time.
&lrm;Thanks, Ladybug.
&lrm;I was getting used to having
&lrm;two Ladybugs around.
&lrm;Now you're going
&lrm;to get used to no Ladybugs around.
&lrm;I gotta split before I change back.
&lrm;She'll fall for me someday.
&lrm;It's just a matter of time.
&lrm;You slipped by me this time,
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir,
&lrm;but one day, past, present, or future,
&lrm;you will be destroyed,
&lrm;and I'll have your Miraculouses!
&lrm;I will be unstoppable!
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;Hey! So...
&lrm;did you have a nice anniversary?
&lrm;[father] We sure did.
&lrm;Although, it was a close call.
&lrm;Yeah. I'm sorry that I kept her waiting.
&lrm;Next time, please wait in the bakery,
&lrm;not in your room listening to music.
&lrm;Got it. I won't screw up next time.
&lrm;Good, cuz mom's right,
&lrm;there's only one Marinette,
&lrm;and we're counting on her.