&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;Welcome back to everyone's
&lrm;No 1 game show, The Challenge.
&lrm;Let's give it up
&lrm;for our next contestant,
&lrm;Nino!
&lrm;[chuckling]
&lrm;So, Nino, you're a student
&lrm;and a DJ, pretty awesome.
&lrm;Check out the decks
&lrm;we've got for you.
&lrm;Grounded? For what?
&lrm;Let's jog your memory.
&lrm;Monday morning,
&lrm;absent from PE.
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;I was in study hall.
&lrm;Friday evening,
&lrm;absent from study hall.
&lrm;[worried sigh]
&lrm;[meowing]
&lrm;I was at PE.
&lrm;You're never where
&lrm;you're supposed to be.
&lrm;The only to keep track of you
&lrm;is by grounding you.
&lrm;But I was invited.
&lrm;Nino's my friend.
&lrm;He was counting on me.
&lrm;So the challenge
&lrm;our viewers have chosen is...
&lrm;to get the mayor of Paris,
&lrm;Andre Bourgeois to dance!
&lrm;Thank you for agreeing
&lrm;to play with us.
&lrm;What are Nino's chances?
&lrm;Zero, I despise dancing.
&lrm;The last time I danced,
&lrm;Madonna was in kindergarten.
&lrm;I know Nino's your friend
&lrm;but until your unexcused absences
&lrm;come to an end,
&lrm;that's the way it is.
&lrm;Awesome.
&lrm;[mysterious music]
&lrm;[frustrated groan]
&lrm;Can you blame them?
&lrm;How are they supposed to know
&lrm;you miss class to save the world?
&lrm;I guess being grounded comes
&lrm;with being a top-secret superhero.
&lrm;It doesn't seem fair.
&lrm;It's not.
&lrm;But hey, if Nino wins,
&lrm;you're not grounded next week,
&lrm;you can go then.
&lrm;Yeah, but Adrien was there today.
&lrm;A challenge...
&lrm;What an interesting concept.
&lrm;A TV show with such potential
&lrm;for negative emotion.
&lrm;Oh, the destructive mayhem
&lrm;we could cause.
&lrm;Seriously? How can you say that?
&lrm;Sorry, but I get your dad.
&lrm;You're never where you say,
&lrm;being late, splitting mysteriously.
&lrm;I'd expect you to be leading...
&lrm;a double life.
&lrm;Gimme a break,
&lrm;you're being ridiculous.
&lrm;Just wait here.
&lrm;Thanks.
&lrm;[trendy music]
&lrm;No, it's OK.
&lrm;Victory!
&lrm;Challenge conquered by Nino.
&lrm;You moved to the beat Major,
&lrm;that counts as dancing.
&lrm;What? That's not true.
&lrm;My neck was itching, that's all.
&lrm;Relieving an itch to the beat
&lrm;counts as dancing too.
&lrm;Nino, congratulations.
&lrm;You'll return in one week
&lrm;for your next challenge.
&lrm;And now for our next contestant,
&lrm;welcome Simon Grimault.
&lrm;Awesome, dude.
&lrm;[Alec] Mr. Grimault,
&lrm;You're a hypnotist,
&lrm;You hypnotise people
&lrm;to get what you want.
&lrm;Well... yes,
&lrm;I'm a hypnotist but
&lrm;I don't use my skills
&lrm;to get anything.
&lrm;So, your challenge
&lrm;is to use your talents
&lrm;to bring a very elusive celebrity
&lrm;to our TV set.
&lrm;Give it for the King of Fashion
&lrm;Gabriel Agreste.
&lrm;What is this show?
&lrm;I was told this was an interview.
&lrm;Dude, your dad.
&lrm;[Alec] Do your thing,
&lrm;Let's see if you can bring
&lrm;Mr. Agreste here with your powers.
&lrm;I told you,
&lrm;I don't make p...
&lrm;A shy hypnotist.
&lrm;How funny is that, Gabriel?
&lrm;Hilarious, your show is pathetic.
&lrm;And so is your contestant.
&lrm;Control me? Never.
&lrm;That's my dad alright.
&lrm;Looks like Mr. Agreste
&lrm;turned down your challenge.
&lrm;Game over.
&lrm;But... that's not fair.
&lrm;I didn't even get time to...
&lrm;[mysterious music]
&lrm;[sighing]
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] Yes...
&lrm;humiliation and anger...
&lrm;the perfect elements
&lrm;for transforming a loser
&lrm;into a winner.
&lrm;[mysterious music]
&lrm;Fly away, my little Akuma,
&lrm;and evilise him!
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;I am Hawk Moth,
&lrm;you are now Simon Says.
&lrm;I will help you to be
&lrm;the most powerful hypnotist ever.
&lrm;You will help me in return
&lrm;when the time's right.
&lrm;So, do we have a deal, Simon Says?
&lrm;[evil voice] Simon Says "yes".
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Simon Says the show is not over.
&lrm;What the...?
&lrm;Silence!
&lrm;Simon Says you're lame,
&lrm;as lame as a duck.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[quacking]
&lrm;[they gasp.]
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;Simon Says stop!
&lrm;Simon Says you are a gorilla.
&lrm;[grunting]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;Marinette, look!
&lrm;I've gotta go, Alya.
&lrm;Have a good one.
&lrm;I'll get back to babysitting.
&lrm;Tikki, what can I do? I'm grounded.
&lrm;You have no choice,
&lrm;you must transform.
&lrm;We have to be extra-careful.
&lrm;Use that pillow
&lrm;under your sheets.
&lrm;[Tikki] Lookin' good.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[whizzing]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Gabriel Agreste turned down
&lrm;my challenge so he'll pay for it.
&lrm;By midnight tonight,
&lrm;he will entertain us
&lrm;in this very TV studio.
&lrm;Gabriel, I'm coming to get you!
&lrm;Dad?
&lrm;It's risky, but it's given me an idea.
&lrm;Good luck, Simon Says.
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;[ushing]
&lrm;Cat Noir says zip it
&lrm;and give me those cards.
&lrm;My gorilla will take care of you.
&lrm;Simon Says
&lrm;knock him out.
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;I may not always land of my feet
&lrm;but I always bounce back.
&lrm;I could use an army.
&lrm;[lift beeps]
&lrm;Simon Says,
&lrm;you are all soldiers.
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;Simon Says search all over Paris
&lrm;and find Gabriel Agreste.
&lrm;[moaning]
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;Better watch out
&lrm;my sensei taught me that.
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;Size doesn't matter.
&lrm;[whizzing]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[Nino whispers]
&lrm;Ladybug,
&lrm;Hey, you OK?
&lrm;I'm fine but my boy Adrien
&lrm;is still here.
&lrm;Don't worry, we'll find him.
&lrm;I quit karate.
&lrm;[lift beeps]
&lrm;Hey, there, Ladybug.
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;[Cat Noir]
&lrm;Enough already.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;[yelling fades]
&lrm;Nice seeing you too, Cat Noir.
&lrm;Sorry. I thought
&lrm;you were Simon Says.
&lrm;I saw him.
&lrm;He's got a whole army.
&lrm;[Cat Noir] He's looking
&lrm;for Gabriel Agreste.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;We'd better get to him fast.
&lrm;You're about to change back.
&lrm;I'll have a look
&lrm;[Ladybug] for Nino's friend.
&lrm;Forget it. He's probably hypnotised.
&lrm;But he's my buddy.
&lrm;You're right. Maybe he's hiding.
&lrm;I'll leave you to look for him.
&lrm;Let's meet
&lrm;at Gabriel Agreste's place.
&lrm;[confused sighs]
&lrm;Finding Adrien will be a piece of cake.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;Plagg, hide.
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Nino.
&lrm;Adrien!
&lrm;Dude, you OK?
&lrm;I'm fine.
&lrm;[nervously] Hello.
&lrm;[nervous stuttering]
&lrm;H-H-Hello.
&lrm;You sure you're OK.
&lrm;I'm fine, really.
&lrm;But we must get to my house
&lrm;my father's in danger.
&lrm;Let's go.
&lrm;Cat Noir will meet us there.
&lrm;Nathalie, where's father?
&lrm;He's in danger.
&lrm;He knows already.
&lrm;Good evening, Ladybug.
&lrm;Father, you've gotta get out of here.
&lrm;Simon Says is coming after you.
&lrm;What? And be dictated
&lrm;by a madman? Certainly not.
&lrm;But he's dangerous.
&lrm;Who knows what he'll do?
&lrm;Go up to your room.
&lrm;You've had enough excitement for today.
&lrm;Nathalie, make sure they stay there.
&lrm;I have to apologise for my son.
&lrm;He's like his mother,
&lrm;too overly dramatic.
&lrm;But he's right.
&lrm;Simon Says is a real threat.
&lrm;You're in danger.
&lrm;What could possibly happen to me
&lrm;with you here to protect me?
&lrm;You sure your old man isn't a robot?
&lrm;Where my father is concerned
&lrm;I'm never sure.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Dude, I've seen stadiums
&lrm;tinier than your room.
&lrm;Make yourself at home.
&lrm;I'll take a shower.
&lrm;Now?
&lrm;What can I say?
&lrm;It's the model in me.
&lrm;Why doesn't my father listen to me?
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[dreamy music]
&lrm;Isn't he flawless?
&lrm;[nervously] Wh-What? Flaw what?
&lrm;Adrien, my son.
&lrm;He's the image of perfection, isn't he?
&lrm;[in admiration] Yes, he's perfect.
&lrm;I mean... I don't know him but he seems...
&lrm;I've never noticed your earrings before.
&lrm;They are quite unique.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;May I?
&lrm;Excuse me.
&lrm;Cat Noir, where were you?
&lrm;I was keeping Simon Says at bay.
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;And?
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;Cat Noir,
&lrm;I couldn't keep him away.
&lrm;He's coming. He's got company.
&lrm;[moaning]
&lrm;[Cat Noir]
&lrm;Close all exits.
&lrm;They're coming from everywhere.
&lrm;Engage the defence system,
&lrm;total lockdown.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Lockdown engaged.
&lrm;[whirring]
&lrm;How do you know about the system?
&lrm;In a house like this it's a given.
&lrm;They won't get in.
&lrm;This house is a fortress.
&lrm;[moaning]
&lrm;Simon Says destroy.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[roaring]
&lrm;[shouting]
&lrm;[alarm rings]
&lrm;Emergency power on.
&lrm;There are too many of them.
&lrm;Your defence system is failing.
&lrm;Adrien and Nino...
&lrm;I'd better go get them
&lrm;Nathalie, take the controls
&lrm;to unlock any exits.
&lrm;She's coming with you.
&lrm;I'll reinforce the defences.
&lrm;Hide in the atrium.
&lrm;No-one tells me what to do,
&lrm;not even you.
&lrm;You're in danger.
&lrm;Just do as I tell you to.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Quite a temper,
&lrm;you remind me of someone.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[shouting]
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;I don't think
&lrm;that's a good idea, Simon Says.
&lrm;Gabriel is here!
&lrm;Yes but don't forget our deal.
&lrm;I feel Ladybug and Cat Noir nearby.
&lrm;Once they're in front of you,
&lrm;you can honour our agreement.
&lrm;Just take their jewels, the Miraculouses.
&lrm;It's as good as done.
&lrm;Simon Says we'll defeat them.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Ladybug, What's going on?
&lrm;We need to get to safety.
&lrm;Where's Adrien?
&lrm;-Taking a shower.
&lrm;-Now?
&lrm;It's the model in him.
&lrm;Go to the atrium. I'll get Adrien.
&lrm;Leave the control with me.
&lrm;Adrien?
&lrm;[Ladybug] Adrien?
&lrm;Yeah?
&lrm;Must...to go...
&lrm;too dangerous... to leave.
&lrm;Can I get dressed?
&lrm;Sure... if you must.
&lrm;I mean... of course you can.
&lrm;[sigh of relief]
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;Where is my son?
&lrm;He'll be here.
&lrm;He's with Ladybug.
&lrm;[questioning sigh]
&lrm;[mysterious music]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;[door opens]
&lrm;My mother. She was pretty, no?
&lrm;SHE'S GOT YOUR EYES.
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;[they chuckle]
&lrm;[shouting]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Stay here!
&lrm;Oh my.
&lrm;What was that all about?
&lrm;Sweet love?
&lrm;Gotta help her.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[squealing] Not again.
&lrm;[moaning]
&lrm;[screens hiss]
&lrm;Are they coming?
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;[shouting]
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;[moaning]
&lrm;[he snarls]
&lrm;Gotcha.
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;Cat noir!
&lrm;[shouting]
&lrm;[moaning]
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Well that's just great.
&lrm;Welcome to another exciting hour
&lrm;of The Challenge.
&lrm;Good evening again from Simon Says.
&lrm;Viewers, I've kept my promise.
&lrm;Here's Gabriel.
&lrm;[he snarls]
&lrm;Simon Says
&lrm;you are a butterfly.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[Gabriel]
&lrm;Flap, flap, flutter, flutter...
&lrm;[Ladybug]
&lrm;We've gotta save Mr. Agreste.
&lrm;Tomorrow, butterfly,
&lrm;you will be no more.
&lrm;The Akuma's gotta be in one of the cards.
&lrm;But which one? There are so many.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;Ladybug, Cat Noir,
&lrm;to save him, give me your Miraculouses.
&lrm;Do the right thing.
&lrm;In your dreams.
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;A regular yoyo?
&lrm;But you've got a magic one.
&lrm;I'll figure it out later.
&lrm;[whizzing]
&lrm;Simon Says your yoyo is useless.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Simon Says your stick is...
&lrm;Useless? I don't think so.
&lrm;I'm not gonna let you
&lrm;get a word in.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Simon Says...
&lrm;[noisy chanting]
&lrm;It doesn't matter if you can hear me.
&lrm;All that's important is what Simon Says.
&lrm;Simon Says give me you Miraculous.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;[Cat Noir chuckles]
&lrm;[Gabriel] Flutter, flutter...
&lrm;Simon Says take off, little airplane.
&lrm;[rasping]
&lrm;He's gone to the roof.
&lrm;We have to stop him.
&lrm;This is the last chance
&lrm;and I can't do it alone.
&lrm;If we free Simon Says,
&lrm;we free Mr. Agreste too.
&lrm;Let's not waste a minute.
&lrm;How will you defeat me
&lrm;without your yoyo?
&lrm;[rasping]
&lrm;Simon Says... it's over.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Follow my lead.
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;[gasping] Simon Says...
&lrm;[slow motion yelling]
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[fluttering]
&lrm;That's not possible.
&lrm;I made your yoyo useless.
&lrm;This one yes, but not that one.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;[twinkling]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[rasping]
&lrm;[he whimpers]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;My yoyo.
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you, little Akuma.
&lrm;[lively music]
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;POUND IT!
&lrm;Your flight's been cancelled, sir.
&lrm;-You?
&lrm;-Prefer Ladybug?
&lrm;[bleeping] Can't say I blame you.
&lrm;Cat Noir, your ring. You'd better go.
&lrm;Like a cat on a hot tin roof.
&lrm;See you again soon, Mr. Agreste.
&lrm;[mysterious music]
&lrm;And you, milady.
&lrm;[sigh]
&lrm;[slow music]
&lrm;[door opens]
&lrm;[endearing sigh]
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;I've never noticed your ring before.
&lrm;That's the only thing
&lrm;you've never noticed?
&lrm;I'm glad everything worked out.
&lrm;[slow music continues]
&lrm;[pop music]
&lrm;Welcome back
&lrm;to the No 1 game show, The Challenge.
&lrm;Last week,
&lrm;our cool DJ Nino won the challenge.
&lrm;So let's welcome him back again.
&lrm;Come on out,
&lrm;DJ... Nino!
&lrm;[pop music]
&lrm;[Tom]&lrm; Looks like
&lrm;you weren't absent or late all week.
&lrm;Excellent news, Marinette.
&lrm;You can go join your friends on the set.
&lrm;I think I'd rather watch it with you.
&lrm;That's if you and mom would like that.
&lrm;[chuckling]
&lrm;So we've upped
&lrm;the challenge tonight, Nino.
&lrm;You have to get 2 celebrities
&lrm;dancing instead of one.
&lrm;But this time,
&lrm;you can choose your opponents.
&lrm;I got this one in the bag.
&lrm;I'm gonna pick two buds
&lrm;I know won't let me down.
&lrm;Ladybug... and Cat Noir.
&lrm;[she squeals]
&lrm;On second thoughts,
&lrm;I'm gonna take a nap.
&lrm;Don't want to be late for school,
&lrm;and mess up that perfect school record.
&lrm;Tell me what happens.
&lrm;-Sure.
&lrm;-Of course, honey.
&lrm;Sometimes,
&lrm;I just can't figure that girl out.
&lrm;Give her a break.
&lrm;You know there's nothing more demanding
&lrm;than going to school.
&lrm;[she chuckles]