&lrm;In the daytime I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life,
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Mrs. Bustier] &lrm;In most fairy tales,
&lrm;the prince breaks the spell
&lrm;by kissing the princess.
&lrm;Who can tell us why?
&lrm;Because only love can conquer hate.
&lrm;[Mrs. Bustier] Correct.
&lrm;Technically,
&lrm;[Max continues]
&lrm;this is only true in 87% of cases.
&lrm;Thank you, Max.
&lrm;Adrien, I hope that's about my lesson.
&lrm;What did I just say?
&lrm;The prince breaks the spell by
&lrm;kissing the princess
&lrm;because love conquers hate.
&lrm;Very good.
&lrm;[bell rings]
&lrm;Don't forget to finish &lrm;Sleeping Beauty&lrm;.
&lrm;Happy Valentine's day.
&lrm;I'll meet you outside.
&lrm;OK.
&lrm;[Adrien sighs]
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;[she chuckles]
&lrm;Hi, Adrien. Sign here, please.
&lrm;You know I hate signing autographs.
&lrm;That's not what this is.
&lrm;It's a petition
&lrm;against cruelty to hamsters.
&lrm;Have you seen the sweaters
&lrm;they're forced to wear?
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;[Chloe giggles]
&lrm;Well, well, Marinette,
&lrm;looking for something to eat?
&lrm;Maybe she's looking
&lrm;for better clothes.
&lrm;[they giggle]
&lrm;[she growls]
&lrm;Ignore them.
&lrm;They're not worth it.
&lrm;You're right.
&lrm;"Your hair is dark as night,
&lrm;Your pretty bluebell eyes.
&lrm;I wonder who you are
&lrm;Beneath that strong disguise.
&lrm;Every day we see each other,
&lrm;I hope that you'll be mine.
&lrm;Together our love could be so true,
&lrm;Please be my Valentine."
&lrm;Wow, now that's a love poem.
&lrm;Who could it be to?
&lrm;"Hair dark as night",
&lrm;"Bluebell eyes"?
&lrm;Well... you.
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;No way.
&lrm;There are plenty of girls at school
&lrm;with dark hair and blue eyes.
&lrm;Yes, but bluebell eyes?
&lrm;What does he mean by "strong disguise"?
&lrm;[Tikki sighs]
&lrm;This is poetry.
&lrm;He means who you are deep down.
&lrm;He wants to get to know you.
&lrm;He's talking about you.
&lrm;[she squeals with delight]
&lrm;Pinch me.
&lrm;[shrieking]
&lrm;Not literally!
&lrm;[Tikki giggles]
&lrm;Operation Valentine's Day
&lrm;is commencing.
&lrm;According to my research
&lrm;of shopping sites,
&lrm;this jewel was ranked
&lrm;highest in popularity.
&lrm;Perfect. I'll hit a homerun
&lrm;with this one.
&lrm;Love is like baseball, right?
&lrm;You need a strategy.
&lrm;And if you aim right,
&lrm;it's a homerun.
&lrm;-Great metaphor, Kim.
&lrm;-Meta who?
&lrm;Wow, sparkly. Is that for me?
&lrm;No, Alya,
&lrm;it's for someone else, it's...
&lrm;Shh! Keep quiet.
&lrm;Scoop! Kim's got a crush.
&lrm;Who's the lucky lady?
&lrm;It's gorgeous, Kim. She'll be ecstatic.
&lrm;She's still gotta accept it.
&lrm;-What if she says no?
&lrm;-She won't.
&lrm;No way, don't hold back.
&lrm;Go for it. No regrets!
&lrm;Operation Valentine's Day
&lrm;is underway.
&lrm;Her route is in yellow, yours is in red.
&lrm;If you run at 10mph,
&lrm;you'll have a 4-minute lead on her.
&lrm;Wait here. It's the 3rd
&lrm;most romantic spot in Paris.
&lrm;-Go, go!
&lrm;-Thanks, guys.
&lrm;I know someone who's good
&lrm;at giving advice,
&lrm;but who can't take any.
&lrm;Let's go.
&lrm;You're right. It's time I told him.
&lrm;Say what?
&lrm;I'm gonna tell him my true feelings.
&lrm;Well, I'll write them,
&lrm;on a card.
&lrm;Yeah.
&lrm;OPERATION VALENTINE'S DAY!
&lrm;[they giggle]
&lrm;[admiring sighs]
&lrm;Wow, he's so cute.
&lrm;Keep dreaming, girls,
&lrm;but the boy is mine.
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;"To Chloe, the most awesome girl
&lrm;in the world,
&lrm;and the love of my life"
&lrm;signed Adrien.
&lrm;[sobbing]
&lrm;[Chloe] She's not crying enough.
&lrm;[Marinette]
&lrm;"Dear, Adrien"... "Dear, Adrien"
&lrm;"Dear Adrien"
&lrm;I'm no good at this
&lrm;love-letter writing thing.
&lrm;I sound like a dorkasaurus.
&lrm;[she whines]
&lrm;Only when you say
&lrm;words like "dorkasaurus".
&lrm;Relax, Marinette, I'm teasing.
&lrm;Think of Adrien
&lrm;and speak from the heart.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Adrien's letter.
&lrm;Why didn't I think of that before?
&lrm;I'll answer his poem.
&lrm;[Alya] Marinette?
&lrm;Check... it... out!
&lrm;It's perfect.
&lrm;Oh, thank you, thank you.
&lrm;[questioning sigh]
&lrm;[Ayla gasps excitedly]
&lrm;Voilà.
&lrm;Don't forget to sign it.
&lrm;[Alya] It's a good omen.
&lrm;Ladybugs are good luck,
&lrm;especially in the love department.
&lrm;Really?
&lrm;Yeah, you of all people
&lrm;should know about ladybugs.
&lrm;Wh-Why do you say that?
&lrm;"The ladybug is a symbol of love,
&lrm;guiding hearts on the paths of devotion."
&lrm;It's on my blog. Didn't you read it?
&lrm;Yes, of course.
&lrm;[sigh of relief]
&lrm;[Plagg]
&lrm;So, she's got eyes, arms, legs...
&lrm;Big deal.
&lrm;How can you be in love with Ladybug?
&lrm;You don't even know who she is.
&lrm;You know nothing about love.
&lrm;Sure I do. I love cheddar, Swiss...
&lrm;and I love camembert.
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;The poor boy's frustrated
&lrm;because he can't finish the poem
&lrm;for his masked sweetheart.
&lrm;I don't need a poem.
&lrm;I can tell her to her face.
&lrm;I love you.
&lrm;[disgusted]
&lrm;That's gross.
&lrm;You're making me lose my appetite.
&lrm;[munching]
&lrm;Almost.
&lrm;[Chloe] That's right,
&lrm;in a 24-carat frame.
&lrm;Deliver it to Le Grand Paris Hotel
&lrm;and bill it to daddy.
&lrm;I mean Mr. Bourgeois.
&lrm;What are you doing here?
&lrm;[nervously]
&lrm;I-I...
&lrm;You... you...
&lrm;[he coughs]
&lrm;Will you... be my Valentine?
&lrm;[bell rings]
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;Don't move.
&lrm;[she laughs]
&lrm;Wait till people see this.
&lrm;No offence, Kim, my heart's saved
&lrm;for someone more awesome.
&lrm;Don't you just hate
&lrm;how harsh love can be?
&lrm;[she laughs]
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;[he sobs]
&lrm;Valentine's Day,
&lrm;the day of love and the day of fools.
&lrm;So many delusions,
&lrm;so much disappointment.
&lrm;My evil Akumas,
&lrm;you are going to have
&lrm;such a field-day.
&lrm;Fly away, my little Akuma,
&lrm;and evilise him.
&lrm;Dark Cupid, I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;I can give you the power
&lrm;to shoot your arrows,
&lrm;pierce love and impale friendships.
&lrm;But, there's something
&lrm;you must do for me in return.
&lrm;No love affair
&lrm;or friendship will escape my fury.
&lrm;No-one will love again!
&lrm;[arrow whistles]
&lrm;[she shrieks]
&lrm;Stupid flowers.
&lrm;Get off me!
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Perfect.
&lrm;Soon, Ladybug and Cat Noir
&lrm;will show up to meet their doom.
&lrm;[evil laugh]
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;Candy-apples, girls?
&lrm;Thanks, dad.
&lrm;Come on, do it
&lrm;before you chicken out.
&lrm;[they cheer]
&lrm;I did it.
&lrm;[vibrating]
&lrm;Chloe?
&lrm;Since when did she start texting us?
&lrm;[questioning sigh]
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;[Alya] What a witch!
&lrm;And I was the one
&lrm;who told Kim to do it.
&lrm;I didn't know he was talking about her.
&lrm;I hope Adrien doesn't do that to you.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;I mean...
&lrm;What have I done?
&lrm;Girl, calm down.
&lrm;I was joking... kind of.
&lrm;Adrien would never do that.
&lrm;What is that?
&lrm;All hearts must be destroyed!
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Ayla?
&lrm;Hey, seriously?
&lrm;You're not my BFF. You're a joke!
&lrm;Adrien will laugh his head off
&lrm;at your lame attempt at poetry.
&lrm;[Ayla cackles]
&lrm;Alya?
&lrm;What did he do to her?
&lrm;I've seen that jewel before.
&lrm;It's Kim's pin.
&lrm;He's been akumatised.
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;This is... not good.
&lrm;We've gotta find him fast.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;[Chloe groans]
&lrm;I never said 18-carat gold.
&lrm;The tones will never match
&lrm;my 24-carat toilet.
&lrm;[Chloe] Idiots!
&lrm;[he huffs]
&lrm;[bow stretches]
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;-Ladybug!
&lrm;-Stop, Kim.
&lrm;I'm not Kim,
&lrm;I'm Dark Cupid. I'll never stop.
&lrm;If I can't have love then no-one can.
&lrm;OK, I get it. Chloe burned you.
&lrm;You don't have to take it out
&lrm;on all of Paris.
&lrm;Yes I do.
&lrm;I won't stop till all hearts are crushed.
&lrm;Say adios to your loved ones,
&lrm;now you'll hate them.
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;If you want to continue
&lrm;destroying love,
&lrm;bring me Ladybug's Miraculous.
&lrm;or I'll remove your powers.
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Fallen for me already?
&lrm;-I need to talk to you.
&lrm;-It's gotta wait...
&lrm;[he hushes her]
&lrm;I swore I'd tell you
&lrm;as soon as I saw you.
&lrm;Ladybug, I-I... Look out!
&lrm;[arrow whistles]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Cat Noir?
&lrm;Ladybug, I...
&lrm;I loathe you!
&lrm;Cat Noir, snap out of it.
&lrm;You're nothing to me, Ladybug,
&lrm;I hate you.
&lrm;[he shrieks]
&lrm;Ladybug, it's about time.
&lrm;Where have you been?
&lrm;Offer to help him
&lrm;in return for Ladybug's Miraculous.
&lrm;I can help you crush Ladybug
&lrm;but you must give me her Miraculous.
&lrm;No... problem.
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;Yes... yes.
&lrm;Once I have Ladybug's Miraculous,
&lrm;taking Cat Noir's will be
&lrm;child's play!
&lrm;You have to leave.
&lrm;Kim's turned into Dark Cupid.
&lrm;He can't find you here.
&lrm;Me? But how could he have
&lrm;a vendetta against me?
&lrm;[whispering]
&lrm;Who doesn't?
&lrm;It's because of this.
&lrm;Everyone would love to have it.
&lrm;That's Adrien,
&lrm;a super-hot guy in my class,
&lrm;and rich too.
&lrm;He's hot for me, of course.
&lrm;Not according to the poem.
&lrm;[Sabrina shrieks]
&lrm;It's alive!
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;[Chloe screams]
&lrm;[Marinette] Chloe, run!
&lrm;Well, well, Ladybug.
&lrm;I don't want to fight you.
&lrm;That friendliness is so revolting.
&lrm;You're not my friend.
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;Why are you so full of hate?
&lrm;Because hate conquers all.
&lrm;I hate to burst your bubble,
&lrm;but hate doesn't conquer all,
&lrm;love does.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;The prince breaks the spell
&lrm;by kissing the princess.
&lrm;Only love conquers hate.
&lrm;You're just buying time....
&lrm;Fight!
&lrm;I'll do better than that.
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;Come on, kitty-kitty, just a peck.
&lrm;Almost.
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;Get back, you savage.
&lrm;Here, kitty-kitty, come here.
&lrm;[he cackles]
&lrm;You can't outrun me.
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;Help.
&lrm;[they scream]
&lrm;Happy Valentine's Day, Chloe.
&lrm;Now you'll get what you deserve.
&lrm;[Chloe] My hair!
&lrm;There's nothing worse
&lrm;than a bad-hair day.
&lrm;First, Ladybug wrinkles my jacket,
&lrm;second, you totally ruined my hair.
&lrm;Go ahead and change me.
&lrm;This day can't get any worse.
&lrm;I don't need to waste
&lrm;my arrow on you.
&lrm;Your heart is so dark and shrivelled
&lrm;there's no room for love.
&lrm;[he laughs]
&lrm;How dare you?
&lrm;Why are you just standing there?
&lrm;Help me up!
&lrm;You think I'd help someone
&lrm;as stuck up as you?
&lrm;Wait till people see this.
&lrm;[she cackles]
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;No, no!
&lrm;I'm not looking forward to it either.
&lrm;I can't believe I'm doing this.
&lrm;[kissing]
&lrm;[he whimpers]
&lrm;[explosions]
&lrm;How you gonna fight
&lrm;both of us now, bug-eyes?
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;I often wonder what
&lrm;my cataclysm will do to someone.
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;A candy-apple?
&lrm;What am I supposed to do with this?
&lrm;Think, Ladybug.
&lrm;Hey.
&lrm;I've a Valentine's gift for you.
&lrm;[they roar]
&lrm;Looks like you're in a sticky situation.
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;Ladybug!
&lrm;And now for the pussycat.
&lrm;Cat Noir, her Miraculous.
&lrm;With pleasure.
&lrm;Finally, I'll find out who you are.
&lrm;Your secret will be out of the bag.
&lrm;[romantic music]
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;Wh-What am I doing here?
&lrm;No time, the quiver pin, Cat Noir, now!
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;[Ladybug] Grab the pin!
&lrm;-No !
&lrm;-Sorry, need that.
&lrm;Happy Valentine's Day.
&lrm;You shouldn't have... Woops.
&lrm;No more evil-doing for you,
&lrm;little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise.
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;What the heck am I doing?
&lrm;What the heck are you doing?
&lrm;[Sabrina] I-I have no idea.
&lrm;[they sob]
&lrm;POUND IT!
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Woops.
&lrm;Wait, I gotta tell you something.
&lrm;Look, the kiss...
&lrm;I had to break the spell.
&lrm;What? A kiss? What kiss?
&lrm;I just wanted to say...
&lrm;Your ring's flashing.
&lrm;Yours too.
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;We're about to turn into pumpkins.
&lrm;And I'd rather not see that.
&lrm;[he roars]
&lrm;Blasted Ladybug!
&lrm;Blasted Valentine's Day!
&lrm;Hey, there's your chance
&lrm;to get your card back.
&lrm;-That was before.
&lrm;-Before what?
&lrm;I realised that even with
&lrm;all this hate, love still wins.
&lrm;If I wanna win-over Adrien,
&lrm;he needs to know the truth.
&lrm;This is a big day.
&lrm;[Plagg laughs]
&lrm;Can you believe all the horrible,
&lrm;thoughtless things you said?
&lrm;You think it's funny?
&lrm;[Plagg] What's the big deal?
&lrm;You've got so many cards
&lrm;from all these lady-fans,
&lrm;just take your pick.
&lrm;[mysterious music]
&lrm;Someone answered my poem?
&lrm;But I threw it away.
&lrm;"Your hair shines like the sun,
&lrm;Your eyes are gorgeous green,
&lrm;I look at you and wonder,
&lrm;Your innermost thoughts and dreams.
&lrm;Your Valentine, I will be,
&lrm;Our love will be so true,
&lrm;Together for eternity,
&lrm;My heart belongs to you."
&lrm;Anyone who writes
&lrm;as sickeningly sweet as you
&lrm;must be your soulmate.
&lrm;It isn't signed.
&lrm;Could it have come from Ladybug?
&lrm;Oh, please.
&lrm;What? You don't remember?
&lrm;Did you sign it or not?
&lrm;I don't know.
&lrm;The ladybug came while I was writing.
&lrm;Then you were yapping about your blog.
&lrm;It's all a blur.
&lrm;[she giggles]
&lrm;I don't believe you.
&lrm;The girl didn't even sign it!
&lrm;I love you,
&lrm;but sometimes, you seriously bug.
&lrm;You know that, right?
&lrm;[they giggle]