&lrm;In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life,
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet,
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;[Rock music]
&lrm;[singing] &lrm;My miraculous!
&lrm;[clapping]
&lrm;So, what do you think of my new album?
&lrm;Can you feel it, Bob? Isn't it killer?
&lrm;Not bad, Jagged, not bad,
&lrm;but if you really want
&lrm;to make something killer,
&lrm;let's talk about this duet with Mr XY.
&lrm;No way, he's not a rocker.
&lrm;He's a baby. I bet he doesn't even shave.
&lrm;This "baby" just pushed you
&lrm;off the No 1 spot.
&lrm;And? Doesn't make him
&lrm;a true musician like me.
&lrm;Penny thinks everything I do is killer.
&lrm;Penny's your agent but I'm your real boss.
&lrm;Bottom line is that Bob Roth Records
&lrm;cannot afford to be No 2
&lrm;or rep a No 2 rock star.
&lrm;Get real.
&lrm;You have to modernise your music,
&lrm;change your look, get a new style.
&lrm;You wanna talk real?
&lrm;I'm a genuine rock 'n' roller, Bob,
&lrm;not some popstar in diapers.
&lrm;I'm an artist with real talent.
&lrm;Even my hair's real.
&lrm;That's what people love about me.
&lrm;Isn't that right, Fang? Yeah.
&lrm;The artwork you did for my album
&lrm;is a waste of my time.
&lrm;Seriously, Bob? What is this trash?
&lrm;It looks like a perfume ad.
&lrm;That's what people want these days.
&lrm;Well I don't.
&lrm;My album covers exude the smell
&lrm;of sweat and leather.
&lrm;If your next album doesn't rank
&lrm;No 1 in the charts,
&lrm;it'll be your last
&lrm;with Bob Roth Records!
&lrm;I'd rather do nothing
&lrm;than sing a pathetic duet with
&lrm;a baby-faced nobody.
&lrm;Jagged and I had an idea.
&lrm;Its concept is modern
&lrm;but it also respects
&lrm;Jagged's own "rugged" style.
&lrm;The girl who made
&lrm;these glasses has real talent.
&lrm;She gets my style.
&lrm;She'll design the cover of my new album.
&lrm;A schoolgirl?
&lrm;See? That's just it.
&lrm;She's the same age
&lrm;as the target audience.
&lrm;Here's her address.
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;[snarling]
&lrm;OK. But think about that duet
&lrm;with Mr XY.
&lrm;Find that girl, Bob!
&lrm;[Bob] &lrm;So, are you interested?
&lrm;[Marinette] &lrm;Wait,
&lrm;let me get this straight.
&lrm;You want me to design
&lrm;the album cover for Jagged Stone?
&lrm;My... all-time favourite singer?
&lrm;That's right, requested
&lrm;by Jagged himself.
&lrm;I brought a few visuals
&lrm;so you can get an idea.
&lrm;This doesn't seem like Jagged,
&lrm;more like a perfume ad.
&lrm;It's the direction
&lrm;of his new image, more modern.
&lrm;Really?
&lrm;I was thinking more...
&lrm;Don't think.
&lrm;This is what is selling these days.
&lrm;Sure.
&lrm;We're in a hurry, we need a proposal
&lrm;by the end of the day.
&lrm;You up to it?
&lrm;Yeah, OK.
&lrm;[Bob] See you later then.
&lrm;[Tom] My daughter, famous designer.
&lrm;You're gonna kill it, Marinette style!
&lrm;Boo-ya!
&lrm;[electronic music]
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;Why does Jagged Stone want
&lrm;to change his style?
&lrm;XY's music is so... cold
&lrm;and lifeless, repetitive, mundane...
&lrm;The total opposite of Jagged's.
&lrm;And what I've just done is...
&lrm;so not my style, either.
&lrm;So why're you doing it, then?
&lrm;That's what I was asked to do.
&lrm;Follow your gut feeling,
&lrm;do something that's really you.
&lrm;But you heard what Mr Roth said,
&lrm;"This is what's selling these days".
&lrm;Yeah, but Jagged Stone wanted you
&lrm;because of your style.
&lrm;[groaning] The pressure... I can't deal...
&lrm;Marinette, superhero,
&lrm;defender of the innocent,
&lrm;fighter of all the rights,
&lrm;can't deal with the pressure?
&lrm;[electronic music]
&lrm;What happened to the raw
&lrm;impulsive artistry that make this?
&lrm;Yeah, about that... Mr Roth told me...
&lrm;She represents our target audience.
&lrm;Her modern concept is
&lrm;exactly what you need.
&lrm;It looks like the cover of that YZ guy.
&lrm;Don't listen to Bob.
&lrm;Can you do another one... Jagged-style?
&lrm;Yeah, sure...
&lrm;But I don't know if...
&lrm;You're my girl, Marinette, remember,
&lrm;raw, impulsive artistry.
&lrm;-We're all done here, Bob.
&lrm;-No, we are...
&lrm;[snarling]
&lrm;[Bob whimpers]
&lrm;[Penny] &lrm;Come, Marinette. Don't worry.
&lrm;Just do your best.
&lrm;[snarling]
&lrm;We are not...
&lrm;Why am I No 1?
&lrm;Simple, it's all about technology.
&lrm;This computer produces music
&lrm;and lyrics people will like.
&lrm;It's guaranteed success.
&lrm;You knocked Jagged Stone off
&lrm;the No 1 spot.
&lrm;What do you think of him?
&lrm;Jagged Stone?
&lrm;The "Hero of Rock n' Roll"?
&lrm;Try "Ragged" Stone.
&lrm;He's old school, a has-been.
&lrm;Me? Old school? A has been?
&lrm;His career is over now.
&lrm;He'll never be No 1, not while XY here.
&lrm;Why you... little perfume ad!
&lrm;My music is killer.
&lrm;He's stealing my catchphrases!
&lrm;Mr XY will be giving
&lrm;a very special one-time concert
&lrm;from the Eiffel Tower
&lrm;to celebrate his album's success
&lrm;and thank his fans.
&lrm;Ragged, wanna hear
&lrm;what today's music sounds like?
&lrm;Come to my concert.
&lrm;I'll get you a front-row seat, old man.
&lrm;He can't say that!
&lrm;He's an insult to rock, and me!
&lrm;[rock music]
&lrm;[munching]
&lrm;I feel a disharmonious soul,
&lrm;an angry discord.
&lrm;ideal prey for my evil Akumas...
&lrm;Go find that Jagged Stone
&lrm;and rock his world!
&lrm;[rock music]
&lrm;Guitar Villain, I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;I'm giving you and your crocodile
&lrm;the power to show the whole world
&lrm;that you are the No 1 rocker.
&lrm;Just make sure you get me
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir's
&lrm;Miraculouses in return.
&lrm;Yeah, let's rock.
&lrm;Hey, Marinette. Hey, hi.
&lrm;Hey...Oh,
&lrm;What's going on?
&lrm;I mean, how's up? I mean...
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;Adrikins!
&lrm;There you are.
&lrm;Amazing Chloe has a surprise for you.
&lrm;She knows you're a fan of Jagged Stone.
&lrm;I am.
&lrm;So... you get a private meeting
&lrm;with your favourite star.
&lrm;He's staying right here in daddy's hotel.
&lrm;Is Chloe the best? Is Chloe the best?
&lrm;Did you hear that?
&lrm;Chloe speaking in the 3rd person?
&lrm;Totally... annoying.
&lrm;No, the part where Adrien likes
&lrm;Jagged just like me.
&lrm;Now I definitely can't
&lrm;mess up the artwork.
&lrm;So now what?
&lrm;I'm going to design
&lrm;Jagged Stone's album my way
&lrm;and no one else's.
&lrm;Way to go. Follow your instinct.
&lrm;[questioning sigh]
&lrm;Talking bag,
&lrm;new technology... imported from Japan.
&lrm;You and I like the same kind
&lrm;of music, isn't that awesome?
&lrm;I thought you liked Mr XY.
&lrm;Of course. Don't you?
&lrm;Not really.
&lrm;Well, neither do I.
&lrm;See? We have the same great taste.
&lrm;A duet with Mr XY
&lrm;will prove that Jagged's still...
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;From now on,
&lrm;you can call me Guitar Villain.
&lrm;I'll never do a duet with Mr XY.
&lrm;In fact, soon,
&lrm;there won't even be a Mr XY.
&lrm;Rockin' Riff Baby!
&lrm;[rock music]
&lrm;Soon, there'll be nothing
&lrm;but Guitar Villain fans.
&lrm;The one and only rocker.
&lrm;Such symphony to my ears.
&lrm;It won't be long before
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir show up
&lrm;to meet their doom.
&lrm;Hurry, Adrien. Get me outta here.
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Yeah, Guitar Villain.
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;[gasping]
&lrm;Rockin' Riff, baby!
&lrm;[Rock music]
&lrm;[squeaking]
&lrm;Rockin' Riff, baby!
&lrm;[rock music]
&lrm;Hey, Jagged, try and rock my world.
&lrm;The name's Guitar Villain, pussycat.
&lrm;Awesome Solo!
&lrm;Welcome to my fan club.
&lrm;[rock music]
&lrm;[rumbling]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;Do see what I see, Tikki?
&lrm;If you see a dragon, then yes I do.
&lrm;I've gotta transform.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;Cat Noir, you OK?
&lrm;Good to see you, milady.
&lrm;Cat Noir, your stick!
&lrm;[he yells]
&lrm;[he chuckles]
&lrm;You're wasting my time.
&lrm;I've got a concert to get to.
&lrm;We've gotta follow him.
&lrm;His power comes from his guitar.
&lrm;We've gotta stop him from playing.
&lrm;I won't let you do this solo.
&lrm;[electronic music]
&lrm;You're an insult to the music world, XY!
&lrm;An hologram?
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;Where's the real XY?
&lrm;He's not here.
&lrm;The concert's not till tonight.
&lrm;I'm just setting up the special effects.
&lrm;Awesome Solo!
&lrm;[rock music]
&lrm;[exploding]
&lrm;Where's Mr XY? Answer me!
&lrm;On TV. He's at the TV station.
&lrm;Rockin' Riff Baby!
&lrm;[gasping] You again?
&lrm;To the TV studios, Fang.
&lrm;He'll get there before us!
&lrm;We'd better make sure
&lrm;he doesn't find XY.
&lrm;[Mrs &lrm;Chamack]&lrm; Kids plus TV,
&lrm;how can I help?
&lrm;Ladybug says we're in danger.
&lrm;Mr XY, we have to leave now.
&lrm;What the heck?
&lrm;Ladybug said you're not safe.
&lrm;Hit the credits.
&lrm;[dramatic music]
&lrm;Where's that studio?
&lrm;[Receptionist] Third... floor.
&lrm;[frustrated sigh]
&lrm;Awesome Solo!
&lrm;[Alec] Everything will be fine.
&lrm;It's just a precaution.
&lrm;We must get you to safety.
&lrm;What's he gonna do,
&lrm;blow me away with his "evil guitar solo"?
&lrm;YES!
&lrm;We'll catch him,
&lrm;and get you to the Eiffel Tower
&lrm;in time for your live concert.
&lrm;[puffing] Who cares?
&lrm;My roadies can project my image.
&lrm;Live concerts are so 10-minutes-ago.
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;Good job, Fang.
&lrm;I've found you at last, XY.
&lrm;Ready for the show?
&lrm;Dude, are you Jagged Stone?
&lrm;Was Jagged Stone...
&lrm;Now I'm Guitar Villain!
&lrm;[he laughs] Don't worry,
&lrm;you don't deserve to become
&lrm;one of my fans.
&lrm;I've got something special
&lrm;in store for you
&lrm;something with a little rock 'n' roll!
&lrm;No!
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Back to square one.
&lrm;We're in for quite a concert. You ready?
&lrm;To Rock 'n' Riff, baby!
&lrm;[rock music]
&lrm;[cheering]
&lrm;Hello, Paris!
&lrm;You said your music is
&lrm;the only killer music around,
&lrm;is that right?
&lrm;I-I d-didn't mean it.
&lrm;Listen, Mr... Guitar...
&lrm;we can...do the duet your style.
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;[cackling]
&lrm;Too late. I'm going to show you
&lrm;what killer music really is.
&lrm;Ultimate Solo!
&lrm;[rock music] Stop, please.
&lrm;[Ladybug] &lrm;XY's gonna fall!
&lrm;Talk about being
&lrm;between a rock and a hard place.
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;Easy, easy, nice dragon.
&lrm;Enough already,
&lrm;we've got a stuffed kitty to rescue.
&lrm;[Cat Noir]
&lrm;Well, the bug mastered the dragon.
&lrm;How d'you like the concert?
&lrm;Still think your music is
&lrm;the only killer music?
&lrm;N-No. Please... don't.
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;-Awesome Solo...
&lrm;-Not so fast!
&lrm;[dragon roars] My dragon?
&lrm;Ladybug, Cat Noir, hurry!
&lrm;Nice job.
&lrm;Too late.
&lrm;Nothing can stop Guitar Villain.
&lrm;Rockin' Riff Baby!
&lrm;We only rock to the real Jagged Stone.
&lrm;The Akuma must be in his guitar.
&lrm;How we gonna get to that?
&lrm;[Ladybug] Let's go backstage.
&lrm;Where did they go?
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;You OK?
&lrm;Too bad.
&lrm;They're gonna miss the final song.
&lrm;[cackling] Solo!
&lrm;[whimpering]
&lrm;Are you scared?
&lrm;Or is it too awesome for you?
&lrm;Please, Mr Guitar Villain.
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;-Extreme fixing gel?
&lrm;-You plan on doing his hair?
&lrm;[rock music]
&lrm;Actually, yes!
&lrm;Go get him, Cat Noir!
&lrm;Maybe you haven't heard it properly.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;Awesome Solo!
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;[he screams]
&lrm;I can't see! Where are my fans?
&lrm;[XY] &lrm;Hey,
&lrm;don't forget me!
&lrm;[screaming]
&lrm;[he squeals]
&lrm;Music's over, Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Rock 'n' Roll!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;POUND IT!
&lrm;What's he doing here?
&lrm;He came to tell you that
&lrm;you've underestimated his music
&lrm;This guy's crazy!
&lrm;Thank you.
&lrm;How about an autograph, Jagged?
&lrm;I still have work to do. Bug out!
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;Don't do your victory dance
&lrm;just yet, because one day,
&lrm;I'll play you my favourite music,
&lrm;the anthem of your defeat,
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir!
&lrm;[rock music]
&lrm;Done!
&lrm;Jagged Stone will love it.
&lrm;I hope so, it's 100% Marinette.
&lrm;It's my... awesome solo!
&lrm;[Tikki] Rock 'n' Roll!
&lrm;Yeah, this is it.
&lrm;You did it, girl.
&lrm;I can almost smell
&lrm;the leather and sweat
&lrm;radiating off of this design.
&lrm;[he sniffs]
&lrm;You actually are smelling it.
&lrm;I made a scented sticker
&lrm;for your album.
&lrm;I want it. I gotta have it.
&lrm;It's authentic. It's original.
&lrm;It's...so jagged.
&lrm;No, you can't. It's not what...
&lrm;Fine, then I'm outta here.
&lrm;I'm sure another record company
&lrm;would be perfectly happy
&lrm;with a No 2 chart-topper.
&lrm;[Bob huffs]
&lrm;[excited squealing]
&lrm;I've just designed the cover
&lrm;for Jagged Stone's new album.
&lrm;I'm so proud of you, Marinette
&lrm;Jagged Stone's new album
&lrm;hit the charts at No 1,
&lrm;knocking Mr XY off of his throne.
&lrm;Welcome back, King of Rock.
&lrm;Hey, Marinette.
&lrm;I'm a huge fan of Jagged Stone's
&lrm;and I saw you designed
&lrm;his album cover.
&lrm;I-I did. Crazy, isn't it?
&lrm;I wanted to ask if...
&lrm;I could get it... autographed?
&lrm;O-OK, sure... I'll ask him.
&lrm;No... actually, I meant you.
&lrm;Me?...Me?
&lrm;If you wouldn't mind.
&lrm;Awesome! Thanks, Marinette.
&lrm;[growling]
&lrm;Did I imagine it or did you sign
&lrm;an autograph for Adrien?
&lrm;I can't feel my legs.
&lrm;Hold me up. I'm gonna fall over.
&lrm;Is he still around?
&lrm;It's OK, he's gone. You can fall over.
&lrm;This is the happiest day of my life.
&lrm;[Marinette] Rock 'n' Roll!