&lrm;In the daytime I'm Marinette,
&lrm;just a normal girl with a normal life.
&lrm;but there's something about me
&lrm;that no-one knows yet
&lrm;because I have a secret.
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! Simply the best! ♪
&lrm;♪ Up to the test when things go wrong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! The luckiest! ♪
&lrm;♪ The power of love, always so strong! ♪
&lrm;♪ Miraculous! ♪
&lrm;-Ready, dad?
&lrm;-As much as I'll ever be.
&lrm;Happy career day, my darlings.
&lrm;[Dad] My day begins
&lrm;at 4 am every morning
&lrm;because the bakery opens at 7.
&lrm;You'd think it's a routine life,
&lrm;making the same pastries, rolls, cakes...
&lrm;but every day's different.
&lrm;One day someone might order
&lrm;an Eiffel Tower cake and the next...
&lrm;You've reached Gabriel Agreste's
&lrm;voicemail.
&lrm;Please leave a message.
&lrm;Hi, father, it's me.
&lrm;It's parents' career day, remember?
&lrm;I was hoping you'd show up.
&lrm;Call me back.
&lrm;-You OK?
&lrm;-Yeah, whatever. Nothing new.
&lrm;[he sighs sadly]
&lrm;[Dad] Marinette will come round
&lrm;to pass out some fresh croissants.
&lrm;Thank you, Mr. Dupain.
&lrm;Now, let's meet Alya's mom.
&lrm;She's head-chef at Le Grand Paris hotel
&lrm;owned by Mayor Bourgeois.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;It's beautiful.
&lrm;Look, don't touch.
&lrm;[Mayor] Put it away, Chloe.
&lrm;It could get in the wrong hands.
&lrm;How many croissants would your dad
&lrm;have to sell to buy one of these?
&lrm;What am I saying?
&lrm;He'd have to sell the whole store.
&lrm;If you're so rich,
&lrm;you don't need free croissants.
&lrm;[she groans] Jealous.
&lrm;Is that camembert?
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;That's not camembert,
&lrm;but it is very shiny.
&lrm;I like shiny.
&lrm;I have no dishes to share
&lrm;but maybe Mr. Bourgeois will invite you all
&lrm;to the hotel for lunch.
&lrm;[policeman chuckles]
&lrm;[Plagg giggles]
&lrm;[she squeals]
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;Do you ever not trip up?
&lrm;[Marinette groans]
&lrm;[Plagg struggles]
&lrm;Next is Sabrina's father, a policeman,
&lrm;Officer Roger.
&lrm;I've been a police officer for 15 years,
&lrm;and I believe that everyone
&lrm;is innocent until proven guilty.
&lrm;My bracelet, it's gone!
&lrm;I had it a second ago.
&lrm;You, you stole it!
&lrm;What are you talking about?
&lrm;You tripped on my bag
&lrm;so you could steal it.
&lrm;You're a policeman, arrest her.
&lrm;[angrily] My daughter is not a thief.
&lrm;Hold on, Miss Bourgeois.
&lrm;We don't accuse without proof.
&lrm;Everyone calm down.
&lrm;Maybe you simply misplaced it.
&lrm;You're calling me a liar?
&lrm;Daddy!
&lrm;Roger, I demand you search this girl.
&lrm;[Chloe chuckles]
&lrm;[teacher] Please, everybody.
&lrm;Need I remind you
&lrm;that as mayor, I am your superior?
&lrm;But it's against the law.
&lrm;I can't just go...
&lrm;OK, then you're fired.
&lrm;Mayor, you can't be serious.
&lrm;Over a missing bracelet?
&lrm;This is my daughter's bracelet.
&lrm;You're incompetent, and you're fired.
&lrm;Get out!
&lrm;[he sighs sadly]
&lrm;[Chloe] Let's call Ladybug.
&lrm;She'll actually do something.
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;Parent-child relationships
&lrm;can be so complicated...
&lrm;and a perfect breeding-ground for stress.
&lrm;When there's no more law and order,
&lrm;there's only chaos left.
&lrm;Fly away, my evil little Akuma,
&lrm;and take control of this policeman.
&lrm;[flapping]
&lrm;He expects me to break the law?
&lrm;That's just... criminal.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] Rogercop,
&lrm;I am Hawk Moth.
&lrm;This city needs a true, ruthless,
&lrm;righter of wrongs
&lrm;and that is where you come in.
&lrm;Yes, sir.
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir
&lrm;must be destroyed if you want retribution.
&lrm;You will seize their Miraculouses for me.
&lrm;Do we have an agreement?
&lrm;[robotic voice] &lrm;Affirmative!
&lrm;Cat Noir and Ladybug
&lrm;will be powerless against me.
&lrm;Justice will prevail in Paris.
&lrm;Don't even think of going
&lrm;near my daughter's bag!
&lrm;Do you know who I am?
&lrm;Gentlemen, this is a school.
&lrm;Think of the children.
&lrm;I'm sure the bracelet is
&lrm;around here somewhere.
&lrm;It probably just rolled out of her bag.
&lrm;I'd try and get as far away
&lrm;as possible from that brat too.
&lrm;[giggling]
&lrm;Hey, Nino's been filming everything.
&lrm;We can see what really happened.
&lrm;Marinette will come round
&lrm;to pass out some fresh croissants.
&lrm;[accelerated voice]
&lrm;[Marinette] There you have it.
&lrm;Sabrina was holding it.
&lrm;Yes, but I gave it back straight after.
&lrm;Chloe, take a look in your BFF's bag.
&lrm;Are you saying I'm a thief?
&lrm;No.
&lrm;Chloe's the one calling people thieves.
&lrm;I'm going by what's on the video.
&lrm;[irritated groan]
&lrm;[gasps]
&lrm;Yes, I sketched it,
&lrm;but I didn't do anything else.
&lrm;[questioning sigh]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;You're under arrest.
&lrm;What? What for?
&lrm;Littering,
&lrm;jaywalking, and crossing on a red light.
&lrm;Well, I suppose...
&lrm;I did but you can't arrest me.
&lrm;Who are you any anyway?
&lrm;You don't look like a policeman.
&lrm;I sentence you to litter duty.
&lrm;[whistle blows]
&lrm;[she gasps]
&lrm;[whirring]
&lrm;Next mission,
&lrm;seek justice from Mayor Bourgeois.
&lrm;[Mayor] Give me the tape.
&lrm;I'll have it analysed.
&lrm;-No, it's my camera.
&lrm;-Do you know who I am?
&lrm;[Plagg struggles] I'm the Mayor!
&lrm;[Mayor] Where's the principle?
&lrm;I want to see him now!
&lrm;I won't bother you with the story,
&lrm;it's a long, boring...
&lrm;Yes you will, and fast.
&lrm;We have a big problem.
&lrm;If by big you're referring to my hard abs,
&lrm;thanks for noticing.
&lrm;[whirring and stomping]
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Now we have a bigger problem.
&lrm;Hey! You can't just walk in here.
&lrm;I can go wherever I want,
&lrm;whenever I want.
&lrm;I am the law.
&lrm;Well, I'm the authority here.
&lrm;You are guilty of obstructing
&lrm;the path of justice.
&lrm;[zapping] &lrm;I sentence you to do laps.
&lrm;[he sighs]
&lrm;[whistle blows]
&lrm;[yelling] Wait.
&lrm;I can't... control... my arms.
&lrm;Why can't I transform?
&lrm;The bracelet will get absorbed
&lrm;with me and damage your powers.
&lrm;[irritated groan]
&lrm;[evil cackling]
&lrm;Soon, Ladybug and Cat Noir
&lrm;will show up to meet their doom.
&lrm;See, Chloe? I tripped on the bag,
&lrm;Sabrina held the bracelet
&lrm;and Nathaniel sketched it.
&lrm;We are all suspects.
&lrm;What's that supposed to mean?
&lrm;I didn't swipe it.
&lrm;And neither did I
&lrm;but Chloe could accuse
&lrm;anyone and everyone.
&lrm;Fine, since you're a suspect,
&lrm;you'll let me search your bag.
&lrm;Ok, but only if search everyone else's
&lrm;too.
&lrm;No-one's rummaging in my bag.
&lrm;Marinette, let the adults handle this.
&lrm;She called me a thief.
&lrm;I'm just defending myself.
&lrm;You're also accusing your friends
&lrm;like Chloe's doing.
&lrm;I'm Chloe's BFF.
&lrm;I wouldn't steal from her.
&lrm;What about Adrien?
&lrm;He's in 4 seconds of that video.
&lrm;And we haven't seen him since.
&lrm;Not Adrien.
&lrm;Why would he steal a bracelet?
&lrm;If anyone's guilty, it's one of us.
&lrm;Are you accusing us?
&lrm;I want an attorney.
&lrm;[Dad] Marinette, stop.
&lrm;[Max] We should search the parents.
&lrm;[Rogercop] &lrm;Where is the Mayor?
&lrm;Dad?
&lrm;That's your dad?
&lrm;-Hello, may I help you?
&lrm;-Where is the Mayor?
&lrm;I think he already left.
&lrm;Are you lying?
&lrm;Yes... I mean no.
&lrm;If nobody speaks up, I'll arrest you all.
&lrm;Where is your father?
&lrm;I don't know.
&lrm;[Mayor shouting] Mr. Principle,
&lrm;find out who stole it ASAP!
&lrm;[Mayor] Or your job is on the line.
&lrm;My Daughter has been treated
&lrm;with disrespect.
&lrm;I was only defending myself.
&lrm;My dad's right,
&lrm;I accused everyone in the process.
&lrm;I don't think any of us took it.
&lrm;You'll find a way to make it right.
&lrm;Yeah, well, right now,
&lrm;I've gotta transform.
&lrm;Tikki, spots on!
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;I thought it was camembert.
&lrm;Anyone can make a mistake.
&lrm;You're always thinking
&lrm;with your stomach... Wait.
&lrm;A bit of pepper...
&lrm;[Plagg sniffs]
&lrm;[he sneezes loudly]
&lrm;[Adrien] &lrm;Gesundheit!
&lrm;Plagg, claws out!
&lrm;I'm warning you,
&lrm;if you don't find it by this evening,
&lrm;I'll cut off all funding for the school.
&lrm;Understood?
&lrm;But how am I supposed to...
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;Didn't anyone ever teach you to knock?
&lrm;Justice doesn't need an invitation.
&lrm;Mayor, you're under arrest
&lrm;for abuse of power.
&lrm;[Gasping] Look who's talking.
&lrm;Paris has a new righter of wrongs.
&lrm;Your services are no longer required.
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;You can't accuse everyone
&lrm;of every little wrong-doing!
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[caretaker whimpers]
&lrm;[sigh of relief]
&lrm;Mr. Rogercop, I need your help.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;[he gasps]
&lrm;[she gasps] Hey, come back.
&lrm;[thudding footsteps]
&lrm;[she yells]
&lrm;[she struggles]
&lrm;[she squeals]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;You're obstructing justice.
&lrm;You'll pay for this.
&lrm;You can add bodily harm
&lrm;to the charges.
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;Listen,
&lrm;you're Sabrina's dad and a good cop.
&lrm;Don't let the evil person
&lrm;who gave you these powers
&lrm;make an evil cop out of you.
&lrm;Don't listen to her.
&lrm;Take their Miraculouses!
&lrm;Their powers belong to me!
&lrm;Justice must prevail
&lrm;in the streets of Paris.
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[she screams]
&lrm;The mayor must pay for getting rid
&lrm;of his best police officer.
&lrm;Mr. Rogercop!
&lrm;I've got a serious problem,
&lrm;worse than a bad hair day.
&lrm;-Come, we'll talk about it.
&lrm;-OK
&lrm;[Cat Noir] Chloe, no!
&lrm;[thud]
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[ladybird pants]
&lrm;I bet you missed me.
&lrm;[they yell]
&lrm;[she huffs]
&lrm;I know that Marinette stole my bracelet.
&lrm;She must be arrested.
&lrm;[car] &lrm;Auto-pilot engaged.
&lrm;[Chloe] Hello, are you listening to me?
&lrm;Thanks for the lasso, Lassy.
&lrm;Where are you going?
&lrm;Who's going to drive this car?
&lrm;Did I thank you for the lift?
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;[yelling]
&lrm;Nice shoes.
&lrm;I could use a pair like that.
&lrm;[Ladybug screams]
&lrm;Grab onto me.
&lrm;No, Ladybug!
&lrm;What have you done?
&lrm;Snatch his Miraculous!
&lrm;[Hawk Moth] His ring!
&lrm;[whirring]
&lrm;[Cat Noir yells]
&lrm;[struggling] Nice day for a swim.
&lrm;[he whimpers]
&lrm;[sigh of relief]
&lrm;Well, hey. I'm head over heels
&lrm;to see you, milady.
&lrm;[kissing]
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;You're welcome. You owe me one.
&lrm;Sure but I'll take credit for that.
&lrm;[car] &lrm;Mayor's Limousine located.
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[Ladybug] There's no point
&lrm;running after him.
&lrm;He's way out of reach now.
&lrm;Well, if it's the mayor he wants...
&lrm;He'll be heading for the city hall.
&lrm;Do I sense a plan?
&lrm;[whooshing]
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;Let's go.
&lrm;[sizzling]
&lrm;Call all available police forces ASAP.
&lrm;That's an order!
&lrm;[shouting]
&lrm;[fearful cries]
&lrm;[sizzling]
&lrm;Bourgeois,
&lrm;I'm taking over.
&lrm;Relinquish your powers.
&lrm;Never!
&lrm;[whirring]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;These handcuffs won't change my mind.
&lrm;Then maybe this will.
&lrm;[whistle]
&lrm;Hey!
&lrm;Don't you dare lay a finger
&lrm;on my little girl.
&lrm;So much for your powers.
&lrm;[mocking laugh]
&lrm;Paris has a new superpower.
&lrm;His name is Rogercop.
&lrm;I hereby relinquish
&lrm;all authority to Rogercop.
&lrm;All citizens are ordered to answer to him.
&lrm;Ladybug and Cat Noir are now outlaws.
&lrm;They must be hunted down
&lrm;and taken into custody immediately.
&lrm;[grunting]
&lrm;[struggling]
&lrm;Let's go get 'em.
&lrm;[he grunts]
&lrm;[helicopters whir]
&lrm;So now we're the nation's
&lrm;most wanted felons?
&lrm;We haven't done anything.
&lrm;You can't accuse someone
&lrm;without proof.
&lrm;We should defend ourselves in court.
&lrm;Not while Rogercop's
&lrm;the Chief of Justice.
&lrm;[sighing]
&lrm;How many times have we saved Paris?
&lrm;We're still saving Paris.
&lrm;[Cat Noir pants]
&lrm;Something about Paris
&lrm;just makes you wanna dance.
&lrm;You won't be dancing
&lrm;after I'm done with you.
&lrm;Arrest him.
&lrm;So you won't be joining me?
&lrm;[thumping]
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;[door creaks]
&lrm;[tiptoeing]
&lrm;[hushing]
&lrm;[whispering loudly]
&lrm;Go, Ladybug, go!
&lrm;[she groans]
&lrm;Ladybug, it's time for justice to prevail.
&lrm;You've got justice and revenge
&lrm;all mixed up, Rogercop.
&lrm;Lucky charm!
&lrm;Oven mitts?
&lrm;What am I supposed to do with these?
&lrm;[she whimpers]
&lrm;Fabulous, so wretchedly fabulous!
&lrm;[groaning]
&lrm;OK, show's over.
&lrm;Sorry, no encore tonight.
&lrm;[policemen groan]
&lrm;[Ladybug groans]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Get Ladybug
&lrm;and Cat Noir.
&lrm;[squealing]
&lrm;[angrily] Hey, my hair!
&lrm;Stop shooting like an idiot.
&lrm;You're supposed to seize
&lrm;their Miraculouses!
&lrm;The Akuma must be in his whistle.
&lrm;We've got to get to it.
&lrm;How?
&lrm;[they gasp]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;Whenever you're ready milady.
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;[she sighs]
&lrm;I have an idea,
&lrm;but I need something like... a ring.
&lrm;[panting]
&lrm;[zapping]
&lrm;Where am I gonna get a ring?
&lrm;[tinkling]
&lrm;Ladybug, over there.
&lrm;That's Chloe's bracelet.
&lrm;Exactly what I need.
&lrm;Fend off Rogercop as long as you can.
&lrm;Whenever you're ready.
&lrm;Cataclysm!
&lrm;[he groans]
&lrm;[he chuckles]
&lrm;Gotcha.
&lrm;[fading cry] &lrm;No!
&lrm;Do more evil-doing for you,
&lrm;little Akuma.
&lrm;Time to de-evilise!
&lrm;Gotcha!
&lrm;Bye-bye, little butterfly.
&lrm;Miraculous Ladybug!
&lrm;[she cheers]
&lrm;[he gasps and laughs]
&lrm;[gasping] What am I doing up here?
&lrm;[together] Pount it!
&lrm;As Rogercop would say,
&lrm;[Robotically]
&lrm;Justice has prevailed in Paris.
&lrm;[bleeping]
&lrm;I'd stick around
&lrm;but you'd see me without my mask
&lrm;and you wouldn't be able to resist me.
&lrm;I doubt it,
&lrm;but I'll take your word for it.
&lrm;[she chuckles]
&lrm;You may have eluded me this time,
&lrm;Ladybug,
&lrm;but one of these days,
&lrm;I'll be ruling the world,
&lrm;and you and Cat Noir
&lrm;won't be a part of it!
&lrm;[Roger] I think this belongs to you.
&lrm;My bag... my...my bracelet.
&lrm;But... how?
&lrm;Roger... you found the bracelet?
&lrm;It was in Chloe's bag all along.
&lrm;It must have fallen
&lrm;into a side-pocket
&lrm;when that girl tripped.
&lrm;Roger, I apologize for being accusatory
&lrm;and for firing you for no good reason.
&lrm;I think Officer Roger
&lrm;has proven his worth.
&lrm;You'd be wrong not to keep him.
&lrm;Of course, Ladybug,
&lrm;you're absolutely right.
&lrm;And it's actually Lieutenant Roger now.
&lrm;Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
&lrm;I'm proud to be on the force
&lrm;and I vow to uphold my belief
&lrm;that everyone is innocent
&lrm;until proven guilty.
&lrm;[earing bleeps]
&lrm;Very good, a valuable lesson learnt,
&lrm;right Chloe?
&lrm;[she groans] Yes, daddy.
&lrm;Lesson learnt.