Welcome to today's race.
This circuit has a length
of 4.5 kilometers
and a total of 12 turns.
Everyone has a chance to win,
but if nothing goes wrong,
keep your eye on car number seven.
Let's see if he'll finally win
the championship
after a long and competitive season.
And it's the final lap.
Number eight shoots ahead from the curve.
Can car number three block him?
What a tight race.
Look at that.
Number three missed that right turn.
Number seven overtakes him
from the right side
in the last 50 meters of the race.
That's the flag.
That's awesome! How incredible!
The winner is Got Kiattipoom.
He's the champion
of Thailand Super Turbo 2020.
Who would you like to thank
for your success today?
First of all, I have to thank my crew.
They're the real heroes.
And of course, I want to thank…
my parents
for always supporting me
and doing everything for me.
Are they here today?
My parents…
They are watching me from heaven.
All right then. Thank you.
Hey.
Congratulations.
It's incredible that you've come
this far with Hot Rod.
Hot Rod?
I've told you a thousand times
that my car is called King of the World.
Why King of the World?
It's the ruler of the blue planet
in the Solar System.
That's too long. Hot Rod is way better.
No, it's not.
It's an obscene joke for obscene people.
If you had known I'd get here,
would you have stopped me
from racing when I was a kid?
Your mom told me to look after you.
Car racing is dangerous.
Not every racer can win a championship.
Is that right?
Mom shouldn't have asked you
to do anything.
If you hadn't gone to prison,
she wouldn't have killed herself.
You're going too fast.
People say that
in the seconds before you die,
your whole life will flash
before your eyes.
Is that true? How can that be?
I don't see anything. Am I not dying?
Hey. Wait a second. Hang on.
No. I don't want any flashbacks.
Put these away, Got.
-You need to make him study hard.
-Your grades are shit.
Help me.
Where are you going, Got? You punk.
Troublemaker!
If you want to be
a race car driver, call me.
Do you have a problem?
Dad.
Didn't he die with me?
Out of my way! Watch where you're going.
Thank you.
Miss…
Are you Ms. Somsong?
It's really you. I'm Kiattipoom.
You were my teacher in sixth grade.
You showed my report card to my dad
and he kicked my ass in front of you.
It must have been around 2010
if I remember correctly.
Are you nuts? 2010?
We're in the year 1998.
-What?
-Get out of here.
Ms. Somsong.
It's Got.
I'm Kiattipoom.
What the hell?
Do you have a death wish?
Watch where you're going.
He stole my purse! Help!
Hey.
I'm already dead.
I can do anything.
Watch out!
What the hell is that?
You rock, dude.
I'll take it from here.
That's not fair.
You're a real badass.
You're awesome.
Let me go.
Dad?
Who's your dad?
-Dad.
-Dad, my ass!
You're still alive.
What?
Hey. Wait.
This is the police.
-Hands up! Don't move!
-All right.
What's going on? What the hell is this?
It doesn't look like an official ID card.
I already told you everything.
Stop wasting our time.
Tell us the truth,
or I'll add another charge
to your crimes besides perjury.
You'll also be charged with forgery.
When is your birthday?
Next year.
You have the right to remain silent,
but not the right to be a pain in the ass.
What the hell?
I didn't do anything wrong.
For God's sake.
If you don't want to go to jail,
you must get someone
to confirm your identity.
-Take that.
-Damn.
Boss, you suck. You're a wimp.
Come here.
Anyone can insult me
except you, Bo.
Come on.
Boss, why did you hit me?
-You drew on my face, punk.
-It's the police, Prem.
The police are here. I'm out of here!
Who's that monkey?
That's Lham's son, Bo.
And who are you?
I'm Bae.
My dad owns a clock
near the eyewear tower.
I mean, he owns an eyewear store
near the clock tower.
This doesn't concern you.
Is this thug your brother?
I'll be damned! It's my little brother!
Damn! Long time no see.
I almost didn't recognize you.
He said it's been a week.
We're tight. One week feels like forever.
That's right. I miss him
after not seeing him for a day.
Two days is excruciating.
I barely remember his face
after three days.
Right, brother?
Who's your dad?
-Somchai
-Sommai.
-You're lying.
-Hey!
We're half-brothers.
You two kind of look alike,
but I won't believe it
unless you can show me proof
that you're really brothers.
I'll tell you what.
You can go look under my bed upstairs.
Crawl under the bed and look up.
You'll see a wad of cash taped underneath.
-Lieutenant Tu.
-Yes, sir.
-Hey!
-Deputy.
I found nothing, sir.
This means…
You asshole! I hid my money there.
Did you dare steal it?
What money? What are you talking about?
Come on. You'd better come clean.
Get over here.
Come here.
I had to do it
or they wouldn't believe me.
You didn't have to punch me so hard.
What's your name?
-I'm Got.
-Got?
Like a Tamagotchi?
What was your dad thinking,
giving you such a silly name?
It's just Got.
Did he name you
after the monster Godzilla?
Hey, Godzilla.
Godzilla.
Stop it. You watch too many cartoons.
What kind of name is Got?
It's so kooky.
"Kooky"? No one uses that word anymore.
What are you doing?
It's for your bruises.
Stop it.
If Dad is this young,
Mom must still be alive.
This means I can finally meet her.
-Do you have a girl, sir?
-What the hell?
Why are you being so formal?
Are you a snob?
We are chums now, okay?
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
No.
It's not appropriate.
What's your girlfriend's name?
What's the matter with you?
You haven't asked me my name,
but you want to know hers.
Don't tell me you're hanging around here
because you want to steal my girl.
Are you nuts? Who would do that?
Your name is Prem.
I already know, so I didn't ask.
Listen.
Do you want to join my gang?
What gang?
Gangly and lanky?
Hot Rod Gang.
Why does that sound familiar?
Hey. Do you know what hot rod means?
Of course. That's why I call my gang that.
Before you can join Hot Rod,
you need to pass a test.
Do you see that guy with a gun?
That's Neung. He works
for a mob boss in Bangkok.
He runs a used car tent
as a cover for his loan shark ring.
How did you know all this?
Through my girlfriend.
She mortgaged
her dad's karaoke bar with him.
I actually hit the target.
Shit.
He's practicing shooting.
This isn't a good hiding place.
Got.
Come have dinner
at my girlfriend's place tonight.
Can I come too, boss?
No.
Why not? Please let me come.
There aren't enough seats.
This is an old house.
It looks exactly the same.
An old house is supposed to look the same.
Otherwise, it would be a new house.
What a stupid thing to say.
Hey. Why do you seem so excited?
I want to know what's for dinner.
I'm hungry.
The fish is ready.
-It's coming out now.
-Okay.
Holy shit!
Are you Mom or Grandma?
I'm not your mom.
-I'll smack you with this.
-Take it easy, Mrs. Toy.
This guy is a loose cannon.
Don't mind him.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'll head out to the market.
Won't you have dinner with us?
No. I'm not in the mood.
This is Got, our new gang member.
This is Bew, my girlfriend.
-Oi!
-What?
-She's my girlfriend.
-Okay.
Wait a minute. Her name is Bew.
-Give me lots of it.
-Okay.
Hang on. What's your real name
and last name?
Well, I used to be a fortuneteller.
I can tell things from your name.
Really? Do mine. My name is Prem--
No. I only do girls' names.
I'm not good with guys' names.
So, what's your real name?
I'm Pranee Cheevakul.
Damn it. She's not my mother.
No way. It can't be. This can't be right.
How long have you been together?
Is it serious?
Well, we're planning
on getting married soon.
-You can't!
-What the hell, man?
I mean, you can't do that
because you shouldn't rush into marriage.
We've only been together for 12 years.
Shit. They are serious.
I would never be born.
You should eat more.
-Stop it.
-What's your problem?
Just eat your food. She can help herself.
-Have more veggies.
-No.
Just eat your food.
Do you need a hand?
No.
Bew.
Do you like movies?
Yes.
If you're free at 7 p.m. tomorrow,
shall we go to the movies?
Shall we?
Okay. The bar's closed tomorrow.
Why are you smiling?
It's nothing.
I'm just helping Bew with the dishes.
All right.
Bew, I'll take off now if you don't mind.
Okay.
-See you.
See who?
I mean, I'll come see her
with you some time.
Let's go home.
I know Jo gave you this gun
so you can finish your job.
Don't keep him waiting.
I know what I have to do.
I'll take care of it.
Be patient.
Should I wait
until you're done screwing this whore?
She's my wife, you prick.
Just get your job done.
You'll be in deep shit
if Jo has to get his hands dirty.
Got it?
Got.
How did my date turn into this?
NEW WORLD RAMA
Bew.
Hey.
-What's that for?
-Sorry.
We should go inside.
You keep hanging out with those thugs.
Pha.
Life is tough
when you're a gangster's wife.
Hey.
Do you know a girl named Naree?
Yes.
She sings that song which goes…
I prostrate myself before--
No.
That's Sunaree.
Didn't you mean her?
Orn.
Yes?
Can you do me a favor?
Can you do something for me first?
Of course. I can do anything for you.
Get your head out of the way.
I can't see the leading actor.
Can you do me a favor?
What favor?
Let me join your gang.
Come on.
Got, duck your head.
Take it easy. Calm down, people.
We're just changing the reels.
Can't you wait?
Not if you talk like that.
Then don't! Just get the hell
out of here, but there's no refund!
Stop it! What about you people?
-We'll wait.
-Okay then.
Bo, did you get a lotus for a monk?
Sadhu.
No! It's not for a monk.
It's for Orn.
You're the man!
Most girls get roses,
but he gives his girl a lotus flower.
Now it looks like a rose.
Bo, I already have someone I like.
Hey.
Who is it, Orn?
Tell me. I'll smack his ugly head.
I'd better go.
Orn.
-Let me go.
-Orn.
Don't touch me.
Bo.
I think you're trying too hard.
You make Orn uncomfortable.
That's why she left.
Girls like something unpredictable.
They like something like…
this.
Marry me, Bew.
Jesus Christ!
Shit.
What did you say?
Nothing. I didn't say anything.
You know, Bo likes petite girls.
She's exactly his type.
Do you really like her?
-Yes.
-All right. Let's talk business.
Our Hot Rod Gang is…
Hey! Are you even listening to me?
This is serious business.
Our main source of income
is from the protection racket money
from businesses in the area.
Mister, you need to pay
the protection racket.
One basil fried rice costs 25 baht.
You ordered three.
That's ten baht.
-Pay up then.
-You pay me, asshole.
Another source of our income
is from girls.
Are you the matron here?
Why not? My dad owns this place.
These girls grew up in this neighborhood.
This is where they can make a living.
Hey. You're the new member of our gang.
You can pick any chick you like.
There are too many of them.
I can't decide.
Are you a chicken?
Never mind. Come on, Bo.
Watch and learn.
I pick…
No.
I'm too shy, boss. I can't pick.
Hot Rod guys are the top dogs
who help protect these girls.
It just so happened that
I fell in love with the gorgeous matron
who runs this place.
What do you think? Aren't I a genius?
-Cheers!
-Cheers, guys.
I think our gang needs a proper salute.
How about this?
Hot Rod, arise.
Is that cool enough?
-It's cool.
-What?
-It's brilliant.
-Is it?
But it's too simple. Anyone can do it.
Let's do something like…
Get your ass up and do it together.
Come on.
Hot Rod,
arise!
-Assemble.
-What?
Lock our legs together.
-Lock your leg with mine.
-Okay. Wait.
-Shit.
-Damn it.
Just untangle our legs.
This place is closed! Get out!
Listen, Bo. When you talk to him,
keep your voice deep to sound formidable.
Boss.
I want your bar.
Come on. We pay interest every month.
What's wrong with your voice?
You'll get kicked.
Forget the interest.
I want the bar.
Are you nuts? This is a real business.
We're not playing Monopoly.
You can't just march in here
and take it, asshole.
Of course, I can.
You all probably recognize this.
If you want to see him alive,
sign the bar over to me.
Let's go.
Whose glasses are these?
Screw the glasses.
We can't let them insult us
on our own turf.
Boss, watch your foot.
What about his foot?
It's on my hand.
Sorry, Bo.
Why didn't they come for him?
If we had taken Prem's girlfriend,
they would've come running.
You dickhead.
Mark my words.
I do not hurt girls.
Can't we find a better bait
than this wimp?
This is so rad.
Where did you get it?
I went to the mall yesterday.
They were setting up
a sticker-photo booth,
so I gave it a try.
This is it. This is the future.
Just imagine.
Teenagers love taking pictures.
We'll put a bunch of these photo booths
where kids like to hang out.
Can you imagine that, Got?
We're going to be rich.
You're always so sure of your ideas.
It's why we were so poor when I was a kid.
Bo, you jackass.
What's that for?
What are you doing
putting these stickers on my bike?
You made a mess of it.
Get them off.
Yes, boss. I'll just put them on my bike.
We don't need that wimp
now that we have this guy.
I see. Do you all work for Nueng?
Shut your mouth, asshole.
Hey, Got. What's up?
Nueng and his men took Bae.
They tried to take me too, but I got away.
Do they want to test me?
No. You sit tight. I'll drive.
Move it. Come on.
Again, Lieutenant?
-Sir, watch out!
-Lieutenant!
Move it. Stop!
Come on, Lieutenant Tu. Hurry.
Wow! You were like superheroes.
Then how come you look so beat up?
I made up a few details.
But remember this, Bo.
Every dog has its day.
I'll get my revenge next time.
Come here.
-No.
-I haven't even touched you.
This will hurt.
I don't mind getting hurt from this.
Sweet Jesus.
You're acting weird, Got.
No, I'm not.
It's nothing.
Don't believe everything Prem says.
You know he likes to brag.
-Come on, Bew.
-She's right.
Even Bo was onto him.
I have to go.
Wait up, Bew.
Bew.
Have some hot pot with us.
That's right. We're about to eat.
I can't.
I have to close the books.
The girls will complain
if they get paid late.
I feel bad for them.
So, I guess it's just us.
Come on, Bae. Let's prepare the food.
Hey, Got. What really happened?
Do you want to know?
Freeze!
Turn around slowly.
Take your fingers off the trigger.
Don't try to shoot me
or you'll go straight to jail.
Here, Got.
Tell me the truth.
You guys didn't even know
that I was kidnapped, right?
Come on, Bae.
Take this fish tofu. It's my favorite.
Just forget about it.
-Right. Have some pork.
-Eat up.
Seriously, though.
Don't you have anything better to do
than being in this gang?
I mean, don't you have dreams
that you want to achieve?
Do you have one? Do you?
Tell me.
Of course, I do.
I want to be a godfather.
But my gang…
will only do good things.
I'll help people.
I'll take down the bad guys
and protect the good guys.
I'll be like an action movie hero.
You're delusional.
What about you, Bo?
Me?
I want to help my boss
make our gang the greatest.
We'll rule this country together.
That's my man.
-I'm your man, boss.
-Good.
And you? What's your dream?
I want to be a film director.
Come on. Nobody wants to see Thai movies.
Well, some people do.
At least there will be four of us.
Hey, Bae. Cast me in your film.
I'll take Bew to see it.
That's five people.
You bet, boss.
What about you, Got?
You're doing all the asking.
What's your dream?
My dream?
I want to be…
I want to be a race car driver.
A race car driver?
That's super cool!
Good for you, man.
A race car driver?
That's good. That's fantastic.
He'll be a race car driver.
But my dad doesn't approve.
He tries to stop me all the time.
What a prick.
What kind of father stands in the way
of his son's dream?
A father should let his son
live his own life.
That's just wrong.
Calm down, boss. He's still Got's dad.
Tell your dad to change his attitude.
Otherwise, I'll go kick his ass.
-You will?
-Definitely.
-Let me help.
-Good.
-We'll kick his ass.
-We'll change his mind.
-Shall we go now?
-Hey.
Let's forget about my dad.
Come on.
-Cheers!
-All right!
-Bottoms up!
-Yes!
-Cheers!
Drink up.
Why do you want to see me?
My TV is broken.
Can you fix it for me?
Can you fix it?
Of course.
Just the TV, right?
I see. It must be the CRT.
So, do you know where Prem is?
I don't know.
He said he'd be back late tonight.
Goodness. It's so muggy today.
Can you do me a favor?
Do you want ice cubes?
We don't need ice.
Just use this.
Can you massage me?
Here?
You have a unique name.
Well, it's Got
as in America's Got Talent.
Sort of.
My lousy dad gave me that name.
I've got a lousy dad too.
He left me and my mom.
So, I've been using my mom's family name.
Our fathers are assholes.
Right?
If I went by my father's last name,
it would sound awkward.
How?
My name would be Pranee Rogers.
Rogers?
Are you mixed-race?
Yes.
My dad's an American GI.
Do you know anyone named Nui?
I don't.
But a fortune teller once told me
that I should change my nickname to Nui
and change my first name
from Pranee to Naree.
Pranee to Naree?
That's it.
I don't think I can do this.
Take off your shirt then.
No, that's not what I mean.
It's okay, Got. I don't mind.
But I do. I do mind.
-I don't mind.
-Please do.
-It's okay.
-It's not okay. I can't.
-Please don't do this.
You passed the test.
What?
Congratulations.
You're a true friend.
This is a test to see
whether I can trust you.
And you did great.
You've proven that you can take over
our gang once I'm gone.
What?
-Gone?
-Yes.
Gone where?
And why me? Bo joined the gang before me.
Got.
You're a smart guy. Stop acting dumb.
Look at Bo. How can I trust
that loser with anything?
Our gang will fall apart.
Hey.
Bo.
How did you get in there, Bo?
I came to deliver your stuff.
I didn't see anyone,
so I just walked in here.
Then I heard you and Bew come in.
I didn't want to get chewed out,
so I went to hide in the cupboard.
At least we weren't hiding in the same…
Bo!
Do I mean anything to the gang at all?
I know I'm a dimwit.
I don't have cool ideas like you guys.
But at least this dimwit is ready
to die for our gang.
I may be just a tiny cog in a large wheel,
but Hot Rod Gang…
is my whole life.
One day, I'll prove to you
that you can always rely on me.
Hey. Come on.
You should go apologize to him.
No. Let's have a drink.
Come on, Got.
Wait.
I thought we were going to see Aunt Toy.
Can we go later? I'm not in the mood.
Your aunt isn't going anywhere, is she?
She's ill. That's why I want to visit her.
Should I wait for her to get better first?
Let's go some other day.
It's not just Bo.
None of us means anything to you.
Hey. I think you're blowing this
out of proportion.
All of you seem to love each other.
Mom…
I mean Bew.
Maybe you just don't see what he's like.
Why are you taking his side?
Do you think you know him well?
How long have you known him?
The women here are so fierce.
Prem might have been a bit too blunt,
but I think Bo will understand.
See? You're taking his side.
A guy like him is too selfish
and insensitive to care for anyone.
You don't even care
about your most loyal guy
who devotes himself
to his equally dim-witted boss.
Is that right? Really?
Really?
Really now?
Hey.
Guys, come on.
Just calm down.
What I'm trying to say
is Prem really values Bo.
Isn't that right?
You'll go look for him later, right?
There's a fine line
between valuing someone and using them.
I'm not sure how Bo feels about it.
Hey. Hang on. I just mean…
Please make up and move on.
Don't be mad at each other.
-Let's go drink.
-Hey!
We have to find him.
Do you mean Bo?
Yes.
Hey. Couldn't you find him?
He's not in that alley.
Let's try that way.
Hey.
Listen.
I must admit…
that I never knew before…
that the you I used to know
and the you that I know now
would be so different.
-Hang on. When did you know me?
-Let me finish.
You are so kind and caring.
You look out for other people.
I'm utterly perplexed
how you were then and now
are as different as chalk and cheese.
Are you finished?
I don't want to interrupt you.
I'm done.
Just to be clear,
that guy you're talking about is not me…
because I'm not a shifty guy.
I've always been like this.
All right.
Tell me honestly.
Let's say you got married
and you got thrown in prison.
Your wife killed herself
and left you a son. Would you--
Jeez! Why is my life so miserable?
-It's a hypothetical scenario, okay?
-Okay.
I just want to know
how you would raise your child.
If it were only me
and my son,
I would be devastated.
I would probably be
very protective of him.
I would never let him
put himself at any kind of risk.
Maybe that's not what he wants.
You said a father
should let his son live his own life.
Yes, but freedom always comes with risks.
That's how I will raise my son.
I'll force him to do as I say.
Nobody likes being forced.
I don't care!
If it means he'll have a better life
and it helps him survive in this world,
I'll be strict with him.
Here you are, you punk.
You're nothing but trouble.
Get the hell out of here! Go!
I might have to give him
a beating or punish him sometimes.
Got.
You've seen how pointless my life is.
I want a better life for my son.
I don't want him to end up like me.
He can get mad and curse me,
or hate me all he wants,
but his life must be better than mine.
I'll make sure of that.
Got.
What's with you? Get your hands off of me.
What's wrong with you?
Wait for me here.
I have to go talk to someone.
Who?
Never mind that.
Just wait here and don't go anywhere
until I come back.
Okay?
Okay. I'll wait here.
I just thought of one good thing
about my father.
When someone tells him to wait,
he will wait there
without ever asking why.
Since I have no idea how I got here,
it means that
I can disappear at any second.
I can't waste any more time.
Where's Bew?
She's taking a day off.
Please accept our alms offerings.
May you be blessed with a long life
filled with happiness and strength.
I don't know why,
but I feel like you and Prem
have something in common.
What is it?
I don't know. It's just a feeling.
Why didn't you tell anyone
you were staying
with Mrs. Toy at the hospital?
I was looking for you all night.
Is there something urgent?
Is it about yesterday?
Don't worry about it.
I didn't really mean what I said.
I know he's like that.
He's a straightforward guy
who always speaks his mind.
But when he loves someone,
he doesn't know how to express it.
He always does the opposite
of what he feels.
Clean your face up.
I can't read him.
I can't tell what he's really like.
Are you sure you can't?
What?
You spoke up for him yesterday.
Listen.
Let me ask you something.
How come you never talk about your family?
To be honest,
I hardly ever call him my dad.
I don't want to talk about him.
What about your mother?
What is she like?
My mother?
I don't remember what she was like.
She died when I was little.
My dad was sentenced to six years in jail
when she was pregnant.
She had depression
after giving birth to me.
She jumped off the building to her death.
That's a shame.
If she had a chance to see you now,
she would be so proud of you
and she wouldn't have done such a thing.
Well…
I should go.
I kept Prem waiting all night.
Are you leaving already?
I'm so happy I got to meet you.
If she had a chance to see you now,
she would be so proud of you.
She wouldn't have done such a thing.
Damn you, Got.
Where were you?
I waited for you all night.
I'm sorry.
Can you do me a favor, sir?
You don't mess around, do you?
You've got some nerve.
I'm out of cigarettes.
Here.
Nice cigs.
Before you ask me for a favor,
do me one favor first.
Stop being so formal with me.
Stop calling me "sir" already.
Be real, man.
-I'm begging you.
-No. Don't do that.
If that's what you want,
I'll do as you ask, man.
Yes! That's much better.
That's what I'm talking about.
What favor do you want from me?
-Number one.
-Okay.
Don't get into any fights
in the next six months no matter what.
Can you do that?
Sure. That's easy.
I'm not one to start a fight anyway.
Number two.
Have your wedding as soon as possible
and let me be your wedding planner.
Okeydoke.
I'm fine with that.
Why do you want to plan my wedding anyway?
There's one more thing.
Are you not done?
If you have a kid,
don't ever hit or kick him.
Are you nuts?
I'll be a good father to my kid.
Why would I lay my hands on him?
I will never treat my kid
like a punching bag
if he's a good kid.
I knew it.
Is someone grilling chicken?
I don't think so. Look at the smoke.
-Shit! My house's on fire!
-What?
Shit!
Wait up.
My house!
Let's get out of here.
You go ahead. I have to go get something.
No way! I'll go with you.
I'll be right back!
Let's just go.
-Let me go!
-We have to go.
Hey!
Let us through, please.
Hey. What's that?
-You're still here?
-I'm waiting for you.
Let's get out of here!
Let us through.
Damn it. I told you not to wait for me.
Did you risk your life for this?
It's my dad's photo. It's important.
Damn. I've really misjudged you.
I almost didn't get to have my wedding.
These are my life savings.
Boss!
-Boss.
-Bo.
Are you hurt?
I was worried sick about you.
I'm fine. Don't worry.
I think someone is trying to hurt us.
We'd better stick together at all times.
What if we need to use the bathroom?
Should we stick together then?
Look at this.
This is one chopstick.
It can be broken easily.
But if we put three chopsticks together,
they won't be so…
That didn't work.
Here, Bo. Try and break these.
When you put a bunch
of them together, they won't…
They won't…
Here.
They won't break.
What are you trying to say, Got?
Here's my point.
If we stick together, they can't…
Hey.
Don't look so confused. You don't know me.
But you might know this guy.
You probably don't know
that this karaoke bar is situated
in a very good location
filled with positive energy.
I want it.
Why are you telling me?
That's my girlfriend's bar.
You dimwit!
You know, I actually don't like
doing illegal businesses myself.
I want you to do it.
Come work for me.
Hot Rod Gang has dignity.
We don't work for criminals!
You'll have an easy job that pays well.
You won't have to borrow money
from anyone again.
Your girl can keep her job.
She's good at it, isn't she?
Come on, you asshole! Bring it!
I gave you a generous offer.
Asshole!
Dad.
Prem.
-Got.
Got. Damn it! My leg hurts.
Aunt Toy!
How are you feeling?
Do you want to see a doctor?
No. I'll be fine.
You're always like this.
Did you two get into a dogfight somewhere?
We would've been fine
if it was just one dog
and not a pack of mongrels.
Don't be so cocky.
You keep causing trouble after trouble.
Aunt Toy, are you cooking something
on the stove?
Right. I forgot.
How did you get into a fight?
Who did this to you?
It was nothing.
It was just a little row.
Can you let it go then?
No. There are scores to settle.
If something happens to you,
what will I do?
How can I let them go after--
I'm pregnant.
Bew.
Are you pregnant?
Yes.
I'm so happy, Bew.
Prem.
Yes?
Hey! What the hell? Back off.
I'm having a moment with my wife.
I want to be part of this.
I'm happy for you two.
Are you really pregnant?
Yes.
Can you promise
not to get into any more fights?
Of course. We promise we'll stop fighting.
I promise. There will be no more fights.
He can't fight anyone
with that crippled leg.
I can still kick you with my good leg.
Calm down. I'll give you a massage.
Hey! Watch it, Got!
Hey. What are you doing?
I'm giving you a foot massage.
Pregnancy will make your feet swollen.
What the hell are you doing, Got?
Got, stay away from my wife.
-It's just a massage.
-Just stop.
Come on, Bew.
-Get up slowly. Be careful.
-Let me help.
Back off.
If I hadn't seen it with my own eyes,
I wouldn't have believed that my dad
and this crazy guy are the same person.
At least I know now
where I got the crazy streak from.
I wonder if it's a boy or a girl.
A boy, of course.
You'll have a handsome boy.
Will we have a healthy baby?
Don't you worry.
He'll be as tough as a nail.
Damn it! Can you shut up
and let me talk to my wife?
I'm just happy.
Our baby will be…
Boss.
Bae ran away again. He only left a note.
What did he say?
"Dear Prem, Bae…"
Jeez! Give it to me.
You read it.
Do you call that reading?
Let me read it. Can't you read?
"Dear Prem."
That's me.
"Bot."
-It's Got.
-Right. Got.
"I can't distance farewell."
I know. He wants to say goodbye.
Damn.
-Is that right?
-Right. Damn.
Why did he write to me just to say that?
Please stop. You're not even close.
You're a bunch of idiots.
I'll read it for you.
"Dear Prem, Bo, and Got."
"If you're reading this letter,
it means I've already left."
"The distance between reality and dreams
has driven me to embark on a journey."
"Thank you for everything."
"All along,
I know that I'm different from you guys."
Shit.
"I really don't belong in the gang."
"I don't want to be a burden to anyone."
You guys keep loitering around
like a bunch of losers.
Get up and help me clean up.
Are you drinking beer?
-It's chrysanthemum juice.
-Right.
-Like hell it is.
-Give me five.
-Hey!
-That's your high five.
"No one knows what the future holds,
but I don't want to become
an old man who runs an eyewear store."
"Goodbye, my friends."
"Until we meet again."
"No one can escape their future."
"But we can choose
the kind of future we want."
"With love, Bae."
Why did you close your eyes?
We have to take another one.
-One, two--
-Hold on.
Hey! You can just tell me.
Move closer together.
Okay. We're good.
-One, two--
-Just a second.
Lift the camera higher. No. Go lower.
It doesn't look right.
-The angle is--
-Just stop it.
All right then.
What are you doing?
You do it. Just take
the picture the way you want it.
Do it yourself since you're so fussy.
Are you ready?
One, two…
Hey, Got. Have you seen Bo?
He disappeared after the morning ceremony.
He'll come back.
It's a good thing
the dress code isn't green.
Why is that?
Today is Saturday.
It's unlucky to wear green today.
Those who wear green will have bad luck.
Right.
This is for the Hot Rod Gang.
Is that everyone?
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The MC hasn't arrived
due to heavy traffic.
As the wedding planner,
I have to apologize for that.
While we're waiting,
I'll dish some dirt on the bride and groom
in the meantime.
First of all, I have to say
that the bride looks
absolutely stunning tonight.
I don't know what Prem ever did
to deserve this beauty?
Do you agree?
Look at this.
I have a confession to make.
I used to hate this guy with a passion.
Before I knew it,
he became my best buddy.
I never knew who I was
or where I came from,
and how I got here.
Until I met these two.
If you know Prem, you'll know that
he doesn't deserve Bew at all.
-Watch your mouth, Got.
-But…
But let me tell you that you're wrong
because there's no one in this whole world
whom I'd rather see by Bew's side
except for this wacko.
The hand of destiny
It brings us together
We were once far apart
But destiny played a trick on us
And it led me to you
Maybe we are soulmates
Fated to be together
Since the moment I met you
My world became brighter
You and I are meant to be
If we weren't destined to be together
Our love wouldn't have survived it all
We wouldn't get our happy ending
Sorrow would've found us
We would've drifted apart
Never to see each other again
We are destined to be together
To cherish and love each other
Our love is written in the stars
You and I are meant to be
I now believe in love
For I am madly in love with you
Lost in my reverie now and forever
What do you want?
I want your leg
as a wedding present for my boss.
Or you can bow at his feet
and I'll spare your life.
I'll give you a chance to leave.
I have work to do.
All right then.
You can say goodbye to your leg.
I gave you a chance to run
and you refused.
The police are here!
-Good evening.
-Hello.
What's going on?
One day, I'll prove to you
that you can always rely on me.
I want to help my boss
make our gang the greatest.
We'll rule this country together.
Damn it!
Fuck!
Hey. Where are you going?
-Leave me alone.
-Stay. Don't go.
-Let me go.
-You're not going anywhere.
-Out of my way!
-Stay here.
Don't go. Don't you remember
your promise to Bew?
You promised her you would stop fighting.
Damn it!
That bastard Jo.
Where are you going?
Are you okay?
No problemo.
Dad!
Dad.
Dad! Wake up, Dad!
Dad!
Wake up!
Stop calling me Dad.
Don't squeeze me so hard. It hurts.
Got.
Bo.
I've avenged your death.
Although I couldn't change anything,
but to hell with it.
Are you okay?
Got, I just thought of something.
I don't care if my child
will be a boy or a girl.
I'll name it Got.
What do you think?
I've always suspected that my name
must have had a story behind it,
but I never expected the story
to be so silly.
If you name your baby after me,
you can't hit him, all right?
I know. I already told you I won't.
You have to give him
a generous allowance as well.
All right.
-And you have to--
-Why are you so obsessed with my kid?
You're too much.
Hey.
Prem!
You promised
there would be no more fights.
Bew.
I'm sorry.
Got.
If something happens to me,
take care of Bew for me.
Bew.
There's a box under the bed at home.
You can sell everything in that box.
Use the money to raise our kid
and keep our family going.
This is how we'll communicate
in the future.
This will be worth more than gold one day.
The finish line in front of you
may be just the beginning of a new day.
As long as you're still breathing,
you can always start over.
You're 16 weeks pregnant
and the baby's very healthy.
It will start kicking more often.
Don't be alarmed if your baby starts
to kick you harder.
Sometimes, you only realize
who means the most to you…
when it's already too late.
Dad.
How are you doing, son?
Don't you think…
that gesture is a bit too simple?
Everything will be all right.
Subtitle translation by: Kong Rithdee