Try Oishi Honey Lemon.
Made with Hyakka Mitsu honey.
Itt, I'm going to...
I'm sorry.
The number you have reached
is not in service at this time.
Sorry. It is not possible to reach...
You left already?
You disappeared.
(BAIBA: You left already?
BAIBA: You disappeared.)
(Pahun Jiyacharoen, Marc)
(Pawin Kulkarunyawich, Pawin)
(Pattadon Janngeon, Fiat)
(Napat Patcharachavalit, Un)
(Chayakorn Jutamat, JJ)
(Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee, June)
(Neen Suwanamas, Neen)
(Amarin Nitibhon, Am)
(Ratchanok Sangchuto, Nok)
(Nicole Theriault, Nicole)
(Phollawat Manuprasert, Tom)
(Intira Jaroenpura, Sine)
(Chonwari Chutiwatkhotrachai, Aom-am)
(Longlao School)
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
(My Gear and Your Gown)
Here. It's for you.
Pure, did you talk to Itt?
I can't find him.
Why don't you answer him?
Do I have to?
Itt...
...you don't have to answer him.
But you have to answer to yourself.
What are you going to do next?
Is it in the cabinet?
Are you sure
that you lost your earring here?
I'm sure.
Your family is rich.
You could even buy an earring factory.
Why are you wasting your time
searching for one earring?
Waan...
...have you ever had something
that was very important to you?
An irreplaceable item?
That's what...
...that earring is to me.
If it was that important to you,
you shouldn't have lost it
in the first place.
I didn't choose to do that.
Oh, there you are.
I heard that you disappeared last night.
Did you get a girlfriend
and not tell anyone?
Where were you?
Move our things out of this room.
Sure.
Where are you moving to?
I'm moving out of this clubroom.
Why are you moving out?
Didn't you agree to study with me
so that you could get this room?
Isn't this room important to you?
You've got some nerve to ask me that.
I think you two
should sort this out outside.
Waan and I will take care of things here.
Come with me.
What?
I said come!
Did you find it?
This earring is very important
to you, isn't it?
All right.
I'll return it to you
if you move out of the clubroom.
What are you talking about?
I'm making you an offer.
Just like how Teacher Wilailak
laid down her condition to you.
You knew?
This world doesn't want me
to be stupid for long.
I heard your conversation with her.
I told you. A top student like you...
...would be able to help someone
at the bottom of the class, like Ittikorn.
You can rest assured
that you didn't do this for free.
The room will belong to the Bishop Club
as per the agreement.
Okay.
Do you have anything to say for yourself?
What you heard is true.
You're the worst.
No, don't do it.
Give me my earring back.
Please give me my earring back.
I will do whatever you want.
Whatever I want?
Then give me the clubroom.
Itt...
...you know that I can't do that for you.
...if it's something else, I can do it.
Just tell me what you want.
I'll do anything for you. I promise.
Do you expect me to believe you?
Itt....
...I don't want things to be this way.
You're my friend.
You should know this.
Friend?
Is that what friends are supposed to do?
Do friends lie to each other?
How dare you call yourself my friend?
You're not my friend.
I don't even know you.
Okay.
If that's what you think,
then I can't stop you.
What do I have to do
to get my earring back?
Tell me.
The more you want it back...
...the less I want to give it to you.
Now that you've taken my clubroom...
...I'm going to take your stuff.
No, don't!
Come on.
Prepare to say goodbye to your earring.
You will never see it again.
(Together We Can -Exam preparation
campaign for university admission)
(Together We Can)
Thanks.
And...
...sorry for bumping into you.
I wasn't paying attention.
It's fine.
I wasn't paying attention either.
Do you know which way Room 950 is?
I can't seem to find it.
Nine-five-zero?
Math tutor, right?
Yes.
Even if you go to Room 950,
you won't get to study math.
Why not? Did I come on the wrong day?
No.
Math is in Room 905.
Nine-zero-five.
Well, that's embarrassing.
What's so funny?
You shouldn't get something
like that wrong.
What if you missed the course
and couldn't pass the exam?
Would you still be laughing?
-Why are you so serious?
-You should be serious.
The person tutoring you
puts their effort into it.
They want their students to do well.
If their students
don't recognize their effort,
then what's the point?
I get it. You don't have to get upset.
Forget it.
You should hurry.
Their values are very similar.
Secondly, they have very high boiling
and melting points.
Third, atom sizes get smaller
as we progress,
but they are very similar.
Have you talked to him yet?
What kind of person is like that?
He's so sensitive.
Forget it.
I've let it go.
Preach it, brother.
But can you do what you say?
Whatever.
Let's talk about the characteristics
of the transition element.
There are as follows.
First,
they have variable oxidation numbers,
except for group 3B and group 2B.
Most of the compounds are colored,
-except for group 13.
-Hey.
-Fourth.
-Take notes for me.
-Complex compounds are easily formed.
-I'm going to take a nap.
Hey, what are you doing?
So have you really let it go?
Who threw this?
It's my business.
I think that he's letting things go too.
It's not about you, though.
I mean, the tutoring session.
Look, he's fast asleep.
Do you want to continue the session
at my house?
Which subject?
The subject of...
...flexibility.
You're an idiot.
You can't go?
Not today.
My dad's picking me up.
How about tomorrow?
Sure. And the day after tomorrow too.
I'll walk you to the pick-up spot.
Let's go.
Hey, you.
Give these notes to Itt.
Don't tell him that they're from me.
Otherwise, he'll throw them away.
He's been ignoring you...
...but you're still nice to him.
I promised him
that I'd help him get into the university.
I have to keep my promise.
Why?
If he can't get in,
will Teacher Walailak
take your club room back?
You're a real pain.
I was just kidding.
Come on.
I'll give these to him.
Don't forget what I told you.
I won't.
He'll hit me if I tell him
that they're from you.
You can count on me.
I'll make sure he gets them.
I'm taking off now.
-See you.
Well, I don't quite understand.
Will you do another session with me?
About what?
About flexibility.
You...
You dropped this.
Hang on, it's not her.
Her? Who?
The one he asked about doing a
flexibility tutoring session at his house.
But she said that she wasn't available.
I'm not available today either.
-Wait.
-Leave me alone.
Go get flexible by yourself.
What?
Don't be such a loudmouth,
unless you want to get hurt.
Miss, please wait for me.
Miss.
(Chemistry notes)
Itt...
...take these chemistry notes.
Who gave them to you?
A girl from another school.
I flirted with her,
so she gave them to me.
Don't forget to read them.
Okay. Thanks.
-Let's go.
(After reading,
pay respect to Teacher Pai)
Why are you here?
Are these your notes?
Why?
I remember your handwriting.
A lot of people
have the same handwriting.
If they're not yours,
-then I'll throw them away.
-Wait.
They're mine.
Pai, let me ask you this.
What the heck is wrong with you?
You're not going to let this go, are you?
That's why you gave me these notes.
You want me to realize
that you're smart, don't you?
Yes, you're smart.
Are you happy now?
That's not my intention.
-I just want...
-Quit acting like you're a good person.
And quit acting like you're my friend...
...because you're not.
Our friendship...
...is completely fake.
Leave me alone.
Come on, run!
Here.
Come here.
Be careful.
-I'll get you back.
-You will?
Stop.
(Longlao School Grade 12 Room 1
Counselor: Mr. Panuwat Im-aimsuk)
(L.B.C 13)
Equilibrium i...
Stop.
(Bishop Club/Knight Club 1061
Counselor: Ms. Wilailak Jaijong)
(Announcements)
Let's see.
Hey, check this board.
And I'll check the one over there, okay?
Okay.
Which university?
-Have you seen your name?
-Not yet.
What about you?
No, I see other names.
Really?
Where's my name?
(No. 16 Mr. Ittikorn Noppanaradon)
(Faculty of Engineering
Chiang Mai University)
Itt, you got into the Faculty
of Engineering at Chiang Mai University.
-I know already.
-Come here.
Pai...
-You got into the Faculty of Medicine.
-Yes.
Your university is close to my house.
Way to go, dude.
You're the best.
Don't you want to congratulate yourself?
I would have gotten in anyway.
What about you?
Prepare to call me Doctor Witsanu.
It's no surprise
that both of us were accepted.
But it's your former friend
who's the incredible one.
Is everyone ready?
-Ready!
-Go!
Dumb Itt
got into the Faculty of Engineering!
Woo hoo!
Awesome.
Now that I've been accepted,
you guys can't call me dumb anymore.
All right!
Don't you want to congratulate him?
No, I don't want to ruin his happy moment.
My mission's already been completed.
What a gentleman.
Are you sure you want to leave
without saying goodbye?
Dude, the distance between Bangkok
and Chiang Mai is 700 kilometers.
So what?
Even when we're only a meter apart,
he still doesn't want to talk to me.
The problem isn't the distance.
It's him.
He doesn't want me in his life.
That all.
Let's go.
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
Mr. 950 wants to give this to you.
950?
Who is he?
Hello.
Do you remember me?
(My Gear and Your Gown)