Try Oishi Honey Lemon.
Made with Hyakka Mitsu honey.
Pure!
Why are you like this?
Like what?
You walk away from everyone.
Since I was born,
I've never walked away from anyone.
Because you're a good person?
No.
Because I've got nobody to walk away from.
Come on.
Let's be serious.
Can you help me flirt with a girl?
Please teach me how.
I want to feel the joy of love.
All right. You're so naive.
I'll pass on my knowledge to you.
Do you have someone in mind
that you want to flirt with?
I want to flirt with...
(Pahun Jiyacharoen, Marc)
(Pawin Kulkarunyawich, Pawin)
(Pattadon Janngeon, Fiat)
(Napat Patcharachavalit, Un)
(Chayakorn Jutamat, JJ)
(Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee, June)
(Neen Suwanamas, Neen)
(Amarin Nitibhon, Am)
(Ratchanok Sangchuto, Nok)
(Nicole Theriault, Nicole)
(Phollawat Manuprasert, Tom)
(Intira Jaroenpura, Sine)
(Chonwari Chutiwatkhotrachai, Aom-am)
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
(My Gear and Your Gown)
There.
Stir it.
-What are you doing?
-Come on.
It has to be green.
-How are you?
-Shoot!
It's June!
June is super cute.
She is my first love, you know.
I've watched her get on the bus
since she was in the 8th grade.
Now she is in 10th grade,
and I can't say a word to her.
Can you teach me how to flirt with her?
I want her to be my girlfriend.
Now pay attention.
There are three steps to flirting.
One.
Make eye contact.
Look at her.
This will send her a signal
that you're interested in her.
Make eye contact with her.
But don't ogle over her.
When she realizes you're looking at her...
...and looks back at you, smiling...
...go to the next step.
Hey.
I think there is a pervert in this place.
Right.
What on earth did you teach me?
It didn't work.
Do you really want to teach me?
All right, all right.
I will show you how it's done.
Don't blink.
Step one.
Make eye contact.
How's that?
Step two.
Introduce yourself.
Watch closely.
Hi. My name is Pure.
This is my first time coming here.
Do you have any suggestions?
It looks like you come here often.
So what are your names?
I'm June.
I'm Pam.
Pam.
The last step is to compliment her.
Compliments rule the world.
That's a pretty name.
Is that all?
Yes.
Wait and see.
She got up. She's coming this way.
Well, Pam wants your contact details,
but she is too shy to ask you.
But don't give her your contact.
Oh...
Why not?
Well...
...it's because I want it too.
Why would I want her to have it?
Let's exchange contacts.
I'm sorry. I'm not interested in you.
Okay...
You could've gone for her.
She seems to like you.
No.
Although I like to fool around...
...I won't take my friend's girl.
Even though you don't want her,
she still doesn't want me.
It's just one girl. Why do you care?
Let's go, man. Come with me.
I have 10 girls that you can choose from.
-Ten more?
-Yes.
-Are you sure you have 10?
-Don't worry. Yes.
I'll give you 20.
-Twenty?
-Yes.
You're always chatting with them.
Don't your fingers get tired?
Not really.
I'm used to it, I guess.
You're used to it...
By the way...
...don't you think
about getting a new lover?
Someone you're committed to.
Someone you would never cheat on.
I used to have one.
You used to have one...
Who was it?
It was my first love.
First love...
Wait, why did you break up?
Well, I wanted him,
but he didn't want me.
After that, I stopped caring about love.
Looks like you were so disappointed
by love...
...that you don't believe in it anymore.
If your girlfriend let you get beat up...
...would you still believe in love?
Get out of my sight!
Anyway, what did you do after that?
-I did nothing.
-Nothing?
It made me realize that love...
...is just a fantasy.
Only sex is real.
Only sex...
Tonight, buddy.
I will take you to see the real thing.
The real thing...
-Are you ready?
-I'm ready.
-Let's go.
(Inappropriate behavior. Do not imitate.)
How's it going, guys?
Hey.
How are you?
We've got all night.
-This is awesome.
-Do you like it?
-It's sick.
-I told you.
This private party is lit.
This is sick.
The real thing is right here.
Come on.
Waan, let's drink.
-Are you sure?
-Yes. Come on.
To our friendship.
Bottoms up.
-How's that?
-Whoa!
It's strong.
Let's do another shot.
-Another?
-Yes.
Are you all right?
I should ask you that.
Hey.
Did I make you think about your ex?
Dude, did you know...
...that 99 percent
of first love relationships...
...eventually end in heartbreak?
Don't drown yourself in disappointment.
Move on.
Yes.
You're right.
Take my mom as an example.
She had so many relationships...
...but they all failed.
Love doesn't exist.
Hey.
Are you stressed about your ex...
...or your mom?
Both.
Heck!
You're depraved.
You've infected my girlfriend with HIV.
I have AIDS because of you!
(Patient Room 1206,
Utumpon Noppanaradon)
How was your night?
It was a good night. I slept very well.
You don't have a fever,
and your blood pressure is normal.
Thank you.
-Last night...
-I'll tell him myself.
Okay.
What happened last night?
What could it be?
I just had a sweet dream.
What was it about?
That you got into university...
...had a good job,
and a good life ahead of you.
You have to make my dream come true, okay?
I want you to be happy every day.
Do you know that?
Of course I know.
I want to study,
go to a university,
and have a good job.
I'll do it for you.
There he is.
The person who can help you
get into university is here.
-Hello.
You're not wearing your earring anymore?
No.
It hurts.
Let's call it a day. I've got to go.
Why?
The last exercise that I gave you...
...has already pushed you
to the average level.
If you can maintain it,
your GPA should get higher.
You're not normally like this.
What's wrong with you today?
I'm fine.
Where are you?
(Where are you?)
My mom wants me to treat you to noodles
as a thank you.
(My mom wants me to treat you
to noodles as a thank you.)
See you at the usual place.
(See you at the usual place.)
You already read the text.
Why won't you reply?
Are you just going to let me eat alone?
I didn't let you eat alone the other day.
I really can't go.
(Five Fellas Wonton Noodles )
-Itt, have you been waiting for long?
-A little bit.
-Have you already ordered?
-Not yet.
What do you want to have?
What's their signature dish?
-Let me order for you.
-Okay.
Mister, can we have two bowls
of noodles with meatballs?
Okay.
-He's a good cook.
-Really?
-See?
-Wow.
-It's so fast.
-Sure is.
Can you pass the chopsticks?
Chopsticks.
How did you know
that I don't eat vegetables?
Because I don't eat them either.
Chopsticks, please.
-All right.
-Here's your spoon.
Let's see if it's as delicious
as you say it is.
Go ahead.
So?
Here. The meatballs are dope.
Let's go.
I don't want to go home yet.
It's already late.
-Okay.
-Get in.
-Bye.
-Get home safely.
-See you.
Hello.
(Emergency Room)
I'm sorry for your loss.
Son.
You just woke up. Don't move too fast.
What happened to me?
You were hit by a car,
but all your injuries are minor.
You must have been in shock.
You were unconscious all day.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You had a CT scan,
and the results are normal.
You have to be more careful, okay?
Take good care of yourself.
You have your entrance exam
for university this year.
You've been preparing yourself
for a long time to become a doctor.
I don't want there to be any mistakes.
Okay.
Here.
Your phone.
You weren't using it
while crossing the street, were you?
You've never made us worry before.
I'm sorry.
Get some rest.
Does it still hurt?
Yes.
-Rest.
-Okay.
I'll be back.
(Itt, 11 Missed calls)
-Nurse.
-Pai.
(Patient Room 1206,
Satit Nareerak)
Nurse?
Where's my friend's mother?
She passed away last night.
And...
...what about my friend, Itt?
Who did he come here with?
He took care of everything by himself.
He seems very strong.
-Nurse?
-Yes?
My mom isn't eating much.
Is she getting worse?
Well...
If you force her too much,
she will feel uncomfortable.
Mr. Know-It-All.
Are you a doctor?
I will be.
Okay, you win.
But I'm worried about her.
There's nothing else you can do.
You're right.
I don't think
that there's anything else I can do.
I'm aware that she won't get better.
You don't think
that there's anything else you can do...
...because you've already done your best.
Pai...
...I'm scared.
Let yourself feel it.
I'll be here by your side.
(Directed by
Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
Hey, has anyone seen Pure?
-What about Itt?
-He's dropping out of school.
Can you take me to see Itt?
No, I don't want to go there again.
It gives me goosebumps just mentioning it.
Itt!
No!
Don't you feel disgusted?
Why should I?
You're not infecting me with HIV.
Is this what you want to do?
What do you want from me?
Come to your tutoring session tomorrow.
I'll wait for you at home.
(My Gear and Your Gown)