Try Oishi Honey Lemon.
Made with Hyakka Mitsu honey.
(Welcome New Students)
I'm Beau, a third-year student.
I'll be your supervisor.
I'd love to be supervised by her.
No talking.
Everyone here is under the SOTUS system.
The name SOTUS is an English acronym.
Does anyone know
what the first letter stands for?
The guy talking earlier.
What does the first S stand for?
S...
stands for seniority.
It means to respect your seniors.
That's correct.
Now, the other guy.
What does the letter O stand for?
Um...
O stands for...
O...
Oh my god, I don't know.
Did you come here
without knowing what SOTUS was?
Everyone,
get on your knees.
Come on.
I'm sorry, guys.
Hold on.
I'm just kidding.
We don't welcome new faces
with that outdated ritual anymore.
You can't keep ordering people
to get on their knees, right?
Our faculty welcomes new students
by urging them to do...
community service.
But first, come and get your name tag.
Be right back.
I'm going to see my future wife.
My name is Waan.
-Waan.
-Yes.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Sure. What's your name?
-Tar.
-Alright.
-Thank you.
-What's your name?
(Pahun Jiyacharoen, Marc)
(Pawin Kulkarunyawich, Pawin)
(Pattadon Janngeon, Fiat)
(Napat Patcharachavalit, Un)
(Chayakorn Jutamat, JJ)
(Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee, June)
(Neen Suwanamas, Neen)
(Amarin Nitibhon, Am)
(Ratchanok Sangchuto, Nok)
(Nicole Theriault, Nicole)
(Phollawat Manuprasert, Tom)
(Intira Jaroenpura, Sine)
(Chonwari Chutiwatkhotrachai, Aom-am)
(Longlao School)
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
=My Gear and Your Gown=
Paint upwards.
Student number 950 sent you a message.
Nine-five-zero?
Do you know who that is?
I don't know. Someone else gave it to me.
Nine-five-zero?
Who could it be?
Hey.
Do you remember me?
The guy who got the room number wrong...
when we were studying
for admission exams.
You said I was insincere too.
Did I do that?
I don't remember.
I remember everything.
Well...
Don't you...
wear glasses anymore?
Are you wearing contact lenses?
No.
I got LASIK.
You were cute when you wore glasses.
But without them,
you're even cuter.
I'm Folk. I'm studying dentistry.
Are you Pai?
You have a cute name.
Not really.
It's ordinary.
When you like someone,
everything about them will be cute to you.
Oh!
You're a player, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
Well.
But the other day...
I saw you go to a hotel with someone.
-Why are you saying that?
-Well...
Pai, your friend gets riled easily.
What?
Do you know each other?
We don't just know each other.
The two of us...
are very close.
Are you jealous?
Come on, man.
I'm just teasing you.
Pai and I are friends.
There's still lhope.
That's a relief.
(Pai)
Folk.
Hurry. The seniors are calling us over.
-I'll go now.
-Alright.
Pai, well...
I have to go now.
See you later.
Wow.
He was very forward.
Did he make your heart stir?
That's nonsense.
Man.
Actually...
I think he's cute.
Like a golden retriever,
he looks docile and easy.
But I'm not a dog person.
By the way,
how are you?
I'm doing well.
What about...
Itt is also doing well,
in case you wanted to know.
He got into the faculty of his dreams.
Everything is good.
Well.
Chiang Mai is nice.
It suits him.
Right.
But now...
you should go.
The seniors are calling us.
Let's go.
Follow that puppy.
He really is like a puppy.
♪Chicken skewers, chicken skewers...♪
(Welcome New Students)
♪The chickens will be pierced♪
♪Pierce its left cheek♪
♪Pierce its right cheek♪
♪Very hot, very hot, very hot♪
♪Chicken skewers, chicken skewers♪
♪The chickens will be pierced♪
♪Pierce its left cheek♪
♪Pierce its right cheek♪
♪Very hot, very hot, very hot♪
Alright. Now that us seniors are tired.
I'd like each faculty...
to send one student to come up here
and entertain everyone.
Whoo!
Pai from the Faculty of Medicine.
Alright. Pai from the Faculty of Medicine.
I didn't that know you're an entertainer.
Come on. Let's dance.
Oh, well.
I... I don't...
You don't play around, do you?
Alright. I'll let you choose your song.
Come on. Let's dance.
Guys, let's give him a hand.
How did Itt get here?
Didn't he go to Chiang Mai?
Pai, what song would you like?
Chiang Mai is nice.
But he didn't choose it.
The Hippo Song.
Alright. Guys, let's sing
the Hippo Song for Pai.
Come on.
♪Hip, hip, hip, hippo♪
♪Oh, look at its size♪
♪Plodding from side to side♪
♪La la la la la la♪
♪Hip, hip, hip, hippo♪
♪Oh, look at its size♪
♪Plodding from side to side♪
♪La la la la la la♪
Who said that he's an entertainer?
He is a party pooper.
(Folk)
(Pai)
I'll help entertain everyone.
Whoa!
Come on.
(Folk and Pai)
(Welcome New Students)
(Itt)
Itt!
Why did you call out my name?
I just felt like it.
Do you have a problem with that?
I know that you don't like me.
But can you just leave me alone?
Who are you to boss me around?
What I do is my business.
Waan, can I talk to you?
Sure. I'm single.
I didn't ask you that.
I just wanted to let you know.
Anyway, what do you want
to talk to me about?
I have nothing to say to you.
I just wanted to talk to Pai.
Do you know where he is?
Oh...
I want you to be the faculty's King.
-Me?
-Can you do that?
I don't think...
that I fit the role.
You should find someone else.
Hey. Look over there.
Oh.
That's Phai, Queen of Engineering.
Itt is King of Engineering.
You see, other faculties
have their kings and queens, unlike ours.
Pai.
Come on. Do it for me.
No, it's better not to.
Extracurricular activities aren't for me.
Even if I entered the Star Contest,
I wouldn't win anyway.
It would be a waste of your time.
Excuse me. I'm going to get my lunch.
(King of Wonton Noodles)
Do you like wonton noodle soup?
Yes.
If I didn't,
I wouldn't be waiting in line.
Right.
If you didn't like it,
you wouldn't be standing here.
What would you like?
-I'd like a bowl of dry wonton noodles.
-Sure.
-Actually, two.
-Okay.
Oh.
Well...
Beau's friends
couldn't find a place to sit.
So I moved over here.
You can sit here too, right?
Sure.
I don't have a problem with anyone.
I made a mess.
Yummy.
Pai.
Can I sit here?
Yes.
You don't need to ask me next time.
It's a public table.
Feel free to sit.
Pai,
he's the one...
who danced to the Hippo Song
with you, isn't he?
Since when have you known each other?
You didn't tell me.
Just today.
I'd love to get to know him more.
Itt.
Itt,
don't eat that.
It's high in carbs.
You'll get bloated before the contest.
Stop eating that.
I'll get some salad for you.
Good.
Wow.
How nice is that.
She takes care of you.
You're legit, dude.
Pai,
take him as an example.
If you participate in the contest,
you'll be taken care of
by our faculty's Queen.
Wouldn't that be good?
Don't try to talk me into it.
He knows what I'm up to.
I'm one of the contestants.
It seems fun.
Why don't you give it a go?
See? Listen to him.
Even he said that it seems fun.
Please do this for me...
so that I can have an excuse
to talk to Beau.
You forced me to be the club president
in grade 12.
Now you're forcing me
to be the faculty's King?
I won't fall for that again.
No way.
You know everything.
He was the club president because of you?
Yes.
It's Folk.
(It's Folk.)
How did you get my Line ID?
It's not hard to get.
Lots of my friends
are studying medicine.
Watch your step.
I have something to talk to you about.
Hop on.
What?
Is your butt made of gold?
Can't you sit on a bike?
Hop on.
Folk,
have you seen Cher,
your senior?
Do you like her?
I can help you.
Then help and tell me...
where she is.
Let's trade.
I'll help you with her,
and you help me with Pai.
You want me to pimp him out?
I don't think so.
If you can't get him yourself,
then you lose your chance.
Then find Cher yourself.
Even if you find her,
you'll never get your chance...
because she's a lesbian.
Don't know how to use the brakes?
We're here.
Get off.
Say it.
Have you forgotten your promise?
You know that...
I can't do that for you.
If it's something else,
I can do it.
Just tell me what you want.
I'll do anything for you.
I promise.
I didn't forget.
Tell me what you want.
If you want your earring back,
participate in the contest.
Is that what you want?
It's nonsense.
If you can't keep your promise,
you shouldn't have made it.
Is that all you want?
Yes,
that's all.
Because you've never done...
something like this, have you?
Okay.
I'll do it.
I will make you see...
that someone like me...
can win the contest.
What?
You suddenly changed your mind
about the contest.
What has gotten into you?
It's absurd.
It's better that you don't know.
Look, just do whatever you can...
to make sure that I will win.
Anything?
Sure, Pai-Pai.
I'll ask for some advice from an expert.
You needed an appointment
to talk to me about Pai?
What's the deal between you two?
Well,
we're just friends.
He is...
an introvert.
He doesn't talk much.
I'm an extrovert,
so I'm here to talk on behalf of him.
Alright, you really are a smooth talker.
So what is it?
What is it?
Well,
do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
You don't?
But how is this related
to Pai being a contestant?
How?
Well, it's relevant...
because...
if he participates in the contest
and wins,
I wonder...
if he will get a girlfriend.
I see.
Well,
many winners from the past contests
got dumped.
So it's not an indicator.
But one thing is for sure.
He cannot have a girlfriend now.
Otherwise, his popularity will drop.
I'm serious.
It's the nature of the contest.
He can't have a girlfriend,
but I can?
Of course.
I'm serious about Pai though.
Don't forget to tell him
to prepare for the photoshoot.
-Don't forget.
-Yes, and the photos must be perfect.
Because if they are perfect,
it's a sign that our faculty
is likely to win.
Tell him not to get too much sun.
Okay.
-I'll tell him.
-Okay.
That's a lot of information.
Is there anything else?
Anything?
How about this ice cream?
It's delicious.
Okay.
Mine is melting.
Where are you going?
Why?
Is that for Pai?
What?
What are you doing?
Let me tell you this.
Stop trying.
No matter how persistent you are,
he's not interested
because he doesn't like dogs.
I'm telling you this for your own good.
Do you get it?
No, I don't.
Give it back to me.
I don't need your concern.
Good.
Nice.
He's cute.
The next one
is the Faculty of Dentistry's King.
He's a shoo-in.
His features are striking.
You're right.
There's no way he won't win.
He's gorgeous.
You're very handsome.
That's good.
The last one
is the Faculty of Medicine's King.
You can do it.
Oh my!
He looks like a stone.
Does he think
that he's taking a visa photo?
I can't believe my eyes.
I think that he needs some rest.
He looks stiff.
He does.
You can pose however you want.
He's a robot.
He is.
Stiff and robotic.
All done.
Finally.
Look at this.
What do you think of this one?
Don't worry, Pai.
It's just a photoshoot.
It doesn't necessarily indicate
the result of the contest.
But if I can't even do this,
how will I win?
I thought
that you were Mr. Know-It-All.
I never thought that...
you'd be dumb about dumb things.
I'm sorry.
Someone like you...
will never win.
I might have to throw the earring away.
Next time...
if you can't keep your promise,
don't even bother making one.
It was just a photoshoot.
I still have some tricks up my sleeve.
Just wait.
I will beat you.
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
Everyone put on your blindfold...
and hold the hand
of the person next to you.
We will slowly walk together.
Pai, hold my hand.
Pai.
I have something to ask you.
Would you be my boyfriend?
=My Gear and Your Gown=