Try Oishi Honey Lemon.
Made with Hyakka Mitsu honey.
Why?
Because I won't do it again.
Ball didn't do it last time.
Come on. I won't do it again.
Right.
Hey!
Itt!
Be careful, man!
Sorry.
Come on, Itt. Join us.
Itt, listen to me first.
Hold on.
Itt, wait for me.
I'm sorry.
I know you care about Pang.
I understand you,
but you still have to study with me.
If you don't leave, I will.
Hey.
(Pahun Jiyacharoen, Marc)
(Pawin Kulkarunyawich, Pawin)
(Pattadon Janngeon, Fiat)
(Napat Patcharachavalit, Un)
(Chayakorn Jutamat, JJ)
(Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee, June)
(Neen Suwanamas, Neen)
(Amarin Nitibhon, Am)
(Ratchanok Sangchuto, Nok)
(Nicole Theriault, Nicole)
(Phollawat Manuprasert, Tom)
(Intira Jaroenpura, Sine)
(Chonwari Chutiwatkhotrachai, Aom-am)
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
=My Gear and Your Gown=
So what's your problem with Itt?
Nothing.
Do you still see me as your friend?
He is angry at me.
-Where are you taking me?
-Just walk.
What's going on between you two?
Stay out of it.
Do you guys still think of me
as your friend?
Itt, there's nothing going on
between me and Pang.
I don't know why she did that.
But I've never thought...
...and will never think of your girlfriend
that way.
Yes, I know that.
What?
She likes rich people.
And you are rich.
I guess she wanted to have you.
You knew?
Yes.
You knew this,
but you're still mad at him?
You can hate me.
But don't forget that I am useful to you.
I can help you
get into engineering school.
Yes, that's why I went to your house.
Hold on.
Itt, I'm confused.
So you knew.
You're not mad.
You'll go to school as usual.
But when he asks to tutor you,
why do you make that face?
Well, I...
I...
I don't know how to start with him.
Come on, man.
What's wrong with you?
The whole thing is my fault.
I'm mad at myself because I need him
to do everything for me.
Even though he didn't do anything wrong,
he still tried to make it up to me.
I'm mad...
...that I let Pang mess with him.
And I'm mad...
...that I don't know
how to start a conversation with him.
Man.
Itt, you big oaf.
You're as dense as a brick.
I can't believe you.
Come on, Itt.
You just don't know how to approach him.
Do you have any idea
how much you've messed with his head?
-What?
-Yes.
A good kid like him
ran away from his parents...
...to make it up to you.
-Really?
-Really.
Well, I don't like to be misunderstood.
Right.
Either way, you're still guilty.
What are you saying?
That friend of yours told Pang
to make up to me.
You knew about that?
Yes.
I just pressured her a little
and she told me.
I'm sorry.
I understand, but I won't forgive you.
Then, what do you want me to do?
Tutor me again.
I knew it.
Either way, I'm still smarter than you.
Oh, you little...
No, no, wait.
Whoa.
Pai's sure got a mouth on him.
But it's the truth, man.
Oh!
Hey.
A nerd on the outside,
a bad boy on the inside.
All right, all right.
Very well.
Now that you two have made up...
...let me see you hug.
-Yes.
-You've made up, right?
-Come on.
-Show me.
What are you smiling at?
-Yes.
-Man.
Come on. Show me.
Wow, wow, wow.
Wow.
Wait for it.
All right, all right.
-This is funny.
-Good for you.
-Whatever.
Hey, wait.
I think it's too quiet.
How about some music?
-I got it.
-There you go.
Let's see, Itt's taste in music.
Let me guess, EDM?
Bring it on, man.
Definitely, EDM.
Now!
-Whoa...
This is nice, man. It has a good vibe.
Give me a hug too.
-Well...
-I'm happy they made up.
Do you like this song?
Yes.
Look at them.
I know.
My friends are happy. I am happy.
I'm sorry.
I know.
The weather is nice.
It is.
What are you saying about me?
-What?
-I heard you.
I saw you talking.
-I haven't finished.
-Give me a smile.
Give me a smile.
-Cute.
-All right, enough.
-Let's go home.
-Right.
I still remember the first day
I moved here.
Mom said I would have plenty of space
to run around.
Back then, we lived in an apartment.
It was so cramped.
But, honestly, it was kind of warm.
Your mother was a brilliant woman.
Yes, she was brilliant.
She worked so hard to get this house.
Which is why I have to hold on
to this house.
Because it belongs to my mother and me.
You can do it.
I can, if you help me.
I will help you.
How's that?
Am I good at choosing friends?
Am I as smart as you now?
I got you.
All right.
-Good night, man.
-Night.
Hey, do we have any homework?
I already finished mine.
Did you do your homework yet?
I haven't done mine yet.
Why's that?
Hey, can I copy your homework?
I know you were...
-...busy playing video games.
-Yes, I was busy playing video games.
I'm addicted to video games.
I completely forgot about my homework.
-Hey, Waan!
-Oh!
-Come at me, man.
-Guys!
I'm here!
-Dude!
-Come here.
-Let's go.
-Go.
I'll get you.
(Longlao School Grade 12 Room 1
Counselor: Mr. Panuwat Im-aimsuk)
All right.
First question.
The sugar component of DNA
is called what?
A sugar called deoxyribose.
That's correct. Okay.
What are the bonds
between nitrogenous bases...
...in DNA called?
-Go ahead.
-Hydrogen bonds.
That's correct. Okay.
(Longlao School Grade 12 Room 6
Ms. Sirikan Pupet Social Studies Teacher)
(Exit Ticket)
Write down the notes.
Come on.
Where are we?
Page three.
Paragraph two.
The players on our team are small.
We have to use our speed.
-Come here first.
-Suppose you pass the ball here.
-The goalkeeper is here.
-That's right.
This one passes the ball.
Suppose this one comes forward.
This one moves up and passes the ball.
(Bishop/Knight Club)
Take a look at this.
This one.
Look at the question.
And try to solve this one.
Let me try.
I'm working on it.
I'm paying attention.
That's it.
Come here.
I can fight back.
-What?
-Come here.
Look at the question.
Do I really have to explain it?
That's a polynomial equation.
Now, what is a linear equation?
That's it.
-Continue your lesson.
-All right. Just hold on.
Look at the chemical equation of...
When burned in oxygen,
how should you write the product
of this chemical reaction?
Equilibrium...
What?
Stop.
My teacher gave us so much homework.
Dude, my classes are way harder
than yours. One, two, three.
I have three subjects.
-Really?
-My brain hurts already.
Yes.
You fell asleep.
Just go home and do it.
Sure, I will.
Uncle Dong.
-Hello.
See you.
-See you.
-Bye.
-Get home safely.
-Do your homework.
-I will.
Yes, dad.
I'll copy yours
if I forget to do it, okay?
How bossy.
Dude, I have to finish my homework.
How boring.
So do I. Relax.
No rush. Just chill out.
-You always do, Itt.
-I want to be smart like you, Waan.
-Let's go.
-I'll pay a taxi fare for you.
Okay.
I need to brag about this.
Look at how proficient I am.
I can't read it.
These are my cumulative scores.
I've requested all of them
from all of my teachers.
What a liar. They told you before,
but you didn't write them down.
My point is...
...that I passed all my subjects.
Aren't I smart?
Right.
What?
But if you want to get
into the faculty of engineering,
you have to be smarter.
What?
You need to reach their entry score.
Passing the exam isn't enough,
especially if you want
to get into your chosen university.
I'm aware of that.
-You're such a downer.
-Don't be so hard on him.
He'll start his tutoring sessions
at university next week.
He'll humiliate himself
if I'm not hard on him.
What you said is completely true.
I totally agree.
Did you just slip?
-Easy, dude. I'm your friend.
-Okay.
Okay.
It's true,
and you need more tutoring sessions.
I already have a session every day.
I think that it should be two hours a day.
Darn, I can barely handle an hour.
His brain will explode.
Definitely.
I'm sorry, dude.
Fun time is over.
Shut your mouth.
What?
Did I say it wrong?
I don't care.
My scores are good.
Lucky you're sitting across from me.
Do you think that you're so great?
Look at my friend here.
Let's show them.
I'm ready.
-Yellow.
-Color.
-Mango.
-Fruit.
Turtle.
Mutant ninja.
-What's next?
-Knife.
Samurai.
So?
We're good, right?
You look stunned.
Speechless.
Pai, I think
that I should find you some pearls.
Why?
To cast pearls before swine.
He won't make it.
Find the colorful ones.
Sure.
He's sleeping like a log.
He is.
Oh!
That hurts.
Is he waking up?
What?
Who said that they were going
to pay attention?
Sorry.
Go and freshen up yourself.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Can you guys go home late tonight?
Sure.
You have to finish this book.
Look at him.
He's so sleepy.
Are you okay?
Unbelievable.
Poor him.
-So?
-Let's go.
Pai, we're going.
-Okay.
-See you.
-Bye.
-Guys.
Can you tell the teacher
that we'll be in this room until late?
Sure.
-See you.
-Bye.
I'm back.
Let's continue.
-Continue?
-Yes.
Okay.
Where are all the teachers?
Dude, just leave a note.
(Bishop guys
will use the room until late.)
Wow.
Matched.
What?
Hot stuff.
She's in the school.
She's only 100 meters away.
Let's go.
To where?
To keep me company.
If I don't like her...
...you're welcome to have her.
-Really?
-Yes.
Let's go.
Close the door.
(Bishop guys will use the room until late.
We'll lock up ourselves. Witsanu.)
Let's start.
There are three types of arithmetic mean.
The first one is the one
with distributed frequency.
The second is the one
without distributed frequency.
Okay.
Use this formula for the one
with distributed frequency.
Fx is the frequency...
...and Xi is the middle point.
The third one is weighted arithmetic mean.
You use this X = A + I.
And this parentheses.
Hey.
Yes.
Some expressions
equal the maximum value.
A is the middle point,
and the median average...
...is...
...the middle number.
We call it Med or Median.
Do you understand?
Hey.
(Knight Club)
(Every problem has a solution.)
Wake up, Itt.
It's already 10 PM.
Go home.
Okay.
Let's go home.
Come on.
Darn.
It's locked from the outside.
So what do we do now?
You tell me.
I don't want to tell my parents.
I don't want to get in trouble.
Then tell them that you're sleeping
at your friend's place tonight.
What about you?
No one cares about me.
Okay.
How about we continue?
You sound so depressing.
All right. Let's do it.
I can barely keep my eyes open,
so I'll lie down and listen to you.
(Every problem has a solution.)
We're looking for the median average.
We call it Med.
There are two types,
with and without distributed frequency.
The formula is M + 1/2.
For the median
with distributed frequency,
you have to create
the cumulative frequency...
...and find the position of the median,
which equals N/2
in order to identify class interval...
...and find the Med value.
What?
What are you doing?
You were sleeping,
so I took off your glasses.
Where is my earring?
Did you leave it somewhere?
No.
Is it a real diamond or something?
Why are you so upset?
No.
I'll buy you a new one.
It's the one that you and I...
What?
Let's just say it's important to me.
I need it back.
Hey, kids.
What are you doing here?
We spent the night here.
It's good you got here so early.
What's going on?
Pantoon...
...what are you doing here?
You're here early.
I have a morning shift.
What is it?
They...
We have a tutoring session.
We made an appointment
to come here early.
Yes.
Okay.
That's good.
Now that you're here, Pantoon,
I want to talk to you.
Okay.
I saw Ittikorn's math score,
and I'm very happy about it.
Okay.
I knew it. You're the smartest student.
So, of course, you'd be able
to help someone who's struggling like him.
You can rest assured
that you didn't do this for free.
The room will belong to Bishop Club,
per the agreement.
Okay.
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
(Next week on My Gear and Your Gown)
Did you find it?
Are you sure
that you lost your earring here?
Yes.
I heard that you disappeared last night.
Move our things out of this room.
Tell me what you want.
I'll do anything for you.
Do you expect me to believe you?
(My Gear and Your Gown)