Try Oishi Honey Lemon.
Made with Hyakka Mitsu honey.
Where are Pure and Folk?
Folk isn't feeling well.
So Pure is taking him to a doctor.
He also said he's sorry
for not being able to tell you himself.
I see.
It's fine, actually.
The activities today don't matter much.
Anyway, he is okay, isn't he?
Pure said he's feeling better.
Was it because of me?
Folk will be fine.
He has Pure.
Pure is good at comforting people.
Trust me.
(Pahun Jiyacharoen, Marc)
(Pawin Kulkarunyawich, Pawin)
(Pattadon Janngeon, Fiat)
(Napat Patcharachavalit, Un)
(Chayakorn Jutamat, JJ)
(Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee, June)
(Neen Suwanamas, Neen)
(Amarin Nitibhon, Am)
(Ratchanok Sangchuto, Nok)
(Nicole Theriault, Nicole)
(Phollawat Manuprasert, Tom)
(Intira Jaroenpura, Sine)
(Chonwari Chutiwatkhotrachai, Aom-am)
(Longlao School)
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
=My Gear and Your Gown=
What are you smiling at?
You seemed fond of my smile last night.
So I'm smiling at you again.
What's up with you?
Are you into me?
Yes.
You're exactly my type.
It's too bad...
that we are friends.
Woe is me!
Have you heard of the term
"friends with benefits?"
Hey.
That's my favorite English expression,
second only to one-night stand.
Why do you ask?
Are you smitten by me?
Not really.
I just don't know
why I should make my life difficult.
If love is hard,
I want to try simpler things,
like sex.
Right.
Good for you.
But...
to do "friends with benefit" with me...
there's one thing
that you might find hard.
What is that?
Positions.
Ah, don't get excited.
Do you see this?
Okay. Fine.
I see.
Now that you've slept with me,
you think you can do whatever, right?
How about some other time?
I'm tired today.
Okay.
I'll leave then.
By the way,
I'll be right next door.
Holler if you need anything.
My friend with benefits.
See you later.
Oh.
Darn it.
What's the matter with you?
Oh.
There's a car crash outside my room.
Can I take refuge here for a while?
Manage your traffic light better then.
Or else, it might happen
outside my room too.
I don't want to deal with any casualties.
Come on.
Don't worry about that.
I'm not high maintenance.
I don't care if you cremate
or bury my body.
You can do whatever you want.
Anyway,
what are you doing?
Making breakfast.
I'm making porridge.
There is pork, shrimp, and seaweed.
Do you want some?
The taste, however,
isn't that great.
Want to taste?
Here.
What's up with you?
Nothing.
It's just I never had this kind of moment
with any of my partners.
When you drop the "with benefits..."
you still have "friends," right?
So, do you want some?
Hurry up.
All right.
-What do you have?
-I'll let you choose.
I choose...
Can I have this?
No, you can't have it.
There's only one packet.
Why can't I?
-Choose something else.
-All right. I'll choose this one.
You're choosing mine.
Can't I?
-You can't.
-You said there's one packet.
Are you lying to me?
Are you almost done?
Yes. Just one more question left.
Whoa.
That's quick.
Oh, Folk!
Come sit with us.
(Ethics?)
Greetings.
It looks like a lot of first-year students
enrolled in my class this year.
I'm delighted to see this.
So, I've prepared a pre-test for fun.
It's for you to assess
your pre-existing knowledge.
Boo!
But before we begin the test,
I'd like to ask you the classic question.
The question is...
What is ethics?
Yes, Ittikorn?
Pantoon wants to answer the question.
So, Pantoon?
I'm listening.
Ethics is separating right from wrong.
The Thai term is derived from two words,
etiquette and virtue.
Etiquette is the rules for behavior.
Virtue is moral goodness.
To put it briefly,
ethics means having a sense
of what is right and wrong.
That's a very good explanation, Pantoon.
Guys, give him a round of applause.
Stop messing with me.
You're clever.
You should know how to stop me.
I will win the contest.
I will beat you.
And I will get my earring back.
Quit promising the impossible.
Get it for me?
Get it yourself.
-I'm leaving.
-Sure.
See you.
Folk.
Can I talk to you?
Folk, are you mad at me?
No, I'm just...
I'm just trying to get over you.
Can you give me some time?
All right.
I understand.
What are those?
Face masks and hand sanitizer.
This Mr. 950 of yours
sure has a creative mind.
(Take care. Mr. 950)
Got the present. Thanks a lot.
Next time, don't bother. I feel bad.
Please let me do something for you.
(Mr. 950: Please let me do something
for you.)
(2020 Star Contest)
Okay, guys.
There will be special rules
for this year's Popular Vote award.
This time, they're different.
Since our contest is based
on the concept of social responsibility,
the voting scores
will come from two sources.
First is the vote count
for each competitor.
Second is the amount donated
to the account...
for which each competitor is a campaigner.
But what hasn't changed
is that each individual...
has to prepare their own show.
Did I make myself clear?
If not, please read the sheets.
All right. That's it for today.
You're dismissed.
Waan, is there anything you want to say?
Well...
It's my friend.
He wanted to invite you to a meal.
This friend of yours
has asked about me a lot.
So, who is he?
Well, I guess he couldn't make it today.
My apologies.
I should go.
No, wait.
I'm not accepting your apology.
You invited me.
You should take responsibility for that.
You want me to take responsibility?
Okay. Sure. I got this.
-Sure.
-How bad of him.
I'll take responsibility.
-For sure.
-Right.
-Let's go. Okay.
-Should we go now?
Come on. I'll take responsibility.
(2020 Star Contest)
Let's go eat.
No.
I just came up with a scene for my novel.
I've got to write it down quickly.
You're always like this,
burying your head in a novel.
This is why your life doesn't go anywhere.
Well, if my real life
didn't have a good man like Pai,
I'd prefer to continue
burying my head in a novel.
What about sex?
Unlike you, I'm not like a lover boy.
Besides, I've got other things
to do in life.
Don't you ever get bored
thinking about it every day?
I should go.
See you.
Hey, Pure.
Are you free tonight?
Let's party.
I've got something to show you.
I'm not going.
Parties are boring.
See you around.
What's up with him?
May I come in?
Don't you have a party to attend to?
It gets boring sometimes.
Tonight...
I'm hanging out at your place.
Sure.
Do as you please.
Make yourself at home.
But...
I'm writing my novel tonight.
So, try to keep your voice down.
All right?
Okay.
I'll be quiet
Okay?
Oh!
Well...
-What's up?
-Keep your voice down.
Out of ideas?
Yes.
Here.
Drink some water to clear your mind.
And relax right here.
Feeling better?
A little.
Now, tell me where you got stuck.
You see,
there are two characters in the story.
The first character
is secretly in love with the other one.
And the other one is incapable of love.
I mean,
I can't figure out a scenario
where they fall in love.
Well...
That's hard.
Do they need a scenario to fall in love?
Without a doubt.
Then how would love happen?
I haven't been in love
for a very long time.
But I don't think that...
it would take a complicated situation
for me to fall in love with someone.
For example,
if I fell down a mountain
and he came to rescue me.
Not everyone will fall down a mountain.
Sometimes, it could
just be the little things in life...
such as the way someone talks,
their temperament,
or how they paying attention.
I read something about this.
It's said that love...
can happen easily.
It might happen
as soon as you open up your heart.
Wow, that's good.
I like it.
You must be so forgetful.
I read it from one of the novels here.
-Did you?
-Yes.
Anyway, thanks so much.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have thought of that.
You don't need to thank me.
I'm having a good time.
Reading the novel?
I'm having a good time...
being with you.
Well...
You two,
can you move this speaker over there?
Thank you.
There's a subwoofer, too.
Who can move it?
I'll do it.
Thank you.
Okay.
Is this spot okay?
Pure, can you move this one?
I'm checking on a speaker over there.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Is everything okay?
Yes, it is.
(2020 Star Contest)
Do you want to drink with me?
Let's have a drink together.
Are you here by yourself?
Yes.
I don't think you'll have fun
all by yourself.
Right.
You're cute.
Do you want to join us?
Our table's over there.
We're having fun.
Come join us,
and later, we can go somewhere else.
Yes.
Are you interested?
What's wrong with him?
Wake up.
Pay attention.
Here's a microphone.
One, two, three.
Hello, one, two.
One, two.
Please come and cheer on us on
at the contest day.
Thank you.
-Let me help you, Beau.
-Thank you.
Should we adjust it a bit?
Is it too high?
I think it's okay. Thank you.
It should be okay now.
Is it?
Yes.
Okay.
Is there anything else I can help with?
What's that?
(The contest is soon. Take care
of yourself. Do you best. Mr. 950.)
Well...
How are you?
I...
I'm sorry.
Do you still need some time?
Well, actually...
The crab fried rice is here.
I have finally gotten over you.
Excuse me.
See you.
Let's go.
Folk and Pure?
"I have finally gotten over you."
I'm curious to know
who helped you get over him.
Shut up.
I just don't want him to worry.
So, you really got over him.
What?
Would you stop chatting with girls?
You're not eating?
I bought it for both of us.
I'm waiting for my bubble tea to get here.
Okay.
Then I'll go take a shower.
What are you doing?
From now on,
you can do whatever you want
with my phone.
I won't keep secrets from you.
Pure, you told me
that you wanted to hit on Beau.
But why on earth are you messing around
with Folk?
You can fawn over her
for the time being.
About Folk,
let me enjoy him until I get tired of him.
(Basketball Tournament 2020
Medicine VS Communication Arts)
(Medicine 39 VS Communication Arts 28)
Are you all right?
That brute has no idea.
He's just a dimwit.
If he hits you again, say something.
Here.
You'll get hit if you stand there
being lost in thought.
Don't you want to play basketball?
I can teach you.
I won't annoy you.
That's why I should be afraid.
Because it's you.
Yes.
Many of our faculty's freshmen
are good players.
-He missed it.
-Yes.
Take it.
What are you doing?
Throw it back.
Generate force from your wrists like this.
Is this what you want?
Here.
Dang it.
Waan.
-Waan.
-Waan!
We need first aid!
Don't move. Let him check on you first.
Is it here?
Ouch.
Are you here for Pure?
He's not here.
Are you his friend with benefits?
He's been making excuses
not to party with us...
because he wants to spend time with you.
What are you doing?
You must be good.
That's why you can tame him.
What do you mean?
Let me check you out.
-What are you doing?
-I want to know how good you are.
You low-life scum!
Let me go!
Ouch!
Let him go!
Get off him!
-What the heck?
-What?
What's gotten into you?
You're not normally like this!
You always share things with me!
What's wrong with you?
He's different.
Get out.
I said, get out!
Now!
Fine! I'll go!
-Are you okay?
-Don't touch me.
-Don't touch me!
-Listen to me.
-I said, don't touch me!
-I've had enough of listening to you.
-Folk...
-You really are a bad person.
(Room 3102 Witsanu Sawetwart
Age: 20 years old)
Your wrist is slightly sprained.
I think that it's more than slightly.
I'm sorry.
You got hurt because of me.
It's not your fault.
I got hurt because of myself.
I wasn't paying attention.
I know you hate me.
But why didn't you take it out on me?
Don't, Pai.
Take your hatred out on me.
Punch me.
Come on.
Do it!
I didn't mean to hurt him.
-I just...
-You hate me.
But from now on,
it won't be one-sided hatred anymore.
Remember,
I hate you too.
Guys, please calm down.
Yes. Talk to each other nicely.
All right.
Now that we hate each other,
I'll make it easier for you.
I won't bother you anymore.
(Photography club)
Itt, are you there?
Folk must really hate me.
What should I do?
Are you ready to settle down?
I don't know.
What will you do about Pai?
Well,
I have achieved all of my goals.
It makes me happy just to see him...
stand up for what he wants.
Even if...
that doesn't include me.
It's painful.
I did everything...
because I wanted him to be confident
in expressing his opinions,
his feelings, and to show his liveliness.
I want others to see
that he's a good person.
I want them to see
that he can be fun to be with.
Also, I want him to know that...
he's the only light in my life.
How will he know your true feelings...
if you don't tell him?
Will you let yourself dwell on regrets?
It's over.
It's over between me and him.
It's okay.
Thanks.
I'm sad when you're sad.
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
Pure, can you not hit on Beau?
I don't want us to fight over a woman.
And you don't need to use 950 anymore.
950?
Yes.
The number isn't for this room.
I want to sing a song for someone
who's very important to me to listen to.
Won't you let me see
how the room looks like?