Try Oishi Honey Lemon.
Made with Hyakka Mitsu honey.
Watch me, Itt.
I will beat you.
Folk, what's up?
Well, my car is inside.
I'm waiting for you to move.
Right, right.
Sorry. I'll go now.
Hey.
Don't tell me you're following me.
No.
I live in this building.
Although, I did follow you.
What a coincidence.
(Pahun Jiyacharoen, Marc)
(Pawin Kulkarunyawich, Pawin)
(Pattadon Janngeon, Fiat)
(Napat Patcharachavalit, Un)
(Chayakorn Jutamat, JJ)
(Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee, June)
(Neen Suwanamas, Neen)
(Amarin Nitibhon, Am)
(Ratchanok Sangchuto, Nok)
(Nicole Theriault, Nicole)
(Phollawat Manuprasert, Tom)
(Intira Jaroenpura, Sine)
(Chonwari Chutiwatkhotrachai, Aom-am)
(Longlao School)
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
(My Gear and Your Gown)
Wait.
Don't tell me you live on the same floor
and next door to me too.
No.
I meant to follow you this time.
Actually, I live on the ninth floor.
Folk...
-I think...
-Have you ever liked anybody?
If you have, I'm asking you to let me try.
I really like you.
I warned you.
All right, have it your way.
I'll stand by as your friend first.
See you later.
Pai?
If you're still hesitant
to open your heart to me,
you can at least open the door for me.
Did you really just use that pick-up line?
You're making me feel stupid.
But I really want to see your room.
When you think of me as a friend,
then you can knock on my door.
See you around.
-Call me when you're home.
-Bye-bye.
Hey.
Do you live in this room?
Ah, yes.
I live in this room.
Now that we know each other...
and live next door to each other...
do you want to hang out in my room?
Ah, well, I'm kind of busy today.
I want to hang out with you but...
I'm busy. I've got work to do.
Gonna draft my novel.
It's vibrating.
Hello.
Well, yes, yes.
Okay, okay.
Let's eat rice soup with squid.
You bought that?
No.
It's from 950.
Nine-Five-Zero?
(Enjoy your meal, Pai-Pai. From Mr. 950)
Nine-Five-Zero.
Who do you think Mr. 950 is?
I think...
it's Folk.
How can you be sure?
Well, he said he was going to hit on me.
And you let him?
I understand him, though.
When you like someone,
sometimes you want nothing
but to be around them.
Your words got to me.
Thank you, man.
For what?
The thing is, I like Beau.
But she is way out of my league.
But like you said,
when you're into someone,
just being around them makes you happy.
I got an idea.
I will volunteer as a staff member
for the Star Contest Camp.
Well...
But don't get too close.
Be careful of your heart.
You too, Pai.
Don't forget that Itt
will also be at the camp.
What's going on between Itt and I...
is just a bet, that's all.
Pai-Pai, how's the rice soup?
(Mr. 950: Pai-Pai, how's the rice soup?)
Thank you.
How did you know I like rice soup
with squid?
(Thank you. How did you know
I like rice soup with squid?)
Good luck with the Star Contest.
(Mr. 950: Good luck
with the Star Contest.)
I'll do my best. Don't worry.
(I'll do my best. Don't worry.)
Oh, come on.
You caught me off guard.
Give me. Give it back.
It's mine.
This year's Star Contest
will also have a Popular Vote award.
So, let's get to know
the king and queen of each faculty.
Let's start with the Faculty of Dentistry.
Let's hear it for him.
Hi, everyone.
I'm Folk, Rattapoom Jintamanat.
The King of Dentistry.
Good job. Return to your place.
All right. Next, please.
Hello.
My name is Preechaya Pochaisri.
You can also call me Pong.
I'm from the Faculty
of Commerce and Accounting. Thanks.
Wow.
How professional.
Next, please.
Hello.
Phai. Prapawadi Kradingthong.
Faculty of Engineering.
Okay. Next one, please.
Hello. I'm Chalee Worakanthorn.
Faculty of Fine and Applied Arts.
Thank you.
He studies arts, guys.
Now, next.
Hey. I'm Itt, Ittikorn.
Faculty of Engineering.
Looks like this one is hot.
All right. Who's next?
I'm...
Pai, Pantoon Wongworawet.
Faculty of...
(Stars of Socially Responsible)
What faculty?
A person who is as stiff as a board,
what do you call that?
Something "ca...?"
Is it "cadaric?"
It's called cadaveric spasm.
It refers to the stiffening seen
in drowning victims.
It's a result of the victims'
intense struggle for survival.
This doesn't apply to me.
Whoa.
Clearly. you're from the Faculty
of Medicine.
Pai has competed in the Biolympiad before.
That's how you talk to him.
All right. Those are our rules.
Now, everyone,
let's move into your own groups.
Group One, follow Folk.
And, Group Three, stay here.
And, Group Two, follow Itt.
All right. Let's get moving.
Let's go.
Group Two, follow me.
Group Three, form a circle and sit down.
Sugas, could you take care of that group?
Okay.
-Umm. My name's...
-Pai.
Can I call you Dorky Pai?
He's a cute dork, though.
Hmm. Let's call him Pai-Pai.
All right. Next,
we're going to play an icebreaker game.
This game is called "Brrr!"
Also known as the category game.
But this time,
we won't specify the category.
Players must figure it out themselves.
This is how you play the game.
When the first player says "one,"
this means the category is a number.
The following players
must say "two, three, four," respectively,
and the last player,
instead of saying "five",
has to say "brrr!"
Got it?
Got it.
All right. Group Three got it.
Could you demonstrate it for us?
Unagi.
-Sushi.
-Takoyaki.
Sashimi.
Brrr!
(Volunteer)
Umm, Beau.
Do you need a hand?
Oh. Sure, Waan.
Well...
Just organize these books by category.
You can do short stories.
-Sure.
-I'll do fables.
Okay.
-Are these fables?
-Yes.
Okay.
Sorry.
-This is a short story.
-Okay.
Thanks.
Oh, you have something on your face.
Oh, what is it?
It's gone now.
Oh, thanks.
There you go.
These are short stories.
The first step of first aid
is cleaning the wound...
by dabbing the wound with a cotton ball.
Don't scrub it, okay?
Also, you need to check...
if there are any particles
or dirt in the wound.
Dab it with the cotton ball like this,
and avoid using hydrogen peroxide
and iodine.
The last step
is using saline to rinse the wound.
The most important teeth
are the molars, located here.
I'll show you
how to properly brush your teeth.
First, hold your toothbrush
at a 45-degree angle.
Then, move the toothbrush
from left to right.
Do this about four or five times, okay?
One. Let's do it.
One, two,
three, four.
Good job, everyone.
We'll brush our teeth together.
Sounds good?
You can rinse your mouth
after you're done.
Let's do it together.
Don't play with the water.
It doesn't look
like an adult showing kids.
More like a kid showing kids.
Barbra Streisand once said,
"There's a part of you
that always remains a child,"
"no matter how mature you get,"
"how sophisticated or weary."
Explain.
It means your inner child
will always be a part of you...
regardless of how mature you get...
or how complicated or exhausted you are.
Something like that.
Wow.
You're not only a dentist
but also a philosopher.
No.
Barbra is an actress and a songwriter.
And I am a dentist...
and a writer.
You're a nice guy
with a positive attitude,
and you have a way with kids.
You'll win the Start Contest for sure.
I don't know.
I'd rather have Pai be the winner.
The proper way to dress a wound...
is to clean it with alcohol.
But...
don't apply alcohol directly to the wound.
Are you okay, kiddo?
I feel his pain.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
He's okay.
How's it going?
Dude, he's so tense.
Can you help him so he can relax a bit?
The kids are as tense as he is.
No way.
I volunteered
because I wanted to flirt with girls,
not to help you guys.
Let's do it this way.
Pai, leave here quietly and secretly.
-Waan will continue this.
-What?
No one will say anything.
Believe me.
I don't think we should do that.
Calm down.
Itt, what happened?
I got cut from a metal object.
You're teaching first aid now, right?
Can you dress my wound?
Pai, how about you dress his wound?
You'll feel relaxed with him.
Besides, he won't cry.
-It won't scare the kids.
-Yes.
That's a good idea.
But how do I know you won't annoy me?
Just look at my wound.
How could I annoy you?
Sit down.
Everything's fine, everyone.
Don't be scared.
-Please stop crying.
-Don't be scared.
Doctor Pai is very gentle.
He will show you...
how to dress a wound
without causing any pain.
-It's okay.
-Please stop crying.
All the stubborn kids, come closer.
Let's move closer.
Don't cry.
Please.
I have some snacks
for anyone who helps him.
I'll help him.
Here it is.
Everyone, put on your blindfold and
hold the hand of the person next to you.
We'll slowly walk together.
Start walking once you're holding hands.
Keep holding hands.
Pai, hold my hand.
Put on your blindfold.
What?
Be quiet. The ceremony is about to start.
The purpose...
of the voluntary workcamp
is that the university wants...
all the faculty's Kings and Queens
to be an inspiration for others.
The workcamp requires you
to do good deeds, to share,
and to be a light in the darkness.
None of you are special people.
You are all equal.
Seniors have no power over you.
We're brothers and sisters.
All of you stand right where you are.
The seniors will come to you.
Are you a secret admirer type of guy?
No.
What are you waiting for then?
Are you afraid of disappointment?
That's not it.
Then go.
Beau?
Yes.
Since I'm one of the staff members,
can you tie my wrist?
Of course. Give me your hand.
Thank you for all of your help.
-Okay.
-Done.
-I'll go check on the others.
-Thank you.
She's cute.
You're close to her, aren't you?
Can you help me?
Pai?
I have something to ask you.
We can talk later.
But...
I'm afraid it might be too late.
Would you be my boyfriend?
I already talked to you about this...
and I stand by what I said.
Do you like someone else?
I'm not comfortable
to talk about this with you.
He refused me.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Anything.
I don't want to be here anymore.
How about we decamp?
Let's go.
She's cute.
You're close to her, aren't you?
Can you help me?
What are you doing there, Waan?
You can't sleep?
Let's go for a walk?
Beau...
what kind of guy do you like?
Well, I like women.
What?
I was joking.
Why do you want to know?
Do you want to hit on me?
No.
Actually, a friend of mine wants to.
Can he?
Well...
Of course.
Would you excuse me? I'm going to bed.
I told you he likes you.
Are you happy?
He doesn't like me.
His friend does.
Where's your booty call?
Probably in bed with someone else.
It seems so easy for you guys.
It's just sex, not love.
It isn't that hard.
How easy is it?
How easy do you want it to be?
Are you sure?
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
I've never felt this way
with my booty calls.
If I were to love someone,
I wouldn't need to wait
for a sign from the universe.
When love happens, it happens.
It might happen as soon
as you open up your heart.
Let me help you, Beau.
(Next episode)
I will be the winner,
and I will get my earring back.
Quit saying things you can't accomplish.
You hate me.
But from now on,
it won't be one-sided hatred anymore.
Remember,
I hate you too.