Try Oishi Honey Lemon.
Made with Hyakka Mitsu honey.
What are you doing?
What the heck?
These are Chemistry Olympiad papers.
How could you do this?
Don't be serious.
It was an accident.
You told me not to be serious?
You brought a girl in here
just to fool around.
Why don't you go to a hotel and do it?
Are you that excited?
You went too far.
What did I say that was wrong?
My papers are ruined
because of your sexual excitement.
You punk.
What's going on?
(Pahun Jiyacharoen, Marc)
(Pawin Kulkarunyawich, Pawin)
(Pattadon Janngeon, Fiat)
(Napat Patcharachavalit, Un)
(Chayakorn Jutamat, JJ)
(Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee, June)
(Neen Suwanamas, Neen)
(Amarin Nitibhon, Am)
(Ratchanok Sangchuto, Nok)
(Nicole Theriault, Nicole)
(Phollawat Manuprasert, Tom)
(Intira Jaroenpura, Sine)
(Chonwari Chutiwatkhotrachai, Aom-am)
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
= My Gear and Your Gown =
Who broke the projector?
I didn't do it.
What do you mean?
You were the one that pushed me.
Then I bumped into the table,
and the projector fell off.
He's lying.
He was upset with me
because I accidentally spilled some water,
so he pushed me.
-He's lying.
-Stop arguing.
I will invite your parents here
to discuss this.
Hello, Dad.
Are you on the way?
His parents are already here.
Okay.
Please hurry up, Dad.
Okay. I'm hanging up now.
Please don't worry about this.
We will make a fair decision.
But if Pitsarut turns out
to be the one at fault,
he will be banned
from all sports competitions...
...because this will be his third strike.
Will you be okay with that?
If Pure is at fault,
he deserves to be punished.
Is there other options?
(Longlao School Grade 12 Room 1
Counselor: Ms. Panuwat Im-aimsuk)
Just wait.
I'll share Pure's secret
so that he gets banned from school.
What a good eavesdropper you are.
You overheard just a few minutes of their
conversation and want to expose him.
You don't have any proof.
Pai.
Can't you just give me
some encouragement?
I'm just telling you what I see.
You might turn out to be the one at fault.
Who knows?
No way.
I didn't do it.
I refuse to be a scapegoat.
I've figured it out.
I know what to do with him.
What is it?
I'll tell his mother.
Yes, I'll tell his mother.
When will you stop causing trouble?
I didn't give birth to you so that
you would become this type of person.
Go take care of your own mess.
And make sure that I don't have
to come here again, understand?
Your mom's still as fierce as a lion.
Why did your dad come this time
by the way?
He's not my dad.
He's my mom's new boyfriend.
Just forget about it.
She'll have a new one in no time.
Tell yourself that.
Aren't you the one
who cares about her the most?
Clear things up with Waan
as soon as you can.
Don't take the blame if you didn't do it.
Otherwise, she'll get upset again.
I already talked to your parents.
I have their full permission
to impose a punishment...
...if either of you is wrong.
So,
I'll give you one more chance to confess.
Does anyone have anything to say?
Don't think that
I won't be able to find out?
I did it.
I broke the projector.
I see you won't give in.
You won't stop?
Get this.
Guys, make sure
you don't throw it at big boss Waan.
If he gets upset,
he'll push you, break stuff,
and then deny it.
I'm the winner.
Gosh.
It's so dry. It's like I'm chewing grass.
You're the one who wanted
to eat this bread.
If you can't eat it, do you want to go
to the cafeteria then?
No, I'm tired of being teased.
You told me that Pure did it.
I don't know why you needed
to act like a hero.
Darn.
Anyway, let's forget it.
I'm not serious about it.
Witsanu.
Pantoon.
I have something to discuss
with both of you.
Yes.
But it has nothing to do with him.
Why do you want him here?
He's the President of Bishop Club.
A club member did something wrong.
He has to be informed.
Does it mean
you will separate them from us?
I will disband Bishop Club.
You can't do that.
What about the agreement to gain
achievements within three months?
-Also, we've already prepared so much.
-Witsanu.
Listen to me.
I will disband Bishop Club
if you don't agree with my proposition.
Pantoon, you have to tutor Ittikorn.
Pai will tutor Itt?
But it's my fault.
Do you mean it's your fault
that you lied?
Of course, I know.
But I will let you off
if Pantoon agrees to do what I just said.
Why me?
You're the smartest student
in the school.
Why can't you help the one
who's struggling the most?
Maybe...
Look,
if you can tutor Ittikorn
until he can get into a university,
I promise I'll give what Bishop Club
wants the most.
But I...
Come on.
At least, he helped you before.
Besides, we'll get our room back.
This might be the only chance
I get to repay him.
I'll do it.
No, I'd rather die
than have tutoring sessions with him.
If you insist on that,
I'll have to ask you to move out.
Why are you threatening me about the room?
Isn't Waan the one who did it?
Then why am I being punished?
You're not being rational.
I'm going to talk to the Principal.
Itt.
I'm sorry.
It was me who broke the projector.
You can tell the Principal
that our club is not part of this.
I'll take responsibility.
From today onwards, Bishop Club
and Knight Club will share this room...
...with no arguments.
And you, Ittikorn, need to...
...be tutored by Pantoon every Saturday
for two months until the exam.
If either of you disobey my instructions,
you will be kicked out.
Okay.
So, you're going to do this?
-Yes, I'll do that.
-Yes.
No one likes being forced to do things
they don't want to.
But I'm not mad at the teacher
for forcing me to tutor him.
Maybe, I am hoping that
the villain will change his mind...
...and become the hero once again.
Let's get started already.
Before we start, can I ask you a question?
Yes.
You really don't remember helping me?
Who wouldn't remember someone
they've helped?
Come on. Let's start.
Okay, time for math.
(Noppakhun Hospital)
Yes, Dad.
Yes, I'm here.
Yes, I'm about to go upstairs.
-Mom.
-Oh, Itt.
You're always like this.
That's close enough.
Okay.
Let me lock the wheels.
All done.
How are you?
I'm doing great.
How are you doing today, Mom?
I'm doing okay.
I prepared a meal for you today.
Here you go.
A healthy chicken breast sandwich.
You shouldn't have troubled yourself.
Well, you're probably right.
How about tomorrow
you have the hospital food instead?
Well. What's wrong with it?
No matter how bland or salty
the food is, I can still eat it.
When you say it like that,
I couldn't help but want
to cook something tasty for you.
Come here.
I'm so lucky to have you, my dutiful son.
-Give me a hug.
-Of course.
How can I not love you?
Come on.
All right.
-It's packed tight.
-Wow.
I don't see yours.
Let me prepare yours first.
-You're such a...
-Here you go.
I picked the best vegetables for you.
-Right.
-They are good for your health.
-Thank you. Wait, yours is so small.
-Here.
No, this is enough for me.
I want you to eat more. It's good for you.
All right. Let's eat.
Eat up.
Do you want me to study your work
at the hospital?
Isn't it too early?
There's nothing wrong with that.
You can prepare yourself.
Since you're going to be
a doctor here anyway.
Coming here frequently
might motivate you in your studies.
Okay.
Doctor, it's time for your meeting.
All right.
I told everyone here about you.
Just do your best.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's get going.
(Patient Room 1206)
(Utumpon Noppanaradon)
Are you hot?
No, I'm good.
Kai...
Did you come here together?
She wanted to visit you.
So we came here together.
Right.
Lucky you and my friend
work at the same place.
How are you doing?
I'm doing well.
Seeing you again reminds me
of our first year of high school.
Sorry.
I think my mom should rest.
I'll be fine.
My friend came to visit.
Let me chat with her first.
It's all right.
How about I come back some other time?
All right.
I'm going to get a drink.
Are you all right?
I'm all right. I just need a little rest.
Anyway.
Seeing my childhood friend again,
I feel like...
...I'm a kid again.
Itt.
Have you ever heard the saying,
your best friends are the ones
you found in high school?
You're in grade 12 now.
Do you have any friends at school?
Try to make a lot of friends.
If only good friends
were as easy to find as you think.
You should rest.
Thank you.
I understand
that this must be hard for you.
I just need time.
All right?
Just hang on.
You can do whatever
with whoever you want, I don't care.
But you and your mistress should at least
show my mother some respect.
Kai knows her place.
Don't make a big thing out of this.
Her place?
Then where is the place for Mom and me?
I'm begging you.
Don't bring her here again.
I don't want Mom to look like a fool,
praising this phony friendship of hers.
You heard that, didn't you?
Yes.
Don't tell anyone about it.
Otherwise, you're dead.
If you don't want me to tell anyone,
keep up your end of the deal
with Ms Walailak.
Having you tutoring me?
Why do you even care?
I can tell her that you did your part.
And if I fail an exam,
just tell her that I'm too stupid.
I'm going to be your tutor.
Why are you doing this?
So that you know I'm smarter than you.
If you want to be a tutor so bad,
do it with your dog.
I'm not studying with you.
Then...
What happened today...
Why does it have to be here?
You don't need to know.
Just do what you're here to do.
Why do I have to take this test?
So that I can find out
what level of math you're at,
and create the right lesson plan.
Lesson plan?
Just finish it.
Whoa.
Your math level...
...is very low.
-Pai, you!
-Ah, Itt!
What are you doing?
I saw leaves falling.
So I'm getting them out of his hair.
How do you know I'm here?
Well, I can see you from the balcony.
Anyway.
-Is he your friend?
-Yes.
Hello, I'm Pai.
Well, what are you two doing?
We're studying together.
What?
You're studying? Seriously?
Yes.
I've never seen you read
even a single book.
How come you're studying with him?
I made a deal with a teacher
to help him get into a university.
But I have my work cut out for me.
Because his math skills
stop at eighth grade.
What?
Then...
...didn't you learn anything
from grades 9 to 12?
Then how will you pass the entrance exam?
Is there a way to sharpen his brain?
-Mom!
-What?
Based on his proficiency,
he'll need more sessions with me.
Every Saturday might not be enough.
He also has to study after school.
No, I don't want to.
This is enough already.
No! You have to do it.
Pai, you can be as hard on him
as you want. I approve.
Now, let's move to my room.
It's too hot outside.
Yes, ma'am.
-Let's move.
-Go ahead, Itt.
(Insert coin)
My mom isn't a teacher.
You don't have to fake being nice.
I'm not faking it.
It just helps things go smoothly.
Is that it?
Yes.
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
Pai.
My mom wanted me to give this to you.
And she wants you to tutor me tomorrow.
Waan!
Yes, you.
Come play with us. We're one short.
You don't like it?
I like it.
Then why are you hesitating?
You keep holding it in your hand.
= My Gear and Your Gown =