Try Oishi Honey Lemon.
Made with Hyakka Mitsu honey.
Hello.
Itt?
How are you? Where are you?
I'm okay.
Where are you? I'm coming to see you.
No.
You don't have to tutor me anymore.
There is nothing to negotiate.
(Utumpon Noppanaradon
Born 5 June, 1975, Died 25 January, 2020)
(Pahun Jiyacharoen, Marc)
(Pawin Kulkarunyawich, Pawin)
(Pattadon Janngeon, Fiat)
(Napat Patcharachavalit, Un)
(Chayakorn Jutamat, JJ)
(Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee, June)
(Neen Suwanamas, Neen)
(Amarin Nitibhon, Am)
(Ratchanok Sangchuto, Nok)
(Nicole Theriault, Nicole)
(Phollawat Manuprasert, Tom)
(Intira Jaroenpura, Sine)
(Chonwari Chutiwatkhotrachai, Aom-am)
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
(My Gear and Your Gown)
Hey. Has anyone seen Pure?
What about Itt?
No.
How can you not know their whereabouts?
You're in the same club.
They're your friends.
Aren't you supposed to know?
I saw them.
-What did you see?
-I saw Itt asking for permission to quit.
What? He's quitting the club?
No. He is quitting school.
What?
Are you sure? Itt is quitting?
-It's true.
-Is Pure quitting school too?
What are we going to do
with the club then?
Right.
What are we going to do?
-Oh.
-What about...?
Hey, hey. Let's calm down, guys.
Take it easy.
Let's go somewhere quiet.
-Let's eat.
-I'm hungry.
-Come on.
-Let's eat.
What is going on?
What's next, man?
Itt and I broke up.
But do you know where he is, right?
I know.
Can you take me to see him then?
No, I don't want to go there again.
Talking about it gives me the creeps.
Why? What happened to him?
Pai...
...the battery on my phone died.
I just came to tell you
that I will be waiting for you out front.
Thank you, Uncle Dong.
Do you have your own chauffeur?
Yes.
Please, Pang, tell me where he is.
Then, give me a ride home.
And I will tell you.
All right.
My glass is empty.
What was that sound?
I don't know. It doesn't matter.
Oh!
Hey! Who are you?
How did you get into my house?
I'm sorry.
The door was unlocked, so I...
I'm a friend of Pure's.
Is he home?
Oh.
Is your son home?
Is he?
I don't think so.
Waan.
Pure.
What are you doing here?
It's good to practice safe sex.
If I did,
I wouldn't be stressing out right now.
It was your decision.
There's no one else to blame.
Yes.
I know that.
You haven't come to school for days.
But you're still in uniform.
Don't tell me
that you haven't left your house.
What I do is my business.
What are you doing here?
I came to check and see
if you were still alive.
You haven't answered
any of my texts or calls.
You disappeared.
You're acting like you're my girlfriend.
A friend can also care about you.
You care about me?
My mother has been with me my whole life.
She doesn't even care.
Anyway, did you tell her about that?
What's the point of telling her?
She doesn't even know
that I haven't been going to school.
She only cares when she gives me condoms.
She's probably just scared
that I will get someone pregnant.
Don't tell me that your mother
buys condoms for you.
Yes.
Man...
That's cool.
So, why didn't you use them then?
Have you met a mother
who raises her son by giving him condoms?
I don't want to use hers.
So you rather look at her with disdain
and be nervous about it later?
She isn't your mother.
You wouldn't understand.
I don't think you behaving stupidly...
...because of your first love.
I think it's because of your family.
It doesn't matter now.
I did something stupid,
and now my life is about to fall apart.
There's nothing I can do to fix it.
Yes. It will fall apart
if you keep being stupid.
I know.
What on earth are you doing?
Come with me.
Where are we going?
Just come with me. Don't ask.
Where? I'm not going.
-Don't ask. Come with me.
-Hey!
Waan! Where are you taking me?
-Come on. Just come with me.
-No, I'm not going. Waan!
Let me go. Let go!
Even if you are positive,
it doesn't change anything.
Because right, now you're acting
like you're already infected.
And if the results are negative,
you can finally stop being stupid.
Well...
The test result came back negative.
You are clean.
-Hey, you are clean!
-Yes!
-I'm going to live!
-You are clean!
I'm so happy!
-I'm going to live!
-You are clean!
There, I told you.
That dude got it from someone else.
Besides, you're not the only person
in the world who sleeps around.
You're right.
That isn't something
you should be happy about.
If you keep behaving this way,
one day, you might actually get sick.
I won't do it again, Doctor.
I regret what I have done.
I'm so happy, man!
Man!
You're lucky
to have an open-minded boyfriend.
-No, Doctor.
-He isn't my boyfriend.
-We're friends.
I only came here to keep him company.
-We're just friends.
-Come on, Doctor.
Just looking at his face
gives me the creeps.
I just can't.
Underline that, Doctor.
It's impossible. I've got goosebumps.
Come on. Look at your face.
Like I would want you.
-He's in the friend zone.
-Yes, the friend zone.
I'm telling you.
-What are you looking at?
-No, what are you looking at?
Stop looking at me.
Thank you so much.
We're friends. It's no big deal.
Are you ready to go back to school?
I don't even play basketball
when you weren't around.
Sure.
I'll go back.
I've got heaps of girls waiting for me.
Do you have a crush on me?
You said that you didn't want
to use your mom's condoms.
Thanks, but I don't need them.
Haven't you learned your lesson?
Of course, I have.
No more ego.
I'll use them
no matter who they belong to.
Let me tell you this.
From now on, no glove, no love.
Waan...
What?
Don't you feel disgusted?
Why should I?
You're not infecting me with HIV.
I mean...
...that you don't...
...despise...
Well...
...my mom's behavior?
Why should I?
It's your life.
Isn't it already enough
that you're nice to me?
Well...
Okay, good.
It would be nice
if the others thought the same too.
Who do you mean?
I mean Itt.
Keep going.
It's all good. Keep going.
More.
Keep going.
You're wearing the earring now?
Yes.
I think that Pang
still has feelings for you.
She's just upset
that you're not going to school.
Come back to school.
Your mom wanted you
to study engineering, didn't she?
She's not here anymore.
You still have Pang.
Once she knew that I hit rock bottom...
...she stopped hanging out
with me right away.
I also regret the time I wasted on her.
You chose this.
You chose to hit rock bottom,
to not go to school,
and to work as a parking attendant.
What do you know?
My dad is going to sell the house
and start a new life with his new wife.
I have to work and save up money...
...so that I can buy the house back
for my mom and I.
Well, have you thought it through?
Yes!
Quit thinking for me.
Even though I'm not going to school,
I can still earn money on my own.
I'm not a rich kid like you,
who lives in a palace...
...and looks down on others.
How much do you earn including tips?
It's my business.
How much does your house cost?
Stay out of it.
Let's suppose that you can earn
a hundred thousand baht a year.
Your house costs five million baht.
So you'd have to work for 50 years?
If you become an engineer,
just think about how much more
you'll be able to earn.
You just have to study for a few years,
and you'll get your house back way sooner.
Which one is better?
You're the one who told me
that I only have one life,
so I should do what I want to do.
Is this what you want to do?
What do you want from me?
I want you to come back to school.
Come to your tutoring session tomorrow.
I'll wait for you at home.
Do you want to get hit by a car again?
You knew about it?
Of course, I did.
You and my mom were in the same hospital.
Then why did you act
like you were mad at me?
I thought you were mad at me
because I didn't answer your calls.
I don't know why I was mad at you.
Even though you didn't do anything wrong.
But I'll definitely be mad at you
if you don't come to our session tomorrow.
You're an idiot.
It's okay.
I'm here with you.
Itt...
We only just cremated Mom,
but you already brought
your new wife home?
Itt!
This is my house!
I can bring anyone I want.
This is my mom's house!
(What is the monthly salary
for an engineer?)
I need to be alone.
Who are you looking for?
I'm here to see Pai.
Please come in.
Okay.
Yes?
Your friend's waiting downstairs.
Thank you.
Pai is in the living room.
Hello, Pai.
Your house is beautiful.
How did you know where I live?
Your driver told me.
Are you going to stand there?
Come sit here.
Do you need anything?
It's about Itt.
Well, I've thought about it.
There might be something
I can do to help you.
He's your close friend.
Do you mean that I'm his friend...
-...and that he's your boyfriend?
-Ex-boyfriend.
Can you help me by getting back together
with him then?
I think it will motivate him
to go back to school.
Okay.
But I'll do it in exchange...
...for you dating me.
What?
I know that you like me,
and Itt is your excuse to approach me.
I like you, too.
If you feel guilty...
...then I will get back with him...
...and encourage him to go back to school.
But after that, you have to date me, okay?
What?
Pai...
What the heck is this?
There's nothing going on between us.
There will be.
Why did you say that?
To make things clear.
Itt, I'm sorry,
but it's over between us.
I can start seeing someone else.
I get it now.
Where are you going?
Don't complicate things.
What do you mean? I don't understand.
So, you don't like me?
No, I approached you...
...because I really wanted you
to help him,
but you've just made things worse.
So, this is all my misunderstanding?
I'm sorry then.
Hold on.
Can you talk to Itt?
I feel guilty for causing the fight
between you two.
But now that I know you don't like me,
I think I've already wasted
too much of my time.
I'm sorry, but I don't want
to see either of you anymore.
Itt, listen to me.
What's your problem with Itt?
Do you guys still think of me
as your friend?
I saw Ittikorn's math score,
and I'm very happy with it.
The room will belong to Bishop Club
per the agreement.
Okay.
(My Gear and Your Gown)