Try Oishi Honey Lemon.
Made with Hyakka Mitsu honey.
(Patient Room 3102
Witsanu Sawetwart)
What's the matter with you?
Pure...
I'm sorry.
Is it okay if I don't allow you
to pursue Beau anymore?
I mean,
I don't want us vying for the same girl.
I'm serious about this one.
Even if I don't get her,
I don't want to see her
being jerked around.
Besides,
you seem more serious about Folk.
I don't want her to get hurt.
I thought you'd never say it.
What?
-I don't like Beau that way.
-Oh...
I only wanted to give you a push.
-A push?
-Yes.
Oh, man!
I was so stressed.
Man.
Wasn't it worth it?
At least it made you realize
that there's someone out there...
who can make you break your own rules.
Then who is it...
that makes you break your own rules?
That hurts!
Why don't you worry about yourself
before minding people's business?
You will see.
Although I start out slow,
I'm going to outpace you.
Bring it on.
-Just wait until my arm feels better.
-All right.
Waan, it's me. How are you doing?
Give it your best shot.
The coast is clear.
I'll get going.
-Later.
Good luck. See you later, Beau.
(Pahun Jiyacharoen, Marc)
(Pawin Kulkarunyawich, Pawin)
(Pattadon Janngeon, Fiat)
(Napat Patcharachavalit, Un)
(Chayakorn Jutamat, JJ)
(Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee, June)
(Neen Suwanamas, Neen)
(Amarin Nitibhon, Am)
(Ratchanok Sangchuto, Nok)
(Nicole Theriault, Nicole)
(Phollawat Manuprasert, Tom)
(Intira Jaroenpura, Sine)
(Chonwari Chutiwatkhotrachai, Aom-am)
(Longlao School)
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
=My Gear and Your Gown=
(Trust Love)
(I'm sorry about what I did
to your friend yesterday.)
(I have something I know you'll like.
Forgive me. -Nickie.)
Pure.
Pure!
Folk!
Are you not mad at me anymore?
Wake up already.
You have a class this morning.
Folk.
I...
Pure.
Pure?
I should leave soon.
My boyfriend is calling.
Let's exchange numbers,
so we can meet up again.
What time is it?
It's a little past seven.
Where are you rushing off to?
Wait. Hold on.
I want to apologize.
I didn't do that to you
because Pure told me to.
He's been different lately.
He doesn't go out much.
He doesn't take anyone home.
He doesn't even text me back.
So I assumed...
that you're his boy.
I didn't know...
that he was serious...
about you.
That's all I wanted to say.
Bye.
Be gentle.
Are you sure you're a doctor?
I'm a dentist.
Why does it hurt now?
Didn't it hurt when you got into a fight?
It did hurt.
But it was more painful somewhere else.
Where was that?
Why didn't you answer my calls...
or read any of my texts?
No matter how many fights you get in,
even if you don't hand me off to anyone,
I don't want to be your sex buddy anymore.
I don't want to be that either.
Then...
let's go back to being friends.
No, not that.
What I mean is...
let's not be just friends.
But...
let's go out.
-Right.
-Ow!
Do you get rough when you're embarrassed?
I was just reminding you.
Would someone like you
be serious with me?
I did ask myself that when I was sober...
and when I wasn't.
I want you.
Who did you sleep with last night?
I can smell their perfume.
Well...
I...
I'm sorry.
But from now on, I won't do it again.
I promise.
I don't believe you.
Folk.
But I'll give you a chance.
I just came to realize...
that my life without you is awful.
If we are to start over...
can you promise me...
that I'll be your only one?
I promise.
You've been gone for days.
I figured you were sick,
so I brought you some congee.
Thanks.
It's all right.
You've helped me out a lot.
You don't need to refer to yourself
as Mr. 950 anymore.
Mr. 950?
Yes. Mr. 950
You sent me a lot of stuff.
Wasn't that you?
It's your room number after all.
It's not his room number.
It's the club room number.
(Bishop Club 950)
It's not Room 1061 anymore.
No, it isn't.
Remember the school's decision
to turn it into a recreation building?
When you had to share the club room?
When the construction is finished,
they assigned each room a new number.
This is the result.
Oh.
Well, does anyone else know?
Of course.
People who came back know about it.
It isn't a secret.
Well, did someone come back?
Sure.
It was Ittikorn.
He also asked me where you got admitted.
Did you see him yet?
I did.
That's good.
I thought the two of you were in a fight.
He asked me where you got admitted
and asked Witsanu to be his tutor.
They looked so...
Well, it's Witsanu.
Anyway, how is it going
after meeting up with him?
Do you mean Witsanu?
-Wow.
-Sweet?
Salty.
You're kidding.
This is an import. It should taste sweet.
I'm just kidding.
Beau...
just agree to be my girlfriend.
You're asking me that
when we just started dating?
Take it easy.
But I've had a crush on you
for a long time.
You should've told me sooner
if you know you couldn't wait.
That sounds so familiar.
It reminds me of someone.
Waan, I need to talk...
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you're here.
Oh, it's fine.
-I should leave.
-Wait.
We're dating.
I don't keep secrets from you.
And that includes my friend.
Wait.
-Are you and Beau...?
-That's right.
We're dating.
Just like she told me,
in some cases,
if you don't tell it, people won't know.
And it means nothing.
I don't know...
if Itt will be mad at me
for telling you this.
But what I know for sure...
is that I will be mad at myself
if I didn't tell you.
Pai...
during high school,
Itt was never mad at you.
And everything he did,
he didn't do it to bully you.
♪It has been long since I last saw you
Do you miss me?♪
♪It's been a long time
I wonder if you miss me at all♪
Get on standby, Itt.
Okay.
The rabbit turns the turtle over,
and the turtle can continue walking.
Finally, both of them
reach the finish line together.
The moral of this story is...
if we accept each other's differences,
and we are ready
to move forward together,
it doesn't matter
how far the finish line is.
Wow!
What a touching story.
We had given him specific words
and he came up with this story.
The given words were Rabbit,
Turtle, and Orion.
Well done.
He gave you both knowledge
and imagination.
Please put your hands together for Folk
from the Faculty of Dentistry.
In order to not waste any time,
let's see our next talent show.
Please welcome
the Faculty of Engineering's King.
Judging from the support
from the female fans,
he must be a shoo-in.
Well, I'm not feeling well.
I have to withdraw from the contest.
I'm sincerely sorry.
Everything is okay, everyone.
He must have an important reason.
Well, I think we should continue.
Please welcome
the Faculty of Medicine's King.
Today, Pai will show us
how he'll solve a mathematical equation...
which is as difficult as the Olympiad's.
I'd like to change my show.
I want to sing a song for someone...
who's very important to me to listen to.
♪The rain might stay for a while♪
♪The clouds might stay overnight♪
Do you like this song?
Yes.
♪But it's different with you
Who stayed just for a while♪
♪And with everything
That changed overnight♪
♪I never forget♪
♪Everything that happened♪
♪As if it became part of my heart♪
Thank you.
Teenagers these days
come and go really fast.
Maybe he needs to go to the bathroom.
Now it's time for us
to watch all of the Queens!
Itt.
You promised me
that you'd return my earring...
if I won.
How could you do that...
if you're not staying until the end?
Is that all you want?
Then I'll stay.
All right.
The final question for Pai is...
This is an interesting question.
What does the word promise mean to you?
The word promise...
used to mean nothing to me.
But now, I realize that...
promises are all about trust.
They give us motivation.
They inspire us.
It doesn't matter where you stand.
You have to keep your side of the promise.
What an excellent answer.
Like a singer once sang,
"A promise must be kept."
For anyone who has made a promise,
just keep it, all right?
And for all the Kings and Queens,
don't forget your promises
to contribute to society.
Thank you very much.
The next step is,
we will count the scores.
While we wait,
I'd like to announce the winner
for Popular Vote.
I have the result right here in my hand.
Are you guys excited?
Yes!
All right.
Like we mentioned before,
this year's contest rules
are very special.
All of our Kings and Queens are required
to do volunteer activities.
They can get the votes from two ways,
which are the ones from the crowd...
and the ones from donations
to the foundations...
where each King or Queen represents.
I'm going to announce the winner.
The foundation that received
the most donations is...
the Children's Creativity Foundation,
with Mr. Ittikorn from the Faculty
of Engineering as its representative!
Even though he withdrew himself
from the talent show round,
his popularity
made him the winner of the popular vote.
Congratulations!
Let's give him a big round of applause!
You look even more handsome with the sash.
Well, thank you very much...
for all of your votes.
This year's university Queen
is from...
the Faculty of Commerce and Accountancy!
Don't forget your duty
as a volunteer this year, okay?
Here comes the moment
all the ladies have been waiting for.
That is, who is our new university King?
And this year, it goes to...
the Faculty of...
Medicine!
Did someone force him
to participate in the contest?
All right.
And that's it
for this year's Star Contest.
Congratulations to all the winners.
Don't be sad if you didn't win.
All of you are Kings and Queens
in our hearts.
Thank you!
Congratulations.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
(Photography club)
Here's your earring.
Won't you let me see
what the room looks like inside?
Yes.
I did it all.
But what's the point?
Because you left me anyway.
Now I know that you love me.
You are Mr. 950.
You've been taking care of me
this whole time, haven't you?
I feel his pain.
It's okay.
Itt, what happened?
I got cut from a metal object.
Pai, how about you dress his wound?
You'll feel relaxed with him.
Besides, he won't cry.
It won't scare the kids.
What are those?
Face masks and hand sanitizer.
This Mr. 950 of yours
sure has a creative mind.
I did it because I wanted to.
I won't regret it...
if you leave me.
You can't leave
because of a misunderstanding.
Did I just get caught?
How embarrassing.
I feel like I'm forcing you to love me.
Do you know...
why this brick-colored earring
is so important to me?
Because it eliminated your fear
of getting your ears pierced?
No.
The earring isn't the reason.
It's you.
You were with me when I bought it.
And your nickname means brick.
It represents you.
Yes.
I love you.
Did you do all of this
because you feel guilty...
for causing a misunderstanding?
A gear is a symbol
of the Faculty of Engineering.
I bought it because I wanted to get
into university at the same time as you.
I changed its color to white...
and I've always kept it with me...
because Pai means the color white.
Pai,
even though I'm a dumb person,
I'm not dumb when it comes to this.
All along, I've never felt guilty.
Loving you...
is the smartest thing I've ever done.
Here.
What?
Let's exchange them.
I'll take your doctor gown shaped earring,
and you take my gear.
It's a promise.
A promise?
Whoever has the gear owns my heart.
It belongs to you now.
I'm sorry for the way
I treated you before.
This gear is a promise...
that I'll stay by your side...
for as long as you want me to.
I promise you...
that I'll stay with you forever.
I love you.
I know that.
And you should know...
that I love you too.
We're not friends anymore.
You're my boyfriend now.
Yes.
Pai!
Mom!
(Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
We want to see your success,
not your problems.
Itt isn't a problem.
He's the reason I won the contest.
Pantoon Wongworawet?
He's dropped out of university.
We should break up.
I won't be here
to take care of you anymore.
Please take care of yourself.
=My Gear and Your Gown=