Try Oishi Honey Lemon.
Made with Hyakka Mitsu honey.
You've solved this before.
Find the solution of the equation.
- How?
- How do you solve this?
I taught you before.
I don't remember.
This is the formula we used before.
Remember?
Find mol 2 times 6.757
and divided by 1 mol.
How?
This is the formula we used before.
See?
Find mol 2 times 6.757
and divided by 1 mol.
Then you get the result.
This is the answer.
Now it's your turn to solve it.
What?
Come on. It's your turn.
I can't do it.
Don't write nonsense.
Mm.
- Mm.
- How's that?
- Is it correct?
- No.
Come on. Focus.
- What?
- Focus.
The result is probably
two...
I'll do it.
Oh.
I'll do it for you.
Thanks.
Do this part in the meantime.
- Okay.
- I'll find some math problems for you.
- Uh-huh.
- Mm.
That's right.
We have to study this next.
Why is there so much to study?
Why is there so much?
- Well. Who told you to be stupid.
- Oh.
I've got to get you good at this.
Is it so wrong to be born stupid?
Yes, it's wrong.
- You want to study engineering, right?
- What?
- Give me a second.
- Sure.
Come here, Mom. I'll give you a massage.
Thank you.
- How does that feel?
- Good.
(Patient Room 1206,
Utumpon Noppanaradon)
The patient's condition is stable.
Her blood pressure is normal.
Okay.
Are there any complications?
We haven't found any complications.
When is her next check-up?
In the afternoon
you will be informed by a nurse.
- All right. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- I'll leave now.
- Okay.
How are you doing?
I'm good.
Good. We're almost there.
- I'm getting better.
- You'll get better in no time.
You'll be out and about soon.
All right. I'll repeat it to you.
The rules for solving
one-variable linear inequalities.
First,
move the variable to one side.
Second, get rid of the brackets, if any.
Third, get rid of the fractions, if any,
by multiplying by the
least common multiple.
- All right.
- But be careful
when multiplying or dividing
with negative numbers,
you must reverse the direction
of the inequality symbol.
For example, switch greater than sign
to less than sign.
- All right.
- Okay.
Now that you got it.
Try to solve this one.
Here.
It's correct.
- Are you serious?
- I am.
- For real?
- Yes.
Good job. You did a good job.
I'm telling you. My brain is good.
I'm happy for you.
Hi, Mom.
I'm tutoring my friend.
I know that tutoring your friend
also helps you review your lessons.
But you have to prepare for
medical entrance exam too.
All right.
I will manage my time accordingly.
Well. Mom,
- my friend's mother has...
- I know.
Don't worry about your friend's mother.
Our hospital takes good care
of all its patients.
Okay, Mom.
(Pahun Jiyacharoen, Marc)
(Pawin Kulkarunyawich, Pawin)
(Pattadon Janngeon, Fiat)
(Napat Patcharachavalit, Un)
(Chayakorn Jutamat, JJ)
(Wanwimol Jaenasavamethee, June)
(Neen Suwanamas, Neen)
(Amarin Nitibhon, Am)
(Ratchanok Sangchuto, Nok)
(Nicole Theriault, Nicole)
(Phollawat Manuprasert, Tom)
(Intira Jaroenpura, Sine)
(Chonwari Chutiwatkhotrachai, Aom-am)
(Directed by
Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
(My Gear and Your Gown)
(Insert coin)
Pai!
My mom wanted me to give this to you.
And she wants you
to tutor me tomorrow.
Got it?
Itt has a tutoring session with Pai.
I guess he can't make it.
Then we're short of a player
and can't play the game.
Hey. Why don't we ask Waan to join us?
We can play three-on-three.
No. He's awful.
Besides, he's in Bishop Club.
I don't like him.
Waan!
Me?
Yes, you.
Come play with us.
We're one player short.
Waan, move.
Behind you, Pure.
Sorry.
Sorry, man.
Go!
Go for it. I'm giving it to you.
Yes!
Why did you suddenly ask me
to join a game?
You unexpectedly took
the blame for me.
So why can't I
suddenly ask you to join me?
But right now
it's time for you to leave.
What's up with you?
There is a certain jerk
being territorial about the club room.
So I had to switch to this room.
So,
8x minus 16 ninth equals 64,
x...
Hi, Mom.
You have a lot of patients to see, right?
Yes, it's fine. I can have dinner alone.
All right.
Can I ask you something?
Is the hospital where my mother is staying
owned by your father?
Yes.
And your mother is a doctor?
My father is one too.
Man.
That's definitely a family business.
Does this mean you will be a doctor?
I guess so.
Otherwise, who will
take over the hospital?
You say that like you don't want to it.
I don't know.
I still have no idea what I want to be.
But if I don't become a doctor,
who will look after the family business?
What about you?
A national athlete?
No.
I want to be an engineer.
You didn't expect that, did you?
I didn't expect it either.
I can't even pass a math exam.
How could I build a house for anyone?
You can.
If you set your mind to it,
you can be an engineer.
It's true.
You're not stupid
like you think you are.
Are you selling me dreams?
I'm getting my hopes up now.
I'm Itt, a freshman
from the faculty of engineering.
Your goal is clear.
It's much clearer than mine.
I have a new goal now.
What is it?
Wonton Noodle Soup.
Wonton Noodle Soup?
Come look at this.
Have you seen this guy?
He's so handsome.
Oh yes, super handsome.
His facial features are perfect.
Eyebrows, eyes, nose.
Even his ears are handsome.
You're exaggerating.
Is there someone more handsome than me?
Where did you get such confidence?
I think that
you should go and see him for yourself.
He's over there.
Seriously?
If you don't believe us,
go check him out.
Let's go.
Stop here.
He's so cute.
He's so handsome.
He really is.
Do you think he has a girlfriend?
I hope not.
Is this what you call handsome?
He's more handsome than you.
So cute.
His friend is coming.
What?
Did you see that?
Oh my!
Maybe they're just friends?
What a waste.
You were going to have dinner alone.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have taken you out.
Don't tell anyone that I brought you here.
Why?
Any stall that receives
a lot of good reviews
is always full of customers.
Everything here is delicious.
You'll have more that one bowl for sure.
I need to stop here for a second.
The color for that pair is off.
Only one of the earrings is off too.
Would you prefer the white gown ones?
You don't like it?
I do.
Then why are you being indecisive?
You don't seem to want to let it go.
He said that the color was off.
That doesn't matter.
What matters is if you like it or not.
I'll take this pair.
Do you want to wear it now?
My ears aren't pierced.
Then get it done.
But
- my parents don't...
- It's just piercing your ear.
This is your life.
Live it the way you want.
Do what you want.
Can you pierce my ear?
That's right.
Thank you.
For what?
For bringing me here.
It's really delicious.
Don't give a good review.
Otherwise, this place will be packed.
The noodles are soft.
The meatballs are firm.
Very good.
Here.
It must be seven or something.
Dad. Mom.
- Hello.
- Pai.
You finished tutoring very late today.
Yes. I'm going to take a shower now.
Hold on.
Did you get your ear pierced?
Did you?
Let me see.
Since when?
Tell me.
If you don't like it,
I'll take it off.
It would be a waste then.
Pai.
It's not that we don't like it.
We just want to know why
you decided to do it all of a sudden?
Okay. It's already done anyway.
You look different lately.
If there's something on your mind,
you can talk to us about it.
You know that, right?
Okay.
Go take a shower.
You don't like it?
I do.
Then why are you being indecisive?
You don't seem to want to let it go.
He said that the color was off.
That doesn't matter.
What matters is if you like it or not.
It's just piercing your ear.
This is your life.
Live it the way you want.
Do what you want.
I'm sorry. I want my mom to rest today.
That's why I asked you
to come here instead.
Okay.
We can do it here.
It's good actually because
I have something to tell you.
What?
Don't tell me that you're going to
stop tutoring me.
You can't do that.
My mom is already dreaming of
me being an engineer.
By the way, the earing
looks good on you.
Yes.
Thank you for making me
more courageous.
Sure. You're grown up now.
Be courageous and do things.
Itt.
Yes?
I...
like...
Itt, have you been waiting long?
I'm sorry for being late.
Not long. We've just arrived.
Are you Pai?
I've heard a lot about you.
Can you tutor me next time too?
Pai.
This is Pang, my girlfriend.
I forgot to tell you that I asked her
to come here too.
We're watching a movie after this.
Itt,
I already booked the tickets. Here.
Why did you book them already?
Well, I wanted honeymoon seats.
So that I can snuggle up to you
while I'm watching.
Isn't that good?
- It's a good idea, right?
- Yes.
This movie is great.
It's very interesting.
Are you sure about that?
We haven't watched it yet.
- I'll send the trailer to you.
- Itt.
I'll be back.
Okay.
You have to watch it.
Don't fall asleep.
Isn't it too early?
No, it's not. We'll go there
after you finished here.
How cute.
Look.
It's so nice.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's hurry up. You're going to
the movies with her, aren't you?
Yes.
Try and solve this one.
You already had me do this one.
Then do this one.
What?
You haven't taught me this one yet.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry. I got the wrong book.
Well, do this one then.
You can ask me if there are parts
you don't know.
Okay.
Here.
A11 and B11. Can you see it?
- Yes.
- All right.
Find the value.
Move this log
to this side.
Here?
What about here?
I don't get it.
That's not it.
Pure's been dating me first.
What matters is whom he will choose.
Pure.
- Choose me.
- Choose me, Pure. Please.
There you go.
That's what you get for being a player.
Gosh. Hold on.
- Choose me.
- Please choose me.
Enough!
That's enough.
I never said I would choose anyone of you.
I see that height doesn't matter
when you're lying down.
Being too handsome is problematic.
Pure, you jerk.
Pure!
Why are you being like that?
Like what?
(Directed by
Siwaj Sawatmaneekul)
Darn it.
Get lost.
- Have you been waiting long?
- Just a bit.
- Did you order yet?
- No.
- What would you like to eat then?
- And you?
Hello?
(My Gear and Your Gown)