The people, places, organizations, events,
groups and professionals
depicted in this program are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Since you're a big fan of mine,
I'm going to appoint you as my honorary consultant.
Usually, you and me
can talk about everything.
Have you ever thought...
about how you'd live
if I'm not in your life anymore?
Have you guys made up?
Earlier you said you said you finally realized you shouldn't prank people..
just because of what, exactly?
Just because they try to get close with someone I care about.
And that person...
is you, Kim.
What are you doing, Mek?
I'm writing my name.
Why would you do it?
Because I want to make a reservation.
You're so cute.
I'm afraid someone might steal you away from me.
Let me see how you made your reservation.
I just signed my name.
"Mr. Meka".
Make a copy.
And finally...
Put a stamp on it.
From now on...
I have you as mine.
Now I see...
that you really are a possessive person.
Come on.
Let's get out of bed.
Nah.
I don't want to go anywhere.
Can I just cuddle you all day long?
Mek!
Come on.
Mek.
We do have another thing to talk about.
I want you to apologize to Tim.
You think I'm that bad of a person?
I already texted him to apologize.
[Tim, it's Mek here. I was the one who did it.
I'm sorry. I didn't know you're allergic to shrimp paste.]
Don't be mad at Kim. And don't forget to take pills.]
Are you trying to write an essay or what?
You see?
I wrote all that stuff yet he didn't reply at all.
Then...
Why don't you apologize to him in person?
Please.
Why?
Is your ego getting in the way?
Yeah, basically.
Everyone has strengths and weaknesses.
I'm not gonna force you.
Because I think in the end...
you can do it.
I'm gonna take a shower.
I'll come with you.
[FLUK
Chatchawal]
[EARTH
Teerapat]
[BEW
Sitthikarn]
[DANIEL
Cheng Yu Chang]
[BOAT
Yongyut]
[KENJI
Siwarut]
[POR
Passakorn]
[YUT
Kritsadayut]
[Directed by
NATTHAMON YIMYAM]
[Dear my precious thing...]
Here.
May I open it?
Wow.
Babe!
This is the same model as
the one I had that got broken.
Thank you.
You like it, right?
Even if you didn't get me any gift,
I'd like it anyway.
Can I ask you something?
The other day, why did you think...
that I cheated on you?
Because Bear got me into this horoscope thing.
It said that I should be careful about love
and that there would be a third wheel.
And it coincided with when you started acting weird.
So I was overthinking about it.
If you'd just asked me directly,
none of that would've happened.
You know, when didn't come home...
I was so worried.
Don't ever be like this again, okay?
I don't like us to be separated.
Babe.
Can I also ask you one thing?
Sure.
Have you ever thought about telling people...
about our relationship?
We never really talked...
about why we kept our relationship this way.
Not that I didn't know about how you feel.
But why do we have to keep it a secret?
[Winner:
Atikorn Assawavanich
Grade 11 Class 2]
[Consolation prize:
Lee Xiang
Grade 11 Class 1]
Oh, wow.
Did you train Park
so he could beat a champion like you...
who is his boyfriend?
Park is talented in his own right.
I only helped guide him to discover what he likes.
But...
Are you really okay with this?
You did have a lot of expectation
when you submitted for this contest, no?
Isn't it the scholarship that you want?
I actually feel glad
to see that Park is the winner.
Never knew you love him that much.
What are you guys talking about?
Congratulations.
You're such a dark horse!
You could beat Lee.
You don't know anything.
I simply just let him win it.
These two lovebirds are so annoying!
It's a great photo.
Nothing.
I didn't win, mom.
I'm not sad for not winning the prize.
I'm sad because...
I felt jealous of him.
[Winner of Photography Scholarship Competition]
You know, since then...
I have always felt pressured.
I think and rethink about it every day.
What did I lack?
Where did I go wrong?
How did you end up doing better than me?
I admit...
deep down I couldn't accept it.
You seem to succeed in everything you do.
And when people pointed that out to me...
It just made me feel...
jealous of you.
I've known it all along.
I also know that the reason you keep our relationship a secret
is because you don't want to be compared with me.
And when you transferred to my faculty
you don't want people to ask why.
You're trying to avoid the feeling of hate
and jealousy towards me, right?
Actually...
It was so bad to the point that...
I thought I wasn't good enough for you.
So that's why you don't want to tell people...
about our relationship, right?
I am sorry.
It's not your fault at all.
It's me.
I shouldn't have let this go on for so long.
From now on...
Let's forget about all those bad feelings
that got in between us.
I want to hold your hands
and move forward with you.
I want to be the person
who will always be there for you
like how you've always been there for me.
Can we do that?
Let's eat.
Please eat a lot.
You don't want those eggs?
I'll eat them later.
You'll probably be too full before you get to.
About the shrimp paste cake incident,
I have thought about it thoroughly and I believe...
all of that could have been avoided.
This is a serious crime, Meka.
Had Tim not been rushed to the hospital,
can you imagine what would've happened?
I sincerely apologize.
I never intended to let it happen that way.
I hope this will be a lesson for you
and remind you to think of the consequences
every time you do something.
And you should apologize directly to Tim.
You're lucky he didn't press charges.
Also, don't forget to thank him.
Now you two don't have to make BL content anymore because of him.
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
I'm gonna cancel all BL activities
and also withdraw the suspension for
all Thunderous Sky channel members.
Yay!
So you no longer want to promote our university?
Oh, no!
Have you forgotten...
that I am a modern chancellor?
I just have a new project coming up.
If you need any help, I'll be happy to assist you.
Thank you both for paving the way
and inspiring new ideas for our university.
You two have enabled the society to realize
that our university
is inclusive and progressive.
After this, you two can move on and do your thing.
Kimhan...
I'm looking forward to seeing the student club thrive
just like how you promised me.
As for you, Meka,
please concentrate on your thesis
so you can graduate with success.
Now...
Let me introduce you my vision for the next quarter.
I'm going to focus on...
Girls' Love content!
Please stay tuned for more details!
Allez Cuisine!
Girls' Love!
The chancellor is brilliant,
and also weird.
Allez Cuisine!
Now you don't have to worry about getting suspended.
I guess you can go wild now.
Wild where?
Thunderous Sky channel is gone.
You guys are still mad at each other?
Someone's looking like a sick puppy here.
Come here.
Brighten up.
Quick, quick.
You're the best.
Since there'll be no more Mek-Kim content,
I hope you don't get too sad.
I'll come by your place every day.
I'm going to lock my door!
Then, I'm going to climb up to your room.
How about that?
Come on.
We only live a few steps apart, remember?
I gotta go.
See you again in the evening.
See you.
I'm so curious...
about what you did at Mek's resort.
I bet he got a free night promotion
plus the son of the owner!
Stop it, you two.
You mean, stop the sweet love between you and him?
Come on. Let's go.
We have work to do, don't we?
What are you waiting for?
Here.
Drink this first.
It suits your sweet and refreshing life perfectly!
How is it?
Sweeeet, right?
Is it as sweet as Mek?
Let's go now!
We've got work to do.
- Okay, okay.
- Go.
Guys, I have good news.
What good news?
Gas price is going down?
No.
The chancellor won't need us to make BL content anymore.
She also removed suspension on the Thunderous Sky guys.
- Yes!
What are you so happy, Lee?
What about you?
Why be so happy?
Well, because my Bear is not going to get suspended.
And that makes me happy.
So now you can call him "my Bear"?
Why can't I?
Don't you know...
that we're together now?
Since when?
And why didn't you tell us?
I wanted to tell you guys.
I was just...
waiting for the right time.
Then I guess...
This is the right time for me to come clean, too.
What is it now?
What else do you guys want to tell me?
I am...
in a relationship with Park.
What? Since when did you have a thing for him?
7 years ago.
So you've had a crush on him for 7 years?
7 years that we've been together.
I think I'm gonna pass out.
Why didn't you tell us?
Well, you guys didn't ask.
I also have my personal reasons.
So I just date him in private.
You know you can share things with us.
You don't have to keep it to yourself.
When you keep things to yourself,
it can get worse.
So...
Any other shocking news you'd like to share?
Just announce it all!
I have one.
You have one more?
I just want to tell you that...
I still haven't finished The One project.
Because I'm working on another project right now.
That's okay.
I'll take over.
I'll bring Mek in to help me.
You heard that, Lee?
He said he'll have Mek help him.
Loud and clear.
I guess he got the son of the resort's owner
as free gift for real!
Guys, stop it!
Let's get back to work!
Do you know that you're distracting me from work?
You need to get punished for it.
Mek, can you open the door for me?
Can you help me edit some videos?
Can I come in?
Well...
Please let me in.
What the heck is this, Mek!?
Is this a bedroom or a garbage pile?
If you're not using these, why don't you keep them away?
You're piling them up for what?
So many pieces of garbage around here!
I know.
You're complaining like a mother.
Then why don't you keep it clean so no one can complain?
What is this?
A bottle garden I made just for fun.
You want one?
I'll make one for you.
Well...
Sure, I do...
if you don't mind.
Did you wear this yet?
Yeah.
Then why didn't you put it in the basket?
The basket is just right there. Only a few steps away.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
Are you going to do that all night?
What's the work you want me to help edit?
It's my work for the student club.
I want some nice transitions.
That's why I'm asking your for help.
But you don't need to make it as fancy as those Thunderous Sky contents.
Actually, I'm not in charge of editing work.
Park takes care of it.
And Bear is in charge of filming.
I'm the performer.
You miss them, don't you?
You miss your friends,
so why don't you apologize to them?
Making up with friends isn't that hard.
It's always hard if you're the one to make the first move.
But it's not hard when it comes to pranking Tim, huh?
And you didn't even say sorry.
Not again! Not again!
You're complaining so much
you start having wrinkles now.
Do you realize that you're distracting me from work here?
Now...
You must get punished for it.
Ouch!
You should get to work!
Okay, I will.
But you need to stay here tonight
and oversee me working.
Please. Please.
You must really get the work done, okay?
Kim, you're the best!
Alright.
Work, work, work.
Here.
Here?
Or here?
Can you guys make up already?
This is annoying.
I can talk to you.
- But I don't want...
- I am sorry!
It's my fault that I ditched Thunderous Sky
and left you guys behind.
I'm sorry for doing that to you.
I'm sorry that I yelled at you
and blamed you for being emotional.
I didn't mean that.
You know I've been waiting for you to say that for so long!
I miss you so much, Bear!
My life was so dull without your annoying voice.
I also miss your fugly face too!
I've been thinking.
I don't want to do Thunderous Sky channel anymore.
I think I lost my passion for it.
One more thing...
I've come to realize that what we did on it...
is not really a good thing.
I'd like to try doing something else.
Something I've been interested in.
If you've discovered what you like, it's great, Mek.
I understand.
No matter what you do, we'll be here to support you.
Guys.
I freaking love us!
Me too.
My feelings are beyond love.
It's about time...
that Thunderous Sky has its final episode.
How are you doing with the new channel?
If you need any help, just let us know.
It's okay.
I have someone to help.
No worries.
Hello, Little Bears out there!
Now, you're watching Bear's Experiment channel!
And you're gonna love me like Rrrr!
And the content for today is...
My first ever part-time job at Taco Bell!
And Bomb will be mother bear who helps me.
Hello.
Do you have anything to say before we start, mother bear?
Little Bears, please give a lot of support to Bear.
Without further ado, let's get started!
Do you think I can make this work?
Yes, you can.
Because I'm right here with you.
So...
Can I get some additional moral support?
Okay.
Let's start.
Let's go!
Here we go!
You can fill your drinks over there.
Bomb, can you help me with this?
Hello.
- The food will be served shortly.
- Sure.
Next time, you need to add more cheese.
Is this "cheese" enough for you?
Bear!
What are you doing?
There are lots of people here.
I'm tired.
And I just need a boost.
Is that enough?
Now my energy is through the roof!
That's the end of the first episode of Bear's Experiment.
Please stay tuned for my next experiment in the next episode.
For today, Bomb and I have to say goodbye now!
Bye!
How are you feeling?
You must be tired.
Yes, I'm tired.
But...
It was so much fun!
See?
I told you. You can do it.
I guess this is why people say...
"Trust your boyfriend and you'll be doing great!"
Ouch!
I think he was flirting with you.
And if he really was,
what are you gonna do about it?
Since you found it, why don't you just go ahead and sign up?
[Contestant calls for a photography competition]
Why don't you just apply for it?
There's no need to hesitate.
I don't intend to apply for it.
I just found it by coincidence.
But since you found it,
why don't you just go ahead and sign up?
No.
Why bother if I'm not gonna win anyway?
Tim.
Mai didn't come to class today?
Right.
Usually, you two are inseparable.
I don't know.
He didn't pick up my calls.
Did you two have a fight?
What fight?
I was running errands.
Don't put us against each other.
Hey!
I was kidding.
I was just worried about you, my friend.
Whenever I saw Tim alone without you,
it feels so strange.
Right.
You guys are exaggerating.
He and I are not that inseparable.
Don't you need to go to the student club next?
Okay, see you then.
Did he just chase us away?
What are you waiting for?
Mai...
About the other day...
I...
You don't need to think too much about it.
I understand.
I won't leave you.
No matter what happens,
we'll always be friends.
That day, I didn't intend to let it happen that way.
I told you I'm okay.
There's no need to talk about it.
In fact, you can just forget it.
Because I already did.
Come on. Let's go.
Did you get all the scripts memorized?
Do you want me to repeat it for you?
It's okay.
I can remember them.
Then, let's go.
Hi there.
Tim.
Mai.
Hello, Kim.
How are you?
I should be the one who asks you that.
Are you fully recovered?
Of course, I am.
Or else I wouldn't be here.
I am truly sorry.
I'm not angry with you, Kimhan.
A misunderstanding like this can happen.
What kind of cook doesn't check his ingredients?
I am the one to blame indeed.
I am sorry for not being careful enough.
How long are you gonna keep saying sorry?
Is it his cue soon?
You can come in and stand by now.
You got a new perfume?
Mm.
Smells good.
Tim, please look at the camera this way.
5, 4, 3, record.
Hello, it's Tim here.
Usually, when I have a free time at home
I would exercise.
And...
It's something I've been doing since I was a kid...
I can also give advice on men's styling and grooming.
Yeah.
My favorite colors are green and black.
My favorite hobby is exercising.
And when it's a rest day,
I would...
read comic books.
Anyway, thank you everyone
for following Absolute Tim channel.
I'm so glad that you guys support me and...
like the contents I created this much.
We're done. Thank you so much, Tim!
Thank you.
I'm done here.
Let's go home.
So...
Can I have your LINE ID?
Pete, can you please come over on set?
I have to go now.
Who's that?
It's Pete.
He said he's an Engineering student.
We've just befriended.
It's boring waiting
so he looked for someone to talk to, I guess.
I think he was flirting with you.
And if he really was,
what are you gonna do about it?
Tim. Mai.
Would you like to join me for lunch?
I have something to talk to you.
We'll have a shoot with you tomorrow at your condo.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Why didn't I know about this?
I thought you said we were going to have lunch.
What are these two doing here?
Be nice.
I brought Tim today so you can apologize to him
about that shrimp paste cake incident.
I'm sorry for pulling a sick prank on you.
Please forgive me.
Tim was hospitalized because of you.
But you don't seem to have come to your senses.
I had no idea.
I never meant to get him hospitalized.
At least you apologized.
And I'm okay with that.
I'm actually more sorry for Kimhan.
He baked that cake with heart.
You should have known better than to do that.
I'm really sorry, man.
If I'd known that you are allergic to the paste,
I wouldn't have put it in the cake.
Anyway...
Thanks for sorting this matter out with the chancellor.
If it wasn't for you,
my friends and I would've already got suspended.
What did you say to your aunt?
I asked her to halt the BL content thing.
And you no longer wanted to do that?
Yes.
I don't want to make people feel uncomfortable.
Well, since we're all here...
I asked you two to come here,
so this meal is on me.
Cool.
It's not everyday someone treats me a meal.
Any dish you recommend?
Bro!
Huh?
Can we please have a menu?
Coming up.
What did you mean by "bro"?
It's "sis" now.
What would you guys like?
There are so many things in here that you don't eat.
Perhaps we should go to another restaurant.
I don't think this place is for those with a delicate palate.
I can eat these.
Feel free to order whatever you want.
I can eat everything.
Bro.
Mm?
I'd like some extremely spicy papaya salad
with salted crab and fermented fish.
Give me 20 chillies.
But make sure you don't put any shrimp paste in it,
or someone might end up at hospital again.
Sure. 20 chillies!
With no shrimp paste.
Here you go.
Enjoy.
I think you two already had enough.
I can do another round with a big bowl of spicy soup.
I think it's time to go.
I agree, Kim.
Go ahead and ask for the bill.
Well...
You two, go home safe.
You too.
Tomorrow we'll be filming some footages
of your lifestyle at your condo.
Of course.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Why didn't I know about this?
It's a student club's work.
I don't want to bother you.
Come on.
Let's head home.
You know you can't handle spicy food.
Why did you play along with him?
You're being so immature.
If it has any effect on you,
make sure you take care of yourself.
I know.
Who's that?
Pete.
If he really hits on you,
you need to let me know first.
Got it?
Mai.
It's none of your business.
I can make decisions for myself.
Got it?
Do you need a ride?
No, thanks.
My cab is here.
See ya.
Mek, what are you doing?
This stuff is expensive.
Go back to your seat.
Don't look.
Mek!
What are you doing?
Mek, let go of me!
Wait until he puts his shirt on.
Stop being naked
so we can start shooting.
Let go of me!
Not yet.
Why?
Let me go!
For starters,
we're going to film you jogging
as part of your morning routine.
You can just run and be your natural self.
Mek will follow you with a camera on his hands.
Sure thing.
I'll make sure you look good.
Shall we get started?
Okay.
Come on.
And action!
You're doing great, Tim.
Can you keep up, man?
I thought you said you are a runner.
Hey!
Seriously, is this all you got?
I'm running backwards
but still going faster than you.
If you fall,
don't blame it on me then.
Seriously?
What is going on?
What do you think you were doing?
None of these footages can be used.
Mek...
I'm here to work, not to mess around.
Tim...
I think we'll probably need a reshoot.
But first, let me see if there's anything I can do with these footages.
Sure, Kim.
Just let me know if you need me.
For you, I'm always available.
I gotta go now.
Do you need a ride?
Don't, Tim.
I can take care of that.
You should at least catch your breath first
before talking big.
What a prick!
Don't worry, both of you.
I can get home on my own.
What?
Let me give you a ride, Kim.
You two should stay here
and enjoy each other's company.
This is all because of you.
You're the reason why he's mad at me.
It's all because you suck at filming.
You screwed up his work.
That's why he got upset
and didn't let me give him a ride.
Why would you want to do that?
Kim is mine.
I liked him first.
He's already got me.
I don't think you're too dumb to see that.
Are you two in a relationship or what?
Not yet.
But it's none of your business.
You act like you own him.
Maybe don't get too ahead of yourself
if you and him are not official yet.
And why does that concern you?
What are you trying to do
by doing all these competitions with me?
Are you really into Kim
or just trying to take him as a win against me?
You can't say you're into him, though,
or I'll punch you in the face!
I'm tired.
Excuse me.
What's the deal with this guy?
Why are you here?
Of course I'm here to show you the draft.
I filmed for you
and even edited it for you.
The mood in it is so good.
I'm sorry for making you upset today.
I'm not going to act like a child again.
But if you ever want me to...
I promise I'll be a good boy for you.
You're finally smiling.
Well then...
What do you say if I take this upstairs
so you can review it there?
You're doing this again.
Don't give me that look.
You, too. You stared so longingly at Tim today, remember?
Now, what do you think I should do with this little bad boy?
What do you think?
What do you think, huh?
Mek!
This bad boy must get a kiss.
Where are you going?
Not yet!
Mek!
Enough!
Hey, hey, hey.
[Pam: Hey, you. I've arrived in Thailand. Wanna meet up?]
I love you.
Who did you say that to?
My boyfriend.
Are you free today?
I'd like to ask you to join me.
To do what?
Something that will bring us closer.
I don't think you're good at anything besides planting trees.
Speaking of which, it'd be great if I could get a plant to put on my work desk.
Just take the bottle garden from my room.
Oh, Kim!
I gotta go.
Why do you always make me worried?
You know, you're so good at playing with my heart.