The people, places, organizations, events,
groups and professionals
depicted in this program are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
Viewer discretion is advised.
I came up with a small business plan.
No one would want to buy a cheesy t-shirt like that!
We need something else to attract people.
He just follows the script.
You remember Fluke?
My classmate at school.
Oh yes, I remember.
Ever since you two got together,
seems like all your skills have been transferred to Park.
Tim-Kim seems like a good match too.
I have invited one of your friends
to collaborate with our channel.
Why do you look so serious?
What are you doing?
I'm planning for the shoot we're having this week.
Ah!
With Tim, your sweetheart?
You like it, don't you?
A collaboration with Tim.
Awwww.
When will you stop irritating me?
I'm tired.
Every time I meet you, you never fail to irritate me.
I don't like when someone does that to me.
Because I can't fight with them.
I don't like being a loser. You get it?
Why did you get serious all of a sudden?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to irritate you.
This is just how I am.
Take it easy.
Really, I just want to talk to you.
You're serious all the time.
Don't you get tired?
I'm not that serious.
Are you for real?
Anyway,
Why is it so important
for you to be the head of the student club?
You work for the club all the time.
It's part of my life plan.
I think...
It'll push me to great success in the future.
What do you mean by success?
To have a great job,
have lots of money,
and build a family in the way that I want.
Something like that.
What about you?
Do you have any plans for the future?
I'm not the type to plan things ahead.
But if you ask me now...
I say it's doing something people accept.
Like the Thunderous Sky channel?
Yeah, like that.
If possible,
I also want to do something that
expresses my feelings.
Because sometimes I'm too shy
to say things outright.
Why do you think it's not possible?
I don't know.
Maybe I'm kind of indecisive.
Whenever I have to make a decision,
I always find it hard to do.
So I just let life takes me wherever it goes
never really have a plan.
I'll just make the decisions right at the spot.
I think I understand that.
We're fine with making trivial decisions.
But when it's about something serious,
there are always hundreds of things to be considered.
Right?
Even a well-planned person like you got this issue too.
Let alone someone like me.
Something like this takes time.
I think when you get into details with anything,
that means you care about it.
And when that happens,
you'll realize that you're on the right track.
Is this a 'Wise Words with Kim' segment?
Are you going to keep working for long?
I'm not sure.
What I meant to say is
I can wait.
We can go home together,
so you don't have to pay for the fare.
But I still have a lot to work on.
It's okay.
I can get some sleep while you finish it.
[FLUKE
Chatchawal]
[EARTH
Teerapat]
[BEW
Sitthikarn]
[DANIEL
Cheng Yu Chang]
[BOAT
Yongyut]
[KENJI
Siwarut]
[POR
Passakorn]
[YUT
Kritsadayut]
[Directed by
NATTHAMON YIMYAM]
[Hearts get flustered]
Hello, everyone!
It's Tim here.
I'm gonna take over Mek-Kim program for a day.
I'm going to do help mix & match the uniforms
for our university's hottest BL couple, Kimhan and Mek.
How's it going to be? Let's check it out!
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Kim, you need to be professional.
All the people around here already know
that you like Tim.
You're grinning from ear to ear.
Grinning my ass!
Stop irritating me.
He made a great speech,
so I needed to listen carefully.
Stop arguing.
You guys should go get changed.
Let's wrap this up early
so I can finish editing on time.
I've never worn something like this.
I think you should roll up your sleeves a bit.
Here, let me help you.
I'll do it.
Park, look at Mek.
What is wrong with him?
He's looking daggers at Tim all the time.
He's jealous, I guess.
What!?
You should go back to work.
Here, let me roll up the sleeves for you.
Yuck!
Hey!
Why did you have to mock him?
He was just being helpful.
He's helpful because he wants something.
I saw it
and I didn't like it.
It's annoying, you know?
No, I don't.
Forget it.
I want to finish this asap.
Okay, let's shoot!
Let me adjust the outfit for you.
Thank you.
Lee, how many sets do we have left?
I think I'm not in the mood for a shoot anymore.
The atmosphere around here is bad.
This is the last one.
Mek, what's wrong with you today?
You've been acting weird.
Don't ask too much, otherwise I'll be even more pissed.
Just wrap this up real quick, okay?
I want to go home.
What the heck?
I was just asking nicely.
Why so mad?
Don't mind him.
Let's just continue.
Kimhan,
Are you going anywhere after this?
Would you like to grab a meal with me?
You guys can come with us too.
No.
I'm not hungry.
In fact, I kinda want to throw up!
I'm so sorry.
I'm just too tired.
Let's go next time maybe.
Sure.
So this means...
You owe me one meal, alright?
Next time you must come.
Important matters like this never slip my mind.
Okay.
Now please excuse me. I'm going home.
Bye-bye.
Guys,
I'm going home now.
See you.
Are you heading right home?
Or you want to eat something first?
Nah, I'll just head back to my place.
I'm not really hungry anyway.
Why did you invite him to dine with you then?
You've already been with him all day.
Isn't that enough, Tim?
I just want to extend the time with him.
You seem flustered every time you talk about him.
Right.
Is it because I like Kim?
If I do, what do you think?
You think he passes your standard?
Of course, I'm okay with him.
No matter who you like or what you like,
I'm all okay.
Wow!
That's good to hear, Mai!
Park!
I'm so confused about Mek today.
What's wrong with him?
One minute he raised his voice.
The next minute he got sarcastic.
His mood swings even worse than the crypto currency.
I'm sure it's nothing.
I think he was just being hysterical as always.
Is this because..
he's so into the role he's playing
that he gets jealous with Kim?
Stop thinking about it.
He'll be back to normal soon.
Perhaps it's just me having bad luck today.
He just snapped at me out of nowhere.
Speaking of which,
I haven't checked my daily horoscope yet.
Let's have a look!
See? It's true!
They said I might be in a discord with friends.
It's Mek for sure!
Park, what day is your birthday?
Saturday.
Things are looking promising for you
in terms of work and finance.
However...
If you're dating someone,
you must beware of the third wheel.
and the seven-year itch.
It might get so bad that you two end up calling it quits.
How was that?
Is it accurate?
I don't know.
It might be.
Is this reliable?
Some part it might.
Do you believe it?
Stuff like this is up to individual discretion.
Anyway...
What about the number you put after your name on LINE?
101. What's that?
Are you joining a survival show in Korea?
Ah!
It's a number a fortune teller gave me.
It's sort of a lucky number.
It's just a silly thing I do.
And you said you didn't believe it.
Oh, hi, Bear.
Hi, Bomb!
What a coincidence!
You said you had a part-time job.
It's here?
Why didn I never meet you here before?
I eat here quite often.
I've just transferred to this branch.
Good then.
Now I can ask you for some extra sauce.
You can normally ask for extra sauce.
I was just kidding.
Oops, I didn't see the long lineup.
I'll get...
one Double Taco Supreme combo set.
Eat here, right?
Yes.
Would you like to change from cheese to fries?
No, thanks.
It's 199 baht in total.
Are you taking a break?
Yes.
When will you finish your shift?
I finish my shift around midnight.
But I'll have to clean up until around 1am.
How can do find time to do your assignments
or watch series then?
I can still manage my time to study.
But for series,
I haven't watched them much.
I only watch Thunderous Sky channel.
That's so nice of you, Hailstone!
I'm dying to go back to work on my channel.
But Mek is not up for it yet.
I guess now we need to focus on BL content.
Do you always come here alone?
Yes, I always come alone.
Why don't you invite anyone else to come with?
Eating alone is lonely.
You should bring your friends with you.
Mek and Park never come around this neighborhood.
Also, their places are on the other side of town.
Then...
Why don't you bring your date along with you?
My date?
I don't have one.
What about...
someone you have a crush on?
Do you have one yet?
Well...
There's someone.
But I don't really know who that person is.
I just know that the person is one of my fans.
But I'm certain that I'm his bias.
I've been trying to find him.
But I still don't know who he is.
He always gives me words of encouragement.
So I'd like to meet him for once.
I think I talked too much now.
Well...
Please don't tell anyone about this.
I won't tell anyone.
What a lucky person he is.
Excuse me.
I need to get back to work now.
Enjoy your meal.
Okay.
Cheer up!
What's wrong with you today?
You're in a bad mood all day.
Nothing.
What more do you want me to say?
You don't have to care about me.
Oh, I know!
You must be angry because you're hungry for sure!
When Tim invited us to have a meal,
you should've said yes.
You didn't have to keep it cool.
I don't want to go with him.
If I do, I'd have to eat fancy stuff rich people eat.
Like what they have at those Omakase restaurants.
Each bite is so small.
I'll never be full.
He wouldn't invite us to a fancy place like that.
So this is why you're in the bad mood?
No, it's not about that.
Nonsense.
Come in.
Come.
So...
Can you be my personal chef from now on?
Hope you're not fully booked yet.
I'm still available.
Feel free to book.
I only have instant noodles.
Are you okay with that?
Mm.
I haven't got much time these days
with the whole content creating thing going on.
Not to mention student club's works on the side.
That's why I no longer have time to buy groceries.
But don't worry.
I can assure you that this bowl of noodles
will definitely satiate your hunger.
Do you need my help?
It's fine.
Just sit tight over there, okay?
The food will be served right in front of you.
Here's Michelin star stir-fried noodles by Chef Kim.
Looks so yummy!
Well...
Let's dig in!
It's so good that you're putting real chefs in shame!
Maybe you were just starving.
Anything would be delicious for you.
I'm being honest here,
but you don't believe me.
I really meant it.
You cook so well.
Where did you practice it?
I'm sure I'm not that good.
I live alone with my sister.
And she's a fussy eater.
I want to make sure that she has good meals
so I do a lot of cooking.
I guess I got to practice along the way.
How lucky I am!
I don't need to line up at restaurants anymore
now that I have Chef Kim living next door.
So...
Can you be my personal chef from now on?
Hope you're not fully booked yet.
I'm still available.
Feel free to book.
OMG, guys!
Our Mek-Kim ship is now saling off-screen!
And it's sailing hard!
For people born on Saturdays...
Things are looking promising in terms of career and money.
However...
Those who are in a relationship
should beware of a third person
and the seven-year itch.
Some couples might even end up separating.
Babe.
Who are you texting?
I'm texting Kimhan.
It's just Kim...
Why are you looking so happy?
This is how I normally react.
It's nothing, Park.
[Would you take it?]
Some couples might suffer the seven-year itch real hard and end up separating.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Just editing some videos.
Are you okay?
You look a bit tired.
Here.
I'll give you a massage.
Woah!
What are those things in the bags?
Yesterday you said you didn't have time to buy groceries and only had instant noodles.
Don't tell me that...
you woke up early to get all these?
Well, yeah.
See?
I bought a lot of things.
Pork, duck, chicken, freshwater fish, sea fish
root veggies, leafy veggies, fruits.
Everything in one go!
Are you a grocery truck or something?
A lot of things indeed.
Here, I'll put them into the fridge.
I already bought these for you.
You have to cook something for me.
My life depends on you now, Chef Kim.
Alright.
What do you want for a meal, sir?
Anything is fine.
Steamed whole fish with spicy soup
or maybe a little bit of Tom Yum.
I like them all!
Enough!
I already know you're a funny guy.
Here, let me help you.
Make sure that Dao get to eat these too.
Don't finish them all by yourself.
Roger that.
Give it to me.
Seems like you've become way too immersed in your role.
Nonsense.
It's just for content.
Kritsada Pakdi.
Where should I start?
Facebook then.
That should be the easiest way.
[Kritsada Pakdi]
What's up?
Storms are coming today!
It's been so long since our last live chat with the Hailstones.
Let's do that again, shall we?
I'm sure the Hailstones are looking forward to seeing us.
Finally!
Mek of Thunderous Sky is making a comeback?
Hell yeah!
By the way...
Since we've been gone for so long
Do you think we should dress up for a little bit?
Let's do a live chat like the Gentlemen of Juthathep.
What are you saying?
Don't you know...
their sequel is already in the works!
I'll take the role of James Ji's son, okay?
Get the announcement ready.
Thunderous Sky is going live at 6pm.
BAAM!
You got it, man!
Well...
I'll be James Ma's son then.
Caution:
Hailstones, are you ready?
Today at 6pm,
see you in a live chat!
Storms are coming.
BAAM!
Wow!
My baby.
I can't believe how much you've grown.
Keep growing, okay?
Daddy will take good care of you.
Well, well.
Is this plant called Kimhan or something?
You're taking such a good care of it.
Seems like you've become way too immersed in your role.
Nonsense.
It's just for content.
When you work on something
you should do it with passion, no?
Alright, I see.
You went to the market at 5 in the morning.
That's a surprise coming from a late, late bird like you.
It's nothing.
He cooked for me,
so I returned the favor by buying those groceries.
Your brother is a good person.
Have you ever thought about that?
Alright, alright, good guy.
By the way...
As the head of the fandom,
do you have any suggestion of what else we should do?
You already have a ship name.
You've already held an event together.
You've already launched merchandise.
How about a Q&A session?
Have you done that?
Not yet.
But it sounds interesting.
Got it, Captain!
I'm gonna go make that content right away.
Don't be confused.
People are eager for new content
and I just want us to stay active.
Up to you then.
Hi, guys.
This is Mek.
Hi. It's me, Kimhan.
Today, Mek and I are going to do a Q&A session with you guys.
We've read your comments.
Lots of you were asking me and this guy
to answer your questions.
Kim, are you ready?
Let's do this!
Is it true that Kim didn't like the content on Mek's Thunderous Sky channel at first?
Please go easy on this one.
Well...
It's true.
You're so cruel.
I mean...
That video did get people in trouble for real.
But...
Mek is not that kind of person anymore.
That's right.
Right now...
I like doing this better.
Mek...
What is your favorite Kim's dish?
Also, I love his fried eggs.
Even though it's just an ordinary dish, it tastes so good!
Fried eggs?
I didn't do anything special.
I just fried them.
Mek is exaggerating again!
Is Kim's sister the admin of Mek-Kim fanbase?
I saw the photos on her IG.
Yes, she is.
Damn it, Mek, why aren't you picking up my calls?
Did you forget?
Then why would you make that appointment with me?!
Jeez.
I got tricked.
You bastard.
You stood me up
and you're embarrassing me.
How come you and your sister
don't look alike at all?
I guess my sister inherited both of our parents' genes.
Meanwhile, I look like my mother.
Actually, Q's father is my stepdad.
My biological father...
is now in heaven.
As a matter of fact, there are some perks of haveing a stepfather.
Whenever we go out for a meal
I never have to spend a dime.
What?
Because...
My stepdad always "steps" up and pays for me.
Is it funny?
Alright, let's call it a day.
I think next time we should run a poll
on whether Kim should keep making jokes or not.
See you guys next time.
Bye-bye.
Are you okay with that mention about your father earlier?
I'm okay.
I used to get sad when someone asked me about him.
But I've come to terms with it.
Here, let me give you a hug
to celebrate your strengths
and also your audacity to pull off that joke.
But we've already turned off the live.
I don't think that's necessary.
I'm hugging you because I want to,
not for the sake of content.
Kim,
you don't have to wake up early for class tomorrow.
Why not?
But traffic is bad in the morning.
What I meant to say is
I want you to go to the campus with me.
Sure.
I'll see you then.
They're sweet, aren't they?
Indeed, they are.
The first signs of cheating:
1. Overprotection of his phone
2. Avoidance of eye contact during conversations
Babe.
Who are you texting?
I'm texting Kimhan.
The rice is too soft, don't you think?
Yes, it is.
3. A lack of conversations and inputs
4. Secretive texting when you're not looking
Just like what the tips say.
It's all of the above.
Spot-on!
"Seriously, I get flustered every time Tim and Kim get together."
"I've already replayed that shot three times."
"They made me smile so wide my cheeks hurt!"
The audacity.
I'm gonna block you all.
These people must be blocked!
"They're so cute together.
Mek-Kim, OTP of the Year."
Thank...
you...
...so much.
Love you.
XX
The OTP of the Year award...
Here we come!
Mek-Kim so cute!
They got so many likes for this video.
Someone says...
they already watched it three times
but still can't get enough.
They're going for a fourth rewatch!
I think you've watched it more times than the channel owner has.
Not yet.
But it's possible.
The views are still going up.
Hey...
What do you think if I start making BL contents?
Are you being serious?
With whom?
Look at you.
You hardly have any friends.
I know.
I think I can do it.
We love Mek-Kim.
Thank you all so much.
We love you too.
Don't forget to eat something
before you go to class.
You always care for your fans.
You, too.
Don't forget to grab something to eat.
Don't worry.
I've already had breakfast.
With Kim, actually.
We had a great meal!
Indeed, we did.
By the way,
I think it's time you guys headed to class,
or you'll be late for attendance check.
Let's go.
Kim,
keep it up!
What's up, my fellow Thunderous Sky people?
How are you guys this morning?
Park,
Are you okay?
You look a little blue.
How can he be blue?
He's not a smurf!
It's nothing.
I guess I'm just tired.
I'll be fine soon.
It's not fine.
You're my friend.
What's the matter?
Tell me.
You can share it with me.
He said he's fine.
Stop bugging him.
It's still morning.
Why are you sitting here looking depressed?
You have to feel good!
What would you know?
You're too busy enjoying that BL fame.
Come on, Bear.
I only stood you up a little
and now you're mad at me?
When are you going to stop being so sulky?
Look at yourself!
Please stop fighting.
I beg you.
Go feeling good somewhere else.
You're annoying me.
Sure.
You said it yourself.
Fine. Up to you.
Are you okay?
Hi there, Kim.
Hi, Tim.
What a coincidence.
I suppose you've already watched our collab video.
Do you like it?
Yes, I have.
Honestly, it felt a bit weird modeling.
Fashion shoots are not really my thing.
Why would you feel weird?
I think you did a great job.
Maybe partly because we enjoyed ourselves during the shoot.
That's why it came out great.
Also, you don't look awkward at all.
It was fun indeed.
So that means...
If I ask you to join me for future collabs on my channel,
you'd be happy to come, right?
Of course.
I'd love to.
Then...
If I ask you
to make BL content with me
you'd also be happy to, right?
What did you say?
Kimhan, I want you...
to be my BL partner.
Doesn't that mean you're going to get sacked?
How did it come to this?
I have a new pranking idea!
So you're coming back to make prank content on our channel?
Let's do a prank on Kim!
You're abusing your power for personal gain.
You know me.
What I want
I get.
I decorated this chocolate cake with orange slices
to add a sense of refreshment.
For the cake texture...
I opted for fudge...
Tim!
No matter what excuse you make,
it doesn't change the fact that you did wrong.