The people, places, organizations, events,
groups and professionals
depicted in this program are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
Viewer discretion is advised.
My name is Kritsada Bhakdi.
Finally, I found you.
Kritsada Bhakdi.
I have a new prank idea.
This time we'll do a prank on Tim!
If you still want to enjoy your BL fame,
it's up to you.
And now you can get out of my room!
Tim, it's time for you to get the taste of
Shrimp Paste Goddess.
It's decorated with orange to add a sense of refreshment...
Tim!
Mek changed it. He said you said
the other one can't be used.
I'm sorry. That was not at all my intention.
I didn't know he's allergic to shrimp paste.
I suppose this bad habit of yours cannot be cured.
In the end, all you do is make rubbish content.
He'd already apologized and you still said that to him.
Dao!
The situation is concerning around here.
It's almost noon and Kim hasn't come out of his room yet.
He never makes me miss breakfast ever.
Same here, Q.
Mek was driving like we were in Fast & Furious.
I thought I was in Dominic Toretto's car.
Seriously, I was so nervous all the way.
We can't just let this go on.
How about you send me your location real quick?
I'll bring Kim there asap.
Sure, Captain Q! I'll do it!
Okay, Captain Dao!
Here.
Kim.
Are you awake?
Yes. What's up?
Here's the thing.
You seem to be in such a bad mood lately.
I think you should go relax somewhere.
Relax where?
Like...we go chill somewhere nice.
Enjoy some good vibes.
So you can feel better.
Look at you now.
So blue.
No. I don't want to go.
Then, I'm using our brother-sister trip quota now!
If you refuse, I'll be mad at you for real!
I just don't want to go.
I don't care! You need to pack now because we'll leave in 15 minutes.
Okay? Deal.
[FLUK
Chatchawal]
[EARTH
Teerapat]
[BEW
Sitthikarn]
[DANIEL
Cheng Yu Chang]
[BOAT
Yongyut]
[KENJI
Siwarut]
[POR
Passakorn]
[YUT
Kritsadayut]
[Directed by
NATTHAMON YIMYAM]
[It's the night to remember.]
Hi, mom.
How are you?
I'm okay now.
I'm back at my condo.
Did Mai tell you about this?
You talk to Mai a lot more than to your own son now, huh?
Stop changing the subject.
If it wasn't for Mai,
I would never know what you're up to.
That's a good point.
How am I supposed to live without Mai?
Don't say that.
Just take good care of yourself.
And take the pills too.
Do you want me to come visit?
You don't need to come.
I'll just rest for a few days and then I'll get better.
You don't have to worry.
I have your beloved son to take care of me.
He's not gonna leave me alone.
Get some rest then.
I love you, son.
Love you too, mom.
[I'm sorry for not being careful enough.]
[Please get some rest and get well soon.]
[I'll be here to support you.]
You're smiling from ear to ear.
Have this so you can feel better.
It helps nourish your health,
so you won't feel weary.
It's not bitter, trust me.
It's delicious.
It does taste good.
Very sweet.
Not as sweet as Kimhan's flowers, I suppose.
Are you going to tease me about this forever?
So what?
Am I not allowed tease you about your beloved Kimhan!?
He's the one who got you sick.
Will you stay away from him?
It was an accident.
He wasn't trying to poison me.
But you almost died.
Maybe...
Next time...
I'll take an anti-allergy pill first.
So you're not afraid of dying?
No, I''m not.
Because I have you by my side.
Then you should try to imagine
the day when I'm not here anymore.
Why did you say that?
Where are you going?
I won't let you go anywhere.
You don't leave me, okay?
Don't touch me.
Otherwise, I'll feed you with shrimp chilli paste again.
I can eat that.
With you here, I can eat anything.
Look who's here!
We miss you!
How was your drive? Are you guys tired?
Not at all.
But I'm so tired.
I kept only thinking if I'd make it here or not!
- Why?
- Because Mek was driving so fast.
Mek, why would you drive like that?
He probable missed me so much.
I'm glad I didn't have to ask him to come for my birthday this year.
It's not like that.
I just ran out of money.
This kid!
Of course, I miss you! That's why I'm here.
Since it's your birthday,
we should all be here together.
That feels much better!
But if you really run out of money,
just call mom.
And you'll get the money transferred right away.
With me, whenever I ask her for money,
she'd complain all day long!
None of you are better than the other.
Let's get inside.
Sure.
Here you go.
Looks yummy, huh?
How is it?
Do you like it?
Is it that good?
It's the best, mom!
Dad, how's business?
Lots of customers recently?
This season? Not really.
So your mother and I get to relax a bit.
Now you have us as your VIP guests.
You're not going to get bored anymore.
Enough already!
It's his birthday. Just let him rest.
It's okay. I can handle it.
Of course, you're my VIP guests.
Anyway, since today is dad's birthday,
did you prepare any present for him, mom?
We've been together for so long.
I guess a present is no longer necessary.
Right, honey?
Yes.
With you here with me, it's like I've already got a gift.
Since I've been with you all my life,
I guess you don't need this anymore, do you?
Wow, you have a gift for me?
This is such a surprise.
Thank you so much.
So...
I suppose now you you'll need to make us dinner
in exchange with the gift.
Am I right, Mek?
Sure, I can.
Just tell me what you want to eat
and I'll make it for you.
Since we're here,
it can't be anything other than Moo Krata,
the famous specialty of this resort!
Exactly!
I'd love to have some tender pork.
But I think, since we're not together often,
shouldn't we go out and have some fancy food instead?
Moo Krata is fine.
It's nice weather around here.
Nothing can beat some nice grilled pork.
Yes.
For me, Moo Krata here is the best.
Let me check your gift first
and see whether it's worth it or not
Let me see.
Wow!
Okay, let's have it!
[Where are you? Why didn't you come back?
Let's talk. Babe, don't be like this.]
Park!
Pick up the call!
I can't work like this!
It's just one of those call center frauds.
I don't want to take it.
Why didn't you just tell me?
So I could take it
and spook them back.
I saw this in the news.
People lost a lot of money because of them.
Don't you ever fall for their tricks!
So you're really not going to tell me what happened?
You're looking like vegetables in a pot right now.
I'm okay.
Don't lie to me, Park!
I may be dumb
but I can tell that something is troubling you.
Let me guess.
You...
You lost your money because of the lottery, right?
Yeah.
You're indeed a fool.
It's okay, my friend.
You know what they say.
Whenever we fall,
it's because we stumbled.
Bear, can you just leave the room?
I want to be alone.
Alright, I'm sorry.
I won't bother you then.
We have guests.
Let's go to the reception.
Oh, Q, Kimhan.
How come you are here!?
Dao, you stay here as well?
What a coincidence!
Hey.
Are you free today?
I need your help on something.
I'll take a break in half an hour. Can you wait?
Sure.
What do you need me to help you with?
Since you're a big fan of mine,
I'd like to appoint you as a honorary consultant
for my new channel!
What?
Just like that?
It's like you're forcing me to take it.
I don't think so.
It's the right time and the right person.
So...
What exactly do you need from this consultant?
It's the same old problem.
I don't know what kind of content I should make.
I've thought about it days and nights but couldn't come up with any idea.
Can you help me on this, Bomb?
Please, please, please.
Alright.
Can you write down all the things you want to do?
And I'll help you after that.
The problem is...
I don't know where to start.
I have to admit
all this time I only followed Mek's lead.
I want to be like him.
But when I finally do it on my own,
I don't really know what kind of content suits me.
You should start with being yourself then.
Stop thinking too much
and try to keep your chin up.
It's that simple. You can do it.
You got me right here to help you.
Okay?
Okay!
Let's start then.
Let's write it down.
How about this one?
Let's go.
- Hang on for sec.
- Follow me!
Welcome.
Hello.
Do you have a reservation?
Yes, we do. The name is Q.
Let me text my friend a bit.
Sure.
Mek.
We have guests. Let's go to the reception.
Q, Kimhan!
How come you are here!?
Dao! Didn't know you stay here as well.
Such a coincidence.
Actually, my parents own this place.
I told you before, remember?
What a coincidence!
Q...
You can drop your act.
You can't fool me.
You know you're so bad at pretending.
Don't ever tell anyone that you're my sister.
Dao, Mek, are they your friends?
They are Q and Kimhan.
The siblings who moved to Auntie Yupa's house next door.
- Hello again.
- Nice to meet you.
Now I remember. You told me that...
a new guy next door
often cooks good food for you.
Yes!
It's good then that you two come here
so now I can return the favor
after you fed my kids with lots of good food.
When you say "fed",
it sounded like he was feeding dogs and cats.
Are you talking about Mek?
Watch your mouth!
I'm talking about both of you.
Come on, dad!
Your friends must be tired after a long drive.
Mek, can you help carry their luggage
and show them to their room?
And this evening, don't forget to come...
have Moo Krata with us.
It's on me!
I'm sure you're going to love it!
Sure, sir, we'll come.
Here's the key.
Alright, then...
Mek, you bring Kimhan to the room.
Q, let's go take some pictures over there.
The light here is perfect.
Okay.
Now that you're here, you should talk.
Q!
It's okay. I can take them.
There're a lot of mosquitos here.
I'll bring you mosquito repellents.
Thank you.
Also...
over there is the pathway to the dining room.
And if you want to take a walk,
there's a creek there.
I think you'll like it.
Mm.
So...
If you need anything...
Well...
You can call room service.
Or you can just tell me.
But...
If you don't want to talk to me
you can just text me.
Why didn't you say anything, Kim?
Kim!
Let's go ride a bike!
We should get some air.
The weather is so nice!
One second.
I'm unpacking.
Just come out. Hurry!
What took you so long?
It's all your stuff!
You're such a mastermind!
I just don't want you to be upset at home.
So...
Have you two made up?
You're so nosy!
Okay.
Once you finish with this,
you can follow me.
I'll wait outside.
Alright, Miss Q.
Bye. Hurry up.
Kim, come on.
Yeah.
Hurry up!
I'll ride with Mek then.
Why are you like this?
You know you're not small!
And you have your own bicycle.
Stop complaining and just go.
Last time I checked,
you're not so good with bicycles.
Let me.
I know. That's why I brought you with me.
You don't have any plan in mind, do you?
- No!
Nothing at all.
Let's go.
The weather is good now.
We should be going before it gets too hot.
Go, go, go.
Let's follow them.
Yay! I got this.
Oh, it's tilting.
It's so nice out here!
Yeah, it's beautiful.
Hurry up!
Coming.
It's been so long since we went on a trip.
Mm.
When mom and dad come back,
we should go on a trip again.
Mm.
I'd like to go with all of us together.
Q, let's go take some pictures.
Sure, let's go.
I'll go with her and be right back.
Would you like a picture here too?
I can take it for you.
You're on a holiday, remember?
I guess a smile wouldn't hurt.
It's cuter that way.
Ready?
1, 2, 3!
3!
3! 3! 3!
Enough!
- I'm sorry!
- I'm sorry again!
I think the fact that you can't do things,
is your selling point.
How?
You're such a dumbass.
I've come to realize that I shouldn't prank people just because...
Are you trying to make up with me?
Mm.
I was too harsh with you.
And I felt bad for it.
I guess you felt sorry too.
It's okay.
I deserved that.
I really did Tim wrong.
Thank you anyway
for thinking of me.
But I really want you to know, Kim,
that I never meant for it to happen that way.
I really should have known better.
But now...
I've realized...
that I shouldn't play a prank on someone
just because...
I think I've ranted enough.
Should we get back?
Where are the two little monsters?
Over there.
Mission complete!
Bye-bye!
I knew it.
You can ride with me.
Woah!
Mek!
Be careful.
Don't swerve.
I happened to take a photo of you.
I got my film developed and thought it looked nice.
So I'd like to give it to you.
It looks nice indeed.
Thank you.
I'm Lee, by the way.
Grade 10 Class 1.
I'm Park.
I study right next to your class.
Can I touch...
...your camera?
Sure.
Taking photos is your thing?
Yeah.
It's the thing I love doing the most now.
I've never figured out what my calling is.
Can I also take a look at the other photos?
Woah.
These are beautiful.
Would you like to try taking photos?
I can teach you.
Well, if you don't mind.
Not at all.
I'm happy to.
Now I'll have someone to keep my company
when I go out taking photos.
Cool then.
Here.
You don't need to reply.
Just make sure you watch this video.
Please don't misunderstand me.
I tried to explain it to you
but you wouldn't let me.
You didn't pick up my calls.
And you didn't come home.
Do you know that you screwed up my plan big time?
Who are you texting?
I'm texting Kimhan.
I bought a gift to surprise you.
But you dared to forget our 7th anniversary!
Park!
You think I'm a fool?!
Did you get hurt?
I'm so sorry.
Here you go.
I suppose this is a gift for your boyfriend?
Yes.
It's my 7th anniversary gift for him.
You said you'd always remember.
Once you get back,
I'm gonna teach you a big lesson!
Be prepared to suffer!
Your gift is waitng.
Won't you come back for it?
If you're curious to know what's inside,
you need to come back and open it yourself.
You dummy!
If you don't come back by this evening,
I'll break up with you for real.
Bear.
You did nothing but sleep.
How are you going to get any work done with that?
Where's your list of ideas?
Show me.
Baking.
Skateboarding.
Styling outfits.
Drawing.
Knitting.
In parentheses...
I don't freaking know how to it!
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
I just thought it was cute.
You don't have to sweet-talk me.
I know I'm such a loser.
I'm not good at anything.
I think...
I'm never gonna make it with my channel.
I was acting all tough and braggy in front of Mek.
But now...
Seems like I won't be able to deliver what I promised.
Bro.
Don't say that.
I think the fact that you're not good at anything
is actually your selling point.
How?
I think comedy content will suit you.
And most importantly...
You're such a dumbass!
Wait a minute.
Are you trying to insult me now?
No, not at all.
What I meant to say is...
The fact that you're a dumb, no-filter kind of guy
is good.
That's the reason why I like you.
As a fan, obviously.
So...
What's the next step?
Well...
You can go ahead and do everything you wrote down in here.
It's okay if you're not good at it.
Even just a thought of you cooking...
...is already hilarious.
You don't need to be good at it.
Just show the world how you suck at it.
And you should name your channel
with something that truly represents you.
Something that tells your viewers that
you are a representative of people who have no talent
but tries to do a variety of things along with them.
And then...
Your viewers will feel that they can relate to you
and identify with your personality.
Now, do you get a picture of what I said?
You seem to know me even better than I know myself.
I'm sorry
that you have to be a fan of someone like me.
What I do is not nearly enough compared to what
you've been doing for me.
What's worse is I even asked you to come up for content ideas for me.
Truly...
I'm such a loser.
You probably think that it sucks to be you.
And that there's nothing good about it.
But for me...
who gets tired of life every day...
Sometimes seeing people like you having fun,
living freely
and doing something stupid
gives me energy to go on.
You make my dull days brighter
and full of laughter.
Being your fan brings me so much joy.
Actually,
I should be the one to thank you...
Thank you, my dear fan.
What do you say if I promote you my boyfriend instead?
Can a BL couple turn into a real couple?
And you don't care about the gift at all?
It's not important anymore.
Now, all I care about is you.
How is it? Do you enjoy the meal?
It's so good just like Dao used to say.
Then, you should eat some more.
Thanks, ma'am.
By the way, what's your relation with Yupa?
We're her nephew and niece.
We've moved in to the house for a while.
So it's just the two of you there?
Yes. Our mom and dad open a restaurant overseas.
They come back here from time to time.
Mom, you see,
Kim and Q stay together just them two.
But Kim takes a really good care of Q.
Their house is squaky clean.
Mek, you should do the same!
Enough! Just eat.
So you can stop talking.
Son, don't tease your sister.
I think you look familiar, Kim.
Are you the one making BL content with Mek?
Yes, he is!
This is him.
Doesn't this mean that you two...
are quite close?
Yes, sort of.
You know, I still want that official Mek-Kim t-shirt for myself.
Do you have some left?
Do we?
Let me tell you something.
Your mom...
She increases views for your content every day.
She tells everybody, "This is my son."
She always shows it around.
By the way...
Can a BL couple turn into a real couple?
Right. I'm curious.
Don't be shy.
Your mom and I can handle it.
We don't mind at all,
if you really love each other.
When people campaign for equal marriage
I always support them by helping spread the word.
That's really cool.
For now, I'll just be a shipper then.
But if you decide to become a real couple,
please make sure that we are the first to know.
Well, well, well.
I guess it'll be real soon.
I know, right?
- Stop talking. Just eat.
- Thanks.
Finally, you came home, dummy.
You ruined my surprise plan.
How are you gonna fix that?
Wait.
What's wrong with you?
This is how I fix it.
After ruining your plan.
And you don't care about the gift at all?
It's not important anymore.
Now...
All I care about is you.
You know...
When I got you wrong,
thinking you had an affair,
I was devastated.
I thought...
I was gonna lose you.
How could I do that to you?
You are my happiness.
And I can't live without my happiness.
So...
What are you gonna do to me
now that I come back?
Hello. What's up?
Today?
Yeah, sure.
Same place?
Okay, see you.
Who's that?
It's Mangkang.
He invited me to dinner at Thonglor.
Haven't seen him for a while so I thought I'll go.
Can you just not go?
I'm feeling better now but...
I don't want to be alone.
Don't you say that.
Keep that for someone else.
No.
Please don't go.
I'll tell Mangkang for you
that you'll hang out with me.
He won't mind, believe me.
Tim!
Let me live my life.
Whenver you want to go anywhere or do anything,
I never forbid you.
Do I need to stick with you forever?
Why do you have to be mad at me?
I was just kidding.
Why do you have to be so upset?
Mai.
Don't leave it like this.
You can tell me everything.
We can talk to each other about everything, no?
Then, I suppose I can talk to you about this.
About how I think you always take me for granted.
Are you really sure we can have this conversation?
What do you mean by that?
I don't get it.
You know what...
I'm so sick
of hearing you say you can't live without me.
At the same time, I feel good about it.
Because it means you still want me.
That's why I choose to tolerate it
while I always think of you
more than just a friend.
Even since we were in school.
Tim.
Have you ever thought...
about how you'd live
if I'm not in your life anymore?
Or maybe you've never thought of that at all
because you always take me for granted.
You think I'll always be here for you.
Can you answer me first?
Can I sit with you?
Of course.
Here, drink this.
You mom and dad are adorable.
Chatting with them is fun.
And they seem to understand their children well.
They don't want to feel old
so they always do what teens do.
I guess that makes them understand young people.
In the past...
Mom used to take Dao to fan meeting events
of BL couples that she liked.
She just went fangirling together with Dao.
Both of them always came back home losing their voices.
It's still funny thinking about it now.
Really?
Seeing your family today,
it makes me miss my parents.
Your face...
Which one of your parents do you look like?
Is it your dad? Or your mom?
I guess I look like my mom.
You do?
I don't think you look like her.
I mean my real mom.
You still remember when we did the Q&A session?
When you got a question about dad,
I truly understood how you felt, Kim.
When mom first joined the family,
I honestly didn't know what to feel
or how I should react.
I felt awkward.
I was sad because I missed my real mother.
I was also afraid of being left alone.
I was afraid dad wasn't gonna love me anymore.
Mixed feelings, really.
I was just a child, but I had to carry so many emotions.
Are you okay now?
I'm okay.
Don't worry.
So...
What made you accept the change?
Was it because of time?
For me,
It took me so long for me to finally accept reality.
I always snuck out to cry alone.
I just thought that she...
made dad, Dao and me very happy.
I think that's enough.
I was trying to understand the others' feelings.
I had no reasons to feel that possessive of my dad.
Are you a possessive person in general?
Yeah.
I may look like I can handle it now.
But when the time comes
and somebody tries to get close with the person I love
I always lose my cool and end up doing stupid things.
It's not cool, right?
Mek.
Can I ask you one thing?
Earlier...
you said
you finally realized you shouldn't prank people
just because of what, exactly?
Just because they try to get close with someone I care about.
And that person...
is you, Kim.
I'm so curious
about what you did at Mek's resort?
I bet he got a free night promotion
plus the son of the owner!
I'm gonna end all BL content activities.
About the other day, I...
I understand.
Don't worry. I won't leave you.
Have you ever thought of telling people
that we're together?
I know how you feel
but why do we have to keep this a secret?
Why would you want to be around Kim all the time?
You act like you own him.
Are you dating now?
Do you really like Kim
or just want to take him as a win against me?