The people, places, organizations, events,
groups and professionals
depicted in this program are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Now that there's no more Thunderous Sky,
it's like I'm being forced to grow up.
Why do you always make me worried?
You're too good at playing with my heart.
I made Kim upset and I don't know how to fix it.
If you wait any longer, it may get worse.
Maybe Mek is the kind of guy who doesn't use the word love to express his feelings?
Happy Birthday, Kim.
I like you.
Mek!
Say something.
Kim! Kim!
[I'm sorry.]
[FLUK
Chatchawal]
[EARTH
Teerapat]
[BEW
Sitthikarn]
[DANIEL
Cheng Yu Chang]
[BOAT
Yongyut]
[KENJI
Siwarut]
[POR
Passakorn]
[YUT
Kritsadayut]
[Directed by
NATTHAMON YIMYAM]
[It's because of you.]
I know you're a man-child,
but I never thought you'd be such a coward.
I am sorry.
Why are you always like this when you did something wrong?
You always hide
rather than facing it.
You should stop being like this.
Right.
It's my fault.
At least it's good that you know you're wrong.
Next time, just make up your mind and say it.
You just disappeared without saying a word.
Other people have feelings too, you know?
Hey.
Here's the sheet.
Mek.
Take it.
All of you seniors...
now it's time for you to shine
and show what you've learnt throughout the past 3-4 years.
I suppose you all have a group already?
Yes.
If you need any advice for your film,
feel free to come discuss it with me.
Once it gets approved, you can present it to the class next week.
Oh!
The Thunderous Sky gang, don't make anything outrageous this time.
Chancellor will come on our screening day.
If you frighten her, she might unleash
some weird power on you again.
Understood?
- Yes, professor.
- Noted.
What's wrong with you, Mek?
Right.
So...
You don't like Kim?
If something's bugging you, just tell us.
Yeah.
You think we're okay seeing you like this?
Do you remember that time I told you...
that I want to take on something new I'm interested in?
Mm.
I just applied for a landscape course in Australia.
And the university replied...
that they accepted me
and I can start my semester this fall.
So...
What does it have to do with Kim?
If I go to Australia,
what's the future for our relationship?
You just have to make a decision.
There's nothing complicated about it.
Don't tell me your reluctant tendencies strike again.
So what are you gonna do?
You shouldn't be like this.
Not to mention the thesis project.
Are you sure you can handle all that?
Do you want to drop out and take a break?
We can do it together with you.
Right.
You guys, stop it.
I can take care of myself.
Now we need to focus on the thesis.
You don't have to worry.
We're not worried about the project.
We're worried about you.
I'm Mek of Thunderous Sky.
I can weather any storm.
Speaking of which, I feel like kicking off the thesis right now.
Come on. Let's go doing research.
We need to write a paper for the professor, remember?
Are you sure about that?
Yeah.
Let's go.
At least I won the last two digits prize this time.
I'm sorry.
It was because of me.
I'm the one who encouraged you to confess to him.
In the end, it's good, isn't it?
I could finally get it off my chest and be done with it.
Kim.
I already applied for the photography contest.
I've taken up photography again.
Don't you want to celebrate with me a bit?
Actually, I went to take photos with Park recently.
Really?
What got you interested in photography again?
Of course, it's because of my beloved Park.
Wow.
Did you just brag about your boyfriend?
I'm creating content with Bear, too.
You two are bragging about your boyfriends. Period.
Kimhan.
Could you do me a favor?
Is there anything you want me to help with?
Can you find these books for me, please?
Sure.
I think we should go to different sections.
You and I should go find those theory books.
We gather again once we find what we need.
Okay, sure.
I don't get it.
The internet exists.
But why does the professor want us to research in the library?
I guess there's something more here
than what's on the internet.
So...
I'll go find thesis documents from the past years then.
So we can have some references.
Make sure you pick the good ones,
so I can copy them.
I'm so sorry.
I'm really not available today.
Let's arrange it next time.
Thank you.
Why did you reschedule it?
Because I'm busy.
Busy my ass!
I already confirmed it with them.
Why are you sitting here?
You should've gone to work.
So you always help him manage his work?
You two seem to be very close.
He's a lot of work, Pete.
I only help him sometimes.
Of course, we're close.
Mai and I...
We've known each other for so long.
I know...
what he likes.
And what he doesn't like.
You seem to understand each other very well.
Are you guys really just friends?
Tim is my best friend.
If we wanted to date,
we would have done it long ago.
I'm courting Mai here.
Could you give me the chance, Tim?
Can't believe you really said that.
You can do whatever you want.
It's not my business.
He's right.
In fact, I'm the one who you should be asking, no?
I've been trying to approach you all this time.
Don't you notice?
I've noticed that since the moment you asked me for my LINE contact.
I see what you did there.
Let's order.
Professor.
Did you happen to see the pile of books on that table?
I have to bring them to Prof. Angkana.
Meka already did that for you.
Thank you.
"Dude, is there something
going on between Mai and Pete?"
"I guess so."
"I think you should know that..."
"Pete is a jerk."
"He fools around."
"Yesterday, I just saw him with a guy from Econ."
"Please warn Mai about him."
"Mai and I are not that close."
"I don't think it's my place to say it."
Hi, what's up?
Are you home now?
Who are you with?
Pete sent me home just now.
And he went home already?
Yeah, he's gone.
So what is it that you're calling me for?
Do you really like Pete?
Why?
I think he's kinda cute.
He takes such good care of me.
Even better than when I take care of you.
That means you really like him, right?
What are you trying to say?
Nothing.
If you like him, it's cool.
Mm.
Is that all?
Mek has something to think about.
What could be more important than this?
What about you?
Have you decided?
Later.
A zombie movie is waiting for us.
"Today, I'm going to show you..."
"how to wear plain-colored clothes
without looking so plain."
"Take my outfit for an example..."
Why are you watching Tim's content?
You want to make something like this?
Do you think it's possible?
I think I can do this too.
Don't you agree, Bomb?
Sure I do.
Papa Bear can always make it happen!
I don't want people to see you shirtless!
I need to fetch some clothes for my boyfriend.
There are only us here. Who would see me?
No, no.
Here you go.
Maybe I can start by matching an outfit for you.
I think...
if I make an outfit mix & match content,
it's gonna be popular.
See?
You look so cute!
You'll do great with any content.
Lots of people are ready to support you.
Subscription is also on the rise.
I've said it before and I'll say it again.
I can make it happen because of you, Bomb.
So, Bear...
Why did Mek react like that?
Kim was hurt so much, you know?
Mek has something to think about.
What could be more important than this?
Well...
He's going to study abroad.
That's why he hesitated.
But don't tell Kim about this.
Mek wanted to deal with it on his own.
Come on.
Don't worry.
Everything is gonna be alright.
I believe so.
Alright.
I like you.
What's exactly on your mind?
I'm so tired of guessing!
No meals for you today!
Just starve.
I don't know what your daddy is thinking.
Waiting is hard, you know?
Next group.
Thunderous Sky, it's your turn.
The title of our thesis film is...
University of Zombie.
It's about university students
who got infected and broke into the campus.
Then they spread the infection all over the place
and people start to transform into zombies.
There are three main characters.
These characters will be the ones to drive the plot and bring us to conclusion.
Right.
And here's how the zombie costume will look like.
As you can see, it will be bloody...
And here're the research info about zombie movies that we found.
Now that you take yourself seriously, Thunderous Sky,
you seem to be doing really well.
I think you've done a thorough research.
You can start writing your screenplay now.
Thank you.
Next group, please.
Our project got approved so easily.
It's unbelievable.
Maybe the professor already got tired of seeing your faces,
so she just greenlit it as fast as she could.
Good then.
So I can graduate fast
and start making a living.
Right, Mek?
What do you guys plan to do after graduation?
I think I'll keep doing editing gigs.
I've become used to it now.
What about you?
I'll live with Bomb
and continue making content for Bear's Experiment.
I've thought about it.
The channel is going to be popular.
I'm 100% sure!
What about you?
Have you decided?
Later perhaps.
The zombie movie project is waiting for us.
Let's make the film our most memorable project together.
Are you sure you're ready for it?
I'm sure.
The hellish week...
begins now!
"Check this out."
"It's so cool."
Bear.
Can you print out another copy for me?
Sure.
I'm running out of ideas.
Park.
Why didn't you trust me?
What you came up with is so cliché.
It's the same in every movie.
Imagine Squid Game.
When they reveal the truth about that 001 uncle.
Don't you think it creates more impact that way?
You just freaking gave away a spoiler, man!
My idea is cliché. So what?
Have you ever heard of mass media?
We're doing it for the mass.
I have a mass taste.
Don't you forget we're making a film for the mass.
Bear.
Are you for real?
I've been friends with your for 4 years.
But this is the first time you have great ideas.
Damn you, Park.
So...
Are you buying my idea, Mr. director?
If so, I'm going take this approach.
Go ahead with it.
[How infections spread:
- Bites
- Contaminated food
- Blood, body fluids]
[Location: campus, abandoned buildings]
Guys.
Will it turn into a disaster?
All I've ever done is editing videos for YouTube.
Can I really edit a film?
If it fails, we fail together.
It's actually even harder for me.
As a director, if the film turns out shitty,
people are going to blame me.
Why are you guys so serious?
You're acting as if some streaming service
is waiting to buy our work.
Just do our best.
Put all energy into it!
Guys, I bought something for you.
Bear, how are you?
Are you tired doing your thesis project?
I'm so tired, Bomb.
Please make time to eat.
And don't only eat instant noodles, okay?
I'm worried about you.
I miss you so much!
Bye for now.
Love you so much!
Love you too.
Bye-bye.
You can do it.
How are the Thunderous Sky guys doing?
They're pretty busy.
Bear said they barely have time to sleep.
Mek too.
Park said...
he worked so hard he got sick.
We need to do something about this Mek-Kim situation.
We felt that the information we'd prepared last time might not be enough yet,
so we decided to to more research.
Now, we got the locations...
In terms of editing, we'll focus on keeping a slow and steady pacing...
to make sure that the audiences get immersed into the film's mood.
We will be filming on Saturday and Sunday.
We'd like to end our presentation here.
Thank you for your attention.
Thank you.
I can't wait to see your film.
You can now start filming.
You know this is a zombie movie, right?
So I want a lot of blood, but not the type that looks fake when splashed.
- Could you prepare that for me?
- Sure.
And if you need anything, just text me.
- Okay?
- Got it.
See you.
Hey.
How about you try directing sometimes?
You have potential here.
Stop kidding.
Do you really want the project to fail or what?
I feel like I'm a burden to you.
I'm sorry.
What burden, Mek?
If you really are one, I'd have called you out long ago.
Your duty is to direct.
Just focus on that.
One more thing,
we're doing this as a team
and we've already come so far.
Don't think too much.
This is not an individual project.
It's our project.
Oh...
Should we bring more people to help us?
The scope is pretty big.
Don't worry.
A lot of people are willing to help you.
Mek, our pre-proposal's just got approved.
Don't you feel happy about it?
Right.
Of course, I'm happy.
I already celebrated in the room.
And that's it?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Let's go home to prepare for shooting.
I saw Mek usually picked you up.
Did I say something wrong?
Hello, Tim.
Hi.
You've just finished your class?
Yes.
So...
Are you by yourself?
Yes.
I mean...
Are you seeing anyone with me?
Of course not.
I just thought that you're always with Mai.
I'm not used to seeing you alone. That's all.
Are you okay, Tim?
Did you and Mai have a fight?
He's just busy lately.
Also...
I guess it's partly because I treated him badly.
So...
Did you do something that made him upset?
I don't really know what to say.
But Mai and me...
We will never be the same.
I think you're very lucky
to have a friend like Mai
who always takes care of you.
In a way that friends don't necessarily need to do.
Actually...
Mai didn't have to be friends with me.
When we were in school,
I didn't have any friends.
People often thought I was unapproachable.
But then there was Mai.
Perhaps he pitied me.
He invited me to play with him.
He talked to me.
He could also stand my fussy habits.
No one knows you better than Mai.
And no one knows Mai better than you.
Isn't it obvious...
that you can't live without each other?
But I think...
you may need to show Mai something
so he'll know that he's important to you.
Didn't realize this would become an advice-sharing session.
What about you?
Why are you all alone today?
I usually saw Mek picked you up.
Did I say anything wrong?
I'm sorry.
It's alright, Tim.
I'm busy lately too.
As for Mek, he's busy with his thesis project.
That's why we are not hanging out together.
Mek and I...
We had some trouble.
I was wrong to say that to Mek.
Maybe Mek doesn't share the same feelings at all.
I just want it to be clear.
I don't want to be confused with my feelings.
But Mek didn't give me any response.
I don't really know...
why he reacted like that.
Although he looks like a brat
and good for nothing,
when it comes to you...
I think he's serious.
He never gives up.
He might have his reasons for being this way.
You know, he said to me...
"Kim is mine."
"Don't you mess around with him."
"He's reserved for me only."
He really said that to me.
Just give him some time.
It's so hard, Tim.
I don't want to think about it anymore.
Screw him!
I said what I said.
Now it's his turn to speak up.
I already embarrassed myself.
Speaking of which,
I need to apologize to you, Kim,
for making the situation even more...
...complicated.
Not to mention that I wanted to win against him so much
that I ended up making you upset.
It's totally fine, Tim.
I was actually glad that you were a part of it.
To be honest,
I look up to you as my idol.
And about that time you made me upset...
It's nothing compared to what Mek is doing to me now.
Stop talking like that.
Hello, mom.
How are you, son?
Does studying make you tired?
Yeah, I'm so tired.
I barely have time to sleep
and now I look like crap.
I think you look as weary as before.
Mom!
What about Lee?
How is he doing?
I'm good, mom.
Good to hear that.
Lee, please take care of Park for me.
Always support each other, okay?
Sure, mom.
Please take care of yourself too.
Don't lift anything too heavy.
Sure.
Also, I miss your tamarind chili paste.
Can you send me some more?
Sure, I can make a ton for you.
You guys seem to be so close.
Of course, he's my son.
You're talking about me, right?
I'm talking about both of you.
I have to do the laundry.
If I don't stop talking now,
it's gonna go on forever.
Please be careful when you sit and stand up, mom.
I know. I know.
You don't have to keep reminding me that I'm old.
Does he complain this much with you, Lee?
Not much, mom.
Because...
I do everything by myself.
Park!
Okay, we gotta go. Bye!
She must be lonely.
Otherwise, she wouldn't call.
You don't come home often enough.
As you can see...
I'm super busy.
By the way...
Have you selected a photo to submit for the competition?
Not yet.
The deadline is approaching.
Come on. Let me help.
Which photo you think is good?
What about this photo?
The lighting is nice.
But I think this one's better.
It has you in it.
Are you sure?
I'm picking this one.
Because if I win...
I want to share the success with you.
Are we done selecting the photo?
I'm tired of the bed.
Where do you want to do it then?
Seeing you now makes me disappointed.
I don't understand why Kim even likes you.
Perhaps he has someone else in his heart now.
We should get our plan started now.
Let's give these stubborn guys a lesson.
Mek, why didn't you come down to dinner?
I kept calling your until my throat hurt.
I said I was working.
How can you live in this condition?
I thought everything was going fine.
How come it turned out this way?
Everybody is annoyed with you.
I know you're hesitating.
But sometimes, you don't need to think too much.
It's a serious matter.
I can't just think of it lightly.
You know, you're not that smart.
Using your brain wouldn't help much anyway.
Dao!
I mean...
You should stop thinking too much.
If you already use your brain and still can't find an answer,
maybe just follow your heart.
You're trying to educate me all of a sudden?
I said that because I pity you.
Seeing you now makes me disappointed.
I don't understand why Kim even likes you.
Perhaps he has someone else in his heart now.
If he wants to be with someone else,
he'd have done that long ago.
You wouldn't have a chance.
I wish you got some smart genes from our parents.
I tried to find a solution for you and now I'm so tired.
Park.
Do you think Mek can handle it?
He's looking like a sick puppy again.
I think...
He looks more like a zombie than a director.
Should we kickstart our plan now?
Are you sure it's a good idea?
I'm afraid that it will make him feel even worse.
I think we better start now.
I'm sick of seeing them not talking.
Both of them are so stubborn.
You're right.
They're wasting time dancing around.
For what?
All they do is make us grew more and more anxious.
I think...
we should get our plan started now.
Let's give these stubborn guys a lesson.
What!?
The actor can't come?
Okay, okay.
What's wrong? Who can't come?
The guy who'll play a zombie.
He got sick so he can't come today.
What should we do?
We need a lot of people to play zombies to make it believable.
Mek, I'll call for some help.
That's nice. Thank you.
Please help make some calls right away.
ASAP.
Okay.
Damn it.
The actor is here.
Thank you for coming.
I never want us to separate.
I want to take care of you like this forever,
but I can't do that from now on.
I can't choose.
- I gotta go.
- Why so hurry?
I'll hang out with Pete.
It'll be fun.
I've made up my mind.
Mek.
I have something to tell you.