The people, places, organizations, events,
groups and professionals
depicted in this program are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Park, you saw Mek? What's wrong with him?
Jealous, I guess.
You have anyone you like?
I only know that he's one of my fans.
Is there anything wrong?
It's nothing. I guess I'm just tired.
He said he's okay. Stop bugging him.
You wouldn't know anything.
You're too busy enjoying that BL fame.
If I ask you to make BL content with me,
you wouldn't mind, would you?
Tim.
If we can't get in to the same university,
do you think we'll still be close like this?
What makes you think that way?
We can do it surely.
Even if we can't,
we'll still be close friends like we always have been.
But somehow I think...
I don't want us to be the same.
Can we be more than that?
More than that?
How?
I like you.
- Mai.
- You don't have to answer me anything.
I just wanted to tell you that.
Because I don't know if we have to go
separate ways in the future or not.
I am sorry.
Don't make your face like that.
You don't need to feel guilty about it.
Like I said, I just wanted to tell you.
Perhaps it's because of changing weather.
I may get sentimental because of it.
Mai.
Honestly...
I want us to stay like this forever.
You do understand, right?
That boyfriends can break up.
But you and me can't stop being friends.
I'd rather be a selfish one here.
Because I want you to be with me like this forever.
Me too.
[FLUK
Chatchawal]
[EARTH
Teerapat]
[BEW
Sitthikarn]
[DANIEL
Cheng Yu Chang]
[BOAT
Yongyut]
[KENJI
Siwarut]
[POR
Passakorn]
[YUT
Kritsadayut]
[Directed by
NATTHAMON YIMYAM]
[Please don't get me wrong.]
[Fame Hunger]
Welcome back to Fame Hunger!
Nom nom.
And the topic we're going to discuss today
is none other than...
#TimKim
Let's have a look on how this hashtag went viral.
#TimKim started from a new BL couple
from the same famous university.
This couple has become a new talk of the town.
They are Tim and Kimhan.
This hashtag is the hottest topic online right now.
Apparently, the fans of Mek-Kim, which is the original BL couple,
have been calling out the university's chancellor about this abrupt change of ship
from Mek-Kim to Tim-Kim.
They demand an answer from the chancellor!
This circumstance has sparked a war between two fandoms.
Let's check out some of the online comments.
The original one is, hands down, better.
The fake ones that come after never last long.
Ouch!
They might come after but they come with a bang!
Nothing to be afraid of. Love you, Tim!
Later the chancellor responded that
when it comes to BL,
one doesn't have to stick to a single ship forever.
The ship can change depending on chemistry and suitability of the content.
She also asked the fans to chill out
and think of the boys' BL role
simply as their duty and responsibility.
Wow. What a harsh comment from the chancellor.
I think I talked too much already.
Well, if there's any progress,
I'm going to keep you drama-hungry people updated for sure!
For today, we must say goodbye now.
Nom, nom, nom, nom...
Doesn't this means you got dismissed?
What should we do?
I don't know.
Can't think of anything.
How come it turned out like this?
You can't just sit here being clueless!
You have to do something
now that the other guy is going in full force.
I'm afraid your Mek-Kim fandom is going to break soon.
And I can tell you...
that perhaps
you might get your heart broken too!
No way.
I never fancy Kimhan!
I told you it's all just an act.
Everyone already knows
how much you get flustered around him.
Why are you such a fool?
Dao, why did you say that?
Dao!
[Thong's]
Hey, Bomb! What are you having?
I'm having noodles.
But I'm here.
Who made that for you?
I made it myself.
Was it good then?
Your own cooking.
Of course, it's delicious.
Then you should make one for me next time.
Enjoy!
Hey.
Can I sit with you?
Yeah, sure.
Take a seat.
Bro!
Can I order?
Sure!
What do you want for today?
Same.
Spicy pork noodles.
Dirty.
Big portion!
Spicy pork noodles. Dirty.
Sure.
- So...
You first.
I just wanted to say that
we run into each other often these days.
It's as if someone has written it for us to meet.
That's all.
How many times have there been so far?
Is this the third time?
I think so.
What was it that you were going to say?
I just wanted to tell you to eat a lot.
Have anything you want.
This meal is on me.
Take it as a compensation for
that time I made you fainted.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Then I'll eat a lot!
Bro!
Where's my noodle!?
Here it is.
Just calm down.
Thank you.
You're small but you can eat a lot indeed.
When there's someone paying for you,
this is how you do it.
You're going a bit too far.
Why don't you order some more and take it home then?
Can I really do that?
I was kidding!
I saw you posted a story the other day.
Did anything happen to you?
Of course something happened.
It's Mek.
He and I planned to do a live chat with the Hailstones.
And then he just disappeared.
Such a bummer.
Lately, he only focused on making BL content with your friend.
He might forget now
that Thunderous Sky channel still exists.
Come on.
I think...
You should have a talk with Mek and tell him what you feel.
You two are good friends. You can talk.
It's no big deal.
It's because it's no big deal.
That's why Mek wouldn't care.
You shouldn't think for yourself that way.
If you two don't resolve this soon,
when are we fans going to get new uploads from you?
I can't promise that,
but I'll try my best.
Did you finally find that fan of yours?
The one you said you liked.
Not yet.
I searched for him everywhere
but still couldn't find him.
I think I only find myself with you lately.
We bump into each other all the time.
I think the reason why we meet often,
is perhaps because we're looking for each other.
Maybe that's the reason why I'm always on your sight.
Where did you get such wise word from?
So sentimental!
Have you finished?
I'll pay now.
Yes, I'm done.
Check, please.
10 bowls of noodles.
It's 370 baht.
Do you have enough money?
Can I do bank transfer here?
No, we accept cash only.
Bomb, can you lend me some cash?
How come?
You said you were going to pay for me?
You even convinced me to eat a lot.
Three hundred and seventy.
Okay, done.
Bomb, give me your bank account number.
I'll transfer your money back.
I said I'll pay so I'll pay.
I'm a man of his word.
Well...
PromptPay okay?
097 884 2643
Once you're done with the transaction,
you may also call me with this number.
Are you for real?
Okay.
Your name is...
Kritsada Bhakdi.
Hey, it's him again!
Kritsada.
I should give him a heart.
I got a lot of motivation from watching you, Bear.
It's clear to me that you worked so hard to make this fun.
Keep it up!
This Kritsada guy always mentions me in his comments.
Bear.
Are you trying to memorize my number or what?
You still haven't transferred the money.
About what you said that we met often
because we might be looking for each other...
It's true, isn't it?
Come again?
You are that fan.
The one I was looking for.
Finally, we meet.
Kritsada Bhakdi.
Hello!
Oh hey! Thanks, pal.
Bomb!
What's wrong with you?
You look like you're sick or something.
I'm okay. I'm perfectly fine.
Am I really okay, right?
Yes, I'm okay.
Here's the thing.
I have some huge thing to consult with you guys real quick.
- What is it?
It happened yesterday after I finished my job.
I had a meal at a popular noodle place called Thong's.
I was starving so I ordered one dry noodle.
And when I started to eat it, I felt that...
if I also had a soup, it'd be even better.
All this fuss just to make us listen to how you eat noodles?
I'm sorry.
I'm just excited.
The thing is, yesterday at the noodle shop...
I met Bear and he wanted to pay for me.
But then he didn't have cash.
So I paid for him and he'd transfer the money back.
And then came the climax.
He saw my full name.
What's wrong with your full name?
Did you register your name with some weird stuff?
Can you just tell us the whole story?
Stop beating around the bush.
The truth is...
Before that I ran into Bear once.
And he told me he had a thing for one of his fans.
and that he was looking for him.
So when he saw my name,
he told me...
I was that fan he'd been looking for!
- That's it?
Don't you guys get excited for me?
I was the fan whom he liked and was looking for!
It's good, isn't it?
You like him and he likes you back.
What exactly is your concern
that you want to talk us about?
I'm afraid he'll be disappointed...
that the person he liked and looked for is me.
Look,
He was searching everywhere for this person.
So no matter who that person is,
he'd surely be happy when he finds them.
Exactly.
Try not to think ahead.
Just wait and see.
[When you finish your class, wait in front
of the building, I'll pick you up.]
Kimhan.
Hello.
Tim, what are you doing here?
I'd like to ask you to have a meal with me.
A meal?
When we shot the uniform mix & match content,
You owe me a meal, remember?
I don't think I can make it today, again.
I have some stuff to do with Mek.
Next time, I promise I'll go with you.
That's a pity.
But it's okay.
Next time, you can't deny me again.
Sure.
Well...
I gotta go now.
See ya.
If you're afraid of falling off, make sure you hold me tight, alright?
What's wrong with you?
Where are we going?
You'll find out soon.
Making content with Tim...
will never be as fun as making it with me.
So you're saying...
You want to keep doing this BL couple thing with me?
You picked me up in front of the building
just to do this?
What's wrong with it?
I'm afraid you'd already forget
what you've done with your former BL partner.
I see you bring a lot of stuff here.
Nothing much actually.
I know you're so busy.
so I want just you to come sit here and relax.
I prepared these lunch boxes so you can relax for real.
Sounds like a great idea.
And we don't need to go far.
I have a lot of work to do.
My head is spinning.
Because of your newfound BL couple fame?
Yeah, it is.
The chancellor told me...
she had a lot of plans for it.
Like planting trees.
Going on a camp.
And for this coming week,
we're set to make a cake content.
With these many contents,
I'm sure she plans to have them posted until next year.
I suppose that's her plan.
It's fun anyway.
Believe me,
Making content with Tim
will never be as fun as making it with me.
Why?
So you're saying...
you want to keep doing this BL couple thing with me?
No!
Kim.
Mek!
You caught me off guard.
Candid shots like this are cute.
I want a reshoot.
Let me see that.
I won't let you.
Mek!
Guys,
I have a new pranking idea!
What?
So you're coming back to make prank content on our channel?
Hell yeah!
Yes!
The old Mek is back, people!!
Yes.
This time we will do a prank on Tim.
What!?
Why him?
If I can do a prank on Tim
and tarnish his image,
all his fans will return to me like before,
don't you think?
Don't you want to do it?
You've become so obsessed with BL fame!
In the end...
you're doing it all for yourself!
I won't do it.
What now?
I'm back to make content with you
and now you won't do it?
You also hated it when I let our channel fade.
Park, are you in this with me?
Stop hesitating.
Park is not going to be in this with you
because you're hungry for BL fame.
Park, do you agree with him?
We both are sick of waiting for you.
If you want to enjoy BL fame that much,
Fine! Do it!
Also, screw the suspension threat!
I don't care anymore!
Now...
You can get out of my room.
You said it yourself!
Don't regret it later then!
Mek.
Yeah!
I'll only regret it when it's snowing in Thailand!
Mek, wait!
Don't you think you were being too harsh?
Park...
I am sorry.
Mek doesn't love us anymore.
Can't believe you acted all tough earlier.
And said all that snow in Thailand stuff.
I'm sure now Mek hasn't even reached the ground floor yet.
But you're already crying this hard?
Just wait and see.
I'm gonna outbest those BL contents!
And I'm gonna win prizes.
Lots of clients are going to flock in and pay me in crypto!
Mek.
Can you help me with something?
What is it?
Mek.
What happened? You look upset.
Bear was being silly.
I asked him to film a content and he made a fuss about it.
He even said he'll run a channel on his own.
Why didn't you guys just talk it through?
Did you ask him why or what happened to him?
Typical Bear.
He felt neglected.
He'll call me when he feels better.
Don't mind him.
About the cake content you're shooting,
I'll shoot it for you.
Bear and Park won't come.
About you being at odds with Bear...
You should talk to him.
Don't let this fight continue.
Understood?
Yes, sir, understood.
So what do you want me to help with?
Here.
I'm preparing myself for that cake content with Tim.
I need a guinea pig for testing.
So I'm a guinea pig?
Nah.
I don't think a guinea pig can be this cute.
I'm scared!
Giant guinea pig!
Go away!
This is good, actually.
Because I'll get to eat something for free.
Alright.
Here. So you don't have to keep flipping your hair.
Never knew you had a cute rubber band.
It is as cute as the owner.
My sister Dao got it for me.
So, what exactly do you want me to help with?
I'm so ready now.
Well...
Hang on for a sec.
Hello, Tim.
What are you doing?
I was practicing baking cake.
I didn't know a pro like you still needs practice.
I'm afraid I'll make mistakes at the shoot.
As expected, you're always cautious.
I suppose Mai already sent you the list of my food allergies.
Have you got it?
Yes, I got it.
My apologies if it's a little too much.
It's totally fine.
I'll see you later.
See you later.
You can start with that.
Like this?
Are you sure?
Or like this?
What's the difference?
You wanted him as your BL partner so much
that you asked your auntie to arrange that?
#MekKim is going well now actually.
If I change that,
won't people come cursing at me?
I don't believe so, auntie.
A BL couple isn't a real couple.
And more importantly...
Have you seen this?
[They come after but they come with a bang!
I'm rooting for TimKim!]
You obviously pull the strings for personal gain.
Why?
Are you jealous?
Jealous my ass.
I just find it funny seeing you trying so hard.
You know me.
When I want something,
I gotta get it.
Up to you, Mr. Tim.
I'll root for you then.
Can you grab butter from the fridge?
What is this?
The smell is so strong!
That's shrimp paste from Shrimp Paste Goddess,
not butter.
Do you know that her magic is very strong?
One time my dad smelled it and he threw up
right here in the kitchen.
Is that so?
Yeah!
That thing is highly dangerous!
Never smell it if you don't have the stomach for it.
See that? The butter is right next to it.
It's time Tim finally got the taste of Shrimp Paste Goddess' magic.
Are you stressed?
Brace yourself.
Something fun is coming up to shake your stress away.
Who's that?
Is this your first time having a meet-up like this?
Yes, it's my first time.
Are you scared?
Just a little.
Don't be afraid.
Anyway, if you like it, let's meet again next time.
Sure.
Park!
You think I'm a fool?
I'll go home now. Bye.
Go home safe.
Bear?
What are you doing here?
Actually, I was waiting for you, Bomb.
So you had a fight with Mek?
And you told him you're going to do your own channel?
Mm.
But you still have no idea what to do?
Why don't you just keep doing the same thing then?
So your long-time fans will come and follow you again.
No!
I hate to admit this...
but if I keep making prank content like I used to,
I'll never be able to beat BL content.
How about you do something you're good at
or interested in?
Alright, I know.
I'm just not sure where to start.
Besides...
If I change to the way I want
and it ends up getting a poor response
then what do I do?
It'll be an epic fail.
You don't have to worry about having no one to watch.
At least you have one fan who will definitely watch it.
Who?
Me.
Kritsada Bhakdi.
Your die-hard fan.
Can I ask you one thing?
When you said I was the one you were looking for,
how did you feel when you finally found me?
I felt great!
I finally met the person who always supports me.
You know what...
Not many people mentioned me in their comments.
But one of the people who did was you, Bomb.
I feel very lucky.
Are you home now?
What was I thinking!?
Are you asleep?
No, no!
Who is that?
Park!
Why are you crying?
Bear,
Can I stay with you for a while?
Park, what happened?
Don't ask me for now.
When I feel better
I'll go back.
Please don't cry.
In three, two, one.
Hello!
Now you're with us, TimKim!
This is our first video together, our debut one.
Since this is our first video,
do you have any special plan for me?
I'm going to make a cake for you.
I just can't wait to eat it.
Let's see what kind of cake Kim is making for me.
Let's go!
Cut!
How was it, Mr. Cameraman?
Stop it.
I never wanted to do this.
If you don't want to do this,
just go reconcile with Bear.
I know.
I'm waiting for the right time.
By the way...
Are you sure you know how to film?
Did you make me look good?
Do not insult me.
Don't forget that I study film.
I was just kidding!
Please concentrate on your work then.
Here, let me help!
For chocolate cream, use this one.
The other one, Kim said it's unusable.
Okay.
By the way, Mek...
Park are not joining us today?
He's probably with Bear right now.
Don't worry about them.
They're a lot of work.
Bomb...
What's wrong?
Why do you look gloomy today?
With Beat absent, you suddenly have no energy to work?
No, it's not that.
I have something else to think about.
You guys already finished arranging?
Let's continue, shall we?
Bomb, are you stressed?
Brace yourself.
Something fun is coming up to shake your stress away.
What was that?
Here it is, homemade chocolate cake by Kimhan.
It looks very yummy.
Only on the outside.
Now, here comes the moment I've been waiting for...
It's time to finally taste it!
May the force of Shrimp Paste Goddess be with him!
Show us your magic.
Bring it on!
It's so delicious!
Really?
You're such a great chef.
I almost forgot...
Let's tell the audience about your recipe.
For today, I made a chocolate cake
and decorated it with orange slices to add a sense of refreshment.
For the cake texture, I opted for fudge...
Tim!
What happened?
Anyone, call an ambulance!
I suppose...
this kind of bad habit cannot be fixed.
I just don't want anyone to be around you.
Mai!
I think I already told you
everything he's allergic to.
If anything happens to him,
it's all your fault.
I was really cautious.
How come it turned out like this?
What did I do wrong?
Why does my cake have a taste of shrimp paste?
I'm sure I brought the right ingredient.
Mek brought a new one to us.
He said you told him the other one was unusable.
I think I found the cause.
[Foods Tim are allergic to:]
[Shrimp, shrimp paste]
Kim, please listen to me.
I am sorry.
That was not at all my intention.
Not your intention?
Are you saying you stumbled
and accidentally spilled shrimp paste into it?
It wasn't like that.
Well...
I never wanted to make him go to hospital.
I didn't know that he is allergic to shrimp paste.
All I wanted was a shot of him throwing up.
Are you saying that what you did
was for the sake of making prank content again?
I suppose
this kind of bad habit cannot be fixed.
I just don't want anyone to be around you.
Are you crazy?
Don't be a coward and make me your excuse.
It's not relevant.
In the end...
all you do is make rubbish content.
And you know what...
That makes you rubbish too.
And if anything happens to Tim,
you must be responsible for it.
Mm.
Again, I am so sorry.
You can think of me whatever way you want.
No matter what excuse I make,
it doesn't change the fact that I'm the guilty one.
You can't bear to throw that away?
Or you think what you said was too harsh?
If you think you were too cruel
and want to apologize,
you should go talk to him.
You guys fought so loud I could hear it.
I didn't do anything wrong.
It was all Mek's fault so he deserved it.
Deserved to be called a rubbish person?
Up to you then.
He already apologized.
But you still called him that.
You're all grown-ups.
Why is it so hard for you to understand things?
Mek!
Dao!
Q, Kimhan, why are you guys here?
I really want you to know, Kim,
that it wasn't my intention to let that happen.
Now I realize that I should stop pranking people
just because...
Does this means we are close?
Can a BL couple turn into a real couple?