The people, places, organizations, events, groups and professionals depicted in this program are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Please have a look on Say No SOTUS project.
What is this?
It's a project we campaign against violent first-year activity.
This project is so cool!
Who came up with it?
That guy over there!
The channel's name is awful.
And the content you produce is rubbish!
Your friend is fainted. Don't you guys help him!?
Why are you still using VIOLENCE?
Why!?
I found a solution.
In a modern chancellor way.
I'm going to assign you to make a music video..
for Say No SOTUS
to be published on university's channel.
What!?
Mek!
Are you going to sleep forever!?
Wake up now!
Mek, wake up!
Wake up!
Alright!
Give me 5 more minutes.
You can go wherever you want!
You're not going to get up!?
Sure! Here you go!!
Are you going to kill me or something!?
Watch yourself. I'm gonna tell dad!
You just want to sleep so much
that you might be late for uni.
Dad would not sympathize you.
Just get off bed!
You are so handsome, Mek!
Mek! Just come down already!
I know, I know!
Can you just eat properly?
You already are a dirty person!
Yuck!
The way you eat doesn't really matter.
Don't forget to get me dinner as well.
Just go, go!
What?
My Somying, why do you look so sad?
I let you stay in the sun too long?
Papa will take care of you.
I hope you're alright.
I'll go to the university now.
- Dao, I'll go now.
- Okay!
Ahem.
[FLUKE
Chatchawal]
[EARTH
Teerapat]
[BEW
Sitthikarn]
[DANIEL
Cheng Yu Chang]
[BOAT
Yongyut]
[KENJI
Siwarut]
[POR
Passakorn]
[YUT
Kritsadayut]
[Directed by
NATTHAMON YIMYAM]
[That Kiss Was Unintentional]
I heard there's some drama about this project?
Drama?
What drama?
One of the students in our uni
made a clip of them pranking people.
A fake first-year activity.
But one student fainted for real.
So the guys from the student club were also implicated.
See this.
[Fake activity, real faint.]
But...
This year's head of student club was brilliant.
He's only a sophomore but has done so much.
We'll see how they deal with this.
Pity them. They're so committed.
Yeah.
Anyway...
How's your mother?
I haven't come see her lately.
I'd love to have a meal she cooks.
She's fine.
You and my mom are alike!
She also said she missed you.
it's a little too much!
Why? You're jealous of me?
What do you want to eat? I'll tell her.
Up to you.
What should we have? Can't think of any.
I want to go in first.
What's wrong with you!? I came here first!
- I want to go in first.
- Hey!
I came here first!
Stop it!
Didn't you see I came first?
What is wrong with you?
We're not even started yet.
Are we gonna get through this?
I don't know.
- I won't let you!
- Don't push!
Such a man child.
The song that has just ended was...
Our Say No SOTUS song.
Our song.
Is she joking or what?
I pray it was a joke too.
Is it really a song for teens?
It sounds like a song from 20 years ago.
When was the last time she updated music for herself?
So outdated!
Look at the bright side.
Now we can reach wider target audiences.
That's not neccessary.
If you want more popularity from this clip,
you should stop right now.
Okay, everyone.
Stop whispering and complimenting my song.
Because...
I want you all to focus on the performance.
I'll bring a choreographer to teach you.
You should pair up with one another to rehearse the dance.
I want this activity to unite everyone
and bring you all closer.
Understood?
Now you can select your partner.
Fast. Fast.
No one wants to pair up with you,
so I volunteer.
Are you, like, shading me or something?
Today we're going to learn some dance moves.
You can repeat the move after me.
Just follow my move.
Move to the right first.
Stretch it. On the right first.
Now on the left.
Now, both sides.
5 6 7 8  go!
1 2 3 4
5 6 7 8
5 6 7 go!
6 7 8 go.
Wait, wait.
That couple. Don't fight.
You seem to have fun, auntie.
Not that much.
Anyway, would you like to join them?
I'll pass. I don't think I'm good at that.
Just give it a try.
Will you?
I will have a shoot later.
I saw you so I just came to say hi.
But I will have to go soon.
Is it a shooting of your personal content?
I actually follow and see them sometimes.
You seem to gather a lot of fans.
Still...
Are you going to do that in a long run?
Why did you say that?
I'm not a quitter.
I mean...
Soon you'll have to run
for your father's hotel, right?
How are you going to continue this hobby then?
You know, your father tells me...
that once you graduate,
you'll take on the business right away.
I'm actually quite jealous of your dad
for having a son like you, Tim.
Your parents must be so pleased to have a son like you.
It's not like that.
You're flattering me.
Please excuse me. I have to go now.
I'll see you at home.
Of course.
Take care.
You guys, I had a serious thought about it.
If this music video gets released,
we're going to be famous for sure!
Our handsomeness is going to help restore uni's reputation!
- You think so?
- I think so.
I want you to look in the mirror when you dance.
If you see it, you might not want to say stuff like that.
And you're so good at it!?
You're as bad as a squid!
I want to splash you with some hot sauce!
Still, I think our performance is better
than those student club members.
Their moves were so lame.
I'm sure we'll be the ones who get all the credits.
Am I going to have energy left until shooting day?
I'm not tired at all.
As long as I get close to Bear, I'll never run out of energy.
No matter what, we must do better than those guys.
If we fall behind,
they're definitely going to say bad things about us.
Don't say it that way. Not all of them are bad.
Why do you have to protect them?
Nothing. I just think we're all in this together anyway.
But you, don't you think you're fanboying them too much?
You can't blame me for that.
Whatever.
I don't like him.
Not to mention that he lives next door to my new home.
I meet him everywhere, university or at home.
What a bad luck!
It's your bad luck, not mine.
Okay, everyone. Let's do it again.
5 6 7 go!
1 2 3 4 go. 5 6 7 8 go.
Now, switch to this move.
5 6 7 8 go. 1 2 3 4 go.
Ouch.
Kim, are you okay?
- It hurts.
- Let me see.
Let's take a seat properly.
I think we should call it a day for now.
Kimhan should go get rest.
Otherwise, it might get worse.
I'm still okay.
Kimhan, you don't have to be the center.
If your performance is good enough,
you'll have a lot of airtime anyway.
Just go get rest.
Yes, professor.
Okay, I think it's enough for today.
You can go back home and rehearse.
And we'll see you again on the shooting day.
It's showtime!
Let's just go home.
Kim, are you okay?
I'm totally fine.
I feel much better now.
Can you go home on your own?
Sure.
If you're not feeling okay, you can just go home with Mek.
Enough! Let's go home.
Be careful.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Yeah.
You two going somewhere next?
We can just part ways right here.
I'm tired and want to go home.
Let's go home then.
Hey, wait.
You want to go home together?
Mind your own business!
You're injured.
You don't have to keep acting like you're okay.
Just hop in.
You might stumble if you keep walking.
Running into you is bad enough!
Are you going to come with me or not?
Otherwise, I'll just go.
Where's the helmet?
I thought so.
What did you just say?
Are you going to take this or not?
You're too slow. I'll go now!
Hey!
My foot hurts, remember?
To be honest, I didn't want to help you.
But I'm afraid you might not recover in time before the shooting and it'll affect me too.
Worry about yourself first, eh?
You already look funny enough when you stand still.
Thanks.
It's fine.
To be honest, I didn't want to help you.
But I'm afraid you might not recover in time before the shooting.
And it will affect me too.
Worry about yourself, will you?
Make sure you rehearse well enough.
You already look funny enough when you stand still.
You cripple!
We'll see who the real center is on the shooting day.
I shouldn't have taken him home.
Let's see who's talking about me today.
This one doesn't have it.
What about the last episode?
Is there any?
No one talks about me.
I was hilarious in this one.
Yet no one likes it?
It's okay. I'll be overly dramatic next time.
Wait, here it is!
The same one again. Krissada.
I should give him a heart.
"I've gained so much energy from seeing you, Bear."
I can totally see how much effort you put in to make it fun.
Keep up, Bear!
This Krissada guy is so active on comments for me.
I wonder what he looks like.
I'll buy him a meal if I meet him.
In fact, make it two.
Enough you, guys.
How long are you going to keep walking in slow motion?
Sorry.
Don't screw it up.
That's quite a mouth you have.
We'll see.
You guys, I still can't dance good enough.
We may have to do multiple takes.
Just don't worry. You're with me, a dance expert.
You can trust me.
Don't embarrass ourselves in front of these guys.
On set, we must be on fire!
Say No SOTUS. Scene 10. Cut 1. Take 1.
Cut!
Great job! That was a good take.
Excellent!
I don't think they can't dance.
Did you see how the director compliments them?
Damn.
But I think that was the sexiest move.
Wow.
Ever since we date,
I've never seen you in such great dance move.
I'm completely surprised.
Anyway, I think the buttons' off not because of the dance.
It's because you're fat!
Hey, don't tease me.
I just wanted to do my best.
Your best indeed.
What are you doing?
Are you going to do it here?
What?
What are you thinking?
Just wear my shirt.
And I'll fix yours.
You love teasing me!
Who did this?
Thank you so much.
Park!!!
What are you doing in here?
What's with you? I just want to compliment you.
That you did so great out there.
The move when you burst out your buttons.
It still lingers in my eyes.
I'm so proud of you.
This is not the time.
We should go out.
Perhaps I can teach you this move.
Okay, let's rehearse in front of the mirror first.
Just go out.
Wait.
Don't tell me...
Just go, go!
Just go already.
Okay now?
Are we filming?
Now I can get started?
Hello, everybody!
Today, I'm taking you to the behind-the-scene
for the Say No SOTUS music video.
It is a special project from our university.
We came up with this project so that our students and future students...
can be confident...
that our university doesn't support violence in any first-year activity.
Without further a do,
Let's take you all to see our main actors.
Follow me!
Is it good?
I need to cover the camera like this, no?
Mek, Kim, please come on set.
Okay.
Your dance move isn't so bad.
Of course.
I have many talents.
You have such high confidence!
Now, let's meet with the actors
who are so dedicated to this project.
Please introduce yourself.
Hello, I'm Kimhan.
I'm this year's president of student club.
Hello, I'm Mek from Thunderous Sky channel.
And you'll love me like a bang!
You've probably seen his face from that famous clip, right?
Yes, Mek is joining our project.
I'd like to take this opportunity to say that...
the clip people that went viral
was only a video made just for fun.
No one was actually harmed.
Is there anything you two want to talk to viewers?
Mek first.
Yes.
It was just a fake content.
It's a misunderstanding of people on the internet.
The only fake one is the video creator.
I'm sure you all can see now...
how our university has absolutely no SOTUS.
Is there anything else you want to say?
As a club president this year,
I want you all to join Say No SOTUS project with us.
I just hope that everyone...
This is the path to our superstardom.
Say No SOTUS! Say No SOTUS!
Should I go audition at 411?
As this year's student club president,
I'd like to ask you all...
to help support Say No SOTUS project.
Wow.
This scene is so cliché.
You're okay, right?
Yes, I'm alright.
Cut!
Great job! The shooting is done for today!
Thank you all very much. Thank you. Thank you.
Hey, fart bag.
After this is all done, I hope not to see you again.
That would be good for me too.
I've never wanted to work with you anyway.
About that thing earlier...
Thanks.
So you can't say I owe you anything anymore.
You're welcome, brother.
But you know, we'll meet again at home anyway.
We can have all the activities without SOTUS.
All activities can be done without SOTUS.
We're friends. We're fun. We're equal.
We're so handsome
slick
and smooth like butter.
I feel strange somehow.
when people staring at us.
You're getting used to it soon.
This is the path to our superstardom.
Say No SOTUS. Say No SOTUS.
This gives me goose bumps.
I think it's not that bad.
Doing something like this once in a lifetime is fun.
Yeah, because once is more than enough.
It's so embarrassing.
I want to do something like this again.
It allows me to be in the same frame with Bear.
You do it alone next time then.
I'll pass.
I'm not sure if this is actually a great work or a real shame.
Say No SOTUS. Say No SOTUS.
Ouch!
Here's Longa for you.
It's a sparkling longan juice.
Try it.
I was craving something refreshing just now.
Baby, you always chooses the best for me.
I've seen you work so hard.
You need to add some vitamin to your body.
Thank you so much.
You're trying to boost more views for yourself, huh?
I've never done such a thing before.
It's fun, though.
Didn't you enjoy it?
Sure I did.
Who would have thought I can see my boyfriend
ripped his shirt and burst his buttons off?
Pop!
You sure love to tease me.
I'll wait and see when it happens to you.
Let's just keep watching the video.
Check this out. Who's that?
How's things with you lately?
Studying hard?
Not at all. After I moved to this faculty,
it's much easier than when I was in Comm Arts.
Friends are great and assignment isn't so tough.
Wasting two years of my life is worth it.
If you need any help, just let me know.
Then, can you help me with something now?
I want to boost my energy.
And here.
Here.
Here. Here. Here. Here.
- Here. Here. Here.
- Is that enough yet?
I realize I am handsome.
But I never knew I was also a talented dancer.
I was thinking...
Maybe I should audition at 411.
What dance? I didn't know that.
The Say No SOTUS song.
I was so cool on that!
Say No SOTUS what?
I was actually excited about this clip.
You act like you hate him
but you actually like each other, do you?
Here!
Shit!
Say No SOTUS mv...
that we put a lot of effort into
have got...
3,000 views.
Kimhan!
Mek!
Did you two realize what you have done!?
You!
And you!
You two DID A GREAT JOB!
You two are the new hope for our university!
How is that possible?
Yeah, how is that?
Don't you see we have only 4,000 subscribers
on the university channel?
But this incident makes us realize...
what people on the internet actually want.
That's why I decided...
You two must do BL content
to promote our university
and get more people to subscribe to our channel.
What!?
No more questions.
Isn't this a great opportunity?
This is how we're going to build a new image for the university
so people will see that...
we are very open in terms of
gender and expression of love.
But what you are trying to do is fake content
instead of being really open.
That's right.
Besides, we all have other things to do.
Also...
Say No SOTUS is going well too, isn't it?
I guess...
I haven't told you that..
when this project ends
you will not be in suspension anymore.
Well, let me just say this officially.
All six of you...
must help create content
with Mek and Kim as a BL couple
to promote our university.
and attract more people to subscribe to our university channel.
The target is 100,000 subscribers.
If you can't make it...
I'll probably have to...
remove you all from the positions in the student club.
And the three of you...
might not be able to graduate.
Goddamn!!!
Just calm down.
This is all because of you!
No, you!
If we refuse to do it, she won't let us graduate.
I guess I'll have to really do this BL content thing.
Don't touch me!
What is wrong with you?
Bear, eat something.
Does this mean we have to abandon our fans and make fake BL content now?
No way! I can't accept it!
If we don't do it, the chancellor won't let us graduate.
She's basically forcing us.
How is this "saying no" to SOTUS?
That's why I want to know
who "Nutsuda57" is.
That person who released your clip.
If I meet them, I'm gonna kick their ass!
I think...
they'll make you do it for just a little while.
You know...
Just to ride this wave a bit.
What about Thunderous Sky?
We should take a break on our channel.
Now we must help out each other on this.
Otherwise, we're all screwed.
Guys, how many IG followers did I have recently?
3,000 maybe.
Now it's 10k!
You're becoming famous now?
Let me check mine as well.
Why do I still have only 1,500?
Why can't I have more followers like you?
I guess I'll really have to do this BL content thing.
This might be the only way...
to gain more hailstone members
without having to create content on our channel.
Awesomeeee!
Brother, brother.
You're listening to Isaan song?
Shit!
Where are you going?
Just sit here first.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Okay.
What's your name?
We've met several times but I didn't catch it.
My name is Bomb.
Bomb?
Did you get that name because you pooped your pants when you were a kid?
You can think like that if you want.
So...where are you headed? Home?
I'm going to work actually.
I work as a part-time waiter at a restaurant nearby.
That's awesome.
I want to return this to you.
Oh, that's okay.
Just keep it.
I have another one here.
It smells really good.
I gotta go now. See you later.
Bye-bye.
Your heart is beating so fast, Bomb.
What?
Baby...
Who did that to you?
You're crossing the line!
Just a little. It's no big deal.
By the way...
It's good that you get some cold water
so now you can calm down a bit.
You're playing like a child!
You calm down already?
Stay right there!
Don't go anywhere!
Oh, so you're coming to see your BL mate right at his place?
Why are you in such a rush?
Yeah, I am!
My, my!
Why are you in here?
I'll splash it.
Sure! Come! Do it.
I'll fight you!
Come at me.
Come on.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't touch me!
What is wrong with you?
Stop playing like a child.
Give it to me!
How you like that, huh?
- Enough. I said enough!
- Come, come!
Come on!
Well, well well.
I didn't know you woke up early to create content.
Here.
This is wonderful!
Hello, Kimhan.
I already saw the clip.
You did a great job.
But next time...
Make sure you publish it on university channel, okay?
One more thing..
This is weekend.
You don't have to work this hard on content.
I don't want to bother you in your personal time.
But...
If you do want to spend time with Mek,
I won't forbid it.
Ugh! What the heck is this!?
[Nutsuda Ittipatchara]
I want to know who "Nutsuda57" is.
That person who released your clip.
They have such a great chemistry.
Should I create a fandom for them?
What should be the name of this fandom?
Can you suggest me a name?
Besides acting as a BL couple,
you need to help sell this t-shirt as well.
If we can't sell this t-shirt, we're all screwed.
What the hell?
You love dancing that much?
I'd love to eat Kimhan's egg.
This is almost like a harassment content.
People want to see something cute, don't you think?
Our brothers are going to win the popular BL couple award!
How long do we need to keep making this kind of content?
I'm definitely not going to leave our channel.
We just need to prioritize on this matter first.
Or maybe you're just enjoying this BL fame.