The people, places, organizations, events,
groups and professionals
depicted in this program are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Don't be sad that we can't make Mek-Kim content anymore.
I'll come see you at your house every day.
I'm going to lock my door!
Any other shocking news for today?
Just announce it all at once.
I am...
in a relationship with Park.
- Since when did you have a thing for him?
- 7 years ago.
You've had a crush on him for 7 years?
7 years that we've been together.
What should I do with this bad little boy?
What do you think I should do?
Mek!
This bad boy must be kissed!
Where are you going?
Hey, hey, hey.
Enough!
[Pam: Hey, you. I've just arrived in Thailand. Wanna meet up?]
Why are you so stressed?
You study so much your brain is going to explode at this point.
I want to get into this university,
so I need to work hard.
When you're too stressed,
you won't remember anything you read.
Look at me, I have a quiz tomorrow.
But I'm still chillin'.
Wasn't it because you were too busy chillin'
that you failed the exam last time?
I'm always chillin'.
It's my style.
Mek...
You can't just keep going on like this.
We're going to university in a few years.
Have you decided on want to study yet?
I'm considering a few options.
Either landscape or comm arts, I think.
But both of them seem hard.
I don't know if I can make it.
I don't know if I aim too high.
Stop underestimating yourself.
Be confident.
You may look incompetent,
but when you get serious, you can make it happen.
So...
Just go ahead and do whatever you want to do.
Stop procrastinating.
Otherwise, you're going to miss the opportunity to do what you love.
I thought you were giving me a compliment.
Why did it end up like a jab?
I guess now you'll have to meet the secret character.
Here!
You seem to love pranking people so much.
Why don't you make it a career then?
Can I do that? At which company? I want to apply.
I'll make Employee of the Month surely!
Some people actually do that,
like those YouTubers or content creators.
Who knows?
Maybe you'll get famous for this bad habit of yours.
This isn't a time to prank!
I though you said you were not afraid!
Are you really sure?
Mm.
I thought about it all night.
Seriously, are we breaking up over this little matter?
Mm.
If you say so.
If we want to keep this relationship,
aren't we supposed to stay close?
Distance will only create a gap between us.
I don't want to be worried about you all day.
You know how I am.
If that happens, we'll eventually break up anyway.
I think it's best to let you go now.
You words are so beautiful.
But it hurts to hear.
You know that?
I'm being serious here.
I'm trying to make it not too serious.
Up to you then.
You've already thought it through.
I'll try to understand you.
I'm sorry for being like this.
No need to say sorry.
At least you made me realize how different we are.
Thank you for being direct.
Take care of yourself over there.
Don't worry about me.
Worry about yourself first.
Just let me know if you need any help.
I'll go now.
[FLUK
Chatchawal]
[EARTH
Teerapat]
[BEW
Sitthikarn]
[DANIEL
Cheng Yu Chang]
[BOAT
Yongyut]
[KENJI
Siwarut]
[POR
Passakorn]
[YUT
Kritsadayut]
[Directed by
NATTHAMON YIMYAM]
[The Uninvited Guest]
So, what are you going to do?
Are we breaking up or what?
"I want to focus on my study."
"But I also want you with me."
"Can we be together again after I come back?"
At this point, you must choose one.
"So you don't think we can't be together..."
- The guy is so fussy, don't you think?
- Yeah.
Right.
Why does he have to hesitate?
He can't even take charge of his life.
How will he be able to take care of others?
If that was me, I'd have broken up with him long ago.
He probably has his reasons.
But it's a plain fact.
He doesn't do anything.
All he does is trying to hold on to the relationship.
It's not fair.
It's simply burdensome.
This is not the final episode yet.
I don't believe he'd be such a bad person.
Right, Captain Q.
We have to send him our moral support!
Why is the commercial break taking so long?
Is it delicious?
Kim...
Are you free today?
I'm free.
Great.
I'd like to ask you to join me.
To do what?
Well...
Something that will bring us closer.
What is it?
Okay.
Here.
So this is the thing that will bring us closer?
Isn't this close enough?
If you want us to be closer,
perhaps we should do something else.
I'm fine with anything.
But for now...
It's just so hot out here.
Here.
Put this on so you won't get too hot-headed..
Mek!
I'm not being hot-headed.
Today, I'll train you how to be calm.
So you can stop being furious with me.
Okay.
Oh!
This one looks just like the one in front of my house.
You're good at this.
At first I thought it was going to die.
But you brought it to life again.
You're so awesome!
Actually, the one on your front door came from my house.
And the dead one is actually this one.
By the way, what is it called?
It's Marguerite.
And it has a good meaning.
What is it?
It represents sincerity and true love.
You grow all these plants yourself?
I just do it little by little.
Before I know it, it becomes a forest here.
Even though you have a lot of plants,
you take care of them all so well.
You're so awesome.
I actually want to grow some more.
Make it like a plant nursery.
Once that happens, I will show it to you.
You're such a bragger!
And what is this one?
It's Monstera obliqua.
And this one?
It's Samse-Veria.
What about that little one?
This one?
Yes.
It's Crossostephium.
It's a pretty name.
Pretty and cute too, eh?
See this shrub?
Cute indeed.
This will do for today.
I put you up to great work, right?
Here.
I'm giving you this Little Fart Bag
so you can practice on how to be calm.
I'll check with you later if it survives or not.
Also...
Now you'll think of me when you see it.
Let this Fart Bag be a reminder of me.
So you give it a name?
Sure.
If you misbehave,
Fart Bag will not get any nutrients or water.
So you start threatening a plant now?
I'm threatening you!
I'm outta here.
It's so hot.
Can I put my stuff here?
I have a lot of things.
Okay.
Why did you stop telling me when you come to campus?
But I didn't tell you every time, no?
What's wrong with you?
Oh.
I didn't realize you attend this class too.
Why didn't you tell me?
We can get in class together.
I didn't know we'd meet by chance like this.
Why have I never seen you in here before?
Well, I skipped class a lot.
So...
Is this seat taken?
No.
You can sit here, Pete.
Did you watch the cat video I sent you?
So hilarious!
Yeah, I saw it.
You can send me more.
It kinda helps relieve my stress.
It's cute.
I thought you preferred dogs.
Didn't realize you're into cats now.
I don't know.
Just try to open up for something new, I guess.
It's actually...
...quite lovely.
Oh!
I have one more cat video to show you.
It's so cute.
Isn't it adorable?
Thanks for helping me with the quiz earlier.
It's fine.
Don't mention it.
Is there any chance you can have a meal with me this week?
I'll go to the men's room.
I'm actually quite busy lately.
Really?
Who did you sit next to earlier?
His nae is Mai.
Do you think he's cute?
I'm making a move on him.
Someone is coming on quite strong!
It's nothing, man.
Since he's very cute,
I need to move fast.
Hey!
Sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Who's that guy?
Don't mind him.
He's Mai's friend.
Hi!
What are you guys doing?
You seem to be in a good mood.
Anything good happened?
Is that so obvious?
Of course, we can read you like a book.
Now, stop talking.
Let's focus on the first content on Bear's Experiment.
Let me see it.
Here it is.
"Hello, Little Bear out there."
"Now you're watching Bear's Experiment channel!"
Bomb's cute, isn't he?
"And the content for today is..."
That was some grand opening, eh?
Papa bear. Mama bear.
Roar!
That's creative.
Bear, you're such a genius!
I have Bomb to thank for.
He always supports me.
I don't know how to return his favor.
All I have...
is my cute, madly-in-love self for him.
Speaking of which, I'm gonna text him to tell him I miss him.
With a selfie?
Someone is madly in love indeed.
By the way...
I think we should tell the Hailstones right away
about the fact that we will say goodbye to Thunderous Sky channel.
I'll write a script for us.
I'll try to find old footages to use then.
Hello.
What's up?
You submitted the application for me, didn't you?
Yes.
I submitted it.
I said I didn't want to apply.
Come on, babe.
I just know that you're gonna regret it later
if you let this opportunity pass you by.
I'm sorry if it feels like I'm forcing you to do it.
You get why I did it, right?
I'm always by your side to support you.
Love you.
You said 'love you' to whom?
My boyfriend.
Who is your boyfriend?
Bear, aren't you surprised by what you've just heard?
Your friend is having a boyfriend!
Park has a boyfriend!
I've known it for some time.
How do you know?
Your boyfriend told my boyfriend.
And then my boyfriend told me.
What is this?
Your boyfriend?
Whose boyfriend?
Who is your boyfriend?
I can't keep up now.
It's Lee!
Park's boyfriend.
Lee who?
Lee Min-ho?
Or Lee Joon-gi?
Neither!
It's Lee from the student club.
He studied comm arts before switching to liberal arts with Kim.
They've been together for 7 years now.
What!?
Park is with Lee!?
Yeah.
Bear...
Perhaps you can let me tell my own story.
So, what's the story?
Lee and I...
We've been together since high school.
Before I met you guys.
As of now...
It's been 7 years.
What!?
Why didn't you tell me before?
Because you never asked.
Also...
Back then...
There was some issue that Lee was worried about.
But we've put it behind us now.
What about you, Mek?
What's your story with Kim?
Stop staying silent.
You think we don't know anything?
It's already more than just the BL thing.
I knew it!
If only guessing the lotto numbers was as easy as this!
Since when?
I'm not so sure.
Before I know it...
I started feeling good to have him living next door,
to wake up to the smell of his cooking,
and to have him riding the bike with me
every morning and every evening.
I don't think you're the only one being madly in love, Bear.
We're so damn hot.
We've won the hearts of three Student Club guys.
We really live up to the slogan of our channel.
I told you...
You're gonna love me like a bang!
Now that there's no Thunderous Sky anymore,
it's like I'm forced to grow up.
I'll go wake him up.
How would you do it?
[Crossostephium]
[How to grow]
Since when did you become interested in planting trees?
I'm just browsing randomly.
Perhaps I can try doing things I've never done.
Lee...
How is it going, your photography contest?
Not much.
Park submitted the application for me.
I guess now I'll have to get a shot and submit it.
It's good then.
Just do it.
I think Park wants you to give it a try.
I'm looking forward to seeing your photo
and congratulating you.
Right.
Don't you want to enjoy such a moment with us?
Bomb and I are right here to support you.
Who knows?
In the future...
You might become a big name in photography.
You are so extra.
Just don't give up, Lee.
You see, I've never won a lottery
but I didn't give up.
One day...
I'm going to be a millionaire!
Speaking of which, it's time I checked the lottery result.
Kim...
Please cover the work for me
for the time being.
I didn't realize you're into that now.
Yeah, I have to pay special attention to this.
Getting rich in this country is not easy.
Hello, Hailstones.
We have a special announcement today.
We have been doing this channel for almost 5 years.
And it was the time of our life.
If it wasn't for Thunderous Sky,
I wouldn't have met...
Bear,
Park,
and every one of you.
After we have...
discussed it internally,
the three of us have come to a conclusion.
It is with great sadness to inform you that...
Thunderous Sky channel...
is coming to an end
and this video is its final episode.
I'd also like to take this opportunity...
to apologize to those who have been pranked by us
or fallen victims to our actions.
We sincerely apologize.
As time passes, the three of us have matured
and come to realize that
what we did was not a good thing.
It is reproachable and should not be followed.
From now on...
Although we are going on different paths that we each choose,
we will always cherish the memories we had in our hearts.
Thank you, Hailstones,
for making Thunderous Sky who we are today.
Yes!
Thunderous Sky!
Bang!
What are you guys doing?!
What the hell was that?!
Mek, you!
You guys done now?
Wait for me.
Hey!
Damn you, Mek!
Mek, my pants!
Mek!
Mek!!!
Here's one last thing we want to tell you, Hailstones.
Thank you for loving us...
...like a bang.
There will be no more Thunderous Sky channel?
I don't want it to end.
I am such a big fan.
I've watched every upload.
Without Thunderous Sky channel,
where else can I find crazy and funny people like you guys?
You have papa bear with you now, Bomb.
This Papa bear here will make you happy every day.
Thunderous Sky isn't a channel.
It's people.
Here's one last thing we want to tell you, Hailstones.
Thank you for loving us...
...like a bang.
[Until we meet again.]
Now that there's no more Thunderous Sky,
it's like I'm being forced to grow up.
I'll never get a chance
to do something like this with them again.
Apart from you,
there are only these guys...
who always encourage me to do new things.
How about...
we're going out today?
It might help carry your sadness away.
Where are you going to take me?
I'm going out to take some photos
to submit to the contest.
Anyway...
You must cheer up.
Because...
I won't be able to take good pictures...
if you're still looking sad like this.
Cheer up, okay?
Please.
Mm.
You've got me smiling since the moment
you picked up the camera.
You're the best!
Come on.
Let me give you some happy energy then.
What's all this?
I'll go take a shower and get dressed.
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
Where's Kim?
He hasn't got up yet?
Not yet.
I don't know why he gets up late today.
Okay, I'll go wake him up.
How would you do it?
Okay. I have to go now.
Bye.
Kim!
Rise and shine!
You're feeling unwell?
Hey, Kim!
I probably should go home.
You can take this bottle garden.
Why do you always make me worried?
You know, you're so good at playing with my heart.
Here's magic medicine from me.
I don't need to taste it to know that it's good!
This is awesome!
Or perhaps a little.
So I'll know how good of a chef I am!
[Make sure you finish it all
because I poured my heart into it ❤]
Oh, what is it that Kim made?
Ugh.
Kim!
Who made this soup? It tastes awful!
Did you finish it?
I'll go return the pot.
No need to wait until I finish.
Just return it fast.
Bye.
I missed Thai food so much living there.
There were some Thai restaurants but...
The taste is just not right.
Not at all.
Since I came back, I've had papaya salad almost every day.
If you love it that much, why don't you make it yourself?
Pam can't even hold a knife the right way.
She's only good at studying.
Speak for yourself!
Your cooking sucks too.
You're only good at planting trees and that's it.
Speaking of which, I want a plant for my working desk at home.
You can take bottle garden from my room.
Mm.
Hi, Kim!
Are you feeling better?
You're still sick.
You should rest at home.
I'm here to return the pot.
Oh!
This is Pam.
One of my close friends.
She just came back from overseas.
Kim, come join us for dinner.
No, Dao.
Kim isn't feeling better yet.
What if you get sick too?
Just let Kim get back to rest.
It's fine, Kim.
Just come have dinner with us.
It's okay, Dao.
I probably should go home.
I'll go now.
Get some rest so you can get better soon.
Fart Bag!
You're not going to get any food or water today
thanks to Mek.
Your room is a mess like before.
Ever thought of tidying it up?
Just let it be.
If I do that, I won't be able to find my stuff.
I'm not going to be used to that.
Got it?
Here.
I thought you stopped doing this after choosing comm arts.
We can be into different things at the same time, can't we?
Being a comm arts student doesn't mean I have to give up this.
What do you plan to do after graduation?
I don't know.
I'll think about it after senior year ends.
At my university, there's this short-term course.
It's a course on landscape architecture that you like.
If you haven't figured out what to do next,
maybe you can apply for it.
Actually, I saw the call for applications.
But I haven't decided.
You don't need to worry ahead about the result.
If you want to do it, just do it.
But...
If you do get in and have to be far away from here,
will you be okay with it?
You probably end up breaking someone's heart again.
Just like when you broke mine.
I let you go so you can meet someone nice there.
That was a huge sacrifice on my part.
That's why I'm feeling grateful as we speak.
I see. You're a celebrity now.
You have a BL partner too.
I only do it because the chancellor told me to.
Nothing much.
And don't you like him?
Yes, I like him.
A lot.
A real lot!
I'm glad that you can now declare your love for something right away,
unlike in the past
where you couldn't answer a thing.
"I don't know." "I don't like it."
If you want to do it, then just do it.
But make sure you think thoroughly.
And don't hesitate.
Whether it's a dream or a passion,
don't just let it float in the air.
Reach out your hand and grab it.
Well...
I gotta go now.
Thanks for this bottle garden.
What?
A goodbye hug.
Bye.
Tidy up, okay?
Yes, ma'am
What if Mek is the kind of guy who doesn't use the word love to express his feelings?
I made Kim upset.
I don't know how to fix it.
What did you do to him?
Something stupid, I'm sure.
If you wait any longer, it could get worse.
Hello.
Ah! About Tim's slot, right?
Sure.
I'll fit it into his schedule next week.
We're looking forward to it as well.
Thank you.
What do you think about this look?
Does it suit me?
I don't think it suits you.
Usually...
You wear it like this.
Now you're looking a lot more like yourself.
By the way...
Can you help me match an outfit?
What for?
Do you have some event to attend?
Well...
Pete asked me out for a meal.
So I want to make sure I dress well.
Where?
When?
On what date?
Why are you asking so many questions?
Do you want to join us?
Will you be there to screen him?
I don't think I have the right to do that.
You told me yourself...
that you wanted to make your own decisions.
You're right.
Thank you for letting me make my own decisions.
Mek.
Why are you hanging around here?
I'm waiting for Kim.
Is he ready?
Kim's left for campus for a while now.
Didn't he tell you?
Kim didn't tell me anything.
Did you do anything to make him upset?
It's about what happened yesterday.
Mek, you're such a fool.
Don't you have any clue?
But we were just having dinner as usual.
I didn't do anything wrong.
It's about Pam's visit.
Do I have to tell you about every single thing?
Come on, Q, let's go to school.
Alright, guys, today we're going to learn about the history of Europe.
Has anyone read in advance?
Is the first item the correct answer, Kimhan?
Did you just sigh at me?!
Do you have any idea...
how sad you're making me feel?
You've changed, Kimhan!
It's not like that, Professor.
I was just...
...spaced out.
I'm the one who sets the paper this time,
so you guys better pay attention in class.
Are you okay?
I'm upset with Mek.
I thought he was going to call me in the morning to clear things up,
but he didn't.
Since when did you become so petty?
That's just how couples are.
It may sound like no big deal
when it's about others.
Only when it happens to you
that you realize how tough it is.
Well...
Mek and I, we are not official yet.
I thought you two were already in a relationship.
Relationship what?
He never even tells me he likes me once.
He only said that...
...he was possessive of me.
Maybe Mek is the kind of guy who doesn't use the word love to express his feelings?
Maybe he'd rather demonstrate it through his actions.
What exactly did he do to upset you, though?
Well...
Yesterday his ex showed up at his house.
And he just told me to go home
because I still had a fever.
Clearly, he was worried about you.
Maybe it was just his stupid way to express it
that makes you upset like this.
Why don't you just tell him you like him
and get it over with?
You don't need to wait for him to make the first move.
You can be the one to do that.
Take me for an example.
I came on strong, but now I have Bear for myself.
He's right.
I think, in the end, you two are on the same page.
Perhaps he can be a bit shy too, you know?
So I should do it?
Give it a try.
Okay.
Let's go.
I made Kim upset.
I don't know how to fix it.
What did you do to him?
Something stupid, I'm sure.
You should patch things up with him.
If you wait any longer, it may get worse.
The thing is, I don't know what I did wrong.
I do nothing but care about him.
Where did I mess up?
My sister said it has something do with Pam showing up.
There you go.
That's where it all started.
Kim probably got jealous.
Well, well.
Didn't you get bitter too when Tim was messing with Kim?
Now, do you realize what you did?
Hurry up and make things right with him now!
I've just come up with an idea to do that.
But you guys have to help me.
The mission starts now!
Roger that!
Yeah, like that.
Add some more of this.
You have to shake it harder.
Like this.
Yeah.
Did you forget to add this?
Higher.
More right.
Q.
Are you home?
Where is she?
Woah!
Who is that?
Happy birthday, Kim.
Please don't be mad at me.
Make a wish.
What did you wish for?
Did you include me in your wish?
I like you.
What do you guys plan to do next after we graduate?
You just have to make a decision.
There's nothing complicated about it.
Is your indecisive tendency coming back?
I know you're a man-child,
but I never knew you'd be such a coward.
Do you remember that time I told you
that I want to take on something new?
And what does it have to do with Kim?
Are you by yourself?
Mai and I, we're not that inseparable.
I'm so disappointed.
I don't get why Kim even likes you.
He probably has someone else in his mind now.