Think of it as a symbol of good faith.
Now I'm here to contribute
to the enlightenment
of the Buddhist sermons,
which are both questions and answers
that complement each other.
-What was it?
-I don't know.
What the...?
Oh!
A monk! I thought you're a man.
Are you crazy, granny?
A monk is a man.
What is a monk doing around here?
Are you a real monk?
Yes, I'm a monk.
I swear.
Sis, who was struck by lightning?
A foreigner or a monk?
A foreign monk, I guess.
Three times in a row?
Bang. Bang. Bang. Seven times!
You're exaggerating.
Save your breath if you're clueless, Tu.
Where's the monk
who got struck by lightning?
Didn't he get burned to ashes?
PETCHARAT HOSPITAL
Alas, he's lying dead
in front of the room.
Father, there you are.
It's good you're here.
I'm at my wit's end.
What's the matter?
I've got a patient here. He's a monk.
He was struck by lightning.
Seems like he doesn't remember anything.
I've diagnosed him.
I think he's got amnesia, Father.
Is he able to communicate with you?
Please go talk to him, Father.
Come this way.
How are you? What's your name?
Can you speak Thai?
You can speak Thai.
This way, Father.
You two are getting along well.
Do you remember anything?
Can you remember your own name?
No?
It's all right
if you don't remember anything.
Come stay with me at the temple.
Father?
Be kind. Be kind.
Great. I'll leave him with you.
You look better, Steve.
Are you calling me Steve?
I saw "Steve" tattooed on your arm.
The patient in the VIP room
needs extra care.
I'm leaving now.
I'll see you out, Father.
-Bless you.
-Good bye.
Thank you for taking care of me.
Thank you. My pleasure.
Thank you so much.
Oh god!
We're in trouble.
We're here.
Welcome to our temple.
Please.
This place is so nice.
I like it so much.
What kind of monk is he?
I don't trust him.
He doesn't have any monk identification.
What if he's a fiend?
Perhaps it's true like you said.
So you understand what I mean.
So Vinai, I'll let you mentor Monk Steve.
Let's see if he's a real monk or a devil.
Athai, come here.
Is that the foreign monk
that was struck by lightning?
It's him.
He's got amnesia.
But I don't know if he's faking it.
I don't trust him.
From now on, your job is
To keep an eye on Monk Steve.
If you see anything suspicious,
report it to me.
You've got it. Right on.
Are you seeing it?
Almost.
Dear Lord,
-I'm seeing it.
-What are you doing?
My Buddha!
All right. What can I do for you?
I bid you farewell. There's nothing.
Why did you scream, Athai?
Brother, you scared me.
Is that the foreign monk
that was struck by lightning?
Yes.
What are you doing, Steve?
Helping the villagers scratch this tree.
People here must love trees,
so they put a powder on them.
Only at the beginning
or middle of the month.
The tree is called
the beginning-middle of the month?
No, it isn't.
Forget it.
So how are you doing?
Do you remember anything?
That's all right, at least
you know that you're a monk.
By the way, what's like being a monk?
What is it like to be a monk?
How to become a monk?
You did wrong from the first day.
Did I do something wrong?
I'm sorry.
It's good
that you acknowledge your offence.
Come. Confess your misdemeanors.
OK.
But who's Miss Demeanor?
Monk Steve, confessing one's misdemeanor‚
is when a monk did wrong and admits it.
He'll confess his guilt to a senior monk
and promise not to do it again.
I've got it.
But what did I do wrong?
You hugged the nurse tightly.
Listen to me. According to the Tripitaka
which collects 84,000 Bhuddhist sermons,
It is clearly stated that
a monk that touches
even a finger of a woman,
is committing an offense.
But that nurse wasn't a woman.
He's a ladyboy.
Although not a woman physically,
her heart is.
You're wrong anyway.
So can I hug a tomboy?
That's wrong too. A tomboy is a girl.
Although she's a woman physically,
her heart isn't. So I can hug her.
Am I staying here?
Yes.
Where's the refrigerator?
Where can I take a shower?
Any water heater here?
Brother.
Would you like to get
some breakfast coupons too?
It'd be great.
What time do I have to check out?
Stop acting funny.
This is a temple, not a hotel.
By the way, watch out for tonight.
What?
Father Mitr,
the former owner of this room.
I think he's pretty possessive.
Where's Father Mitr?
He's dead.
Dead?
Dead.
Where are you going?
You are‚
I'm Monk Noi, Monk Steve.
Will you go asking for alms?
What's asking for alms?
It is giving Buddhists a chance
to make a merit.
Saving mankind from sin.
Can you keep it short?
Ah, it's when we have breakfast.
I'll go with you. I'm hungry.
What is it like to be a monk?
How can we become a monk, Monk Steve?
Are you asking me?
I think being a monk is to have no hair.
No hair?
You have no hair.
Neither I nor Father has hair.
Monks have no hair. Right?
No hair. No him.
No us.
It means we let ourselves on.
Vinai, the villagers were here yesterday
scratching trees to get a lottery hint.
I've warned them many times,
but they never listen.
Why are they so stubborn?
You'd better be strict with them.
Come on.
You. You. You!
Can I change my room tonight?
I saw a ghost last night.
What ghost?
The ghost of Father Mitr. So scary.
Steve, ghosts do exist.
But they only exist in your imagination.
Get back in the line. Go on. Hurry up.
Father Mitr isn't dead yet.
He left and got married
in Japan two months ago.
Ayu Wanno Sukkhang Palang.
If you can't give a blessing, just mumble.
OK.
Mumble.
Ayu Wanno Sukkhang Palang.
Good grief! The monk's eating a banana!
Shut your mouth!
You can't eat with an alms bowl in hand.
What did I do wrong? I don't get it.
It isn't proper.
Monks can only eat in the temple.
We must have self control.
Why are monks
forbidden from doing many things?
I don't understand.
To restrain themselves from desire.
Desire is a temptation.
Steve, do you see that?
That muzzle on the dog's mouth
is for quenching the dog's desire.
Desire is hard to quench.
A muzzle's on that dog's mouth
because that dog bites.
Other dogs are without muzzles.
They bite no one,
so they need not be restrained.
But I don't wanna bite anyone.
Hello, Kat. How are you, gorgeous?
When will you come to Petchburi?
Could you afford to look after me?
You'll never guess how much I eat.
My dad is calling me. Bye bye.
You lie to her that you're rich.
If she was, what would you do, Jack?
I will...
ask my mom for money.
Fat chance.
She's as fierce as a rottweiler.
Look.
I've got an idea.
Jack would like to be ordained.
I take him to your care.
If he has a strong will,
I can't object to his intention.
It's a good thing that Jack
wants to be ordained for his mother.
What about you, Toh?
I want to get married in a group.
I mean I want to be ordained in a group.
Hurry up, Father.
The host has called us many times.
Who's inviting us in, Mr.Pang?
All of a sudden.
It's Mr.Tang. I don't dare to refuse him.
Brother, hurry up.
You don't need to come.
You can't pray even a single chapter.
What did I do wrong?
Why can't I hang out with you guys?
Hang out?
The invitation
is to be out visiting laymen.
Let's go, Father.
Monk Steve,
stay here and watch over the temple.
When I'm back
I'll tell you about the invitation.
OK.
Brother. Father. Aren't we going now?
We'll be late.
That's right. To keep the host waiting is
Not a good idea!
Stay here and clean up the toilets.
They invited monks, not novices.
Here come the monks. I'd better go now.
Kluay!
Father, seeing you here
makes me so glad.
What drama are you trying to start? Hmm?
I'm dying.
Now that I'm dying,
I'd better die with these three monks.
Always think of death.
Careless people
are those who are already dead.
Here you are, Father.
I'm just a Brother.
Please pass it to him.
You don't need to give us
the money right now.
You can give it to us
after we finished preaching.
It isn't money.
I think you should read it.
Bad guys' lives don't end nicely.
Stop running on the treadmill
and your life will be torn.
Don't tell me...
That's right. A bomb.
If he stops running, he'll die.
Now that I'm dying,
I want to cling onto your yellow robes
and go to Heaven with you.
Mr.Tang,
where did you get this belief from?
Do you really need three robes
to cling to?
One isn't enough.
I have a lot of bad karma.
Why didn't you stop to think of them?
Now you’re scared.
I don't think it's a monk's business.
Nor is it mine.
Father!
I give up.
Now that I'm dying,
I'd better die with these three monks.
Calm down, mister.
Nice guys finish last. Bad guys win.
Think of good deeds that you did.
Thinking of them will give you energy.
I tried, but I can't think of any.
Think of something simple.
Such as stopping
for old people crossing the street.
I hit and killed them.
They blocked my way.
Have you ever
given your leftovers to dogs?
I don't even give them bones.
I chewed them down.
He's so blackhearted.
A bad guy like this should be dead.
Kluay!
Are you nagging me?
Boss!
What are you yelling for?
I can hear you from the outside.
-Father, Good morning.
-Wow, you're being so polite.
A bomb...
Bomb? Are you nuts?
You worry so much that
you've become paranoid.
Why did you involve monks
in your nonsense?
You'll go to hell.
Why are you leaving this on?
-When you...
-No!
How many times have I told you
If you finish using it,
you need to pull the plug.
You're wasting energy. Got it?
-Got it?
-All right.
Now that there's nothing else here,
We're leaving.
Or we'll run late for the meal time.
Goodbye.
Hurry up.
Just a threatening letter.
What are you so scared of?
Why shouldn't I?
It said there's a bomb
under my treadmill.
This is another letter.
What's this?
If you stop moving, it'll go ka-boom!
Your very bad deeds will break you down.
Sometimes, being close to death
is a good mental practice,
don't you think?
But I think it's too exciting.
It's not a good idea.
Father!
Father! Wait for me.
Why are you following us, Mr.Tang?
How could I not?
The bomb is under my shoe.
A bomb!
Pang, drive faster. Faster.
Brother Vinai and Brother Noi,
you're impatient.
I guess they're afraid
they'll be late for the meal time.
Damn you, Tang!
-Father?
-I'll have to confess my misdemeanors.
Please give me your yellow robe,
so I can cling onto it and go to heaven.
Pick up the yellow robe.
Step on it. Don't be slow.
Father, this is the fastest I can drive.
It's your order, Father.
Do you have any good spell
you can perform?
-Spell.
-Spell?
All right, Mr. Tang.
Put your palms together.
Raise your hands.
All right. All right.
Share loving kindness.
Pang, drive faster.
There's a bomb with him.
Mr.Tang's got a bomb?
Brother! Brother!
So long.
It's beeping again.
-Father!
-That's great.
Stop the truck!
There's an example.
Is that Tang?
Is he being chased by a dog?
-Hurry up, Pang.
-Father!
Those are monks.
Is that the charity run?
What happened?
Wait for me.
Why don't you stop?
I'm calling you right now.
That's Mr.Tang.
What happened? Why is he running?
Brother!
Let us go.
Keep running!
Here, some water.
Who said people here hate me?
I have a bomb tied to my shoe
and they're running after me.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
There's a bomb in his shoe.
Where are we going now?
Bye for now.
Brother, I have to excuse myself.
Bye bye, sir.
Did you have fun hanging out?
Not at all. We barely survived.
The world is ruled by Karma.
Father!
Karma is following us. Monk Vinai! Father!
Father, please be merciful.
I think
We should stay apart for a while, Mr.Tang.
How could you say so?
You're a monk. Why are you so heartless?
Nice shoes.
I like them. They have lights too.
Yes, lights. I like them too.
How did you take my shoes off?
Perhaps they're running out of batteries.
Let me change the battery for you.
No!
You can leave them right there.
It's just a fake bomb.
Bastard! Who played this trick on me?
If I knew who you were, I'd kill you.
Mr.Tang, you should improve yourself.
Avoid things that are not good.
Yeah? Stop talking!
Are you afraid of dying, sir?
Kluay, why are you saying that?
Who isn't afraid of dying?
I've got a solution.
What solution?
If you're scared
that someone will kill you,
you have to kill yourself first.
Bastard!
You're advising me to kill myself?
Are you nuts?
Well,
I mean you should kill your old self.
And act as a new person.
Well said.
But I can't do it
because I'm not an actor.
I used to be an actor.
What proof do you have?
Do you remember last Chinese New Year?
Last Chinese New Year?
The ghost of your father.
The day that my papa's ghost
possessed you?
He didn't just pay a visit.
He ate all of my food offering.
Kluay, what's wrong with you?
Bastard!
You ungrateful child.
Papa?
Yeah. You snaggle-tooth.
Yes, it's Papa.
You never make any merit for me.
It's not that I never do. I have no time.
How much have you got?
Well... well...
This is all I've got.
Five grand?
I'll take this money
to make merit for myself.
But it's not enough to go to Heaven.
Not enough? Here you are.
Petchaboon ring. Sweet.
Watch.
Here's my watch.
There are seven levels of heaven.
Your necklace.
Are you making merit or buying a car?
Here.
Hey?
You fooled me.
That's awesome.
You're a genius.
-I'm a genius, right?
-Yes.
-I'm so awesome, right?
I want you to pay attention to my acting.
That isn't important.
Give me back my money.
It's for showing respect to your teacher.
Waste no more time.
We should get started now.
Madame.
I'm hungry.
I haven't eaten anything yet, Madame.
Please have mercy on me.
Think of it as merit making, madame.
Please.
Wait for me right here.
I wish your next life
will be full of happiness.
Eat it quickly.
My husband is coming home.
My husband is heartless.
He only has bad karma.
I always make merit whenever I can,
hoping that my merit will go to him.
Hurry up and eat.
It isn't that easy.
If you're really hungry,
you will eat it like this.
Kluay, why did you do that?
Master taught me to do this.
You know that he doesn't like beggars.
He hates them like poison.
He said beggars weren't really hungry.
If he's really hungry,
he will eat it off the floor.
Both of you are psychos.
Look at him.
How could you? It's so filthy.
Dogs walk in and out here.
Not to mention shoes.
Master taught me to do this.
Do you wanna have a problem with him?
Will you give it to me or not?
I'm asking you nicely. Don't irritate me.
Mr.Tang.
I can't give the thing you asked.
No, it isn't true.
Why can't you give it to me?
Why don't you come here
to talk with me yourself?
Father, don't change the subject.
Everything in the temple
was made with my money.
That's mine.
This is mine.
This is mine too.
That's a septic tank.
I'm claiming it too!
Mr.Tang,
if you make merit just to show off,
That isn't real merit.
If you do bad deeds
but try to conceal them,
that's real sin.
I know that you have a lot of good stuff.
The only good stuff that I have
is dharma.
Dharma is what will protect you.
Not amulets.
Can you stop barking?
Mister. Mister.
Shut up!
Damn you! I will take you down.
Mister. Mister.
I'm sorry, Father.
This isn't our business.
I have to excuse myself. Bless you.
Bless you is for monks to say.
Right, Father.
Bless you.
Do you have an M-16?
I'll shoot them all.
Are you shooting monks, sir?
I'll shoot these dogs.
They barked too much. It's annoying.
Let's go.
The two-digit prize. The numbers are
One-Four
I lost again.
It's 14. Right on.
It isn't a big deal that I didn't buy it.
But why didn't you buy it?
That banana fell on your palm.
Who said I didn't?
So you won the lottery?
I did, but I didn't reverse the numbers.
I bought 41.
Monk Steve, please eat a lot.
Yes, eat a lot. Lots of good food.
It's from KFC.
I have to thank you, Monk Steve,
for making me win the lottery.
Thank you so much.
Monk Steve.
Eat a bit of everything,
so that everyone's faith
is equally recognized.
Satu.
He enjoys spicy food.
Eating in Laman style,
Not holding onto sight, taste, or smell.
It's delicious.
Dharma tastes like the food you ate.
It isn't good
to eat food that's too spicy.
to eat food that's too sweet.
Whether it's sour or salty,
it needs to be put just right.
That's the taste of dharma.
It's called the middle path.
The path of dharma
makes me feel nauseated.
Damn. How did he do that?
What's the matter with you, Athai?
Yeah, yeah, Monk Steve...
-He threw me on the floor!
-Brother Steve.
I scolded him, but he didn't listen.
What's more amazing is that
I dropped the plates
And Monk Steve caught them like this.
A moment ago, I threw a rock at him.
And he caught it.
Is it true?
Yes.
Are you sure?
See it for yourself.
Athai, you said he could catch it.
I have no idea.
That hurts. Are you trying to kill a monk?
Monk Vinai, Monk Noi.
I remember now.
Is your memory back?
I remember that I'm a foreigner.
He just remembered it now?
And he even called himself "I".
Boss, how many times did I tell you
that you shouldn't eat carelessly?
Why?
You know that someone wants to kill you.
This is dangerous.
You won't know if it's poisoned.
Damn it. You're rational.
Where would I be, if you died?
Let me die first.
You're so awesome.
I've hired the right man.
Don't be courteous with me, sir.
We should start with this thigh.
How is it?
It's a left thigh.
It's surely safe.
If it's deadly,
you'll be the first one to die.
Definitely, sir.
I love you like a father.
This is a bone.
You can have it. It's calcium.
I'm eating bones.
You're pleasing me.
Once in a while,
we have a meal together. We're all happy.
Do you normally eat chicken's ass, Master?
Chicken's ass? No.
It's full of shit.
Neither do I. Here you are.
-Meat?
-Ass.
You can keep it for yourself.
If it comes through,
my stomach will be so light.
Awesome.
Boss, have I ever failed you?
You know that I've closed many hard deals.
Give me more time.
I won't let Tang go.
I've been following him for so long.
Don't make me stop now.
I'm getting close to him.
I promise
I'll close the deal as fast as I can.
Are you trying to take me down?
No way. I'm not stupid.
Did you see that killer?
Damn it.
This is what I wanna see
from my bodyguards.
You all lay down quickly.
Get up.
I'm asking you
if you saw that bold killer.
No, sir.
There's no fan in the toilet?
You're sweating.
I eavesdropped on him.
Damn it. I heard it with my own ears.
He said he wouldn't miss this time.
Soon...
He'll kill me.
Mhuay?
You've been on a school break
quite a while now.
You said you're coming home.
Why aren't you here yet?
I've been back a while.
But I don't wanna go home.
I'm fed up with you.
You're back but you're fed up with me?
Where are you now? Who are you with?
I'm at the temple, practicing dharma.
You're at the temple?
What are you doing there?
Mhuay. Mhuay!
Mhuay, come here.
Papa, what's wrong with you?
I should be asking you that.
You said you'd come home
during the school break.
I won't.
I said go home. It's dangerous outside.
How can I be safe staying at home?
Papa, look at yourself.
I think you need to come
to the temple sometimes.
I said go home.
I won't.
Mhuay,
this is your dad ordering you to go home.
-I won't.
-you have to.
-You‚
All right, I will.
What's the matter
with this father-daughter pair?
I just want him to come to the temple.
So that he'll get close to dharma.
Look at how he behaves lately.
He's gone too far. He disguises himself.
We barely recognize him.
Hurry up. It's getting dark.
I'm going home.
-My mom must be waiting for me.
-Come.
Here.
So what's your plan?
I haven't chatted with Kat for many days.
To make her believe that you're rich,
At least you'll need
a cool phone to show her.
Where do you think
I can get the money?
We've become novices
but haven't gotten any money.
I asked my mom,
but she just bawled me out.
What's up, novices?
How much is it?
Five baht each. It's pork.
Well‚
I'm very hungry.
Oh.
Ayu Wanno Suphan.
Thank you.
Well,
did you see what I saw?
How are you doing, Monk Steve?
What rule did you break today?
No. Nothing.
Want some?
One stick has five balls.
One-five, five-one.
Did he eat them all at once?
No. He ate three balls in one bite.
Are you sure? My wife will kill me.
Three balls in one bite.
two more sticks. Ten Baht.
You're nuts!
I have to confess again?
You did wrong. You have to.
What did I do wrong?
I ate inside the temple,
not outside.
You just ate meat balls, didn't you?
The mealtime is over.
Water is the only thing you can drink.
I didn't know that.
How could you not know?
You never told me.
I got it.
I was wrong because I didn't know.
People who do not know
are certainly not wrong.
Who said?
Monks here.
So did I do wrong?
Mr. Jobs,
If it's possible,
I'd like to have an iPhone.
If I get an iPhone, I will
run naked around the temple.
Amen.
The last three digits... Fourth round.
The numbers are
Three-Five-One.
The numbers from Monk Steve's hint.
I won the lottery!
-Did my wife win it?
-I don't know.
I think there will be only us
going out for alms.
Because Father Tee's a bit ill.
Ill? What?
He's caught a cold. He's sick.
Monk Steve, lead the way.
Am I leading you?
Go.
Monk Noi, stay behind.
Is that a good idea?
At least I can watch
and save him from misbehaving.
Wait.
I know that you want it.
Here's your new mobile phone.
Damn it.
Ifong?
Ayu Wanno Sukkhang Palang.
Ayu Wan--
Wanno
Sukkhang
Palang!
-Brother, please be invited.
-Brother.
Please give us a blessing too.
Ayu Wanno Sukkhang Palang.
Sappei Sapta Avera Honetu.
May you find happiness. Don't commit sin.
Sappei Sapta.
Brother, please be invited.
Oh god!
I'll miss you everyday.
I'd ask you to miss me every night.
I'll miss you every moment I'm awake.
I'll miss you every single night.
Continue your rhyme later at the temple.
Brother, won't you bless us?
Hello, Kat.
I'm on my private beach right now.
You said you would come here
for a vacation.
The sea here is beautiful.
You can wear a bikini and swim here.
Really? Pick me up tomorrow.
What?
Tomorrow?
I'm kidding.
Maybe next month.
Jack, I don't like liars.
Well...
Toh, you chose the background
near the chapel?
Me?
I...I...I...
I had to be ordained for my mom.
But I didn't mean to lie to you.
I have always dreamed of
a good guy who's into dharma.
And you are a grateful child.
See you later.
Mercy. Do a merit with this blind man.
I'm not here to plead to you.
Here we go.
I haven't eaten anything.
I've gone hungry.
Oops. Oops. Oops.
Aoi, are you bullying me?
If you wanna pretend to be a blind man,
you need to bump around
to make it look real.
Mama, are you playing along with him?
It's your dad's idea.
Don't talk so loud.
Mhuay, I don't know who wants to kill me.
But I do.
People collected money to kill you.
They all hate you. Don't you realize?
Mhuay, what did you say?
Ask them if you don't believe me.
Why do you have to come here?
I'm here to find out
if they hate me so much.
I don't think you should risk it.
Stand still and you won't get hurt.
Are you guys Papa's henchmen?
That's right, Miss.
Please come home with us.
Get off me!
Miss, don't struggle. Go!
I'm pregnant.
Huh? You're pregnant?
Yes. If I miscarry, it'll be your fault.
Uncle, is that Mr. Tang?
Yes. It's that damn Tang!
Uncle, why did you say his name like that?
He always says that.
Uncle, he's my boss.
Cover for me.
-How could you call him so?
-Good job.
He's like my second dad.
That's right.
Kluay, you've been working with Tang.
Don't you know how fake he is?
He's only good to the people
he can benefit from.
Cheats in the rice-pledging scheme.
He's a loan shark.
He cheats dogs.
He cheats beggars.
Bastard!
I've heard many people
wanna take Tang down.
Huh? She's pregnant while in the temple?
What did you say?
Miad called me and said
A girl that's practicing dharma
at the temple
announced that she's pregnant.
Who got her pregnant?
Don't tell me it's some monk!
Bastard!
Girls these days are liars.
-Spoiled.
-Right.
They don't care to study.
Their parents must be bad‚
and don't teach them.
The whole family are bastards.
What?
Hello?
I can't hear you.
Huh?!
Mhuay's pregnant?
What's this?
-Papa!
-Yeah. Go!
Where are we going?
Where, Papa?
Stop talking.
Mhuay.
For goodness sake, my child.
You've just come here and you're pregnant?
Never mind, Papa.
Who is the baby's father?
Some temple boy?
No.
Don't tell me that...
it's a caretaker.
Papa, it's nobody. I was just kidding.
Kidding?
I kidded with your mom and got you.
Watch me. I'll drag him out,
the father of your baby.
Is it you, Monk Vinai?
I used to have faith in you.
I'm so disappointed with you.
It isn't Monk Vinai.
What proof do you have?
It's definitely not Monk Vinai.
Recently he was bitten by ants.
What?
They are swollen.
What are swollen?
Testicles.
Swollen testicles.
Father,
I think you'd better see a doctor now.
You can't make anyone pregnant.
Using the toilet is hard enough for you.
Is it that bad, Monk Vinai?
Do you have any evidence
to defend yourself?
No.
No for what?
No, I don't like girls.
What?
I understand.
Is it you, novice?
Can a wet dream make someone pregnant?
I'm still a virgin.
What about you, officiator?
I'm infertile.
I've slept with my wife many years,
but we still don't have a baby.
Or‚
He's too young. No.
What the hell is happening?
Who's my daughter's guy?
What are you guys doing?
Is it you, Monk Steve,
who got Mhuay pregnant?
Pregnant?
Yes, she is pregnant with me.
Papa, no! Stop it!
-Mhuay!
-Then‚
It's Monk Steve's responsibility.
OK.
Oh, he said OK.
I only practice Balinese with Mhuay.
Why is Tang so angry? I don't understand.
Practice?
Not pregnant?
The truth is the truth.
It will reveal itself.
Don't you worry.
So Monk Noi, are you really gay?
Even you have a problem.
I had no choice.
Are you ready to confess your guilt?
Mhuay!
Child, you're stubborn.
Is the door locked?
Yes.
She didn't open it for you?
Why did you ask me so?
If this scene was in a movie,
It would mean Mhuay is committing suicide.
Mhuay, no!
Panic time.
Why are you still here? Go.
This is my daughter's room. I'll go in.
Wait for me downstairs. Go!
Mhuay? Mhuay! My baby!
Mhuay!
-Papa, What are you doing?
-Open the door.
I said open the door. Mhu--
Why are you bashing in?
The bath tub is filled with blood!
Mhuay, are you all right?
Come here. Sit here.
I'm fine.
How? There's a razor here.
Where's the wound? Tell me.
This is dangerous. You're blood-soaked.
Tang, what are you doing?
She was committing suicide.
Are you nuts?
Do you see this razor?
It's good I was there in time.
If I hadn't found her,
think how it would have been.
Mhuay's got her period.
What?
She's got her period!
I told you that our girl's now a woman.
I'm bawling you out. Why are you laughing?
I'm so happy.
You can blast me for anything.
What are you so happy about?
Remember when you were pregnant with me...
No! With my baby.
You didn't have a period.
Then Mhuay was born.
What are you talking about?
It's embarrassing.
I have to ask you for forgiveness,
Father. I caused a scene here.
The one you need to apologize to isn't me.
I owe you an apology, Brothers.
I owe you an apology too, Brother Steve.
It's good that you're OK.
I heard that you were committing suicide.
No. It was just a misunderstanding.
If it became true,
Your parents would be the most devastated.
Sappitiyo Wiwach Chantu.
Sapparoko Winas Satu.
Good work.
Father, here's your medicine.
Thank you, Vinai.
Father.
Heart disease is dangerous.
You're running out of medicine too.
I think you should go to see a doctor.
That's all right. I'm getting better.
I'm getting better, right?
How's Steve, Vinai?
Is he doing better?
He's acting up. Unpredictable.
Steve is like a baby.
He's growing up.
He'll become something with your guidance.
I'll leave him in your care.
Yes, sir.
Father.
For the robe offering ceremony this year,
we should gather the villagers' faith
and renovate our chapel to be beautiful,
so people will come here to make merit.
Being in the temple physically
is useless, Monk Vinai.
If their heart is far from dharma,
even if they're all living in the temple,
I don't see any use.
Father.
Why do we need to meditate?
Mediatation is to become aware
of your mind.
Our minds move too fast.
If we're aware of our minds,
We can control them.
Sadness is in our minds.
So is happiness.
Oh, I don't want to be sad.
Then you have to know
what causes suffering.
I have no idea. I've got amnesia.
Why don't you start thinking?
Do you have any suffering?
Monk Steve.
We're born with two ears,
but only one mouth.
It means listen more and talk less.
Then why do you talk a lot?
I see you preach to everyone all the time.
I'm old.
I've listened a lot.
So I need to speak more,
to teach the young like you.
Itipi So Pakawa
Arahang Samma Sumbhudtho
Why are we walking?
We're digging a pond here.
For the three-digit prize, the numbers are
two-five-one.
BUILT FOR THE TEMPLE BY MR.TANG
Are you here to make merit?
I'm here to expiate my sins.
I'm rescuing these animals.
What are you releasing to the river?
I see no fish.
I'm sinful.
A few fish
won't be enough to redeem my sin.
I'm releasing mosquito larvae.
Won't there be more mosquitos?
Have you seen any visions
or flashbacks recently?
Yes, that's what I have.
Will I be all right?
I think you're retrieving your memory.
Then it's good news, Monk Steve.
About your pilgrimage
to Myanmar this year‚
it's not allowed.
Let me perform a check-up on you,
to see if you can travel.
My nurse said
you left this at the hospital.
Perhaps it holds a clue to who you were
before you got amnesia.
Then I'll never know who I was.
The self doesn't exist.
There's only the image
we're trying to make.
Who do you think you were in the past?
The real happiness
isn't having your hopes fulfilled.
It's learning how to let it go
when you fail.
Do you still want to know your past?
Neither past nor future is real.
What's real is the present.
But I think you'd better have some ideas.
I know where we should start.
This is the only mall
that has these price tags.
Does it look familiar?
It's no use.
M-100 drink might be an alm.
An alm?
Good evening, everyone.
Welcome to the temple fair,
our annual merit day.
Now that you're here,
please pay homage to the sacred
Buddha image inside the chapel.
Then come to the facilitator office
to donate money.
Tonight is the night.
We are all glad
to see so many of you here.
We have some entertainment
to light up your hearts.
What are we having tonight, Mr.Pang?
-There's a dance.
-Having an annual fair,
the temple is so lively.
Shoot it, Toh. One in the middle.
The one in the middle?
Brother, hold this.
I'll show you what accuracy means.
Give me more bullets.
Gun fight?
Are you stealing my girl? I'll shoot you.
Brother, no!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
You might hit the monk.
Stand back.
Stand back. I don't wanna commit a sin.
You're in trouble.
Shooting a monk or a man are equal sins.
If you don't want to commit a sin,
Shoot no one.
You'd better stand back.
If you don't comply, I'll shoot you.
Brother!
Holy shit!
It's a darn bullet!
He's so sacred.
Kothang Katawa Sukhang Seti.
Kill anger and you'll find happiness.
Oh!
I have an idea how to make money.
The truth of life is emptiness.
We're all born from emptiness.
The world was also born from emptiness.
Is it right, everyone?
-Yes, Father.
-All sensations
are not real.
Light is born from darkness.
Without darkness, there's no light.
Therefore,
neither light nor darkness is real.
How do we know what's right or wrong?
Monk Steve, imagine that you have a stick.
How long should it be to be just right?
I'm not so sure.
Monk Steve.
The stick that's long enough
to be a walking cane
might not be used to pick fruit.
Right or wrong depends on the intent.
And what's karma?
What if I don't know my karma?
I'm not scared of what I don't know.
What scares me is what I know.
We know what's right or wrong.
We know what isn't good.
If it's wrong and we still do it,
that's scary.
Isn't it true?
Yes, it is.
Monk Vinai.
Yes, Father?
You've taught Monk Steve a lot.
Yes, sir.
I barely recognize
that this is the monk
that hugged a nurse at the hospital.
Yes, sir.
Am I right, Monk Noi?
Father!
I think he has overworked himself.
I'd like to put him on observation.
Oh, Father.
Monk Vinai, I think you need to replace
Father to take care of the temple.
Jack, do you think it's cool?
Cool. Monk Steve's a foreigner.
OK is his signature.
-OK?
-Yeah.
What's a signature?
A name signing, I guess.
Novices, what are you doing?
Making coins of Monk Steve
to give to people who have faith.
Yes.
Let me see.
Here it is.
Put them all in the bag.
I'll throw them away.
-You'll throw them away?
-Yeah.
Father doesn't like amulets.
You said you didn't believe it.
How could I not believe it?
He put his finger
in the gun to stop the bullet.
It was awesome.
I saw it with my own eyes.
And all of a sudden,
coins came up under the bodhi tree.
Luckily, I went to the temple.
There's one more coin.
Really? I want it too.
It is still possible,
But good things comes at a high price.
There aren't many coins left.
I'll pay any price.
What's the matter, Pang?
You're all here.
They are here to buy Monk Steve coins.
But I don't have any coins.
We aren't allowed to carry money.
It's against the monk's rules.
It's a different kind of coin.
Someone wanted to buy it from me.
He gave me ten grand,
but I didn't sell it.
It's awesome.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm the one who threw away these coins.
Father is against the idea of amulets.
But he's ill at the moment.
Brother, look. They're all here.
Don't spoil their faith.
Please let Monk Steve make coins for them.
That's right.
Believe what he said.
Anything that Brother Vinai wants,
I'll make it happen.
How did you come here?
Just make Monk Steve coins.
Right, guys?
Yeah, that's right.
Okay, I'll give it a try.
Dhammae Katana Paro-oka.
You can't deny people's faith.
The date that the charms go on sale
will be announced later.
No need to wait.
People's faith can't wait.
So holy.
Can I use these coins to buy things?
Calm down.
Calm down. Calm down.
Here you are.
You didn't get one? Here you are.
-Athai.
-Yes, sir?
We've got a lot or merit-making money.
Next year, we'll have
the most beautiful chapel in the province.
Calm down.
Be patient, sir.
Why did the villagers want those coins?
Because you're famous.
I'm famous?
Father named me randomly.
I don't know if I'm a real monk.
There are many of us.
How could you let Monk Steve disappear?
Go on, Kluay. Find him.
Don't come back until you find him.
Go away!
You nag me every day.
If I get out of here...
This is the reason I hired you!
You've got some nerve.
Can you tell me who sent you here?
It doesn't matter.
Don't forget,
we're in a temple.
At least you need to respect
the yellow robes.
A professional doesn't mind the place.
Wait.
How much did they give you?
I'll double it.
There's no need, sir.
Three times more.
I'm professional enough.
-Four times more.
-If only I could close a deal on you,
then I could rest in peace.
I'm not gonna make it.
Accidental discharge. Sorry.
It's a new mosquito repellent machine,
MTX, from Germany.
2,999 Baht.
Order ten machines and pay
just 2,550 Baht each.
30 machines,
and I'll give you a lot of freebies.
Can you hold it?
If you don't like my machine,
I can offer you facial cream instead.
Your face will be so white.
If you don't like it,
I have glasses. Try them on.
Help me out, I haven't met my sales goal.
You prick!
You're so dead!
Oh shit!
Somebody help me!
What have I done to you
to mess up my face?
-What about our share?
-Yeah.
What share?
We started the coins.
We deserve to get a share.
The villagers' merit-making money?
If you used it,
Hell would come down on you.
You'd better attend to your duties.
Your duty is over there.
Sweep up those leaves.
What? This isn't fair.
He didn't respect our initiative.
Shit!
Kat will be here tomorrow.
What are you going to do?
What should I do?
It's a sin.
What's a sin? I'm stealing my own money.
Can I ask you something?
Do you really love Kat?
I love her the most.
Hi Jack! Hi Toh!
My dad's car is broken down.
How lucky that you drove here.
Sorry.
No problem.
Buy me meals and take me out, Jack.
My dad bought this place.
Next year, he will build a resort here.
I really hope you'll come back again.
I'll open a suite for you.
Wait.
Toh.
Can't you think of
going somewhere far away?
That's what I'm thinking.
I'll be right back.
Shall we continue?
Wanna have some snacks?
I don’t want any snack.
I bought them for you.
What else would you like to eat?
I wanna eat cat.
You horny brat.
I thought you're rich.
Is this all you've got?
Are you worth my gas expense?
Your phone is just a fake iphone.
Damn you!
Jack!
Did we sandwich Kat?
Sandwich, my ass.
It's your Kat. She ripped us off.
It isn't true.
Kat isn't that kind of girl.
You can wait for your darling here.
I'm out of here.
Toh!
Toh! Wait up!
I don't understand.
Why did she do this to me?
If you're broke, don't brag.
From Kat
No!!
Thank you so much.
You're my true friend.
For better or worse,
you're always with me.
I'm always with you
because...
because I love you.
What the hell is with you?
Don't kid me like this.
We've been friends since we were young.
I've loved you since we were little.
Damn!
What a hell of a day!
Where are you going?
Far away from you, freak.
Don't follow me or I'll punch you.
Where have you been, novice?
It's late at night.
Toh, my friend, turned out to be gay.
He just confessed his love to me.
Then why are you sad?
Will you love him back?
No, Brother. I'm not gay.
The one who should be sad is Toh.
Toh loves you, but you don't love him.
Why are you sad?
Just think that I kidded you.
I love you too, but I'm not gay.
Got it?
Yeah.
You shocked me more
than getting ripped off by Kat.
When did you find out?
As long as I can remember.
Since I was little.
You and I often showered
in front of the mirror.
Enough. Enough.
Forget it.
You understand me. Right?
Yes.
I won't be scared of what I don't know.
What scares me is what I know.
We know what's right or wrong.
If it's wrong and we still do it,
that's scary, isn't it?
Monk Noi.
I think I know
who I used to be in the past.
I think I used to be a killer.
I already know.
I always see your killer instinct.
Even today, I still see it.
You're the most determined killer
that I've ever seen.
Are you talking to me?
Who are you?
Don't get too close to me.
Monks can't be close to women.
I think I should go now.
Monk Steve.
Why are you in a hurry to see me?
I've now realized
I was a killer.
My duty was
to kill you, Father.
No killer warns his victim in advance.
And killing an old monk
isn't a hard job, is it?
Bad guys don't call themselves bad.
If your heart knows what is wrong,
you can say you have a good heart.
Remember
that I told you everything's empty?
Thank you, Father.
Can I ask you for a favor?
Take me back to the temple.
It's very dangerous.
If I don't get killed,
I'll die of old age.
GRAND SACRED AMULET SALES
ONE DAY ONLY
Here they are.
In sacks.
So admirable.
Father put an incantation
on the Monk Steve coins himself.
Pang, you're close to him, right?
Can you get me a few coins, pal?
You're all here
because you want
to have a sacred amulet.
-Yes.
-Yes, Father.
I won't ask much of your time.
If you want to get good things,
pay attention to what I say.
Pay attention.
I'm glad to see you visiting the temple.
But you know what?
Your hearts are so far away from dharma.
Dharma isn't an object or a building.
Isn't it true, Monk Vinai?
Yes, Father.
Isn't it true, Monk Noi?
Don't let these things
mislead us.
What are you doing?
Monk Steve asked me to do this.
What we are burning
is worth a lot of money.
What I want to sell you
is this old chapel.
It is useless.
Does anyone want to buy it?
No. You can't sell it.
We won't let you sell it.
It's no use to have a chapel made of gold,
if it pulls our hearts away from dharma.
The Buddhist sermon is the only amulet
that I want you to keep
within your hearts.
Whether you are happy or sad,
always think of it.
You want us to burn it.
I'll burn it now.
Burn it. Burn it. Burn it.
See? I told you guys
Monk Steve was really an assassin.
Do you think we have to tell the police?
If he'd been a bad guy,
I would have been dead.
Being good or bad
isn't about the past or future.
It's up to the present.
It's on us to choose what to be.
Mister Tang!
They're scared of us.
The mask is removed by the heart.
If a bad heart is lost,
Nobody will feel sorry.
It's you.
All right. You can kill me now.
I can't get away from you.
Bang! Bang!
Mhuay?
Yes, it's me.
Papa, were you happy
when those children ran up and hugged you?
I was.
If you're nice, if you're a good guy,
everyone would love you.
Just like I did when I was little.
I felt that I loved you.
Your hug felt warm.
Me too.
I want the old Tang back.
I have a lot more threatening letters.
My daughter and I wrote them.
You acted ridiculous
with your crazy disguises.
Remember when you wanted to eat something,
and you had to eat
your henchmen's leftovers.
Because you're afraid to die!
Are you really happy?
Papa.
How rich is enough for you?
Do you know how much I wanna hug you?
There's no father
that doesn't love his child.
Why don't you hug me, kid?
Only if you're the same person
you used to be.
I love you.
I do everything
for my daughter and my wife.
Looking at ants? They're so natural.
Brother.
I want to become a monk.
TODAY,
THERE ARE ABOUT 700 MILLION
BUDDHISTS AROUND THE WORLD
MAKING BUDDHISM
ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT RELIGIONS.
You think he's faking it?
I don't think so.
I think he's enlightened.
No.
You don't believe me?
Let me show you.
I can do anything, and he won't get angry.
-Really?
-I'll show you.
He has changed.
What a good guy.
He's really reached dharma.
I envy him so much.
We should leave him in peace.
My fingers are stuck.