Hi, it's Munkaew here.
Welcome to the "Moral Breasts".
You want to know
what this live broadcast is about, right?
The flashlight I'm reviewing
is the first version ever.
It's not an ordinary flashlight.
It fits in your hand.
And you can...
I'll show you. You don't need to carry it.
Sometimes you can put it in your mouth.
If you want it,
type a message now.
Send me your comment
and I'll answer you back.
Let's see all the comments
if anyone wants a flashlight.
THOSE ARE BREASTS OR BABY'S HEAD?
LOVE THEM.
There are only comments on my breasts?
I'm selling flashlights right now.
Could anyone care?
"Bitch! You're such an online whore!"
How do you know I'm a whore?
Normally, it's free if I'm pleased.
I even give tips, for taxi fares.
If anyone bullies me like this,
I'm gonna block that person.
And you'll have no chance to come in
to see my boobs.
This is a warning.
BITCH. IF YOU BLOCK ME, YOU DIE!
"If you block me, you die!"
Who is this? You think I'm scared? Really?
I'll slap you with my breasts!
Haha. Hilarious.
Cyber-bullies. Are you on summer break?
Let me see your name. I'm gonna block you.
"Monica."
If you wanna pull a prank,
be considerate a little.
We don't use the name of someone dead
in the joke.
Don't be out of line.
I'm blocking you now.
BLOCK
MONICA (CAN'T ADD MORE FRIENDS,
CLICK FOLLOW): I'M RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
Top seller? Isn't it misleading?
Nah. Just a way of selling.
TRUE BEAUTY MUST COME FROM INSIDE.
ICONNIC CREAM USES NATURAL EXTRACTS.
Now, we'll go to the next step.
I have other vegetables ready.
Next, I'm gonna chop carrots
to add colors to the food.
We're in the process of
getting carrots ready.
Make it a bit colorful.
Okay, it's done.
While we're waiting for the water to boil,
let's read the comments here.
"How are you? You're doing okay?"
Yes, I'm fine.
"Which cream do you use?
Your face looks so bright."
Thank you.
Iconnic cream, of course.
"Cream that net idols trust."
Yes. Advertising a bit.
YOU AND SEVEN MORE PEOPLE ARE TAGGED
IN MONICA'S POST
Well,
the water is boiling.
I'll put all the ingredients we prepared
into the pot.
MONICA (CAN'T ADD MORE FRIENDS,
CLICK FOLLOW), NOW: "ON THIS DAY"
It's creepy just talking about it.
Don't know who used the dead person's
account to pull this prank.
I'm not too worried.
I just find it weird.
Anyway, don't come home too late, okay?
Yeah.
What happened, Sa?
What's wrong?
It's all right, Sa. It's all right now.
Who's Monica anyway?
A net idol
that I once hired to review my cream.
It was under the brand Malisza.
She was so audacious
to broadcast her suicide live.
She must have been stressed.
I heard that
she just broke up with her boyfriend.
There are also many people
that don't like or hate her.
There must be someone who used her account
to pull a prank on you.
If you feel uneasy about it,
then just block her.
Okay?
Well, I gotta go to work now.
It's late.
MONICA (CAN'T ADD MORE FRIENDS,
CLICK FOLLOW)
SOM PINSUDAH (IT'S ME, SOM)
Monica has tagged you in her video.
Missed call from Monica.
You've got a voicemail from Monica.
Hi, Som.
This is Monica.
My face is all ruined now.
Hi, Som.
This is Monica.
My face is all ruined now.
Hi, Som.
This is Monica.
My face is all ruined now.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING, MONICA...
Hi. Today, you're live with Monica
and Ai-ai.
-Ai.
-No.
"Dance a little crazier."
Sure. Look at this.
"Could you moan my name?"
"Can someone please take
the mummy in the back away?"
Ai. They don't want you here.
"You are so cute."
Thank you.
Where are you going, mummy?
Come back here and dance with me.
Come here.
Anyway, if you want the mummy back,
click "Like".
If you want to see me, click "Love".
They said this shop is awesome.
Is it true?
You'll see.
Why?
You don't trust me?
You always say that.
Enjoy your meal.
Can I have a photo with you?
Of course.
One, two, three.
Yeah. One more, please.
After posting it,
don't forget to check in.
Yeah. I'll do it for you right now.
-Enjoy the meal.
-Thank you.
Hey, Sa.
Thank you.
-Please come again.
-Sure.
When I saw I was tagged in that post,
I was shocked.
I'm wondering
who pulled this fucking prank.
There was also
a check-in at your house, right?
Yeah.
Do you have any idea
who knows her password?
I don't know.
I don't even know and I'm her friend.
If you really want to know,
why don't you look in her condo?
You can let me in there?
Well, it's possible.
But, well...
Wait here just a moment.
Here. Try it.
And does anyone else have a key card
to her room?
I don't know.
Probably not.
Please come again when you can, okay?
Sa, why did you bring me here?
I don't want to come to Monica's condo
by myself.
Are all net idols' rooms as untidy
as this one?
Were you like this?
Hurry and find it.
I don't want to be here too long.
Well, I'll check the computer.
Eighteen.
-Jak.
-Yeah?
Try "Munnikar".
It's her first name.
Yeah.
Munnikar.
Forget it.
Look for her cell phone?
Sure.
Sa.
Yeah?
Found it.
Can you turn it on? It won't turn on?
No. Probably need to take it home
to charge it.
-Jak.
-Yeah?
I think we should go now.
Okay.
Sa!
Sa! What's wrong?
It's me. Jak.
What's wrong?
Sa.
I think you should stop
reading social media.
What are you going to do
with Monica's cell phone?
We can't figure out the password.
I think I'm gonna ask my friend
to hack into it.
So that we'll have some idea
of who has been using it to prank us.
So you can relax.
What if it's not someone?
Don't think too much about it.
I'll go work on the inventory
at the factory.
I'll be right back.
"SAN" DIED TRAGICALLY. YOU'LL BE STUNNED
TO LEARN WHO HER FRIEND WAS.
Yes, Mom.
Yeah.
Ah, yes.
I'm so sorry, Mom.
Yes.
I'll take good care of her, Mom.
Okay.
I'll keep you posted.
Yes. Okay.
Yes, Mom.
Yeah. Okay, bye.
How are you holding up?
Please come in, Jak.
DEWII CHECKED IN AT KHING-NGAN STUDIO
NOW.
There's a shoot going on today?
Yeah. A cute, little sexy one.
Sa hasn't been using my service lately.
My girls are all sexy and cute.
And the important thing is
they have a lot of followers.
If you want any girl, just let me know.
I'll arrange it for you.
Mr. Dewii, today...
I'll cut to the chase.
I came here to talk about Monica.
I've never believed in ghosts.
But this has gotten much worse.
Som, who used to work with Sa,
is dead after being tagged in that video.
The most recent person
is one of Monica's friends.
Started hallucinating all of the sudden
right before she got hit by a car.
You were also tagged in the video, right?
You don't find it weird?
I want to know what happened
before she died.
You were her manager.
You probably knew best.
You know I'm no psychic or anything.
But if you came here to ask me
why she committed suicide,
I can say that I know as much as you do.
Why don't you go ask her ex-boyfriend Sun?
He was also tagged in that post.
And he was closer to her than me.
You go and ask him, okay?
Is he the one named
Tawan Biker?
Yeah. You go and ask him, okay?
Would you excuse me? I'd like to
go check on my team at the set.
Mr. Dewii?
You didn't do anything bad
to Monica, right?
Are you crazy?
Monica is my money-maker.
Why would I do that?
Anyway, would you excuse me?
Bye-bye.
Hi. Hello, everyone.
It's me, Lodchong.
Today I'm shooting an ad.
There. I'm here with a pretty girl.
I'll show you around.
Oh, no.
Are you gonna work now?
Or do need me to give you hell first?
After work, you'll go live on the toilet
or whatever, I don't care.
Sorry.
Hi, everyone.
Keep following us, okay?
Seriously?
Hi, everyone.
Would you excuse them
so they can get back to work?
After work, they'll be right back.
Bye.
There you go.
Oh, man. They may unfollow us
because of what you just did.
You better know your time and place
during work hours.
Where is Munkaew?
Lower your voice.
She got a job reviewing flashlights.
High pay.
So I let her work on that job for now.
Why don't we get that kind of job?
You missed this job.
There'll be another one.
Get back to work.
Go!
Hey, everybody.
The girls are ready.
Okay. I'd like to see some strong poses.
Hold the pose.
Beautiful.
Show your confidence, okay?
That's great.
Very good, girls.
Very pretty.
This one is nice.
Lodchong, show more confidence.
-Look at the camera.
-Change your arms a bit.
Cute. Good.
Be a bit more cheerful.
Those eyes were great.
Open your eyes a bit wider?
Okay. Now switch places.
That's good.
Very good.
Great. That's great.
-Is everything okay now? Great.
-Yes.
All right, everybody, that's a wrap.
Let's pack up.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much, everybody.
See you next job.
Aren't you gonna go home?
Go pack it up.
Go.
Hello? Hi.
See you later.
My body is aching all over.
You wanna hang out?
Nah.
I'm tired. I just wanna go home.
All right.
By the way...
Munkaew is Dewii's favorite, huh?
He always gives her
all the easy good jobs.
Actually, that flashlight job should have
been for all three of us, right?
She took it all for herself.
Bitch.
Let it go.
The client probably hired just her.
If Mo hadn't died,
there's no way
that Munkaew would have got the job.
Who posted something in the group?
Fuck.
Hello?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay.
Thank you very much. You're so nice.
You always choose our service.
Yes. Yes.
What about the garden?
Let's do it as we agreed.
Okay.
On that day, we'll take care
of the clothes, hair and makeup.
Okay.
Yes. So you can confirm it on...
Hey, let's go.
What happened?
Hello.
Is anybody out there?
We can't open the door.
Please open it.
What should we do?
Is anybody out there?
Bonsai.
Where are you?
I can't see a thing.
Bonsai.
Where are you? Answer me.
Bonsai! Where are you?
Bonsai.
Where are you?
Bonsai. Are you there?
Open the door.
Anybody out there, open the door, please.
Please open the door.
I'm embarrassed.
What's there to be embarrassed about?
No. Go to Gon over there.
She knows how to be embarrassed?
Excuse me.
Yes?
Sun. Someone's here for you.
Well, excuse me. I'll go inside, then.
Hi.
What's up?
I wanna talk to you about Monica.
What about her?
You've seen Monica's post
that you were tagged in, right?
My girlfriend was tagged as well.
I'm sorry. Who is your girlfriend?
My girlfriend hired Monica
to review Malisza cream.
So, I want to know if the two of them
ever argued about anything.
I wouldn't say they argued.
Monica is dead...
because of your fucking girlfriend, right?
Listen to me.
This is my girlfriend's house.
I don't need to talk about the past here.
I also don't want to talk about it.
You'd better go home
and ask your girlfriend.
Because that bitch knows it
better than anyone.
Excuse me.
I think you should go.
Why did Monica commit suicide?
Why are you asking me?
Sa.
What are you hiding from me?
I'm trying to help you here.
Hi. Welcome to my party.
I'll show you how cool my party is.
Hey, everybody, say hi.
Who's not here? Call them over, hurry.
Call them over, hurry.
Who? Boom is not here yet. Look.
Everybody's having fun.
And we're all getting drunk.
I'll tell you this.
Our party is limitless.
Everything is here.
Lights, music and everything.
It's a party at my house,
so it's gotta be awesome, right?
Okay. Make everyone else jealous!
What's wrong, Sun? You look bored.
Not at all.
Is my party boring?
No.
-Really?
-Yes.
Who's that?
Sun!
What's wrong, Sun?
Sun! Sun!
Sun.
Sun!
What's up with you?
Go away!
Go away! I said go away!
Stop, Sun! What are you doing?
Sun! Stop!
Sun!
Don't do anything crazy!
Stop it!
Don't do it!
Don't!
Sun!
Did you go to Monica's room?
Put it back.
She's already suffered enough.
Cut to the chase.
Why are you here?
I want to know the same thing you do.
And I think your girlfriend
has the answer for us.
Sa...
five people that were tagged in that post
are dead now. You know, right?
Aren't you afraid that you'll be next?
Last year,
when I first launched the Malisza brand,
I was looking for a net idol
to review my cream.
I'm proud to recommend this girl to you.
Nice work. Lots of followers.
You won't be disappointed, I guarantee.
Hi. Today, I'm gonna review Malisza cream.
This one right here.
The box looks like this.
And the jar inside...
looks like this.
It's in a silver-white packaging.
The logo is in pink.
Let's take a look inside.
The cream is white.
Unscented. There's probably no perfume.
There's no strong scent at all.
Here you go. I'm testing it
on the back of my hand.
You can see that it is easily
spread on skin.
It's not ghostly white,
or much different from the skin tone. See?
I'll test it on my face now.
So you can see how it is,
how different it looks
when it's on the face.
Wow. I think I like it.
Because it's quite soft,
not sticky and easy to apply.
Here. I'll let you compare both sides.
This side, with cream.
This side, without.
You can see the colors are not different.
It absorbs into the skin really well.
It would be easy
to put on makeup afterwards.
Anyway, don't forget to follow me
on the Twenty Days Challenge
with Malisza Cream.
Bye-bye.
Okay, it's been a week now
that I've been using Malisza cream.
The package looks like this,
for those who have not seen it.
LET US SEE YOUR FACE CLOSER.
First, I need to say that
since I've been using Malisza cream,
I can feel that my face is softer...
YOU LOOK PRETTY AS ALWAYS.
...and brighter.
And the makeup stays on longer.
LIAR.
Besides, I have to say,
like in my previous clips,
that Malisza cream has no fragrance.
So it's quite suitable for sensitive skin.
SOUNDS WEIRD.
Well, all right, we'll just wait and see
after I'm done with this challenge...
FUCKING LIAR.
SUCH THICK FOUNDATION. I KNEW IT.
...how my skin will be whiter,
brighter, better,
and more interesting
after the Twenty Days Challenge
by Malisza Cream.
Hi, Som.
My face is all ruined now.
Could you try to talk to Ms. Marisa
to see if she can pay me something,
so I can use it to treat my face.
Hi, you're back with me, Mo.
Today is the last day
of the Twenty Days Challenge
by Malisza Brand.
Well, I have used this cream for 20 days.
I have to say it's fucking good.
TODAY IS NOT FUN.
So good that it fucked my face.
FUCK YOU, FUCK FACE.
All right, I'll show you again
about how to apply this cream.
We put it on like this.
WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS?
Like this. Your face will be soft...
DID ANYONE HEAR THAT?
...and super moist.
Your face won't be ruined. No more acne.
No allergies.
SUPER ENTERTAINING TODAY.
It's non-allergenic.
This cream is for hyper-sensitive skin.
GO FUCK YOURSELF!
That's not enough. We'll apply even more.
Like this. More and more.
It is so good.
Don't forget to buy it.
It is Malisza brand.
Buy a lot of it.
Because after using this cream
we will all have a fuck face!
Thank you for following.
TODAY'S HIGHLIGHT
SO EXCITING
WHAT'S GOT INTO YOU?
NO ONE'S CALLING POLICE?
You can think that I'm mean.
But where is the proof
that my cream really ruined her face?
What about the other people tagged
in that post?
How are they involved?
There must be a reason
for Monica to kill them.
What do you want me to do
to make her leave me alone?
I need to die?
I don't know about the rest
that were tagged.
But you...
I think Monica really thought
that your cream was the cause
of all the terrible things.
And so do I.
So?
Want me to apologize?
Sorry! Fine, I'm sorry!
I'll apologize if it'll end this.
How could I apologize to her? She's dead.
Monica killed herself...
because she was bullied by social media...
because of your cream.
If I were Monica...
I would probably like some justice
for what happened.
So?
Should I broadcast live to tell
everybody that my cream sucks?
That it ruined her face so bad
that she committed suicide?
I'll do it if it'll end this.
But how can you be so sure
that if I did do it,
she would stop harassing me?
Sa.
What's on your mind?
I'm not sure.
I don't know what's gonna happen...
if we tell everybody about this.
Sa, right now you need to care
of yourself.
Even if you can't sell cream,
I can still support us.
Right?
How about this? We end this right now.
Then we start it over.
Okay?
Let's go.
Jak.
I don't want to go upstairs.
Okay, you wait right here.
I'll put her cell phone back.
MONICA: WHAT HAVE I DONE TO YOU?
I'LL GET YOU ALL IF I KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
Hey, when am I gonna get paid
for reviewing Malisza cream?
Geez, you're not gonna get it.
Your face is fucked up like that.
You didn't finish the campaign
as you agreed.
You should be grateful
that she didn't sue you.
But I couldn't finish it
because of her cream.
It ruined my face when I used it.
You saw it, didn't you?
Hello?
Som, you know that
-I used Malisza cream to review it, right?
-Yeah.
My face is all ruined now.
Yeah, I understand.
Don't panic.
Could you please
put me through to Ms. Marisa?
Sorry. She doesn't want to talk to you,
and she's not available.
How can you be sure that
you didn't use any other brand with it?
Som, ever since I took this job,
I haven't used any other cream.
Do you have any evidence against us?
Please help me. I'm begging you.
Please. Please, Som.
Don't forget to buy it.
Malisza brand.
So good that it fucked my face.
ANTIMONICA: SHARED A NEW VIDEO
Fun scandal, huh? Gotta share it.
What's the hurry, Sa?
Are you okay?
Hang in there.
I know about everything, Sa.
I know all about it.
How could you do something so cruel?
You ruined someone's life.
And you lied to me afterwards.
Why did you lie to me, Sa?
What I hate about myself right now is
that I forgive you despite all the facts.
I love you, Sa.
I love you, too, Jak.
Sa...
SIX MONTHS LATER
Could you please wait here for a moment?
Your mom is picking you up.
Wait a moment.
You'll be okay, Sa.
I'll be around to watch your doom.
Subtitle translation by Sudaporn
Pluempitiwiriyawej