Good evening my dear listeners.
You're listening to Midnight Riders.
I'm DJ Charnwut Chantarachoke,
keeping you company tonight.
It's midnight on Friday.
Where are you guys right now?
If you're spending time
with your special someone,
I hope you're having a very
romantic evening.
But for those of you who are by yourself,
remember that I'm sitting
right here with you.
Good company and lovely music…
will make your journey of life
feel less lonely.
But before we hear our
first song for tonight,
let's take a quick commercial break.
I'll return back to you soon.
And I'll stick around
all the way until 3 a.m.
So don't go anywhere.
May I talk to Boss, please?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Fuck you, Aood.
You recognize my voice.
What's your deal, man?
Is it bad timing?
C'mon, spill it.
What is your fucking emergency?
Seriously, can this wait?
Did you forget what time
it is in New York?
No, but running a bar means
you work the night shift, right?
Are you busy with a customer?
A female customer, maybe?
Just tell me why you called.
I need to ask you a favor.
Shoot.
You know my dad died of cancer.
Yes, and?
I have it too, just like him.
Come again.
Are you serious?
Who jokes about having cancer?
Leukemia. The doctor said
it runs in the family.
I inherited it.
And you…
There's something
I want to do before I die,
and I need a favor from you.
Sure.
Tell me how I can help.
First of all,
can you come back to Thailand?
CHANTARACHOKE RECORDS
Aood.
Hey.
You really came.
Sure. I…
Your breath stinks, man.
-Long flight?
-Very.
You have to bring that up now?
What?
Shit. It feels like ages.
I'm speechless.
Come.
I'll get you some water,
your breath's awful.
Why don't you just get me a toothbrush?
You want one? You can use mine.
No, thanks.
I don't want to catch cancer.
If you don't want to do chemo,
why do you want me here?
What about…
Skydiving?
Rock climbing? Bungee jumping?
A threesome, maybe?
You haven't done it, have you?
Not my thing.
Seriously, what do you want to do?
I want to return some stuff.
Return what? To whom?
To Alice.
Alice the bitch? Your ex?
Why can't you just mail it?
Nope.
I want to see her.
Return stuff to your ex. Checked.
What else?
Nothing else.
That's it.
Then why did you make me
come all the way here?
The doctor said I shouldn't drive.
Do I look like a cab driver?
Catch.
Don't slam the door. This is my dad's car.
Too late.
Now you're doing it.
-Sorry. I'll be gentle with it.
-Boss isn't happy.
Good evening, Midnight Riders.
You're still here with me, DJ Charnwut
Chantarachoke, your late-night friend.
DJ Charnwut?
Your dad's show?
Cassettes.
I got them from the station.
You love golden oldies.
Now I know…
-why you want to see your ex.
-Why?
You want a farewell fuck, right?
C'mon, you want me to join you?
So, did Alice dump you?
Let's turn this up.
You have something to tell me?
Yes.
Why the hell
are you going back to Thailand?
Well…
Alice wants to open
a dance school in Korat.
A dance school?
Fuck, you can't even dance!
What about our bar?
I'm meeting your friend tomorrow
about renting his place.
-How can you ditch me like this?
-Stop.
Stop what?
How many years
have you talked about this bar?
I can't live like this anymore.
Like not having to pay a dime
to live in a penthouse?
I told you he'd say this.
It's none of your fucking business.
Are you sure you want to
drag my friend home?
It's better than being here with you.
-Hey, calm down.
-Fuck you.
Hey fucker, you drive like shit!
What's up with you?
-What's your problem?
-Easy, man.
Love her much?
You've know her longer than me?
NAKHON RATCHASIMA
You're full of shit.
You didn't even return
for your dad's funeral.
Looks like a haunted mansion.
Does she have any students?
Carry it yourself.
Take this.
What's this?
-Give this snack to her for me.
-Why?
So you can tell her
that I'm here to see her.
Why don't you just call her?
I already did.
-She didn't answer.
-Then text her.
Tell her why you're here.
You're sick and dying.
Not a word about my health.
I don't want her to know.
Like she'd never figure it out.
I'll deal with that later.
Just walk in there and give it to her.
Use your chick-baiting tricks.
What tricks?
-You're a smooth talker.
-Like I'm dying to talk to her.
You haven't seen her in a long time.
She must miss you a lot.
You son of a bitch.
Please, I'll wait at the food court.
Call me when the coast is clear. Okay?
Break a leg.
I don't want to see him.
Just leave.
I have a class.
Come on, don't be so mean.
Just go see him.
Getting dumped hurts real bad,
you know that.
Shut the hell up.
I just…
An asshole like you
has no right to preach.
How many girls have you dumped?
Don't be so righteous.
-But I never dumped Aood.
-Yes, you did.
Playing dumb?
Don't give me that look.
You treated him like shit.
Told him you would open a bar together.
-You gave him a dream.
-Shut up.
You can't blame it all on me.
You're no different from me, bitch.
I'll be honest.
I don't even want to be here.
It's got nothing to do with me.
Then get lost.
If it wasn't for…
Listen.
He just wants to return something to you
before going back to New York with me.
This may be the last time you'll see him.
Just go see him. Is it too much to ask?
Sorry, man. The E Train is suspended.
BALLROOM NIGHT
Good evening.
-Hi, I'm Aood.
-Hi.
I'm Alice.
Nice to meet you.
-Sorry, I'm late.
-Buy me a beer then.
You got it.
Thanks for coming.
You look so thin.
Your hair…
I've seen it on Facebook,
but it looks better in person.
It does?
It looks good on you.
It just takes some getting used to.
But cool…
I prefer red, actually.
Such a hassle to keep dyeing it.
And…
there's no need to be
that stylish in this town.
Things are slow here.
And the school?
It's going fine.
Like… Back when you were here with me
our students used to be teenagers.
Remember that?
Now the target has shifted.
I only have old people in class.
They're all my students.
So it's going pretty well.
I'm here to return this.
Sorry for keeping it all this time.
But I've cleaned it.
Well…
I don't even remember when you took it.
Right when we broke up
and I moved back to Bangkok.
I packed my stuff in it when I left.
-I…
-Never mind.
I'm giving it back now.
You can keep it. I don't mind.
No, thanks.
All right.
Thanks for the trouble.
Is that all? You came all the way
just to return the bag?
That's it?
I had no idea you took it.
Never mind.
I noticed…
you changed your Facebook status
to single.
Stalker much?
Yeah, we broke up. After only two months.
I was doing a spin
and completing a hand-to-hand step.
But he didn't catch me.
I fell and twisted my knee.
I went to see a doctor.
He told me to take a long rest.
Then…
He ran away
to find a new dance partner.
Just like that.
I…
I miss you.
I thought I would play it cool
and act like I was so strong.
But sitting here with you, I just can't.
Your students will see
you're such a cry-baby.
It's your fault. Why are you here!
Dance with me tonight.
-For real?
-Yes.
Still remember the steps?
Okay.
Closer.
Music, please.
Ready?
Three, two, one.
One, two, three, four.
Two, three, four.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Yes?
You're in Teacher Alice's class, right?
Yeah, I guess.
Do you have a dance partner?
Depends on who's asking.
So you're available?
For you, I'm always available.
Thank you.
Mom! He's available.
Can you dance with my mom?
Come, son.
Good night, ma'am.
-See you.
See you.
I'll go check on my students.
You okay?
What is it?
I'll drop you off at the hotel.
Then I need to follow up with that girl.
We'll have to drive to
Samut Songkhram tonight.
Samut Songkhram?
-To see Noona.
-What?
Let's get this straight.
Noona? That's not part of the deal.
I told you…
I want to visit my ex-girlfriends…
Girlfriend with an 's'? That's unfair!
Don't be tricky, man.
-So how many exes do you have to visit?
-Calm down.
Let's talk in the car. Okay?
-Samut Songkhram chicks are cute.
-So you insist?
Just look at yourself.
Look.
When my dad died,
I didn't get a chance to say goodbye.
So I know how sad it is
for the one who's left behind.
And you know I didn't even
fly back for his cremation.
When I found out I had leukemia,
I started calling people.
To thank them,
or to say sorry.
Then I deleted each number
after I made the call.
Until finally,
I only have the numbers
of those I want to see in person.
If you insist, I'll drive you.
But on one condition.
I told you I won't do chemo anymore.
If so, I'm going back to New York now.
You can go see
all your dozen exes or whatever.
Return their sentimental
knick-knacks and shit. Go ahead.
Once done, you have
to come with me for treatment.
How hard is that?
I'll take care of everything.
All you have to do is survive.
Okay.
Seat belt.
It doesn't matter
how your paths crossed…
I said seat belt.
or how long you will be together.
The song may be brief, but its melody
will linger for a long time in your mind.
This song is dedicated to everybody
who lingers in our thoughts.
Then, now, and forever.
Inside turn and back to basic steps.
-Sorry.
-That's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I didn't try hard enough
when we were together.
For me, you did the best you could.
Finally,
this day has come.
The time we spent together
was not in vain.
I know what I'm going to say
may sound like a corny line
from a soap opera.
But I thank fate,
for bringing us back together.
Yes.
I thank fate…
…for bringing me here,
to this moment,
with this feeling…
What feeling? I can't feel anything.
You droned on like a robot.
Do you even feel anything?
I don't think you do.
How do you expect the audience
to feel something that you don't?
This is a dramatic scene, get it?
I didn't want this in the first place.
Isn't it cool that your ex is a superstar?
Cool my ass.
I don't see how we can approach her.
If you can't make me feel it,
we'll keep shooting.
You're doing fine.
Sorry we have to keep reshooting.
No worries.
From the start.
All right, one more take.
No way we can get close to her.
-She's not as pretty as on TV.
-She's cute.
Not bad at all.
Get ready for your love scene.
Quiet, please. On your mark.
HOSTAGE OF THE HEART
Ready, speed…
What's going on?
Who let them through!
Come here kiddos!
One hundred baht apiece!
Stop! We'll take a break!
Calling yourself Nunar
is a brilliant move.
Why are you here?
I came to congratulate you.
I'm so happy to see
you're living your dream.
-It's a huge set.
-Are you being sarcastic?
I told you I didn't want to see you again.
You're back early.
We're auditioning.
This is Nigel, Boss's friend.
He's a film director.
-Aood.
-Hello, I'm Aood.
I'm her part-time manager
-and full-time fucking boyfriend.
-Aood. Aood!
Can you just leave?
Well…
-I just want to say goodbye.
-Okay.
I'm going back to New York with Boss.
Are you done?
And I brought you this.
-You forgot it when you moved out.
-I didn't forget it.
Just leave, please.
I need to focus on the script.
Just hear me out.
Let me say something,
then I'll leave you alone.
Noona…
I'm sorry.
I didn't support you back then.
I didn't help you when you struggled.
How many times have we talked about this?
Too many.
-So?
-You're not ready for an audition.
Why? I have to grab every chance.
Why do you think I came to New York?
I didn't come here to wait tables.
This is my dream.
This is my life. It's what I want to do.
Let me give you this award again.
You're awesome to have
come this far by yourself.
Don't listen to what that director says.
No one can judge you.
You never trust me.
You never believe I can do it.
You're already great without them.
You want to hear the truth?
-Do you?
-Yes, say it!
They never care about your acting skill.
Just ask Boss.
They think you're gullible
and just want to screw you.
I'm ready now.
We can start.
Come on. Hurry up.
Everyone!
-Nunar…
-No need!
Okay. Ready and…
action!
I must thank fate…
for bringing me here,
to this moment,
with this feeling.
Hey.
Are you blushing on one cheek?
The love that you have for me
was once a shining light.
My smile used to…
mean happiness.
But your love has turned into a cage…
Fuck you, I told you to
put the phone down!
…that imprisons my dreams,
my life,
and my smile.
If this is the last time
we're seeing each other,
look me in the eyes…
and remember who I've become today.
No matter how much I may regret it,
these bullets…
Mutita, what are you doing?
They will set us free from our past.
Thank you…
and goodbye.
And cut!
Brilliant!
-Thank you.
-Incredible.
Let's go.
You're perfect for the role.
Give her a big round of applause.
Let's change the setup and take a break.
-Give me the same in the next scene.
-I'll catch up.
Are you sure you want to keep going?
I have to.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Bring my friend
the strongest poison in your bar.
Bed Breaker, Boner Forever…
Stomping Horse, Dragon's Dick,
what do you fancy?
Which one will make me feel alive?
-All of them.
-I agree, everything is great
if you'll drink with me.
Sure.
Bring your glass and sit with us.
God damn it, if her husband
comes and beats you up,
don't count on me to help you.
No need, nothing's going to happen.
She knows I'm only joking.
Still the same Boss, you're already 30.
Still younger than you.
Yes, but you're 30.
You should get your act together.
For what?
Look who's talking.
Getting your act together.
Having a serious relationship.
And look at you now.
I'm telling you,
relationships are like drinking.
You go with the flow,
and you'll be drunk as a skunk.
Look at me, I run a bar
but I never get drunk.
I'm too busy entertaining
pretty customers.
Are you sure you've never been drunk?
Dragon's Dick.
Long and strong.
Your snake will dig this snake.
Enjoy.
Fuck.
What's that? You only drank water.
Aood!
He should stay here for a few days.
He needs a good rest. Not a road trip.
-Who did the driving?
-His friend.
-Is your dive open tonight?
-Not sure.
-You're coming?
-Yeah.
I'll tell my husband then.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Good guys die hard. Look.
Let's go.
Did you pay?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
We're going to see Roong in Chiang Mai.
The doctor ordered you to rest.
-No.
-We can go tomorrow.
I told her I'd be there today.
Tomorrow her hubby
will be back from abroad.
Fuck him.
You need to rest.
I'm fine.
I'm all good.
-No need to rest.
-Shut up, look at yourself.
Right.
I've looked at myself.
That's why I have to hurry.
I will regret not saying goodbye.
A new year is here upon us once again.
To my audiences,
I hope you'll find all
that you're dreaming of.
Are you Aood? Boss's roommate?
I'm sure Boss is downstairs
exercising his charm.
-Am I blocking your shot?
-No. I'm shooting you.
C'mon, pose for me.
It's the last picture.
Let me shoot a person.
It's the New Year. Smile.
One…
Two…
I have to go back to
Thailand in three months.
I know…
you've promised Boss about opening a bar…
but I want you go back with me.
You're here already.
Hi, Roong.
Okay, okay.
It's been ages.
Come on in. Take off your shoes.
Take off your shoes, please.
So what's it like living in Chiang Mai?
It's okay.
Every day is pretty much the same.
I wake up, I cook.
Pack her lunch box.
Take her to school.
Pick her up.
Help with her homework.
Draw pictures.
And play a princess.
I can't imagine myself as a father.
If you hadn't chosen
to stay with Boss and open a bar,
do you think we would be together now?
Yes, I guess.
But instead of living
in this big beautiful house,
you'd have ended up in a shabby apartment.
And…
Lola wouldn't have been this cute.
Can you still develop film?
Thank you for coming to see
my daughter for the first time.
And to see me…
for the last time.
Aood, we're here.
Sleeping or dead?
-Hello?
-Roong, I'm here.
You are? Sorry, the plane just landed.
Landed where?
I'm in Singapore.
Singapore? Why?
I told you my husband
and I had a fight, right?
We made up and took this trip.
I'm sorry.
Hi, Roong.
Boss?
Yes, it's Boss.
Where the hell are you?
Aood arranged this with you weeks ago.
I'm sorry, it was kind of unexpected.
Bullshit.
I didn't drive across Thailand
so you could tell me that?
Hey, calm down.
I'm really sorry.
I had no idea he would be here.
He wants to make up with me.
I know you've driven a long way, but…
it's not my call.
Hello Roong.
It's good you made up with your husband.
See you next time. Okay?
Sure.
I'm sorry again.
Next time then.
Are you hungry by the way?
There's a good curry noodle
place near the house.
Hey, Roong!
Let's talk face to face.
Listen, Aood is…
He's going back to New York with me.
This is probably
the last time you'll see him.
Why don't you ask me if I want to see him?
Why don't you stop for a second
and ask how I feel?
What are you doing?
Come on. Let's go.
NAKHON SAWAN HOTEL
You go check in first.
LAST TAPE
We've come to our last break of the show.
DJ Charnwut Chantarachoke
is keeping you company.
As I told you at the start of the show,
tonight is my last night as your DJ.
That's life, ain't it?
We meet at some point.
We get to know each other,
bond with each other.
Then we part, that's the way it is.
To my audiences
who are tuning in from abroad,
we may not have a chance
to say goodbye in person.
But I hope with all my heart
that you will live your
life to the fullest.
Dream far…
and fly high.
So this old man…
who sits alone in a small, dark room
by himself
would be proud.
CHARNWUT CHANTARACHOKE
1953-2021
Till we meet again.
I've already asked the monk
to let me take it.
I can't leave him like this.
I'd like to say goodbye to all of you
with this very last song.
The final song…
from a radio show that has
lasted as long as my life.
Now…
it's time to say goodbye
to DJ Charnwut for real.
Thanks again for always listening.
Have a safe journey.
Goodbye.
Hey.
Let's go to Pattaya.
Let's go see my family.
Sure. Pattaya sounds good.
I've always wanted
to see Mr. Boss's big house.
A hell of a place…
You haven't been home in ten years.
Didn't you miss it?
Why can't it just be the two of us?
I know it's too much to ask.
But trust me.
I do it for our own good.
I promise when this photo shoot is over,
we'll go celebrate, just the two of us.
Sister.
Your sister is marrying my dad.
So, do I now call you Uncle?
No need, just call me by my name.
It's "Ball"?
It's Boss.
Boss as in "chief".
Right?
Yes.
I'm Poom.
Well…
Welcome.
Next one with the children.
Kids, let's take some pictures.
-Get over here.
-Come, come.
-Poom, come here.
-Yes, ma'am.
Boss…
if you're bored, go wait at the bar.
Order what you want and put it on my tab.
We're ready.
Look at the camera, please.
One, two…
Great. One more shot.
Come.
Give me a sec.
A new order just came in.
No?
You don't like carrots?
-Hey.
-Hi.
Didn't know you were back.
Just arrived.
I came back to see a friend and thought…
I might drop by to see my sister.
Is she here?
You didn't see our group chat?
They're in Europe.
Won't be back till next week.
Have a seat.
Later.
-I'll go get a room.
-Sit.
I need to talk to you.
You know what I want to talk about?
What about?
About the bar.
Told you I've come back to see a friend.
What about your already tight cash flow?
It's not professional
to close for a month.
-What do you know?
-And what do you know?
-Shut up!
-You shut up!
I work my ass off over there,
I need a break!
This is the high season.
Other hotels are fully booked,
but it's deserted here.
So you're blaming my sister?
-Really?
-Hey!
Gigi!
I'm sick of cleaning up your shit.
Slow economy, stingy customers,
or mismanagement, you can blame anything.
The question is,
why must Tak keep propping up your bar?
-It's her money.
-It's my dad's money.
Your sister works for my dad.
Tell me, how much have
you lost in three years?
Next month
I'll take over from your sister.
If you can't turn the bar around
in three months, I'll shut it down.
What now?
You look stressed out. Need a drink?
Man, I do want to visit your bar,
and try your drinks.
Come.
A bar is not a place.
A bar is the bartender.
This is my last drink, man.
Don't let me down.
Last drink my ass.
We'll celebrate again
when you've recovered.
Like a pro!
What's it called?
Alice.
How is it?
Great.
Next…
Noona's Tears.
And the best girlfriend award
from the Aoodscar…
goes to… Noona!
After The Rain.
Our first roll together in New York.
Keep it with you and don't develop it yet.
Which one is your favorite?
What about yours?
My what?
Drinks based on memories of your exes.
We'd be here till the morning
and all this booze wouldn't be enough.
I want you to taste
your most important drink.
Prim.
This is where you met her, isn't it?
Give me a drink.
The most expensive one.
Neat or on the rocks?
I…
Can I see your ID?
Your thumb is on your birthdate.
I can't serve you. You're underage.
Hold on, boy.
Having a hard time?
Heartbroken?
No more questions then.
Sit down.
I'll make one for you.
Since it's your birthday.
Just one, okay?
Let's see…
Why this?
It was the first drink I learned to make,
and I guess it'll be
the first drink of your life.
-Does it taste…
-Wait a sec.
Go on, it's hot!
Hope you like it.
So how's your new school?
Is Teacher Samorn still there?
-I haven't met her.
-Really?
-What's her class?
-Thai language. She's very strict.
-You're going in?
-Come with me.
In this outfit?
Why not?
We'll dry up riding home.
Do you know why I became a bartender?
I saw my dad
mixing drinks when I was a kid.
And the first thing I could do…
was shaking.
My dad liked experimenting with new
cocktails and I begged him to let me help.
Tasting a cocktail is like
discovering a new world.
You put incompatible things together
and try to make them work.
That's how I fell in love
with making cocktails.
I've been training really hard,
because I want to spend
my whole life doing it.
Imagine if I get to
go to New York like my dad…
to live in a new world
and meet new people.
Wouldn't it be awesome to own a bar there?
I already have a name.
-Meaning?
The last drink before heading home.
Let's start a bar!
-Why not?
-Tomorrow then!
Of course. I got this.
You want to? Tomorrow?
Yeah! Tomorrow!
You got it!
Hi, Mom.
Let's open it next door
so you don't have to go anywhere.
Are you full?
-Honey?
-Yes?
-Can we discuss Boss's future?
-Sure.
Where does he want to go?
Maybe Sydney.
The school fees are reasonable.
Miss Tak is so beautiful.
Are you protective of your sister?
I never said I wanted to go.
Don't be afraid.
You can take a language course first.
See if you like it there.
Give it a try.
Don't make him go if he doesn't want to.
Looks like he's happy
enjoying free stuff at the bar.
Aren't you? Is she tasty?
Let me have a sip, will you?
Actually she's not my sister.
She's my mother.
Go back to your room.
It's fucking weird.
Suddenly my mom turned into ''my sister''.
She wants me to study abroad.
She says it's for my own good.
But she just wants to get rid of me.
If I were you, I would leave.
Look at this shitty town…
I grew up here,
but I hate it.
So if I had a choice,
I'd leave.
I don't like it here either.
I just want to be with you.
Remember what I told you about going
to work in New York like my dad?
Yeah.
What if I told you I've been saving up.
Go.
I'll ask my mom to send me
to school in New York.
It's huge!
Your mom really got this place for us?
-Like it?
-I love it.
You're messing up my hair.
Here's our bar.
Sorry.
Here comes your favorite.
Yes!
Only Thai restaurants hire Thai people
without work permits.
-I see. Thank you.
-All right.
I haven't seen Prim in like…
ten years.
We lost touch.
Actually, I…
I didn't just want to see you.
I also wanted to return something to you.
I wanted to return Prim to you.
It's rare to see a clear sky
in the monsoon season.
You can change the station if you like.
No, it's okay.
Hey.
-Prim?
-Yes.
You like this show?
Yes, you too?
-No one listens to it.
-True.
None of my friends do,
and my boyfriend says it's boring.
It's for old people.
-Yeah.
-So I'm surprised you like it.
My mother liked it back home, that's why.
What's your name again?
-Aood.
-Right.
-Sorry I forgot it.
-No problem.
Anyway,
I still believe
that good things will come
to those who have patience.
We just have to keep our hopes up.
Because…
"Time Is On My Side."
Get hot sauce from the bar.
-A soda for this table.
-Okay.
Americans eat lots of carbs
but not enough vegetables.
I was always constipated
when I first got here.
You sweep here and the dust goes there.
There is no way you can
make it completely clean.
Aood.
-Thanks a lot.
-You're welcome.
Aood, let me out.
Aood! I'm getting mad!
-Give me five bucks.
-Go buy new shoes.
Okay, quick.
-Shooting a music video?
-It's my first snow.
See you.
Prim!
Gotta go home right now?
Sort of.
Let's go check out a bar.
-Which bar?
-My friend's bar.
It's brand new.
He's looking for a bartender.
Interested?
Neat. Nice balance.
Great, come work for me.
Are you kidding me?
Come every night,
and when you get better,
I'll enter you into a Vegas competition.
That's great.
-But you have to come every night.
-Absolutely.
-Don't get bored of me first!
-I won't.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
I called a hundred times.
I didn't hear it.
-I was worried.
-Why didn't you wait at home?
I've got a job. I'm working my way
to becoming a real bartender.
Coming home late is part of the job!
We hardly spend time together.
I have time for you on my days off.
Aren't you asking too much of me?
Why don't you do something
useful for yourself?
What are you doing here? I'll get scolded.
That's my order. I'm a customer here.
We only have beer.
-Want it?
-Yes.
-Something to eat?
-No.
My shift ends late.
-And I have to work at Joe's after this.
-I can wait.
Hey.
What the hell are you doing?
Drinking beer, obviously.
Chugging it down like that?
-How else?
-Don't make a scene.
With a straw?
Boss!
You'll get me into trouble.
What do you want?
-No.
-Get me another one.
-I'm a customer.
What's your problem?
My problem?
My problem is why the hell do you have
that much money in your savings?
I found the bank slip in the trash.
So I came to see what kind of work
you do to bring in that much.
-Does this restaurant pay that well?
-Hey.
-Who should I ask?
-Let's talk outside.
Hey you.
Do you get huge tips here?
-Do you?
-Let's talk.
We're outside, so talk.
Talk.
Go on.
You've saved up over million baht
just from working here?
What's that supposed to mean?
What do you think I mean?
I don't know what the fuck you mean!
Exactly, I don't know either.
I have no idea what kind of work
my girlfriend is doing.
Shaking drinks alone
won't bring in this much.
What are you implying?
Say it. How did you get the money?
Cat got your tongue?
-You want me to guess?
-Please…
You want me to guess what you've done?
-No.
-You like that?
-Please listen!
-Listen to what?
We never used to have any secrets.
I'm not trying to hide it from you,
but please…
Why do I have to squeeze it out of you?
You want me to be like this?
Be honest with me.
Where did you get the money?
I got it from your mom.
I'm sorry.
I can explain.
She asked me to bring you here.
I thought it'd be a win-win for everyone.
This way we could
have a new life together.
You're just another greedy bitch.
-You know I'm not.
-Yes, you are.
-I really love you.
-Love me?
Then why are you doing this?
Do you think I could have
afforded it by myself?
Okay.
You got money from my mother.
That means you're working for me too.
So this is what I want you to do.
Quit all your fucking jobs.
From now on your job is to make
drinks for me. And only me.
-Got it?
-Are you nuts?
I can't, I have to work
to pay your mom back.
If you can't do that, you're fired.
And I don't want to see you again.
Fine. Let's break up then.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
Air freshener, in case my bed stinks.
So what's your plan?
Could you tell the manager
I'm taking a month off?
Why?
I need to focus on the Vegas competition.
Sure.
I'll talk to her about
covering your shifts.
One more thing.
Could I crash here for a while?
If you and your friends wouldn't mind.
They won't mind, I'm sure.
Thank you.
I'm off to bed.
-Get some sleep.
-Okay.
Good night.
So when will you propose to her?
-When I have enough money.
-No need.
That's not good, man.
Did you know they're
bumping up the rent next month?
-Can I leave now?
-What's wrong?
I'm not feeling well.
Prim!
Why are you back early?
It was a slow night, so they let me leave.
-What time is your flight?
-2 a.m.
Then you must leave around midnight.
Wow!
-Don't tease me.
-Red-cheeked girl!
Stop it!
-Got room in your bag?
-Why?
What's that?
Shit.
-Do you know this brand?
-Of course, you do too?
Joe told me Japanese shakers
are better than American ones.
-True.
-So I bought one for you.
For me?
What's the occasion?
It's Vegas, right?
You need a decent shaker.
In case you make it to the final round.
Do you like it?
Fancy.
I'll finish this, then go.
Don't get drunk.
I'm really happy for you.
For what?
You have a dream and you're going for it.
That's cool.
You're a sentimental drunk.
I'm not being sentimental.
-Look at me.
-Why?
I have nothing.
-No dreams, no passion.
-Not true.
It's true.
You're a selfless person.
And you make people around you happy.
Like how you work hard
and save up for your father.
I'm happy when I'm with you.
Really?
Happier than when you were with Boss?
Aood…
You…
What?
Are you okay?
Look…
No.
I still love Boss and I need more time.
You moved in here and slept on my bed.
What's that all about?
Because I thought you were my friend.
-Wait.
-So you're not my friend?
-Of course I am.
-Right.
But I have feelings for you.
Don't tell me you didn't know that.
Let me ask you something.
You're still in love with Boss.
How is he better than me?
You broke up with him
over a month ago now.
Boss and I have
gone through a lot together.
But you already broke up with him!
He's not a bad person.
I'm not saying he's a bad person.
I'm not.
I'm asking in what way
is he better than me?
You're just not him.
I have to go.
Not yet.
I'm not him?
Because he's rich and I'm not?
Because I'm poor
and I live in a fucking basement?
How could you say that to me?
Why can't I?
Didn't you tell me his mom
paid you to come here?
-The whole restaurant knows!
-Stay out of this!
I won't stay out of this!
I've supported you in every way.
-I took you to Joe…
-And I'm grateful.
and he is sending you to Vegas.
-You are?
-Yes, I am.
I thought we were friends.
Friends are supposed to help each other.
If you need help, I'll be there.
I know you have feelings for me.
Don't tell me I'm just a friend. It hurts.
You do have feelings for me.
Take me to Prim.
I want to apologize to her.
Should I tell you this?
You do have feelings for me.
If you don't, just say it to my face.
I don't have feelings for you.
What is it?
Prim has a new boyfriend.
Some white guy.
They are very much in love.
-Fuck you, Aood.
-I bought it for you.
It's fucking expensive.
Take it with you.
Prim left with him this morning.
They moved to another state.
I'm sorry.
The truth is…
Prim didn't have a new boyfriend.
But she did…
move to another state.
To train for the bartending competition.
It's illegal to drink on the sidewalk.
I didn't really know you at the time.
I wasn't even your friend,
so I lied to you.
Give it back.
My watch.
I said give it back!
Then you thanked me
by inviting me to stay with you.
If I'd had a conscience,
I would've said no.
Hello.
There's a room…
We're pals now, right?
-Yeah.
-This is your room, dude.
The living room, the kitchen…
I wanted to know what it was like
to live like a boss like you.
-Why did you come to New York?
-I just came.
I thought it'd be better than this.
Still want me here?
I told you I am going back.
I don't know what you're thinking.
But I want you to know
that you're so lucky to have all of this.
Nope.
No mother wants to push her child away.
Never.
Prim returned all my money.
You have a great life. Make it count.
My dad had a classic car.
I told him to sell it
so he could buy me a plane ticket.
He said no. I was so desperate
because my dad didn't give me any money.
As days and weeks passed,
seeing you waste your life away,
I was dying to confess everything to you.
But I'm such a coward.
I kept telling myself
that you were doing great.
Until one day, she came back to New York.
Joe told me she asked
to work at the bar for a week.
At first I wanted to tell you.
But then I thought you didn't deserve her,
so I never said a word.
I was a real asshole back then.
Now I want to bring you back to Prim.
Boss, listen to me.
All this time I tried to find
someone to replace Prim.
Now that I don't have much time left,
I want to say sorry to everyone.
Most of all, to you.
And your way of saying sorry
is to drag me halfway across the world
-to listen to all this crap?
-I wanted to tell you face-to-face
that your life's gone off the rails
-because of what I did to you.
-What?
What's wrong with wasting my life away?
It's my fucking life!
It's none of your fucking business.
I'm happy like this.
I don't need anyone, asshole.
You need Prim.
Am I right?
-I want to return Prim to you.
-What the fuck does ''return'' mean?
She's a person, not a bag.
Fuck you.
I'm going to tell you straight up.
All these shitty things happen
because you're dying,
and you're desperate to find an excuse
to force your way back
into everyone's life.
You lugged yourself
all over to see your exes,
so you could open up their wounds
and make them worse.
You're hurting everyone.
You're so fucking selfish.
I'm sorry, pal.
Pal?
Why did you do all of this to me?
I did it because…
I envied you.
I wanted to be you.
-Prim's waiting for you.
-Get out.
Get out.
I'll leave it here.
The waiter told me you're a nasty drunk.
Three months, man.
Three months.
Prim.
He's on his way to see you.
Hey…
I'm sorry I hurt you.
See you around.
AIRPORT
Why are you here?
Poom sent you to collect his debt?
You shouldn't worry,
just look at the crowd.
Fix me something, son.
What do you fancy?
I don't know.
-Whatever you think I'll like.
You're talented.
There you go.
What's it called?
I don't have cancer.
You can still enjoy the drink anyway.
It's new. I came up with it recently.
You'll be the first to try it.
Do me this favor.
It's bitter.
I'm sorry about Aood.
Before he died, he came to see me.
He asked me to give you this.
Poom will take over my job soon.
If you need a bookkeeper,
I'm good with numbers.
I can come work for you.
I'm glad you came.
I'm thinking…
I'll close down the bar.
I've turned around the loss.
If Poom wants to turn this place
into something else, fine.
The drink's on me.
We're even now.
I'm sorry.
Now start dressing like you're the boss.
LISTEN TO THIS, MY MAN.
Hello there,
my die-hard fan in New York City.
This is DJ Aood speaking.
This is my first and final show.
Exclusively for you, Mr. Boss.
Thank you.
Thank you, sincerely,
for giving me a chance
to have a taste of your life.
One more thing.
I want to thank you again
for always being by my side.
And I… want to say I'm sorry
for hurting you.
I'm sorry for…
hurting everyone.
I deserve to die alone.
But wait…
I'm not giving up so easily.
The new soap series
Hostage of the Heart has begun filming.
Producer Lek Sitthiwong
is giving the audience a treat
by unveiling his new star, Nunar Montarat.
Nunar, this is your first TV drama.
Any acting tips to share?
Like they say, good acting
comes from bad experiences.
So I have to thank everything and everyone
that came into my life.
You know what,
I've given myself a new mission.
I'm going back to do chemo.
The thing is,
I've got to get back on my feet…
Daddy!
…so I might have a chance
to redeem myself
and to start over.
-Checking out?
-Yes.
Boss left this for you.
And this is super-important…
I might get to go to New York again,
and drag you back to see Prim.
Hi there.
I'll have my usual.
New York Sour, please.
Want to see my ID?
Coming right up.
When the time comes
and when you're ready to forgive me,
I'll be the one driving you.