I'm an invisible man.
Can you see me?
But I don't have any special powers.
I'm going to tell you
how am I invisible.
My name is Denchai.
I've been working here
in the IT department for many years.
Hold on. Your ID, please.
But the security guard
doesn't even remember me.
Here, I finished installing the program.
Thank you.
Hey, you.
Yes, you.
Sign here for me.
Sometimes I wonder,
is my name really that hard to remember?
I'll have my usual.
So, what's your usual?
Too many customers. Who can remember!
She never remembers my order.
Fried noodles with no veggies.
Every year on my birthday,
the only person who remembers is this one.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
FREE CALLS TODAY!
CALL 6988984 FOR DETAILS OF THIS OFFER.
Actually, calling this
a "person" doesn't sound right.
-Tee.
-What?
Tonight, we're going karaoke.
Do you want to go?
Yes, let's go.
Only once in a blue moon
does anybody ask me out.
And...
you can come too if you want?
But they only do it for one reason.
To be polite.
I'm not going.
Why did you even invite him?
What was I supposed to do?
He was right there.
What if he really comes?
The only time I'm needed is when...
Hey, can you check my computer?
The Internet is down again.
Why is the font all weird?
There's a virus again.
So what's wrong with this computer?
You clicked on a website
with an embedded script.
It sets off a Trojan
that installed a program
which makes your computer slow because....
Yes, I'm betting on two teams.
One is Barcelona.
All right.
But it seems like
nobody really wants to talk to me.
The person I talk to the most
is my computer.
It is my best friend.
It does exactly as I say.
Press CTRL+P, it prints.
CTRL+S, it saves.
If you make a mistake,
you can just press CTRL+Z to undo it.
I wanted to say thank you for fixing
my computer. It's way faster now.
No need to thank me.
Actually, you should learn
to do it yourself,
so you don't have to rely on IT people.
Just delete the files in Temp
and do a disk cleanup.
Even a primary school kid can do it.
Okay.
Geez!
What the hell, Den!
Dude, the way you talked to her,
why didn't you just call her an idiot?
What did I say wrong this time?
Do you know you make all of us
in IT department looks bad?
Well, I admit we do look bad.
But nobody is as bad as you.
At least, we are not rude like you.
HI, DENCHAI. DO YOU REMEMBER ME?
Who is that?
A friend from high school.
YES.
Damn, she's cute.
ARE YOU FREE? LET'S EAT.
She's inviting you out.
Dude, get off your ass.
I haven't seen her in ten years.
I don't know what to talk about.
There's no need for chitchat
for a girl this cute.
Do something else.
Actually, you aren't that bad looking.
If you do your hair and dress up a bit,
you'd look good.
Right now, Tesco has a sale on clothes.
Go shopping!
You should also trim those nose hairs.
Tarzan can swing on those hairs.
Den.
How are you? It's been a long time.
You're still the same.
You are the same too, miss.
Miss? That's way too formal.
Do you still talk to
any of our classmates?
Really?
So, what do you do now?
I work on computer stuff.
Hey, that sounds like fun.
I'm not good at computers at all.
Teach me when you're free.
Okay.
So, haven't you ever thought of having
your own business?
Sometimes, I wish people had a push button
that you can press and make them
say exactly what's on their minds.
I do direct sales.
I've never used any of this stuff.
But please buy a lot of them.
I saw your profile on Facebook.
You look easy to fool.
Look at my computer.
I clicked on a porn site
and caught a virus.
Do you want to go karaoke?
But I'm only inviting you to be polite.
Yes, if you really come,
that'd be so awkward.
Den.
Damn it, Den!
That new girl in the marketing department,
her computer has a problem again.
Go and help her out.
Sorry I have to bother you again.
I tried hitting print many times already.
It won't come out.
Here.
I'm so dead.
I was late again. I drove around,
looking for a parking space for an hour.
You...
You have to come before 8 a.m.
My house is in the suburbs.
Who gets up that early?
Is the cable loose?
Here's some scotch tape.
Sticking it on won't help.
I'm sorry. I'm so low-tech.
Our computers are so slow, right?
Yes.
Actually, we want to upgrade
the specs of the computers,
but this year is a Tock year.
We thought it's better to wait
until next year which is a Tick year.
What are Tick and Tock years?
In Tock years,
the IC will shrink many nanometers.
As for Tick years,
the value of the clock increases.
The onboard graphics will be
more powerful.
Plus the RAM and BUS...
The printer isn't broken.
It's just connected to the main printer.
You have to go to the 19th floor.
Okay.
I will...
I'll get going, then.
You know,
all those things you told me about?
I want to know more about
all the Tick and Tock years stuff.
I like the words, they sound cute.
Thank you very much, Denchai.
You remember my name?
Of course I remember. Denchai Sewatanont.
It's there.
I'm Nui Passarapa Wattanatrakul.
I have to go to a meeting.
Finally, someone sees me.
Ever since that day,
I've become her number one fan.
Joy, when did you arrive?
The first thing she does
when she arrives at the office is
checking out her farm.
She takes only half a spoonful of coffee
because she's afraid she won't sleep.
She doesn't like trendy hit songs
like most people do.
The DJ didn't say the song's name.
Maybe the DJ wasn’t born yet.
Funny.
She dreams that for once in her life,
she will get to visit the Snow Festival.
She smiles all the time.
I'm hungry. Let's go.
What?
What's wrong?
And she smiles more than usual...
Nothing. It's just my contact lens.
...when she isn't smiling on the inside.
Let's go. I want to eat papaya salad.
Yummy.
All right. This is the final question
to see if Mr. Denchai
is really Ms. Nui's number one fan.
The question is,
out of all the Japanese dishes,
what is Ms. Nui's favorite?
A whiteboard, please.
Here you go. Go ahead.
For the dish that
Ms. Nui orders most often,
there are two possibilities,
Hamachi fish or uni sea urchins.
This year, out of 40 times
that she has eaten Japanese food,
the dish that she ordered first
every time is...
I'd like to answer!
Are you sure?
You can't change your answer.
-Go ahead.
-My final answer is
Uni sea urchin!
Your answer is...
Right. Right.
Is it right or not?
It's right!
Congratulations, Mr. Denchai.
You are the ultimate number one fan of
Ms. Nui Passarapa.
And the grand prize is...
Nui, I have to go talk to
some media agencies.
Please go with me.
Yes, sir.
-Joy, I'll be back later.
-Okay.
They're going out for a meeting again.
Be quiet.
This is the third time already this week.
I wonder if she did all her work.
-She'll do it.
-Do what?
Den, take a look at
Mr. Top's computer for me.
A CD got stuck inside. I have to go.
My mom forgot her house key.
Yes, darling. I'm on the way.
Just pick the restaurant.
I guess it's true what Tee says.
I'm abnormal.
Everybody lies.
Some people lie about
not being in love anymore.
And some people lie to themselves,
desperately hoping that
he'll get a divorce for her.
I see you.
Top, I got to hang up,
my safety pin is poking me.
Hey, don't you think they're too obvious
coming as Peter Pan
and Tinker Bell together?
Come on, they work on the same project,
so they dressed up the same.
That's normal, right?
Joy's on this project too.
Why did she dress up as a donkey?
Good point.
What the hell!
How long has he been standing there?
Before we announce the winner
for best costume for tonight,
Mr. Top Thanon, our handsome president,
has something to say.
Let's hear it for Mr. Top Thanon!
Thank you.
As you know, since this year's economy
isn't very good,
we didn't reach our target.
You mean this target here?
Not this target.
So...
our company outing this year can only
be somewhere close by.
Somewhere basic.
You might be disappointed
because we can only go to...
Hokkaido!
I remember someone saying
they wanted to go to the Snow Festival.
Just now, when I said we didn't hit
our sales target, I was joking.
Everybody did great.
Thank you all very much.
So who wants to go skiing?
Raise your hands up high!
We are going all out on this trip!
When Hokkaido people take photos,
they say, "Taraba kani."
Show me your fingers. Two fingers.
-One, two, three.
-Taraba kani!
Good. Okay.
One more picture, please.
It's New Year,
but I haven't seen anything change.
-You got it?
-I have this already.
My Prince, do you have another coin?
I might get a secret figurine.
I'm all out.
Turkey, how much more?
Do you want to buy the whole machine?
If we do that, it wouldn't be fun
anymore, my Prince.
We're not staying two more days
just to look for these machines, right?
Good idea, my Prince.
Turkey, did you know I have magic powers?
Don't you believe me?
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Tada!
Cool, right?
You're so not funny.
Nui was still enchanted by
the same old magic tricks.
Top, let's go look at those music boxes.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
There's a lot of office staff there.
I see.
Nui.
Will you marry me?
I know you're suffering.
And I've talked about this a lot.
But when I go back this time,
I'll try to cast a vanishing spell
on this ring for you.
I could only hope that
this time, his magic powers
will really work.
-Top.
-What?
You know the restrooms here
have a button to play music?
A button?
It's a button that you press
and music plays.
They use it to cover up the sound
when you fart.
So was the music loud?
Because if it's not, it can't cover up
the sound of your fart.
Gross.
Here you go.
Damn it, Den!
My Prince, give me a hand.
Turkey!
Are you okay?
I thought that guy was you.
You're so clumsy.
I saw this one travel program
and they said whoever rings this bell
can pray for a happy love.
Give it a ring.
Maybe you'll get a girl.
Wow, that's beautiful.
All I ask for is just one day.
Sorry, I forgot something in my room.
You can go down first.
The bus is here. Please get ready.
We are going to the Snow Festival.
Top.
Why didn't you tell me you're coming?
I just finished my work.
I see.
We're here, sweetie.
Do you miss me?
Are you cold?
Top, do we check in here?
Yes.
See? Nui didn't even dare to come.
She said she has a headache.
She's resting at the hotel.
I don't blame her for having a headache.
And how about her staying longer with Top?
How's that going to work?
They can all go together.
Wife and mistress. A big happy family.
I feel sorry for her.
Sorry?
You're the one who can't stop laughing.
You started it.
Hi. Welcome.
Thank you.
Look, shrimps.
Crabs too.
It's reserved already.
Let's go over there.
Come and sit together.
Come. Don't mind us.
Ms. Nui, is your headache gone?
Yes.
Ms. Joy is here already.
I will take you inside.
This way, please.
Where did he go?
Over here.
That's okay.
Then, we can seat you at Ms. Nid's table.
This way.
Are you going back with us tomorrow too?
Not yet. I plan to stay longer with Top.
I will drag him to Tokyo.
The shopping in Hokkaido isn't very fun.
That's true.
I agree.
Oh, yes. Top, have you told your friend?
What?
Well, you told me
you're staying longer to sightsee
with your Japanese friend.
Oh, yes. I'll call him later. I forgot.
I'd better travel as much as I can now.
Soon, I won't be able
to travel for a while.
Why?
Top doesn't even know yet.
Taipan is going to have a sibling.
What?
Congratulations, Mrs. Chu.
That's great news.
Taipan,
did you think of a nickname?
-Tell your dad.
-What's the name?
Ben 10.
Ben 10? It doesn't go with Taipan.
-Ben 10, that's cute.
-You seem to really like the cartoon.
Is this seat taken?
I'm in the ladies' room.
It's okay.
You just go to Tokyo with Mrs. Chu.
I can stay here by myself.
Us getting married or not isn't important.
I can wait.
I've been waiting for three years already.
I'm not being sarcastic.
I really mean it.
I'm okay.
Tonnam, come and help me.
How much did you pack in here?
We're ready to go. Please board the bus.
This way, please.
PRINCE AND TURKEY ON TOUR
Nui!
Passarapa Wattanatrakul.
Hold on,
why are you all speaking English?
Nui, can't you remember anything?
Do we know each other?
ONE DAY
Is it really 2016 already?
I thought it was still 2012.
And all of a sudden, I'm in Japan now.
Nui.
Here, our company took us on a trip.
Hey...
I do work at Thanon Food for real.
So weird.
This is the first time
I'm hearing that name.
And how about you? Do you work here too?
I'm the one in the back.
I can't remember anybody at all.
Where did everyone go?
Are they at the hotel?
They went back to Thailand already.
Why are we the only two left?
We extended our stay
to do some sightseeing.
Only the two of us?
Yes.
Are you a tootsie?
No.
Gay?
Judging from your outfit, probably not.
But I can't think of why
I would be with a guy alone.
I'm not the type to travel alone either.
There are only two possibilities.
If you aren't one of my gay friends,
you must be my boyfriend.
So how did I end up here with you?
What does that mean?
Number two.
I am
your boyfriend.
But from what I remember,
I don't have a boyfriend.
You lost your memory.
That's true.
It's not that...
I don't believe you.
But...
can I see a picture of us together?
Well...
I don't like taking pictures,
so I don't have any pictures of us.
What kind of couple has no pictures?
In the group photo,
you weren't even next to me.
Nobody knows that we're seeing each other.
How come?
Well...
Well, it's...
I'm your boss.
-If people knew--
-You are my boss?
Yes.
Where is my phone? Do you know?
It's probably still damp from the snow.
Let me borrow yours.
Hello, Mom.
Why are you calling
so early in the morning?
Are you back?
You said you're staying longer
with your boyfriend.
Did I tell you that?
Yes. Are you all right?
Mom, what is my boyfriend's name?
Why are you asking me that?
Come on, just tell me.
His name is Top.
What's going on?
Are you on some sort of game show?
No, Mom.
What's your name?
Top.
Mom, what does Top look like?
What is going on?
Why are you acting weird?
Nothing, Mom, just tell me.
Nui, Nui, actually, I'm...
Not now!
Mom, what does he look like?
What does he look like?
I don't know. How would I know?
You haven't brought him to see me.
I've never seen his picture.
I don't know why it's such a secret.
Are you and Top having problems?
No, Mom. I got to go.
I'll call you when I get back.
And how many years have we been together?
Three years.
Three years and I never took you
to meet my mom?
Never.
And how am I supposed to know
if you're really my boyfriend?
There's no proof.
And why do you need any proof?
I am really your boyfriend.
How am I supposed to believe you?
There's no picture of us.
You've never met my mom.
I woke up with no memory.
You could be some stranger from anywhere.
You have a birthmark
under your left chest.
What?
You have a birthmark
under your left chest.
There is a mirror over there.
Nui.
It's okay. I'm not cold.
Are you okay?
Do you still have a headache?
Sorry.
How intimate have we gotten?
Which base?
You said
you've seen my birthmark.
So have we...
done it?
Yes. We're a couple, you know.
Just a second.
Nui,
it will be another hour
before the hotel shuttle comes.
Shall we walk around the city first?
Actually, we don't need
to go back to the hotel.
Turkey, you look much better now.
We should go sightseeing.
Here, look.
Turkey, you've been planning
this trip for months now.
Hold on.
What did you just call me?
Sometimes, we call each other
by our nicknames.
I call you Turkey Neck.
And you call me your Prince.
Here, these are the places
we visited together already,
and these are the places we will go next.
And why is it all torn apart like that?
You were the one who tore it apart.
Well...
At first, I couldn't stay longer
to go with you,
so you got really mad.
Did I want to go with you that badly?
Yes. But I finished all my work already.
We can go together now.
It's all right. I don't want to go.
Please, let's just go.
In the evening,
I will take you to Sapporo too.
Let's go to the Snow Festival.
You wanted to go to this event very much.
You have pictures
all over your desk at work.
I don't remember anymore.
Don't you understand?
I'm not going.
Please go. Today is the last day too.
Can you stop bothering me?
I told you I can't remember anything.
Snow Festival? I've never heard of it!
Nui, did you know I have magic powers?
If you don't believe me, watch this.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Tada!
Oh, please!
Wow, Nui,
the music boxes here are so intricate.
Right?
Nui, they have sushi too.
Here's uni. Do you want it?
I'll buy one for you.
Luckily, it didn’t go
over my credit limit.
There's a famous sushi place around here
recommended by TripAdvisor.
Turkey, let's go eat.
What?
Turkey, what's wrong?
Stop calling me Turkey, okay?
I don't like it.
Why? We call each other this all the time.
We might be a couple,
but today let's just break up.
Save it for another day!
Waking up and losing my memory
is bad enough.
Now, I have to put up with a guy like you
as my boyfriend!
A guy like me? What do you mean?
Like this!
Hey, you.
Hey!
Top!
Hey...
Just now, I...
I found the sushi place.
It's right around the corner.
Let's go. Come on.
Nui, do you want Set C?
It has the uni and hamachi you like.
Then, I'll order
some extra wasabi for you.
Hey,
I can order it myself.
I just lost my memory. I'm not an idiot.
-Yakisoba.
What are you laughing about?
Nothing.
You're in Japan and you're eating
yakisoba, seriously?
Try this. Eat it with wasabi.
It's out of this world.
Are you okay?
I don't eat wasabi.
What a baby!
The sea urchin is so fresh.
Did you know that
uni isn't sea urchin eggs?
It is actually the testicles.
You should say,
"Their testicles are really fresh."
Right?
Thanks a lot.
My pleasure.
The bruise on your face, what happened?
From skiing.
What were you trying to do?
I don't know how to ski.
If you don't know how, why did you go?
You dropped this.
You said I've been planning this trip
for months, so how could you drop it?
Sorry.
Compared to being stuck at the hotel,
I think this plan sounds more interesting.
I mean I'll go with you.
This place has a strange name.
The Valley of Hell.
The Japanese gave it this name because
this hot spring has boiling mud pots
that have steam gushing
out of it all the time.
Like a copper frying pan in hell.
And how do you know this?
I Googled it.
No wonder you sounded so technical.
Can I ask you something?
When you're talking to me,
why don't you look into my eyes?
I look at your eyes.
When?
Right now.
No, you aren't looking at all.
Why are you looking at my ear?
Is there something stuck in my ear?
I'm looking.
See? You're still looking away.
I've been like this since I was a kid.
I'm just used to it.
How about this?
Look into my eyes for one minute.
No looking away.
Okay?
Start counting. Go.
Nui, it...
See? You can do it.
That was just 32 seconds.
You kept track?
Yes.
Am I your first girlfriend?
How did you get me to like you?
You can't even look me in the eyes.
It's like what I told you.
-I am your boss, so I found ways--
-Come on.
I want details.
There was this one day,
17 February 2013.
That day, you wore a long white dress
with small floral prints.
And you wore an orange belt
and high heels.
You remember all of that?
You wanted details, right?
That day, your printer broke,
so I came to fix it.
You’re the boss and you fix
the computers for your staff?
Well, I sort of know quite a bit
about computers,
so I went to help you.
And...
I liked you from that day.
But I never tried to hit on you.
What? I hit on you first?
No, it wasn't like that.
You didn't hit on me.
And I didn't dare to hit on you either.
All I did was...
figure out you were always late
because you couldn't find a parking space.
So, I'd come early and
secretly save a space for you.
And you're addicted to that farming game.
So I hacked into your account
and collected all the wood
and nails for you.
Hey, something happened to my game.
I got a whole bunch of wood.
I've been looking for some forever.
Your desk is very messy.
So I organized your desk after hours.
Aunt, I bought something for you.
Thank you for cleaning my desk.
You like to listen to old songs.
Some are so old that
you've never heard of their names before.
Hey, have you ever heard this song before?
How am I supposed to know, butthead!
You hum like a dog choking on food.
What kind of melody is that!
So, I would go look for those old songs
and secretly put them in your computer
every day.
One song a day.
And I never knew it was you?
No, you didn't.
Sounds a bit like a psycho.
Don't take it the wrong way.
It's sweet.
Right.
TESSEN POND
Who is that?
Another girl?
No. Not at all.
Let me see.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
FREE CALLS TODAY!
CALL 6988984 FOR DETAILS OF THIS OFFER.
Is today your birthday?
-Yes.
-Really? How old are you?
Thirty.
So old. You're six years older than me?
This year, you'll be 28, not 24.
Oh, yes.
I feel so strange.
It's like I'm in a time machine.
So now who's the prime minister?
Uncle Tuu.
Who is Uncle Tuu?
It's a long story.
Then let's talk about entertainment news.
Right now,
who are the most popular artists?
Justin Bieber. Is he still famous?
He is.
Is he still with Selena Gomez?
No.
I thought he'd be married
with kids by now.
Not yet.
I used to think that
I wanted to get married before 30.
Work for about seven to eight years.
So if I have kids,
I could be their friend too.
Time flies. I'm 28 already.
So darn fast.
Hey, have I ever talked
about this with you?
No, not yet.
Or maybe...
I'm not serious about you?
Maybe you're just a fling?
What?
Just kidding.
What is it?
I'm looking for
the secret figurine for you.
What secret figurine?
It's a secret.
Nobody knows what it looks like.
This one.
It's very hard to get.
You're missing just this one.
You almost have the entire set.
Again!
You already have this one.
Nui, I found it.
When I was a kid, I like to do this,
so my friends wouldn't steal any.
Coconut ice cream with lots of palm seeds?
Is there anything you don't know about me?
Hold this for a second.
My first car, what brand was it?
If your answer is wrong, you'll get it.
Yellow Honda Jazz.
Wrong!
BM...
BMX!
Try again.
How many boyfriends have I had?
Four.
Wrong!
Three.
How come you didn't know?
And how about your current one?
I forgot. Sorry.
Okay.
Hey...
Hey, my phone is working now.
JOY SINGLE-ON-CERTAIN-DAYS
TAGGED A PHOTO OF YOU.
Who is Joy Single-on-certain-days?
Is she my friend?
Yes.
This one.
Hey, look.
I really do collect these things.
How cute.
Who is this guy?
Why?
He looks familiar.
I remember now.
Well--
He's the guy next to me
in the group picture.
Who is he?
He works in the IT department.
The IT department? This handsome?
-Yes.
-He's really overdressed.
JR TRAIN STATION
Excuse me.
Calm down. We can check again.
Excuse me!
Hey, he might yell at you.
Excuse me.
I think I'll go outside to check again.
Hey! Wait!
The train still isn't running.
But I saw a car rental company.
We could drive there ourselves.
Are you crazy?
We can't drive in a snowstorm like this.
We don't have to go.
We can go. We can.
It's okay.
Maybe we can come back some other time.
I only have today.
What?
Today is the last day of the festival.
But they have it every year, right?
We can come back next year, okay?
Here.
Thank you.
Hold on. Have you made a wish yet?
Make a wish first.
Okay.
Here.
What did you wish for?
I wished for the storm to clear.
You'll take me there
no matter what, is it?
Who makes wishes for other people
on their own birthday?
And why do you make a wish for me?
We aren't a couple.
I broke up with you this morning.
How about...
I'll give you another chance to hit on me.
Come on.
I'll pretend that
I'm looking for something here.
And you come by and hit on me.
I don't know how to hit on girls.
It won't work.
Well, how did you make it happen before?
Hurry.
Get up.
Hurry up.
Go. Start over there.
Excuse me.
Did you hurt yourself...
when you fell from heaven?
I mean you're like an angel.
An angel who fell from heaven.
I got it the first time.
I'm just still in shock.
Stop it. You Googled that line, right?
Yes.
I don't want that.
I want something sincere,
straight from your heart.
Simple. Just be yourself.
-Try again.
-Straight and simple.
I'm not starting yet.
I just came to grab something.
Your hair is so wet.
Nui.
Do I know you?
You don't know me
but...
I've been watching you for a while.
Actually, for a few years.
I just
want to tell you
that I'd like to get to know you.
Are you hitting on me?
A guy like you?
Are you sure?
I know.
For a loser like me,
just to look at you is already wrong.
But I...
I really do like you.
I like your eyes.
When you talk to someone,
your eyes light up
like you're excited
and really interested in
what they're saying.
And I like your smile.
When you smile,
your eyes squint like this.
Like a little kid.
Just like this.
And I don't like girls with big breasts.
Your breasts are not too big.
Plus you have wide hips.
My mom said
women with wide hips give birth easily.
You almost had me.
Why?
Because I talked about breasts and hips?
Do you even have to ask?
Enough. I'm not playing anymore.
You can't get me to like you.
Wait, Nui.
Have you heard the story about
the people who climbed Mount Everest?
Along the way, many of them fell and died.
And the guy who walked
a high-wire across the World Trade Center?
Your point is?
I'm not done talking.
Sorry.
Before this,
I never understood
why they would do such things.
Until...
Until I met you.
You once asked me
why I even dared hit on you, right?
Today, I finally know.
When you really love something,
you don't need a reason.
Love
makes us dare to do
the most irrational things.
Nui,
you are my Mount Everest.
You're the other side of
the World Trade Center
that I want to walk across to.
You said you didn't know
how to hit on girls.
That was smooth.
The train is here.
-The train is here.
-Thank you.
The train is running again.
Hey, let's go.
Hey!
Is this the one?
This one?
-Yes, you got it!
-It really is!
Yes, it is the one.
I have all of them.
But why should I be happy?
I don't even remember I collect them.
Look, the snowman
wears glasses just like you.
So cute.
Are you complimenting the snowman or me?
Both then.
I want to sleep all night
And dream of us
I don't want to wake up
I want to sleep all night long
Can I stop time to dream?
Can I, please?
Our hearts have yearned for each other
Since we first met
We both felt it
But dreams are unfair
They aren't for real
We're lost in the moment
We only met once
We only spoke for a moment
It's not enough
I want it like in my dreams
Where I was more than happy
The two of us are embracing
Whenever we want to meet
Just close our eyes and dream away
So our hearts can be as one
Let's take a picture together.
Nui, no, it's okay.
What?
You don't like taking pictures that much?
We finally made it all the way here.
Just one picture.
Nui.
We can just remember it.
You are really weird.
When you told me you were my boyfriend,
I wondered what was I thinking?
Was I drunk or pregnant?
But right now, I think I understand
how I became your girlfriend.
Nui, Nui.
There it is. Do you remember?
I told you
this is the highlight of the year.
It's beautiful, right?
What a shame, though.
All the effort to build it, and for what?
Tomorrow, they'll just let it melt?
How would the people who made it feel?
What is it?
What are you doing?
We're going to be in trouble.
What?
Nui...
Will you marry me?
What?
Right now.
Are you crazy?
No way.
You told me that
you wanted to get married before 30.
Yes, I do.
But I didn’t mean today, did I?
Getting married in Japan would be
really cool though.
What are you doing?
Nui, will you take me as your husband?
Isn't that what the priest is
supposed to say?
The priest isn't here.
So will you?
Is there anybody who objects?
That's okay. I have more.
This one is mine.
Gosh!
Years have passed
and my room is still messy.
The view is so beautiful.
You need help?
Yes.
It's nice...
to see you up close like this.
You see me every day, aren't you bored?
We...
have kissed already, right?
I don't remember.
I mean...
I want you to kiss me.
Nui.
What is it?
What are you doing?
I...
I have something to confess.
Say it.
Actually,
we've...
never slept together.
No wonder.
Your face is redder than those monkeys.
Your boyfriend's name is Top.
I know.
What are you saying?
But I'm not Top.
What do you mean?
I'm really sorry, Nui.
I didn't think it would go this far.
Are you playing some crazy joke?
You are joking, right?
My name is Den.
Actually, I just work
at the same place as you do.
And I've been your secret admirer.
I don't find this funny!
Nui, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done this.
I really shouldn't have done this.
I'm sorry.
Are you crazy? What do you mean?
So you're saying you aren't Top.
And you aren't my boyfriend either?
Correct.
And why did you do this?
Why did you lie about being my boyfriend?
This is the only day
I could be close to you.
But I had no bad intentions.
What do you want?
Answer me!
How did you know about my birthmark?
I didn't do it on purpose.
During the New Year's party,
I saw your shirt lifted up and--
You pervert!
-Get out!
-I didn't have sexual thoughts.
Get the hell out!
Nui, please.
-Get out!
-Listen for a second.
-Nui.
Go!
Nui, please just listen first.
Just get out!
Please.
-You're not getting out, right?
-Nui.
-Get out!
I didn't mean to do anything bad.
Get out!
I said get the hell out!
Go!
Get out!
Go! Get out of here!
NO RESULTS
TOP
MY PRINCE
CALLING MY PRINCE
Hello, is this Top?
Yes, speaking.
Is this Mr. Surachet?
No, this is Nui.
Oh, yes.
You're calling about the documents, right?
What documents?
I will hurry and e-mail them
to you again.
Okay? One moment.
Hold on. Is this Top?
Hello, Nui, what is it?
Hello, is this Top?
You are my boyfriend, right?
What are you saying?
Right now, I can't talk. I'm with Chu.
Can we talk when I get back?
Who is Chu?
Dad, I'm sleepy now.
Mr. Surachet, I'll call you back.
Let's go, Taipan. I'll put you to bed.
Hello?
Hold on.
Am I his mistress?
Tell me!
I'm his mistress, right?
You could say that.
What do you mean?
Am I or not?
You are.
And how did I become his mistress?
He tricked me, right?
Why are you quiet? Tell me.
I didn’t know he had
a wife and kid already, right?
Tell me!
Wrong.
You knew.
No way.
I'm not like that.
You're lying again, aren't you?
I'm not lying.
And why would I agree to be his mistress?
There has to be a reason.
He told you he was going to get a divorce.
He's getting a divorce?
That means
they're about to break up, right?
I'm not a home-wrecker, right?
What I did is understandable, right?
The other day, you just found out
his wife is pregnant.
He can't get a divorce anymore.
So what did I do?
You said you understood,
and continued to see him like before.
Understand what?
I don't understand at all!
So he's with his wife and kid
and I still stayed to go sightseeing
and enjoy skiing?
Didn't I feel anything at all?
Of course you did.
You felt a lot.
Actually,
you didn't go skiing.
What do you mean?
It wasn't an accident?
This is weird.
It's like I'm talking about someone else.
The mistress who committed suicide
to get back at her lover.
If this was about someone else,
I would talk bad about this woman.
Why is she so stupid?
But what's funny is...
this story is about me.
Nui, you can say you are stupid.
But what I did today
isn't any different from what you did.
We both are climbing Mount Everest.
What were you thinking?
Why did you lie about being my boyfriend?
I don't know
if this has anything to do with it,
but there is a bell
that people ring to wish for love.
I made a wish.
I wished to be your boyfriend for a day.
Then, suddenly you lost your memory,
so I thought I got my one day.
And why did you ask for just one day?
Just one day is
already hard work for the bell.
Being my boyfriend for just one day,
what do you get out of it?
Tomorrow, I'm going to forget everything.
But I won't forget.
You know...
what you did is really crappy.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
You don't have to say sorry.
I think...
today was a good day.
It might...
even be better than my real life.
But from now on, don't lie to me anymore.
Okay.
I found it!
Nui, take care of it.
Tomorrow, you will be so happy
that you have the complete set.
This one is very hard to find.
I thought it's lost.
This is me kissing you, Den.
Not Top.
Got it.
I sent a message to break up with Top.
Why?
I don't want to be with him anymore.
Nui, you won't think this way tomorrow.
You won't remember today.
You'll only remember that
you're Top's girlfriend.
And you won't come and say anything to me
about what happened today?
What do you want me to say?
Do you want me to say you lost your memory
and I lied about being your boyfriend?
But you'll just let me forget today?
Didn't today mean anything to you?
Nui,
for a guy like me
to be with a girl like you,
it's impossible.
Impossible? How?
Today has already happened.
Why?
What makes a woman like me
so damn special?
Nui, do you remember your expression
when I told you I was your boyfriend?
The face I saw in the mirror?
What happened today was all a lie.
But the look in your face then,
that was the truth.
Tomorrow, I'll be very sad too.
But at least, give me this one day
to keep as a good memory.
You are so damn selfish.
Nui,
today is the 11th of February.
You happened to have
some sort of crazy memory loss.
Tomorrow, you will forget
everything that happened today.
But I don't want you to forget.
Today...
You met the person who loves you
more than anything.
If this guy comes up to you,
you have to give him a chance.
It's useless, Nui.
I did try.
Den,
are you leaving now?
Nui,
you don't have to cry.
What Top is doing might look romantic
by taking the whole office on a trip,
so he can go with you.
But wouldn't it be better
if he ended things with his wife
and went out with just you?
Really, you can find a better guy.
Den.
I just want to tell you...
when you thought you got lucky
in finding a parking space,
it wasn't luck.
I always wake up early
and save a spot for you.
And I am the person
who put the songs you like
in your computer every day too.
And how did you put it in my computer?
I did it after work.
Nui.
I...
I like you.
Hey, sorry.
There were so many people in the restroom.
Sorry, I got to go.
Hurry up, Joy.
Why?
That's creepy. Let's go.
In reality,
to avoid getting in an elevator with me,
you had to lie that you forgot your stuff.
What I did, I can't hit CTRL+Z to undo it.
Nui, don't force it.
No.
Tomorrow, I might not be that way anymore.
And I have this clip.
Tomorrow, just come and tell me
to watch this clip.
And I'll remember we love each other.
Tomorrow, you have to come and tell me.
Please?
Okay.
You said you wouldn’t lie to me again.
Promise me.
Who knows...
I might wake up
and not forget about today.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Yes?
The bus is leaving now.
Thank you.
MY PRINCE: NUI, WHAT'S WRONG?
CALL ME BACK. I'M WORRIED.
CALLING MY PRINCE
Hello? Nui, what's wrong?
Why didn't you pick up my calls?
I...
I'm fine.
And why did you send me that message?
Message?
And when I called you back,
why did you turn off your phone?
No matter what, I won't break up with you.
Don't be this way.
Whatever it is, we can talk about it.
Top, what are you talking about?
I don't remember.
Nui, is everything okay?
I'm okay.
Let's talk when I get back.
Okay.
Don't disappear like this again.
I love you.
Okay.
It's lunchtime. What should we eat?
Anything except Japanese food, okay?
I'm bored of it.
And how was it when you stayed longer?
Did you go to the Snow Festival?
No, I stayed at the hotel all day.
Too bad.
You haven't sent me any pictures yet.
-I forgot. I'll do it now.
-Okay.
Oh, yes,
I have hundreds of photos with you.
Can you please save them
in a thumb drive for me?
Okay, just give it to me.
But I don't have a sync cable.
Really?
I'll go and borrow one from IT.
It's okay. I'll take care of it.
Yes.
Nui, can I help you?
Do you have a cable that syncs
a phone to a computer?
Try looking on Den's desk.
There's one for both Android and iPhone.
It's all there.
-Okay.
-You're welcome.
Nui, I'm sorry.
We're really busy.
Den just quitted all of a sudden.
Did it work?
Try shutting down and restart.
Nobody in our department
is free to have a look.
Posed like a pro.
My nose is so flat!
And look at your eyes.
This one.
My face is so big.
-This is super pretty.
-So pretty.
What clip is this?
Isn't this the Snow Festival?
I thought you said you didn’t go.
...in Sapporo.
This Snow Festival is the...
The 67th.
The 67th already.
Who did you go with?
Whose jacket were you wearing?
This is...
I don't know.
What is up with you?
Let me take some of you.
Hey, how can you be that shy?
Japanese people have such clear skin.
Hey, what's wrong?
I don't know.
What's the matter?
Nui,
why are you crying?
I'm going to leave.
Nui, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
Are you still mad at me?
We can go again next year.
You didn't get to go
to the Snow Festival, did you?
We'll go next time, just the two of us.
Sounds good?
No, it's okay.
I've been there already.
What do you mean?
Excuse me.
Nui, what's the matter?
Nui, come back. Talk to me.
Nui.
Actually,
I should have let Nui forget everything.
As if that day
never happened.
Nui,
today is the 11th of February.
DELETE
But I didn't want her to forget
the smile on her face that day.
Because that smile
showed exactly how she truly felt inside.
Hakodate warehouse.
We are at the Hakodate warehouse.
It's so cold.
It's snowing too.