Get down here.
Jack, are you getting drunk already?
Here, Jack. Here.
This is fun.
I'm sober now.
Bottoms up.
This is so fun, guys.
Great. I'll get it for you.
-Cheers!
-Bottoms up!
I remember.
Great!
Friend, look.
Tao!
Hey.
-It's my turn.
-Oh, no.
-Is he new here?
-Is he new?
I have no fear of the rain
Or even the storm
Always stand tall
Up to the sky
Tao.
Thunder crashing
Lightning flashing
I'm standing tall
Against them all
What the hell?
Hey!
My name is Tao.
I love singing "Lightning Rod."
However, I don't understand
why my singing annoys some people.
KOONG-TEN KARAOKE
Mister, please don’t make tonight go ugly.
Hey.
Who are you calling "ugly?"
I'm handsome!
Hurry. Follow them.
Damn it.
This is my friend, Tun.
We’ve been friends since primary school.
His dad was named Tai.
I've never seen his mom though.
According to his dad,
she ran off with a guy when he was young.
His dad was a well-known amulet expert.
Everyone in the country knew him.
But after Guru Tai passed away,
Tun ran his dad’s amulet store
even though it was against his will.
He has never had faith
in the legacy his dad passed on to him.
Instead, his faith was in a shell of lust,
the thing which romancers
have beautifully labeled as "love."
Tun deeply believed in love.
His belief was beyond the word "faith."
But one day,
his faith
was destroyed
by a girl.
A girl
named
Maew.
He was completely devastated
and since then,
he has kept everything to himself,
disconnected himself
from his social life and friends.
It must have been the environment,
or his father must have possessed him
because since then,
he has become an expert on amulets
and turned himself into an amulet guru,
widely respected
by other experts in Pattaya,
just like his dad.
TUN AMULET EXPERT
He now makes a living
from people’s beliefs.
Frank Edward Muller once said,
"Belief is the cause of faith,
and faith makes miracles happen.
Sometimes, there is a fine line
between a miracle
and a coincidence,
as fine as the line between
faith
and obsession."
It's real.
Can you sign to authenticate it?
Of course.
I HEREBY CERTIFY
THAT THIS AMULET IS REAL
Thank you. See you, then.
-Take care.
-Thank you.
Don't you have work today?
It's a holiday.
Actually,
it’s a rich man’s holiday.
-What's this?
-It's all the money I owe you.
Thirty thousand baht.
Where did you get the money?
Oh, I know.
You won the soccer bet, right?
Why?
Did you think I was going to lose forever?
Tonight,
I’ll take you out for a thank you party.
A thank you party?
Like the other day?
But, I don't need one.
I don't want to get hurt.
Come on.
There won't be a fight this time.
It's a nice, high-end bar
with a great sound system.
Their microphone is awesome.
I’ve already asked Ped and Kai to come.
No, I'll pass.
Don’t be a prisoner in your own home.
You need to go out and see the world.
Maew isn’t the only fish
in the sea, you know?
Okay, I get it.
I just want to ask you
to go to a karaoke bar
because it pains me to see you
always at home.
Last time,
you didn’t have a chance to sing, right?
It’s my treat.
Where?
Pattaya Karaoke.
Okay, but can you promise me one thing?
What is it?
Don’t sing "Lightning Rod."
-Your voice is amazing.
-Please pass on the microphone
-to the next singer in table two.
-It's a good song.
-Your voice is good.
-Next song,
let's make it more fun.
-Microphone to table two.
-You won't...
What song will you sing next?
Don't sing "Lightning Rod," okay?
Okay, bro.
That bald man has bad taste.
Oh, as if your taste is fucking good.
Who requested this song?
It's my song.
Are you serious? Is it your song again?
A girl with big boobs, dancing, dangling
What a beauty
Walking on the street
What song is this, Ped?
Actually she’s a he
With an HIV
A trouble seeker’s song.
He got his dick cut off
Trying to be a heartthrob
I hate faggots
What is your problem?
Come on, bro.
-I’m just getting in the mood here.
-Quit it.
You’re scaring other customers away.
Do you want to get me fired?
There’ll be no more songs for any of you.
It serves you right.
It’s your fault.
I haven’t sung yet.
I didn’t sing "Lightning Rod," though.
Yes, you didn’t.
But what you sang was nastier.
That’s not it.
Chang is just prejudiced.
Even if I sang our National Anthem,
he’d still pick on me. Damn it.
Let’s get out of here.
Hey, hey.
I haven’t sung a song yet.
If I don’t get to sing, neither will you.
What?
You’re such an asshole.
This song again?
Don't you know any other songs?
No, I didn’t request it.
If it wasn’t you, then who?
How would I know?
-Was it you?
-No.
Then who requested it?
I’m right here waiting for you
Whenever she makes you so blue
Oh, oh
Whenever I see your heart broken
My heart is also drowning
In pain
If her love
Is too mean and unkind
I’ll wipe your tears away till they dry
Give me your bruised heart
Let my true love heal it fast
Oh, oh
Hey.
Hey!
Have you never seen an airplane?
What do you mean?
Like how a dog eyes an airplane.
Don’t you get it? Beauty and the beast.
Do you know her?
You have me who loves you
Your stupidity cannot be cured.
Her name is Nok.
Madame Nok.
The daughter of a well-known mafia leader
in Pattaya.
You're disappointed, aren't you, dog?
I’m not.
Because I’m not a dog.
I’m Ped, the duck.
I have wings.
I’ll fly there to quack-a-boom-boom her.
Hey, where are you going?
To quack-a-boom-boom her.
Ped.
Her father is a mafia, remember?
So what? He isn’t my father.
You fucking duck. You’re going too far.
If her love
Is too mean and unkind
I’ll wipe your tears away
Till they dry
Give me your bruised heart
Let my true love heal it fast
If her love
Is too mean and unkind
I’ll wipe your tears away
Till they dry
Give me...
Your bruised heart
Let my true love heal it
Fast
I’ll cherish you
With all my heart
Can you take me home?
What did she tell you, Tun?
Tun!
Hey, Tun!
What did she tell you?
She asked me
to take her home.
Cross it! Cross it fast!
Cross what?
The bridge of love!
It’s the bridge of love
that she’s extending to you.
What the hell are you waiting for?
Nok.
I want you to know
that I deserted the soldier camp...
That's not it.
No.
I just want to let you know
that you are such a fantastic singer.
Do you like that song, too?
Me?
Yes, I really like it.
I’ve never seen any girl before
that sang that song as well as you did.
What’s your name, by the way?
It’s Tun,
like a mole, living in a hole.
And...
do you have a car, Tun?
For Tun, the mole in the hole, no.
But for this Tun, yes.
But it's not really a car,
it's a motorcycle.
Here it is.
It’s pretty old, as you can see.
-It’s gross.
-How is it gross?
I didn’t ask you how you did it.
I just want to know if you did it.
Well, Tao has a good point.
Look at him.
I saw you and Nok
on the motorbike together.
Why are you talking like
“sex” is a big thing?
Because if it wasn’t,
I wouldn’t have been born.
This asshole came up
with another good quote again.
Whose quote is it this time?
Aristotle's.
So did you two do it or not?
Yes?
-Yes.
-Oh, yeah!
That's it.
So how did you do it?
You’re getting too nasty.
Which one of you is Tun?
Chief Mhee wants to see you.
Her name is Nok.
Madame Nok.
The daughter of a well-known mafia leader
in Pattaya.
Hey!
Is it you who screwed my daughter?
I really didn’t know
she was your daughter.
Please put it down.
All of this is a bit unfair for me.
How dare you disrespect me?
I didn’t mean to.
Besides,
it was your daughter who started it.
What’s wrong with you?
Didn’t you understand what he asked you?
Are you Guru Tun?
Yes.
Yes, it’s real.
That’s what I want to hear.
I knew Guru Tai, your father, quite well.
If he wasn’t such a womanizer,
he wouldn’t have died young.
What about you?
Are you a playboy like your dad?
No, not at all.
Hey, Kae.
Bring my daughter out here.
Do you know him, honey?
No, I don’t.
What?
Is that your daughter?
Yes.
She’s so nice.
I thought you were going to get killed.
Hey.
Why was I going to get killed?
There was no reason for him to kill me.
Don’t you know that Chief Mhee
kills people without a reason?
How do you know that, Ped?
Well, that’s what people say.
"That's what people say" again?
What if they said
your mom was a crocodile?
What would you do?
Stupid, then I would run away from home.
That's enough!
All right, guys.
-Let’s get our asses back to work.
-Wait, wait, wait.
What’s our position tonight?
What do you mean?
Usually, we do it missionary style.
Do you think that’s funny?
I asked if we’re going out tonight.
Do you believe that?
Guru Tun asked us to go out.
I just happen
to get some money
from authenticating amulets.
I just want to treat you guys.
Treat us?
If it’s on you, you can choose
where you want to go.
Pattaya Karaoke.
Hey, dear, I have come already
I'm here already
Move in a little closer
Hey, dear, we are a true loving couple
No lying, oh, my best lover
Hey, dear...
I'm so sorry, Sir.
I'm so sorry.
Please come back next time.
Hey, dear, we are a true loving couple
No lying
Oh, my best lover
I promise you with true love
And I really love you
Keep dreaming of you
While I sleep dreaming of you
I don't want anything from a playboy
Gucci and Prada I have given you
Lying baby
Lying ta, la, la
Stop!
What the hell are you singing?
-It’s entitled "My Honey."
-"My Honey"?
I thought you were singing "My Ass."
You barked and chased
all my customers away.
That’s it. Get out!
What?
When I become rich, you'll see.
What will I see?
I’ll open up my own place
-and you’ll be sorry.
-I think I’d be happy.
Thank you.
When you happen to get rich,
please give me a call.
But right now, get the hell out of here!
Get out!
Here, take this number.
Whose number is it?
It’s Nok’s, your babe.
Where did you get it?
I just got it, okay?
Happy birthday, dude.
I’m really jealous of you.
The entire hectic story starts here.
The woman named Nok
was neither a madame
nor a daughter of a well-known mafia
in Pattaya.
May I speak to Nok, please?
Nok? Who's calling?
-I’m Tun.
-Who's Tun?
I’m Tun, Tao’s friend.
I see. Tao, Kiad's friend?
Listen, Mr. Tun.
That bitch is no longer working here.
What do you mean?
What do you think I mean?
She doesn’t work here anymore.
What kind of work?
Goddamn it!
A prostitute.
Why did you call her, then?
A prostitute?
So...
How can I...
get to...
book her, I mean,
meet her?
Hey.
Just give me 100,000 baht,
and I’ll deliver her to your bedroom.
So please stop calling.
I'm trying to sleep here.
One hundred thousand baht?
Who would have thought
that love could happen in one night?
What is it, Pla?
However, it did.
Hello, Nok. I need a favor.
Can you do one last job for me?
Another job?
I can’t do it.
I told you Kamnun Moo
has already hired me, right?.
Three million baht per year, remember?
I do.
-But--
-I can't.
All right, I understand.
How about you just go meet him?
It’s Kamnun Moo we’re messing with.
Do you want me to get killed?
I really can’t.
He already paid me.
And even worse,
I’ve already spent it all.
I have to go now.
The number you have dialed
is not available.
Tao.
The police are here.
Hey, stop!
Hey, you.
Yes, officer.
I’m just a security guard.
What movie do you want?
Scent of the Night Flower 3.
Listen.
Part two is still in production.
How can I get part three for you?
How about this one instead?
Sex of the Night Fondler.
Orgasm guaranteed.
-Orgasm guaranteed?
-Yes.
How much?
Hey, where the hell is Tun?
Why hasn’t he opened up his stall?
He might have gone crazy by now.
As if.
He may not know what a prostitute is.
You're right.
Rotorour Sigford once said
"Sometimes,
it’s hard to tell the difference
between a genius and an idiot."
Who the hell is Rotorour Sigford?
Bullshit. This moron
doesn’t know anything.
Stupid.
Why are you closing
your stall up so early?
I need to watch the soccer match.
I bet a lot this time.
How much did you bet?
One hundred thousand baht.
-What?
Stupid.
Are you trying to get a new bike?
What is going to happen if you lose?
Lose?
That's impossible.
Tonight, ManU is going to win.
I’m really sure.
Kenny Miller is dribbling past Wes Brown.
And he kicks it in! One-Nil!
Kenny Miller got a chance and took a shot.
It's hopeless for Howard.
The Wolves who barely attacks
waited for the golden opportunity.
And they seized it.
Finally, the referee blew the whistle.
Wolverhampton Wanderers
did the impossible.
They won the match
with Manchester United one to zero.
I don’t have it.
If I did, I’d lend you some.
Where did you spend your money on?
I transferred a 100,000 baht
to a person named Pla.
I barely have anything left.
Who the hell is Pla?
What?
You gave me his number.
Why did you give him
that much money?
Tun.
Why did you do it?
I want to meet Nok.
Nok?
Why does it cost so much
just to meet that slut?
I don't know.
Pla told me it’s a security deposit.
Security deposit, my ass!
You, fucking genius.
I paid that whore
only 10,000 baht to sleep with you.
You hired her?
I thought you already knew
when I gave you that number.
How could you do this to me?
I just returned your favor.
What’s wrong with that?
Well, did you finally see her?
I didn’t fucking see anyone.
Don’t tell me you got conned
by that faggot.
If you want that money,
go and get it back from that faggot.
How dare you trick my friend?
Give me the money back.
Hurry.
-Hey, what's that?
-What's happening?
-What's happening, Pae?
-I don't know.
I thought I’d make money from this shit
and pay him off.
I wasn’t trying to trick your friend.
Sell this, then.
I want that money right now.
Well, follow him upstairs.
And where are you going?
I have to pee.
I'll follow you.
Come on.
Wait here.
Have you never seen a woman before?
Don't you guys have a house to return to?
I really feel sorry for your parents.
Bring it out.
Give me a knife.
Hey!
I have a knife here.
Got you!
Isn't it funny?
I think it’s fucking funny.
My joke rocks.
Hey, bro.
I don’t think I can give you a refund.
Why not?
-It's fake.
-How come?
Pla said he got this drug from you.
Taste it for yourself.
Try it.
Bro.
How can you be sure he didn’t fool you?
What a stupid person.
He doesn’t know a thing.
That's free cocaine for me.
Keep it, Krarok.
He's the first.
That was a lot of cocaine.
I completely fooled that asshole.
He's so dumb. I got him.
Krarok, tell your friend
to put her hair up.
She creeps me out.
Haven't you watched the The Grudge?
Oh, my god.
It’s me.
Arng?
I thought you got whacked.
Do you think
they would recognize me?
You're right.
I could hardly recognize you.
If you can just control your stutter.
By the way,
who was the creditor
that you ran away from again?
I think it was Moo.
We've got the same creditor.
How much?
A hundred thousand baht.
Here.
Who's this?
The plastic...
surgeon.
Just change your appearance.
It's your only way to get away from them.
But must I look ugly like you?
Your appearance
does not matter in life.
Whose quote is it this time?
Well, Franco.
Anthony Hawkins.
Stravinsky.
David Fisherman.
Ca...
Oh, my god.
Next time, don't forget
to get your voice changed too, Arng.
Tun.
Can I crash at your place tonight?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Are you drunk?
Leave me alone!
Who the hell are you?
I’m Tao, the turtle, your pal.
Turtles can't talk.
Have you been drinking?
Did you think I drank sea water
to get drunk?
What a moron!
Which part of your fucking brain
gave you that idea?
-Asshole!
-What?
-Who did you call an asshole?
-You.
Damn you.
Even my father never called me that.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Do you want to do it the hard way?
How about a fist fight?
Muay Thai?
Hardcore wrestling?
You name it.
Or do you want my sidekick...
-to whip your ass?
-Who are you talking about?
Kid Silencer!
Take this.
Are you knocked out already?
Are you?
You're already bleeding.
You should take care of that.
All right.
Do you want a piece of me?
-I'll teach you a lesson.
-Come on.
I'm going to whip your ass.
Sure.
This happens every time you drink.
This kind of amulet cannot be considered
as a collectible.
You should keep it for yourself.
It’s dirt cheap.
Fuck.
-I stole it for nothing.
-What?
What did you say?
Nothing.
What happened last night?
Hello.
Are you Guru Tun?
Kamnun Moo wants to see you.
But...
I don’t have any business with Kamnun Moo.
I don't know Tao personally.
He just bought an amulet
and we had a little chitchat.
And I never bet on soccer games.
Hey!
-Let me go! I said, let me go!
-Where are you rushing to?
Let me go.
I said, let me go!
-I was kidding.
-Did you just punched me?
Why did you punch him?
He tried to run away.
Why did he try to run away?
Wake him up.
Wait.
What's that bucket for?
I am waking him up.
Moron, you watch too many movies.
You’re going to drench him.
I hired henchmen to back me up,
but look at the way you all dress.
You make me look like a dumbass jerk.
Koong, Kung,
let me ask you something.
Why do henchmen
have to wear wacky outfits,
and goofy black sunglasses?
What's with the hats? Are you a hipster?
Why not pick red, white, orange,
or other damn colors?
He is awake now.
Put that damn bucket away.
Bro.
You checked the amulets
for Chief Mhee, right?
Yes.
How's it going?
A sweet talker
With a heart of bile, I won’t buy it
I had been warned
Not to fall for your bullshit
A sweet talker
With a heart of bile, a hypocrite
How many hearts have you broken
To bits and pieces?
When can I take this damn thing off?
My voice would sound a lot better
without this.
Are they all real?
Yes, sir.
That's great, then.
It will go into my collection,
the Sacred Seven.
Do you have all seven models?
All but one.
Can you find it for me?
Which model?
A supermodel.
Give me the envelope.
I'll get going, then.
Wait.
Tell your friend, Tao,
don't even think of running away.
He won't make it.
Show him the way out.
Nok.
-Hey.
-Let me go.
-I want to talk to--
-Do you know him?
-Hey.
-Let me go.
-Let's go.
Do you want to die?
That’s Kamnun Moo’s chick.
Come on.
Let's go.
-Get out.
-Come here.
Hurry.
038-225476.
Your father owns a crocodile farm, huh?
Yes.
Then you must be rich.
What's your dad's name?
Poo.
Your dad's name is Poo.
Then your name is Pla.
-Your mom's name must be Puke--
-Puke your mother!
You better watch your mouth.
May I speak to Poo?
I'm speaking.
Poo.
Listen carefully.
I’ve kidnapped your son, Pla.
If you don’t want
anything tragic to happen,
pay me a ransom of one...
two...
Three hundred thousand baht!
-What? Three hundred thousand baht!
-Three hundred thousand baht!
Hey. I only owe you 100,000 baht.
How did you hear that? The speaker is off.
My ears are good.
Do you hear your son crying?
Let me tell you.
I won't give you a dime.
There’s no relationship
between me and that faggot.
Who the fuck bit you?
Nanta, the crocodile.
Nanta, the crocodile?
Anyone can put their feet
in Nanta's mouth,
and it never bites anyone.
It never bit me before, too,
but it bit me today.
What kind of a father are you?
How can you disown your son?
Why can't I?
He had the guts to disown his own dick.
Listen to me, loud and clear.
I’m neither a saint nor a soft-hearted dad
of a faggot that you see on TV.
I don't know
how to be one of those fathers.
Hot damn.
He's so cold-blooded.
Pla.
Did you really cut off your dick?
It's none of your business.
Listen.
If I don't get my money back,
I'm going to shoot you.
Come on. Shoot me.
I might look like a little pansy,
but I can tell that that gun is fake.
If I had seen it yesterday,
you couldn’t have fooled me today.
Is that so?
Why don’t you try this shit first?
No.
-Keep laughing.
-No.
"Shoot me."
Fuck you.
Hello.
-Tao.
-You're sadistic.
-Tun's drinking again.
-My whole body hurts.
Is he drinking again?
Was it my fault?
Was it because of my fickle heart?
Or was it your fault?
Or was it your gullible ears?
Whatever pulled us apart
I just want to tell you the truth
I want you to listen to me for once
I'm confused going down
-Because of your changing heart
-Look at your friend.
What is going on?
He said he’s heartbroken.
Heartbroken?
Which bitch was riding
past his house this time?
Still that whore, Nok.
What?
Didn't I warn you
that that guy is too sensitive
when it comes to girls?
Whatever pulled us apart
How much did he drink?
About half a bottle.
Why didn’t you guys stop him?
How could we?
We got here too fucking late.
Just be honest and say you didn’t dare to.
All right. I didn’t dare to stop him.
You know he becomes Mad Max
when he’s tanked up.
Even Chang wouldn’t dare to mess with him.
Take it easy, man.
Take it easy.
I don't get it.
Nok is Kamnun Moo’s girl.
Tun.
Don’t talk bullshit.
That's not funny.
Who the fuck is joking here?
Huh?
Tao.
Kamnun Moo said,
"Don't even think of running away."
Hey! Look!
Sit over there.
Holy shit!
What he said was true?
Tun.
Don't.
Please.
Do it for me.
You are on your own.
But I’m your best friend.
Sit down, you jackass!
No!
Tun.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
He already said sorry.
Just let it go, will you?
No.
There’s much more
between Nok and me.
What the hell is it?
It’s what you don’t have.
What don't I have?
True love.
True love, my ass!
What kind of love grows in one night?
It’s something
you guys wouldn’t understand.
Yes, I’d like to hear you sing.
Where are you going?
Tun.
Didn’t your friend tell you?
He did.
Didn’t you say you loved me?
Are you stupid or what?
Is there a guy who still believes
in such a thing?
Yes.
No, there isn't.
Men don’t have the word "love"
in their dictionary.
All guys...
are the same.
I’m just one
Of the love choices she discarded to her
I’m only a useless cigarette butt
She breathed in all the sweetness
And dumped me
Left me crushed under her feet
I’m just one of the love choices
She discarded
It feels like being hit
On the head by a mallet
Tun.
I’m too sensitive and naive
Kamnun Moo.
It's okay.
You’ve just interrupted me
in the middle of my song.
I butted in
because I’m a dipshit.
I’m an idiot who doesn’t even know
what love is.
But honestly,
I...
have a sincere
affection
for this woman.
This asshole is a sweet talker.
Award-winning poets
should call you "Father."
Are you drunk?
I admit that I'm drunk.
But I know
what I’m talking about.
Do you know him?
Do you?
Do you really love this woman?
If love means sincerity,
then the answer is yes!
Can your sincerity be put into price?
No, it can't.
If that's the case,
then your sincerity might not be love.
The love of this woman
is worth 3,000,000.
Do you have that?
If you do,
go ahead and take your love back.
She's all yours.
Or is your love
worth less than that?
Deal.
I'll give you 3,000,000 baht.
All right. You’re the man!
But for now, get your ass out of here.
Whenever you have the money,
you can come and get your love.
All right.
I'll go.
I’m just one of the love choices
What's the plan?
I can't do anything
until those pricks leave.
To her I’m only a useless cigarette butt
She breathed in all the sweetness
And dumped me
Left me crushed under her feet
I’m just one of the love choices
She discarded
It feels like being hit
On the head by a mallet
I’m too sensitive and naive
I’m nothing but a beginner
In this game of love
Hey.
Is he dead?
How much did you pay for it?
Three million baht.
-It's not true.
-What?
-Really?
-Yes.
There are only nine authentic amulets
of this kind in the world.
Three belong to Mr. Por.
The fourth one is with Chief Kwang.
The fifth one is with Big Mod.
The sixth one is with Tri-Croc Temple.
The seventh one is with Father Sua.
The eighth one is with Dr. Keng.
And the last one
is at my house.
Anything other than these are fakes.
Where did you get it from?
I got it from someone I know.
The one that you own...
can you sell it to me?
It was passed down
to my dad by my grandfather.
So, it's kind of our heirloom.
I'll pay you 3,000,000.
Agatha Kinsky once said
"Love
makes you do stupid things.
And so does greed."
Hey.
What's your name?
Noo.
You're Noo, huh?
You look mixed.
Where do you go to school?
Bangkok.
What are you doing in Pattaya?
My parents live here.
Great "Butt-siness" Company.
It’s "Business."
What the fuck are you laughing at?
"Butt-siness?"
Who’s your father?
Mickey.
Like Mickey Mouse?
What about this,
since you think your English is good,
I’m going to call her father
and then you talk to him.
Tell him
that his daughter
has been kidnapped for a ransom.
Like a kidcracker.
What the fuck are you laughing at?
"Kidcracker," my ass!
I thought you were good.
My father isn’t a foreigner.
My father can speak Thai.
Why didn’t you say so, bitch?
You’re a bitch.
Do you want your ass kicked?
Oh! You’re going to get it, you bitch!
Pla.
Shut the hell up.
Are you Mickey?
Listen carefully.
This is a ransom call.
Your daughter is with me right now.
If you don't pay me a ransom of...
of...
three million baht.
Greedy asshole.
Why?
Her dad is richer than yours.
Hello. Do you hear me?
If you don't give me 3,000,000 baht,
I’ll cut your daughter into pieces
and send it piece by piece to you.
Your dad stood me up.
When are you going to release me?
When I get the ransom.
When will that be?
It seems like her father is ditching you.
Shut up, you monkey’s ass.
You... Skunk.
Ass-licker.
Bitch. You're a slut.
-You're a slut.
-Bitch!
-Why don't you hit her too?
-It serves you right.
You’re getting on my nerves.
I can’t help it.
Your father is aggravating me.
You’re dead meat, bitch.
Cut her.
Cut her tongue out.
What a mouth she's got.
I’d love to see you in pain.
I thought you were kidding.
Is it in full?
Yes, sir.
I'm a man of my word.
Can I pay you only 2.9 million?
Why?
I want to pay Tao’s debt of 100,000 baht.
I see.
What a man you are.
Don’t you think
you drink Red Bull too much?
Anyway,
since you dared to ask,
I'm going to give it to you.
You have the guts to bring me 3,000,000.
I respect you for that.
-Koong.
-Yes.
Be a man and do your job.
Nok.
Love is yours.
Why did you do that?
What do you want to prove?
Nothing.
I just wanted you to know
that men are not all bad.
Are you sure you’ll set me free?
Yes.
So somebody already paid my debt?
But you're banned
from playing games with us.
Of course.
I won't gamble anymore.
That will be my last time.
I'm done.
Shit.
It was only 3,000,000.
Why didn't you give it to them?
How could you let them cut off her finger?
Don't you remember
I lost all my money
to you?
You’re damn right.
I came here
to borrow some money from you.
Let me ask you this, Mickey.
How long have you known me?
I've known you
for only a year.
See? It hasn't even been a year
and you're already
borrowing money from me.
-Koong.
-Yes, sir.
Get Tun's money.
There is 3,000,000 in here.
Take this money
to the designated location.
Thank you very much.
And my henchmen
will take care of those creeps.
Hello.
It’s me, Chief Mhee.
I know your amulet is fake.
If I don’t get back my money today,
you are dead!
You cruel, evil-minded son of a bitch.
All right. I’m sorry.
Your apology
can’t make my finger grow back.
Why didn’t you cut
that skunk’s finger off?
Why did you cut mine?
Well.
I wanted a human finger,
not a skunk's.
Bastard!
-Dick face!
-Hey!
You had your dick cut off before.
This is just a pinky.
Stop screaming like you will die.
Damn you!
One more word,
and I’ll also cut out your tongue.
I’ll let you go.
If you tell anybody,
I’ll carve your lips off.
Do you understand?
Go home now.
Your car’s at the back of the building.
Why? Don’t you need the money anymore?
Not anymore.
Also,
it seems like no one is coming
to help you.
I knew it.
Please don't cut the rope.
Just leave it like that.
It turns me on.
Sir?
Sir.
Your phone's ringing.
Oh, right.
Tun.
Where are you?
I can't stay in Pattaya anymore.
Chief Mhee will kill me.
Why does he want to kill you?
He found out that I sold him
a fake amulet.
Why did you do that?
How much did you get from him?
-Three million baht.
-Three million baht?
Fuck you.
Yes, fuck me!
I have no idea
how to return his 3,000,000.
He wants his money back today.
Where did you spend your 3,000,000 on?
I paid your debt of 100,000 baht.
Oh, thank you.
What about the other 2.9 million baht?
Tun!
This is Mickey speaking.
-Okay.
-I've got the money.
Where do you want to meet?
The same place?
In 30 minutes?
-Hello.
Is that Noo? It's me, Tao.
What's up, darling?
Where are you now?
I’m in front of my house,
about to drive in.
-Has anyone seen you?
-Not yet. I just got here.
-Pull the car out of there.
-Where to?
Anywhere.
I'll come see you.
Really?
Yes, I miss you already.
Shall I wait at my friend's condo?
Yes. Wait for me there.
Don't go anywhere until I call you.
Hey, where is my daughter?
You can call her cell phone now.
Do you know why your father died?
Because he was a playboy.
But you are going to die
because of your trickiness.
Whose phone is ringing?
Is it yours?
No. It's his.
Why did you take his phone?
Damn. Pick it up.
-Hello.
-Tun.
I've got your 3,000,000 baht.
Sir,
the caller said
that he has the 3,000,000 baht.
Give me that goddamn phone.
-Hello.
-Who's talking?
-I’m Chief Mhee.
-Where's my friend?
He is about to die.
Do you want to say some last words to him?
Please don’t hurt him.
I'm on my way to return your money.
Are you?
All right.
I'll give you 20 minutes.
Nok is here.
Send her in.
-Kae.
-Yes, Sir.
Get her something to drink.
Yes, sir.
It looks like nobody's coming.
Honey.
Let's go.
The amulet saved me.
Oh, shit.
Where do you think you’re going?
I’m taking the money to your boss.
You’re already hours late.
He doesn’t want it anymore.
What happened to my friend?
Do you think you're cool?
Son of a bitch.
Fuck.
Tell me now that you want to die.
Tell me.
Tell me, son of a bitch.
Say it.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
I really can't do it.
Give me my 3,000,000 back, then.
You saved my life.
But I...
Hey.
Are you stealing my amulets?
Are you still alive?
I would have been dead
if I waited for you.
How did you make it out alive?
Please don't kill him.
Suppose a woman
sells herself as a sex slave for a year
just to save a guy’s life,
what would you do if you were him?
What would I do?
What?
What's this?
Three million baht.
If I were him,
I would use this 3,000,000 baht
to get her back.
Where did you get this money from?
ManU.
Someone once said
that love only begins
when you have faith.
And when there is faith,
there’s always a miracle.
I'm sorry.
I thought it was Nok's car.
This car now belongs to Chief Mhee.
What do you mean?
I guess girls
aren't worth as much as cars.
That's why he chose the car instead.
Miracles don’t always happen
to people with faith.
Because since that day,
Tun has never seen Nok again.
LIGHTNING ROD KARAOKE
We’re going to drink
And get drunk to eternity
-No check, no chase, no end of me
-Earth.
-What?
-Take your girlfriend home.
I'm closing the store.
Get up.
His crying and babbling may sound annoying
But nobody knows that
My friend’s heart is breaking
She’s way out of his league
Hey.
We're closing.
What's wrong with you?
It's your friend's birthday today.
He's my friend, not yours.
You're drunk, so go away now.
I told you to invest in something else.
Krating.
Where are you looking at?
She’s my girlfriend.
-Oh?
-He stares at me like this every day.
Right. Why don’t you just get used to it?
Stupid.
Get out. I’m closing the place.
What kind of owner
that drives his customers away?
Look at Chang over there.
I’ve quit singing.
I know.
Think of it as a birthday present from me.
I’m right here waiting for you
-Whenever she makes you so blue
-Happy birthday!
Oh, oh
Whenever I see your heart broken
My heart is also drowning
In pain
-If her love is too mean
-And unkind
-I’ll wipe your tears away
-Till they dry
-Tll they dry
-Give me your bruised heart
-Let my true love heal it fast
When two people love the same song,
it shouldn’t be called "destiny."
And as for the return of Nok,
it shouldn’t also be called a miracle.
Einstein once said
"There are no such things as miracles.
Everything that happens
has its cause and effect.
The repercussions of an action
that some races
and religions
call
"Karma."
Why don’t we use real guns?
That’s too merciful.
These air guns would give him
a slow and painful death.
Are you all ready?
-Yes.
One hundred thousand baht to the first
person who cuts off Tao's finger.
-Yeah!
Charge!
Subtitle Translation by
Thanatcha Saksiamkul