When will we get there?
This is as fast as we can go.
We'll be late for the auspicious time.
Hurry up.
Hey!
Where is the mahout?
Where is everyone?
Mahout!
Help me.
What are you doing?
I'm about to be ordained for you.
No!
GENERAL BUDDHIST SCRIPTURE SCHOOL
THUMMANAKANIMIT TEMPLE
WEDNESDAY APRIL 11, 2019
NOVICE'S PRECEPT EXAMINATION
There will be a precept examination today.
Prepare yourself.
Okay.
As for the novices who were late,
you must clean the classroom later.
"During the time
before the Buddha reached devaloka,
he told Moggallana
to make merit to the people
and told Anathapindika to feed everyone.
For that reason, Anathapindika
let my body return to devaloka
accordingly."
MAENMUANG JITSIRI
You're getting better at this.
Your grandpa must have felt at peace.
Luang Na, he died with his eyes open.
He won't be at peace.
Don't mess with me.
How are you doing now?
I'm fine.
My grandpa had life insurance.
He said I would get a huge sum of money.
I can withdraw the money
if I need to use it.
You should consider getting insured,
so your family won't struggle.
All right. I think I will…
You little punk.
Don't jinx me. I've been unwell lately.
Did he really get ordained
to avoid the curse?
He was cursed since he left this temple.
Bad things kept happening to him.
Even after he got ordained again,
the curse was still after him,
until it finally took his life.
I never thought
that the curse I heard about
when I was young
would be real.
Did no one survive after they disrobed?
From what I heard,
no one did.
No one could escape
even though they got ordained again.
Does this mean that Balloon and First
will die?
They shouldn't have left.
They would only cause trouble
if they stayed.
This is good for everyone.
First!
Balloon!
What happened to your arm?
Hey!
Keep it down.
I think he meant me.
Come here, First.
Sorry.
Listen.
Ever since I disrobed,
that damn ghost has been haunting me.
I almost died many times.
I'm in the same boat as you.
I lost my job and all the guys dumped me.
I nearly die every day.
More importantly,
I see him almost every time
that something happens.
He's wearing a nak's robe.
He must be the same one.
He always says that if you--
If you disrobe, you'll die.
Exactly.
Right. I'm like…
If you disrobe, you'll die.
Die!
-Die!
-First.
If you disrobe, you'll die.
Balloon, wait for me.
Hurry, First.
If you disrobe, you'll die.
THUMMANAKANIMIT TEMPLE
One down, Novice Bom.
Mission success.
Novice Good.
The whole party is gone, Novice Nott.
The fort is down, Aod.
Great.
All crushed to the ground.
That's a bit too dramatic, Novice Bom.
Wait. Where's Fahlan?
-Right.
-I don't know.
Fahlan!
-Fahlan!
-I'm here, everyone.
Over here.
-What?
-Keep walking straight.
-I'm here, everyone.
-We're over here.
-Where?
-Right here.
-Where are you?
-We're over here.
That was so fun. Should we continue?
Take this off.
I totally forgot.
Thank you, Novice Nott.
He's over there.
Thank you.
Should we continue?
-Sure.
-One moment, everyone.
Use this, Aod.
It's the best.
Great.
This year's Loy Krathong Festival
will be awesome.
-Let's try it now.
-Wait.
This is dangerous.
It's for the badass people.
Don't mess with it.
Novice Nott, they're all dangerous.
-What about those two--
-Wait.
That's my voice.
Right.
What about those two trannies
that you told us about?
I wonder how they're doing.
They must be dead by now.
It's funny. They can't be ordained
because of the curse,
and they also can't disrobe.
How can someone be so unlucky?
It's good that they left.
We can finally have some peace.
Aod.
Are you sure we'll have peace?
Look over there.
Novice!
Aod!
The bad luck of Thummanakanimit Temple
has returned.
Novice!
Are you sure you want
to get ordained here?
-Alms bowl?
-Check.
-Yellow robe?
-Undergarments?
-We got the fireproof kind.
I can't do it.
Why not, Luang Pee?
I am not qualified.
Luang Loong is not around.
He's on a pilgrimage.
How about this?
While we wait, you can ordain us as naks.
Luang Loong can ordain us as monks
once he's back.
But if it takes too long,
we can get ordained at another temple.
Good. Should we go to Luang Pu Kem?
Recently, someone also ran away
just like you two.
He was haunted,
so he came back to get ordained again
in order to revoke the curse.
Do you think he made it?
No.
We can't get ordained,
and we also can't disrobe.
What do you want from us?
Luang Pee.
Is there a way for us to survive this?
Well,
you can stay here for now.
When Luang Na Yong recovers
from his illness,
he can perform an ordination ceremony.
In the meantime,
we'll find a way to revoke the curse.
There might be a way.
But this time,
you can't disrobe again.
I know.
Greetings, Luang Pee.
I brought my son to be ordained here.
You can call me "eomma."
What a pretentious bitch.
Min-Jun, come here.
I know she's faking it.
Does she think she's Dae Jung Geum?
Should we place an order?
First, I'll place my order with the chef.
Balloon.
Behind you.
Toh Min-Jun!
Toh Min-Jun.
Come here.
He's so cute. What do we do?
Mom.
Can I not get ordained?
No.
He's my son.
Hello, ma'am.
-She's pretty.
-But…
this place is full of strange people.
They look weird.
I can't stay here.
What is he saying?
-Maybe he wants to buy us a meal.
-Trust me.
-I made a vow here.
-They're still talking.
If you won't get ordained,
don't come back to Korea.
Do you understand?
Mom.
He's so cute.
Toh Min-Jun.
Cute, my ass. You bastard.
Shit, First. He just said it.
He said you're beautiful, First.
-You're right. He said I'm beautiful.
-Shit.
Are you sure you want
to get ordained here?
Is there a problem?
Well, there is…
Let's get to the point.
Well, I made a vow here
that if Min-Jun became
a boy band member in Korea,
I would fulfill my vow
by bringing him here to be ordained.
-You made a vow to this temple?
-Yes, I did.
Min-Jun has been down on luck this year.
He almost died so many times,
so I want him to get ordained today.
Almost died?
Does the curse still exist?
If he gets ordained here,
he can't disrobe.
If he disrobes, he will die.
You have to fulfill your vow.
You'll die if you don't keep your word.
I experienced it myself.
He can get ordained at another temple.
It has to be here.
If he gets ordained here,
we will take care of your son
like he's our beloved.
I told the boys and the novices
to sleep at the school.
You can stay here.
First, my heart is going to explode.
It's not every day
that we get to see
a superstar like Toh Min-Jun
looking bulgy like this.
What's bulgy?
Luang Pee, I can't just say
he has a bulgy crotch.
I just said it.
Where are you going?
I'll invite him to stay with us.
If you don't really want to get ordained,
just leave.
That's right.
You haven't changed at all.
Gosh.
You can carry your own stuff.
This is just great.
My bulgy baby.
Your bulgy…
Mom! How do I do this?
-Shit.
-You're the little shit.
No shit.
This is destiny.
Are you here to take a shower?
I just finished. You can go right in.
Have you just finished?
Neither of us have finished yet.
-I should leave.
-Hey.
What's the hurry?
Are you scared of ghosts?
I'm scared of you.
First, you're not being flirty.
You're being horny, bitch.
You can just talk normally.
I can hear you.
I have to apologize for my friend.
I'm right here.
I can't take this anymore.
Me neither.
Fuck.
Another compliment.
You're so lucky.
He's speaking Korean to you all day.
-Fuck!
-Please stop.
He said it again, First.
I said fuck!
It's a snake. I'm out of here.
-Shit.
-Balloon, help me.
Help me! My balls!
My balls!
-My balls!
-It's my balls! Fuck! Let go of me!
Novice!
Everybody, stop!
Let me.
Novice, help me.
Come on, Novice.
Novice.
I think I should leave.
Novice, stop.
Is it safe?
-First.
-Pick it up, Novice.
-Do I pick it up?
-Yes. Hurry up.
Quickly.
-Get it away.
-First.
First.
First!
-My glasses.
-First.
-Where are my glasses?
-What?
-Grab it.
Shit!
-Pull it.
-On three!
I'm here.
-It's so big and so long.
-No.
Bone!
-What bone?
-I'm still here.
You have a boner.
Fahlan.
-First.
-Stop, Novice.
I'll slap you. Stop!
Stop!
Get back.
First, why are you down there?
To be with your man.
It's a snake.
You can't leave me!
First!
Wait for me.
Mr. Toh.
Calm down. Where are you going?
Let go of me. I'm leaving.
Mr. Toh, calm down.
You're wet.
-Calm down. Where are you going?
-Mr. Toh.
I don't want to be ordained.
I can't stay here.
-Goodbye.
-Mr. Toh.
Please stay.
-I'll tell you later.
-Are you okay, Balloon?
Mr. Toh, if you leave now,
you will be in danger.
It's dangerous everywhere.
I have bad luck anywhere I go.
-I'm leaving.
-If you leave,
there might be an accident.
I don't know what you've been through,
but all of us have experienced it before.
You will die.
That's why we don't want you to leave.
That's right.
Haven't you been down on luck lately?
So who's the cursed one here?
Is it Mr. Toh, First, or Balloon?
I think this is either
the ordination curse
or the disrobement curse.
Let's not risk it.
That's right.
The ordination curse here is no joke.
You have to fulfill your vow.
From what your mother said,
there might still be
the curse of the previous Pee Nak.
The disrobement curse is just as bad.
Is it worse than Nak Non?
It's a lot worse.
Not only do we have the ordination curse,
but people say the disrobement curse
is much more frightful.
Whoever gets ordained here
can never disrobe.
If they do,
the curse will take their lives.
Help me!
Somebody, help me!
Help!
Luang Por!
Help me, Luang Por!
If you disrobe,
you'll die.
Wait a minute.
If the curse really exists,
that means if I get ordained here,
I…
You can't disrobe.
So I can neither get ordained nor disrobe.
Mr. Toh.
if you don't get ordained,
you might die.
But don't be afraid.
We are trying
to find a way to break the curse.
-Aod.
-Yes?
Did your grandpa ever tell you
how to revoke the curse?
I don't know.
If he and Luang Por were here,
we would've had some clues.
Now that you know about this,
what will you do next?
If what you all say is true,
I guess I'll stay.
May you be well all year round.
May you always be happy.
-I'm aching all over.
-Hello, Luang Pee.
Greetings, ma'am.
Shit.
You scared us again.
I'm just joking, Luang Pee.
Are you trick-or-treating?
A ghost is up early to give alms.
He's a human. Don't be rude.
Where is Jay?
He's inside, Luang Pee.
He must be a halfling.
Half spirit, half ghost.
His brother must look worse.
Hello, Luang Pee.
Greetings.
Your alms round procession
seems livelier than usual today.
I have two friends that want
to be ordained.
There is also a Korean superstar.
Really, Novice?
-He's at the market with Novice Bom.
-Won't the market be in mayhem?
I don't think so.
-Luang Pee.
-Hurry.
Luang Pee!
Novice!
Hey.
Stop!
Are you here to get survival packs
or something?
It's because of your superstar.
Everyone, please guard me.
I was caught off guard.
It's too late. The whole town saw you.
I think this is kind of exciting.
Yes. I wish it was like this every day.
That's enough.
Please step back, everyone.
Get back.
Take a step back.
Go on.
Please step back.
This isn't nice.
Come on, Luang Pee.
We just want to see
our beloved Toh Min-Jun up close.
It's not every day
that we have an opportunity like this.
That's right.
The man you love is about to assume
a new status.
He is about to be ordained.
What he wants is peace.
-Is he getting ordained?
-What?
It's okay.
Thank you very much
for your love and support.
I am about to be ordained.
Let's all make merit together.
-Really?
-So we'll meet again in our next lives.
-Everybody.
-He's handsome and kind.
You once turned an ordinary man
into someone extraordinary.
If you listen to me,
you can turn an extraordinary man
into a man of religion.
Sadhu.
Excuse me, Luang Pee.
Don't worry about Mr. Toh.
I will take care of him
like I'm guarding Buddhism itself.
-I'm sorry, Novice.
-Thank you.
Listen to me. Don't worry.
Watch my face, bitch.
Don't worry about him.
Don't…
Don't worry. I will take care of him.
You can go home now.
Go on. Let's all go home.
Put the food in the alms bowl.
It's lunch time.
Novice, why are you napping here?
Aren't you supposed to be studying
with your friends?
Keep it down, sir.
-I'm sorry.
-I'm just resting my eyes.
What about you?
I thought you didn't want to be ordained.
Why do you seem so committed?
Do you want to be ordained or not?
Novice.
Although I don't want to do it,
I'm obligated to do my duty.
You should do the same.
You must do your duty as a novice.
Criticizing a novice
is like criticizing Buddhism itself.
Is that right, Novice?
One, two, three, four.
That's everybody.
One, two.
Aod.
Aod, wake up.
Shit.
What's with you?
There's someone here.
Can you go take a look?
Go have a look yourself.
Please, Aod. I'm scared.
They're over there.
Who's there?
Come with me.
Balloon.
-First.
-Balloon.
-Aod, we have to collect alms at dawn.
-First.
-Balloon.
Aod.
-Damn it.
-Calm down, Aod.
Aod.
Let him sleep.
Novice Nott.
What is it, Aod?
There's a burglar.
A burglar?
Novice Nott.
Do you have the flashlight?
Novice Nott, turn the flashlight on.
Wake up!
-It's a ghost.
-Wake up.
-Wait.
-Hurry.
-What now?
-Come on.
-Calm down.
-A ghost is here.
What?
It's a ghost!
A ghost!
Novice.
You shouldn't talk bullshit.
It's true.
First.
Let's go.
Hey.
It's here.
What a cliché.
The door is locked.
Something will fall to the ground.
Then the door will slowly open.
This is every horror movie cliché.
Novice Nott.
Yes?
Please come forward.
-Please.
-Why…
Why me? There are others here.
Novice.
But I'm a novice.
-I'm not--
-You're not an X-Men, right?
Today you are.
Easy.
We're trying our best.
-Walk slowly.
-I am, Novice.
I'm scared.
I…
Novice!
Novice.
Novice, chant something.
-Thou shalt not commit adultery.
-That's not right.
-Just tell me what to say.
-Hurry.
Thou shalt not drink--
Come on, man. Be serious.
Come on, Novice.
Chant whatever comes to your mind.
-I got one. Honor to the Blessed One--
-No!
Come on!
Stop!
Novice.
That's it, Novice!
Keep chanting!
I've chanted that mantra
even before you were born.
First.
Why are you doing aerobics here?
-First.
-What's wrong with him?
First!
-First, no.
-First.
Stay calm, First.
Don't do it! No!
-Stop!
-First!
-First, no!
-First.
First.
-First, no!
-Don't do it!
Please stop it!
First.
That's enough. Stop it.
-Stop it!
-Stop!
-Knock it off.
-Stop it.
First, stop it.
Fahlan!
Let me hide in here.
-First, stop it already.
-First.
-Please stop it.
What's wrong with you?
It's me, Balloon.
I'm Balloon.
Aod.
Aod, why are you lying down here?
Help me.
-Are you all right?
-That hurt.
What's going on?
You two, please don't fight.
Friends don't fight.
First, Balloon can't take it anymore.
Novice!
First, please stop.
-First, let go.
-First, it's me.
Stop it.
First.
If you disrobe, you'll die.
Luang Pee.
Well, Novices.
Novice Good. Novice Kiddee. Novice Bom.
You ran out on us.
Now we're all in trouble.
-That's enough!
-Aod.
Aod.
Aod, calm down.
Don't you both realize it?
I think both of you should leave.
-I can't take it anymore.
-Aod.
Calm down.
Calm down? Everyone almost died.
Do you want me to be calm?
Aod, do you think I want this to happen?
Don't you think you're being too harsh?
Why did you disrobe?
All of this happened because of you two.
Your best friend is a monk,
and you abandoned him!
Aod!
Aod.
What we did was wrong.
But don't you think...
you're being too hurtful?
Aod, this isn't the time
to blame one another.
We must solve this together.
The solution is for both of you
to leave the temple.
-You crossed the line, Aod!
-Balloon.
-Please calm down.
-Novice.
I know I can be stupid sometimes,
but I'm not so stupid
that I can't tell he meant it!
-Calm down.
-So what if I did?
-Stop!
That's enough.
Please don't fight.
Aod, please stop.
You should leave too.
-Watch your mouth!
-Stop it, Aod.
Aod!
Aod.
Get up, Jay.
I don't like how aggressive you are, Aod.
Apologize to them.
Do I have to apologize?
Now.
You always side with your friends.
Aod.
Novice.
Aod, listen to me.
I know
that you're not really mad at those guys.
You're just worried.
But don't you think
Luang Pee would be hurt
by what you said?
He loves you
and worries about you.
But this Pee Nak
is much more menacing than Nak Non.
If I lose you and Luang Pee,
how will I live?
I have no one left.
That's why we need to fix this,
so we don't lose anyone.
Luang Pee.
Please forgive me.
Aod, get up.
It's all right.
We will be okay, Aod.
I won't let anything happen to us.
No matter how scary Pee Nak is,
we'll get through this together.
Mr. Toh.
We're not sure
if we will be given another chance
to get ordained here.
But you must do it.
You can do it.
We've come this far.
All of us will get to be ordained here.
I believe that the monk
will help all of us get ordained.
We don't know...
if we're going to make it.
During our last ordination,
we caused so much trouble
that we had to run away.
Luang Pee.
Have you never thought about disrobing?
I thought about it after you left.
But the longer I stayed,
the more I started to see.
I get to teach kids,
help people,
and improve myself.
I started to have self-worth.
I want to have that too,
that self-worth you mentioned.
I want people to like me.
I want to get many likes
and I want my band
to gain more and more followers.
But the more I keep at it
and the harder I try,
the more I feel like I'm losing myself.
I get stressed.
I feel pressured.
It's so difficult
to force myself to smile like this.
Novice Nott.
Give this to Mr. Toh.
Hold it like that.
For how long?
Try holding it for three hours.
My arms will be tired.
Anyone would feel stiff
after holding it that long.
Then why are you doing it?
Why don't you put it down?
You told me to hold it.
And who's in pain now?
Is it me
or you?
Thank you.
Luang Pee.
Balloon.
-Is that her?
-First.
I think so.
If Luang Pee decides to disrobe,
what will we do?
If he disrobes,
I'm going to make a move on him.
Bitch, that's a sin. We're in a temple.
I'm just joking. Can't you tell?
Damn.
Luang Pee has been ordained for so long.
He won't disrobe.
But still.
His ex showed up
at the temple with his son.
Don't you think they have
a father-son bond?
Did you see the kid's face?
He doesn't look like Luang Pee at all.
Maybe it's not his.
How would you know?
The kid's age fits the time frame
of their breakup.
I think it's Luang Pee's son.
His son?
I'm sorry, Novice.
-Novice.
-That hurts.
Novice.
Why did you push me?
Well, what were you up to?
It's Balloon.
What now? What did I do this time?
We're here.
First.
You said it, and the novices heard you.
Then you got startled.
Are you sure?
I've never been more sure of anything.
If you and I had just kept quiet,
no one would know
that Luang Pee has a son.
Balloon, keep it down.
What's the point?
Everyone in the temple already knows
that Luang Pee has a son.
Why are you rubbing it in?
I'm not rubbing it in.
I'm just making myself clear.
Just ask the novices
if Luang Pee has a son.
Let's come this way.
Don't tell anyone
that Luang Pee has a son.
Just say it's my son, bitch.
Hey!
Balloon.
Well… No one here can handle the truth.
You accused me of ratting him out.
Tell me what you think, Novice.
Don't act solemn.
Aod.
Where are you going?
Luang Na Yong asked Jay and I
to fix the light.
They don't have an electrician.
I'll come with you.
-Luang Pee Nong.
-First.
Is something the matter?
I need to talk to Luang Na Yong.
-Let's go.
Hop on, Luang Pee.
Luang Pee.
-Luang--
-Jay.
-Swing by my residence first.
-Okay.
Where is he rushing to?
To see Luang Na Yong.
He said he needed to talk to him.
The disrobement myth
has been around for ages,
even before I was born.
If you really want to know,
you should ask older people.
I don't know if they are still alive.
I think you came to see me
because of something else.
I teach everyone to let go,
but I'm the one
who keeps holding on.
Are you thinking of disrobing?
It's time for me to rest.
Let me help you.
-Balloon.
-Balloon!
Balloon!
-Is he over there?
Mr. Toh, don't point that at random.
-I'm sorry.
-Where is he?
Why do we have to look for him
in this hot weather?
Balloon!
Let's just get it done.
Will this take long?
Aod.
Jay.
What are you playing at?
I can't see with my head stuck
in an alms bowl.
Why did you let me walk off alone, First?
Where am I?
First.
Monk Nong.
No.
It's this way. I remember.
It's starting to come back to me.
Aod!
Aod! Aod!
Stay out of this.
Luang Pee.
Stop it.
Who are you?
-I'm Aod.
-I'm Jay.
That's a cloth.
Something isn't right. Shit!
What is it?
It's over there, Mr. Toh.
Balloon!
Stay right there.
Mr. Toh.
I'm sorry, Balloon.
My nose!
Be patient, Balloon. It's coming off.
I have an idea.
Balloon, are you ready?
I've been ready since last week.
Novice.
Why didn't you cut the whole thing off?
I'm sorry. I forgot.
This looks kind of awesome.
Right.
But it's missing something.
You look awesome, Balloon.
Get out of the way.
-What is it?
-What?
Novices, what's wrong?
Luang Pee, help.
Wait. Be careful.
Balloon.
What should we do? It's an elephant.
Do you want me
to catch a grasshopper on its back?
First, help me.
Be gentle.
My head.
If you disrobe, you'll die!
Help me.
First.
First, help me.
Mr. Toh.
Get out of the way.
First. Mr. Toh.
Balloon.
-Hey!
-Where are you taking me, you bastard?
Balloon!
Let me go!
Balloon.
Please let me go!
Don't do it!
No!
Please don't hurt me!
Balloon!
EMERGENCY
How are you feeling?
Can you afford the payment?
You can tell me.
It's no problem, Luang Pee.
Balloon has insurance.
It covers everything.
THAI LIFE INSURANCE
Where is Mr. Toh?
He's outside looking glum.
I don't know if he's scared
or reconsidering his ordination.
Do you want to go and rest at the temple?
Luang Pee.
I'd rather stay here.
I…
I tried to help Balloon.
But I couldn't grab his hand in time.
Is it because of my curse?
No matter whose curse it is,
I'd like to thank you
for risking your life to help my friend.
Sure.
Mr. Toh.
Thank you so much.
It's okay, First.
We've been through a lot together.
We are like brothers now.
Here. Keep it for protection.
This looks familiar.
I think I saw it before I passed out.
A Naga Prok pendant.
Pee Nak had it around his neck.
This could be an important clue.
I went to search
the late abbot's residence today,
and I found old pictures of
when he discovered the Naga Prok pendant
at the ancient arch.
That's Luang Por and Luang Loong.
They look young in the pictures.
Does our temple have an ancient arch?
Yes, but I don't know where it is exactly.
Hello, Novice Bom.
Novice Nott, I've got something.
Just a moment.
What is it, Novice Bom?
Greetings, Luang Pee.
I'm with the abbot of Nua Temple,
He is the oldest monk around here,
and he knows about the ancient arch
at our temple.
You need to come here, Luang Pee.
I don't know
how it happened.
The fact that he is still here
means he's holding a grudge.
Who is he?
Luang Pee.
Luang Pu seems tired.
Let me ask you one last question.
Okay.
Do you know how to revoke the curse?
He was born with a grudge.
You have to make him let go
of that grudge.
There was a plague.
All villagers and monks
had to evacuate.
SMALLPOX
SMALLPOX - AN ANCIENT PANDEMIC
HOW TO CURE SMALLPOX
BAIWAN
How old is he?
He's two years old.
-Is he my son?
-I'm here to say goodbye.
I'm moving abroad.
I'm here to ask for your forgiveness.
BAIWAN
Why are you all lying here?
Kid!
Kid, wait for me.
-Hey.
-Mister.
Get the kid some medicine.
He's in bad shape.
Shit. Are they all dead?
First!
Kid!
What the hell?
Are you all dying?
Fuck.
Luang Pee.
Please help my mother.
Sir.
We have no more space. Go somewhere else.
Can't you take one more?
I said we have no more space.
What's all the racket about?
Luang Ta. Please.
Follow me to my residence.
But…
Bring some medicine too.
Come with me.
Yes, sir.
Venerable Monk.
First. Ball…
No, I'm Balloon.
Why are you so hideous?
Why are you walking towards me? Fuck off.
According to First,
Pee Nak has a Naga Prok pendant
around his neck.
His corpse must have one too.
Our second clue
is the pictures of Luang Loong
when he found the pendant
at the ancient arch.
That means…
Pee Nak's body must be there.
We have to find the ancient arch.
It's all trees.
Do you think it's been torn down?
I don't think so.
Luang Pu would have told us.
He might have forgotten.
It might be hidden in the woods.
Where?
It's the whole arch we're talking about.
Where would you hide it?
In a tree?
I've only seen anthills so far.
I think it should be…
Luang Por.
Right here.
Why would Pee Nak hurt people?
Balloon!
Balloon.
First. Is he possessed?
-Possessed?
-Yes.
Balloon.
Where's the amulet?
-Do you mean this?
-Ghosts are scared of amulets.
-Hurry.
-Balloon.
Balloon.
Why are you hurting people?
Luang Por.
I'm out of here!
What the hell is happening?
Balloon.
-What's wrong?
-Are you okay?
Balloon.
Who are you?
It's me, First.
-Who are you?
-I'm Toh.
Who am I?
You are Balloon.
I'm not. I'm out of here!
What is it?
My face looks like shit!
What?
-First.
-What?
We need to see Monk Nong.
-Calm down.
-Slow down.
You need to calm down.
First.
What?
Both of us
shared our past lives with Pee Nak.
Bullshit, Balloon.
First.
Luang Pee.
Wait for me, Aod.
Stay out of this.
They hurt me. They must die.
Have you two finished talking?
Is it over?
He's retreating,
but he still seems vengeful.
Did you really talk to a ghost?
I found his bones.
Everyone.
Find tools to help me dig.
Go on.
Okay.
What is this cup doing here?
Aod, come and give us a hand.
-Novice, come help us.
-Aod.
Everyone, get out of the way!
Move!
Mr. Toh.
What is this?
What is going on?
Hey.
Are you clearing out the graveyard?
Is this considered normal?
Since you came here,
everything has become normal.
But one thing is not.
Everybody.
Listen to Balloon.
He is not lying this time.
Go on.
That day, when I got…
You need to be polite around clergymen.
Venerable Father, on the day that I…
I…
I'm not good at this.
What's wrong?
Let me talk normally, Luang Pee.
-Pardon my language.
-Okay.
On the day I got thrown,
I couldn't remember how I passed out,
but I didn't wake up in the hospital.
-Where were you?
-Bitch, it was like
a temple hall. I started walking.
I came outside,
and I saw millions of ghosts.
There were millions of them.
This was just the first group.
Right?
You weren't there.
All of them looked like toad queens.
Their skin was all bumpy.
I told them to stay away from me.
I had this superpower.
I kept walking, and I saw monks.
An old monk turned around, and I went…
-Not there. Right here.
-Here.
I was shocked.
They turned out to be you and me, First.
But we were old!
You look terrible as an old man.
That's right.
You weren't there.
-What?
-You weren't there.
I'm being scared.
I was at an old arch.
-Were you in The Siam Renaissance?
-No.
I saw him walking…
I saw ghosts.
It was Pee Nak, Luang Pee.
But we still don't know
what causes Pee Nak to be so vengeful.
From what I just heard,
I think it has something to do
with you two, Balloon and First.
Then Pee Nak might not want anything
from Min-Jun.
This is totally on us.
-Everyone.
-Balloon.
-First.
-What's the matter?
-Wake up.
-Balloon.
-Balloon. First.
Everyone, we need to cremate
Pee Nak's bones.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Novice.
Jook and Klae, prepare food for Luang Ta
and meet me early today.
-Yes, sir.
-Luang Ta.
You shouldn't have let them stay here.
You might end up contracting the disease.
That's right.
Besides, you haven't been feeling well.
We are monks. People rely on us.
When they need help, how can I do nothing?
I really look shitty like you said.
First, that's Luang Ta.
You look worse than him.
That's you right there.
Lotus flowers.
You can have them.
Give them as offerings to the Buddha.
Here.
Here, Mom.
Ordain.
Luang Ta.
I promised my mom
I would be ordained for her.
Can you please
ordain me?
Please, Luang Ta.
Do you know about the Naga Prok myth?
Legend has it
that Mucalinda Naga,
a powerful being of the underwater world,
lived in a grand lotus pond
where the Buddha
remained in meditation
after attaining enlightenment.
Then it started to rain
for seven days straight.
Mucalinda Naga
admired the Buddha's virtue and morality,
so he coiled himself
and spread his hood
to protect the Buddha
from the wind and the rain.
Mucalinda Naga was the mighty
serpent king.
With his faith in virtue,
he offered himself
to protect the Buddha
against the elements.
This great merit
helped him to become enlightened later on.
You can do it too.
Nak Son.
It's great that you want to be ordained
for your mother.
But remember this.
If you hold onto self-entitlement
and harm those who make you suffer,
it will lead you to ruin,
and you shall never be reborn.
Remember my words, Nak Son.
And all of you as well.
If you keep thinking
you are better than others
and think only about yourselves,
the whole world will become your enemy.
-Luang Ta.
-Hey.
Luang Ta.
You should go rest inside.
Luang Ta!
Hey.
We can't stay here, Monk Thong.
Luang Ta.
We need to leave.
Wait, Luang Pee.
I'm begging you.
Please ordain me.
I want to dedicate the merit
of my ordination to my mom.
Please, Luang Pee.
-Please.
-Nak Son.
-You asshole.
-I beg you.
-Please ordain me.
-Nak Son.
-Please, Luang Pee.
-Hey!
-Stop it!
-Please, Luang Pee.
-Stop! Move!
Do you want the yellow robe for your mom?
Yes, Luang Pee.
Fine.
Here.
-Let's go.
-Wait.
-Hey.
-Wait, Luang Pee.
-Please ordain me.
-What now?
-Ordain me.
-Let me go!
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Take this as an offering, Mom.
I love you, Mom.
Do you hear me?
I renounce my ordination.
I'm sorry.
-May you all keep in mind
-I'm sorry, Mom.
that I am a layman.
You must conduct a funeral for my mom.
Can't you see
we aren't monks anymore?
You bastards.
You disrespected my mom.
-You must die.
-Hey.
You son of a bitch!
I let your mom have the yellow robe,
just as she wished.
You disrobed, so you must die.
Let's go.
Jook. Klae. Take the boat out.
You disrobed and left us to die.
May those who get ordained at this temple
never disrobe.
Those who do...
must die!
Look.
This Naga Prok pendant
is the one Luang Loong gave to Monk Nong.
It actually belongs to Nak Son.
It's the reason we ended up here.
What grave sin did we ever commit?
I understand now
why you had to make a vow here.
We were destined to be ordained here.
We are cursed to die
whether we get ordained or disrobe.
I get it now.
Balloon.
I'm scared.
First.
Look.
Lotus flowers.
It's hot. Help.
This is the crematorium.
-Help!
-We're screwed.
Come on.
-Hurry.
-Burn everything.
Bring it over here.
Where are my glasses?
They're here.
Look, First.
Nak Son.
-Stay back.
-Get away from us.
-Get back.
We need to run.
Get away.
-Don't come closer.
-Luang Pee!
Luang Pee!
-Don't hurt us!
-Luang Pee!
-I'm scared.
Luang Pee!
Where are you going, Balloon?
-Luang Pee.
-Stay with us.
Why did you help them?
Nak Son.
Please do this for me.
Let's all forgive and forget.
Your vengeance
is like the fire that's burning you.
Don't let that fire
consume your heart.
I'm not scared
even if hellfire
consumes my whole body.
Luang Pee.
I will drag them to hell.
Please forgive us.
We did wrong.
You ran away to save yourselves.
You left my mom to die.
We feel guilty about what we did.
We didn't know
how evil we were in the past,
but that was a long time ago.
Please give us a chance in this life.
Please forgive us.
You are lucky
that Luang Ta is still protecting you.
Otherwise, you would be dead.
Luang Ta.
You have always been kind to me.
In any lifetime,
you are always good to me.
Nak Son.
Your mom died...
because her time was up.
It is nobody's fault.
I also died of illness.
It's karma.
If you hold onto self-entitlement
and harm those who make you suffer,
it will lead you to ruin,
and you shall never be reborn.
Remember my words, Nak Son.
Did you forget the Naga Prok pendant
that I gave you?
If you keep thinking
you are better than others
and think only about yourselves,
the whole world will become your enemy.
Nak Son.
I take your teaching to heart.
I haven't forgotten.
But I'm so enraged.
If so,
maybe you can do this for my sake.
Let go of this rage
and dedicate this good karma
to yourself and your mom.
Let go of your grudge against them.
Their karma
will catch up to them when it's time.
I forgive those who have wronged me
for Luang Ta.
I forgive you.
I must bid you farewell.
People can die just like that
when their time comes.
We can die at any time.
No one knows the future,
so it's important
that we prepare ourselves
by doing good deeds
and thinking good thoughts.
We should help as many people
as we can before we die.
Most people always put themselves first,
but Luang Ta
put other people's lives
before his own.
That's why he was always willing
to help everyone
without thinking about himself.
Pee Nak saw that
and decided to let go of his grudge.
Giving is truly the greatest form of love.
Luang Pee.
When your ex came to see you,
did you ever think of disrobing?
For a brief moment, I did.
But when I thought it through,
I wondered if disrobing
would make me happy.
Would Baiwan be happy?
What I know for sure
is she seems happy
that I became a monk.
So I chose that happiness.
I understand now
how we can find that happiness
and how to return true happiness
to the people around us.
Sadhu.
May your soul rest in peace, Son.
You can stop hurting us
and let go of your grudge against us now.
Listen.
Vengeful spirits aren't bad people
who try to hurt us.
They are good people
who got hurt in the past
by sinners like us.
That's so wise, Luang Pee.
-I got it from the Internet.
-Jeez.
Aod.
Take it back.
Are we doing this again?
Jay.
No, thanks. I prefer Phra Somdej amulets.
Fahlan.
It's okay. I have my Luang Pu Kem amulet.
Novice Kiddee.
No.
-Novice Nott.
-I'd rather not.
I think we're safe now, Aod.
Pee Nak has let go of his grudge.
You should keep it.
All right.
By the way,
you didn't see me in the past, right?
Why? Do you always want to be with me?
I'm just asking.
Who would want to be with you?
Aod, you have a crush on me.
Tell everyone what you told me.
Is that right?
I saw it with my own eyes.
You gave him a look, Aod.
How confident!
Aod.
Punch him. Let him have it.
Punch him.
Is he still selling ice-cream?
Is it him?
-Jook. Klae.
-Yes, sir.
Take the boat out.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
Did you steal from a corpse again?
-No, we didn't.
-We didn't.
Hurry up.
I undertake the precept to refrain
from taking that which is not given.
I spent yesterday fulfilling my vow.
Chickens and offerings didn't seem enough.
Sadhu.
I want to go all out for Monk Min-Jun,
so I hired dancers to perform.
They're probably setting up the stage.
Wait. Can you set up a stage
at Pee Nak Shrine?
Of course. It's a big stage.
Anyway, what is Pee Nak Shrine?
Didn't you pray at the shrine out front?
I made a vow to a red shrine.
Please make my Min-Jun a global superstar
who is known all over the world.
What? That's a spirit house.
Mom, you prayed at the wrong shrine.
Hey.
He's wearing a yellow robe.
It's not a yellow robe. Let's go again.
He's wearing a nak's robe.
Cut.
Shit.
Aim, look.
It got in my mouth.
Come on, Novice.
It's open.
Why is it open?
Are you hurt, Pat?
Are you hurt?
First.
-Sorry.
-I'm going to faint.
I have an inhaler.
-Why am I staggering?
-Relax.
Take a deep breath.
-You should be ordained.
-Butt out.
-"Disrobe."
-Disrobe.
Disrobe.
Look more fierce.
Luang Pee.
Cut.
He's not playing along with us.
-Don't mess around.
-Mr. Toh, come here.
Be careful.
-Mr. Toh!
-He's mine.
I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
-What?
-Sangkham…
Luang Pee is going to…
Sorry.
-Luang Pee.
-What's that?
I have the boys…
Don't laugh.
What's so funny about boys?
Subtitle translation by
Thanatcha Saksiamkul