Help.
I need help.
Pee Mak.
A long time has passed.
And still no help has come to our rescue.
The enemy have surrounded us.
Our forces...
have taken heavy casualties.
Thus, dying in droves.
Should this persist,
I fear that...
we shall certainly be defeated.
Why the hell are you talking like that?
That's so lame.
Are you from the middle ages?
Private Mak is injured.
Mak!
How bad is it, doc?
You'll be okay.
You just sprained your leg.
Sprained my leg?
You bastard!
From the sound of your groaning,
I thought you broke your spleen.
Am I going to make it back home
to Phra Khanong?
My wife, Nak, probably gave birth already.
Are we really going to die here?
Damn it!
Why are you all giving up?
Haven't you heard
about the Battle of Thermopylae?
King Leonidas.
Stelios.
They were all outnumbered
by thousands of enemies.
But in the end, didn't everybody die?
Really?
Sorry.
I haven't got to that part.
Take Rocky for example, then.
Rocky road?
That's yummy. Where is it?
Where is it?
Oh, gosh!
How about The Last Samurai?
During his final battle,
he fought so hard his blade shattered.
He didn't even think of giving up.
We still have our swords here.
We're not missing any limbs.
Asshole!
Forgive me.
Just all our swords, then.
Do we not have a fighting chance?
-Yes!
Kill them!
-Kill them!
Shit!
They've got guns. I forgot.
Are you okay, Mak?
Hey, Shin.
Since we are all going to die anyway,
can I ask you something?
What's with your hair?
When I was little,
there was a cholera outbreak.
I almost died.
So my mother swore to God if I survived,
I would keep this hairdo
for the rest of my life.
I would rather die than live
with that ugly topknot hairdo.
It looks like a dog's talus.
What about yours?
I'm a trendsetter!
Stop shooting already! Damn it!
Mak, do you have any last words?
No, I don't.
I will make it back to see my wife
and my baby no matter what.
I will not allow myself to die here.
Nor will all of you.
Pee Mak.
Why did you come out?
I told you to go inside. Hurry!
Pee Mak.
There are too many people playing.
I won't deal you in.
Come on, man.
No cash, no chance to play.
Let's deal.
Are you going to shuffle until dawn?
Why don't you go put on a card show?
Is your dad David Blaine?
Hurry up! Come on.
What the hell?
A double.
Shit. I got zero.
I got one! Pay up.
What's wrong?
My wound hurts.
I can't believe you survived.
You must be invincible.
I must thank all of you
for bringing me all the way here.
We are the ones who should be grateful.
Without you,
we would all be dead by now, Mak.
Actually, my name is pronounced
"Mark" with the R sound.
Merk?
It's fine. You can call me Mak.
The only person
who calls me Mark is my daddy.
But he went back
to the United States of America
with the missionaries.
Everyone in my village calls me Mak.
What the hell?
Hey, guys. We made it to Phra Khanong.
We're here?
Finally.
Where is everybody?
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Nak!
Nak, honey!
I'm back!
Nak!
Is Nak taking a dump?
Where were you?
I was really worried.
I thought I would never see you again.
Don't cry, baby.
You won't look handsome.
You know,
when I was at war,
I missed you so much.
I missed you a lot.
I missed you so, so very much.
I missed you more than anyone
in the whole world.
Man, Mak is whipped.
Baby, did you miss me at all?
No.
Why not?
You don't love me anymore?
You crazy man.
Of course I do.
You're joking with me?
Don't joke like that.
So cheesy.
Nak, what about our baby?
He's playing over there.
Let me see. Come to Daddy.
Wow, he is handsome just like his Daddy!
I named him after your favorite name.
Really, Nak?
Dang!
Dang, my boy.
What's so cool about the name Dang?
I know.
Even my servant has a cooler name.
Hey, you guys.
This is my wife, Nak.
Hello there.
Nak. These are my friends.
This is Aey,
Ter, Puek, and that's Shin.
So, what are you guys going to do now?
I guess tonight will be difficult
to find a boat out.
We'll stay here for a night.
Why just one night?
Why don't you all stay here
until the war is over?
The house across the canal is empty
ever since my aunt passed away.
There's a boat for you to use too.
Jeez.
Will his aunt come to haunt us?
Shin. She will definitely haunt you
until your hair falls out.
We'll stay here for just a night.
We don't want to be a bother.
Come on.
They are welcoming us
and you just turn them down?
You have no manners, Aey.
Right?
Mak's wife is so damn beautiful.
Easy, man. That's our friend's wife.
You know, I am a very bad soldier.
How come?
When I was at war,
I never thought of Siam.
I never thought about my country.
All I thought about was you.
This soldier should be executed
by a firing squad.
Yes.
You should be.
You know something?
I waited for you at the pier everyday.
I am here now.
I promise you.
I won't go anywhere again.
Hey.
Nak.
Our house has fireflies as well?
That's so beautiful.
That's a filth-eating spirit.
What?
Nak!
Why are you joking with me like that?
You know I am scared of ghosts.
What are you looking for?
I'll put my Buddha amulet back on.
The doctor took it off
when they bandaged me.
Goodness.
There's a lot of blood on it.
Just put it away for now.
Let me clean it for you first.
Okay.
My wife is the sweetest person in Siam.
And you smell great too.
At this temple
There are
Seven palm trees
The hill myna
Is out
But has not returned
Hey, guys. Look.
They aren't scared of people at all.
Cute, huh?
Yes. So cute.
-"Cute" my ass!
-Damn!
Why do you have to be
an animal lover this early?
Can't you see we're all sleeping here?
How can anybody sleep
with you chirping away?
This damn gluttonous bird too.
Go. Go eat somewhere else.
Go. Fly out of my house.
Hey! Wake up, you guys.
You're here early.
The market will close if we're late.
What's on the boat?
The bodies of soldiers
who died in the war.
The cemetery is full.
So we must return the bodies
to their families
to be buried at home.
Hey!
Keep rowing.
Jeez.
Snakehead.
Fresh fish. We have them in all sizes.
The market is very crowded today.
Hello.
Snacks.
-We got sticky cakes and cookies too.
-Miss Nim.
Miss Nim.
May I have two cookies
and two coconut milk custards?
-Mak.
-Yes?
We're all out!
-Hey!
-Hey.
Damn it.
We won't get to eat any.
Mr. Aum.
-Mak.
-I want to buy some fish for Nak.
Not for sale.
Today's a Buddhist holy day.
I am releasing them for merit.
Rejoice. Go on.
Get out of my way.
Hey!
Do you think he did that right?
What's gotten into him?
LIQUOR SHOP
Mrs. Priek.
Wake up. You have customers.
You don't remember me?
Do you have a job for me?
No.
You punk.
How many staff do you think
a small liquor shop need?
You think I need a salesperson,
a mixologist, a waitress,
a hostess,
a bartender, a dishwasher, and a busboy?
I got them all.
Drink up, dear.
She's even got an escort.
Very good.
You look familiar.
I am Mak.
I just got back from the war.
If I hadn't met Nak first,
I would've hit on you.
You're so damn pretty.
As pretty as your ghost!
You really don't know, Mak?
If you want to know the truth,
go bend down, look between the legs,
and you'll see that Nak and your kid are--
Mom.
-Be quiet.
-Ping.
You're drunk now. Go rest.
-I'm not drunk.
-Mom!
-Why did you stop me? I'm not drunk.
-Go. Get up.
I'm sorry. My mom talks nonsense
when she's drunk.
-Get inside.
-Nak!
Nak. Let her come. I'm not scared!
Nak! Let her come!
What's wrong with her?
Everyone is acting weird, don't you think?
Yes. What did Mrs. Priek mean, anyway?
Why do you have to look between the legs?
Yoga exercise?
My mom once told me,
if you look at someone between the legs,
you can tell if they're ghosts.
You mean...
Nak is a ghost?
That's crazy.
She's too hot to be a ghost.
Right.
If she can be that beautiful,
I would take her even if she's a ghost.
Why did Mrs. Priek talk to Mak like that?
Because she was wasted.
So she just blabbered on about things.
-Yeah.
Where the hell is Mak, anyway?
How come he isn't here drinking with us?
Aey, you idiot.
You're spilling all the booze.
You go and get Mak here.
Hurry up.
Why me?
Because you drank the least.
It's been over an hour
yet you can't even finish one glass.
That's right.
We are all drunk. So you go.
Right.
That was my bad.
-Hey, don't waste it.
-Hurry up.
Mak.
Nak, is Mak here?
Hey, Shin.
Nak.
Is Mak here?
He's sleeping.
I will wake him for you.
Please come in first.
Where is Dang?
Nak.
Are you okay?
You ran out of coconut husks?
What the hell is wrong with you, Shin?
Puek. Slap me, please?
That's hard.
You told me to.
Where the hell is Mak, anyway?
How come he isn't here drinking with us?
Aey, you idiot.
You're spilling all the booze.
Shit. Déjà vu.
What déjà vu?
You go and get Mak. Hurry up.
No. Why me?
What are you scared of?
If Nak is really a ghost,
then you just seduce her.
There's no such thing as ghosts.
You want to bet?
You won't get me this time.
The drums of war sound off
Like rolling thunder
As we set out to protect our homeland
Our thirst for battle is great
Even though there are no elephant rides
Dusk fills my emptiness with thoughts
Of love for my beautiful dearest
Roused to the point of release
I raise my white flag in sweet surrender
And polish my sword
What the fuck?
What's with you, Shin?
Where is Mak?
Nak is a ghost!
Nak is really a ghost!
What are you babbling about?
If you're drunk, go vomit somewhere else.
Seriously! I went up to Mak's house.
His house looks run-down and abandoned.
Hey.
Maybe Nak is feeling lazy.
But the crib was swinging by itself.
Hey.
The wind was pretty strong.
You are imagining things.
I'm not!
I saw Nak upstairs,
but she was able to reach to the ground
to grab a lime.
Hey.
Maybe one of her arms is longer
than the other?
Don't you know it's possible for our arms
not to have the same length?
Look at mine. See? Not the same.
Or maybe Nak was just using a long stick
to get the lime.
You're drunk
and your imagination got the best of you.
Yes.
Hey.
Did you memorize our marching song, Shin?
Let's dance. Ready?
The drums of war sound off
Like rolling thunder
As we set out to protect our homeland
Our thirst for battle is great
Even though there are no elephant rides
Dusk fills my emptiness with thoughts
Of love for my beautiful dearest
Mak.
Can't we sleep a bit longer?
Come on. Help me out.
I don't know what's going on
with the townsfolk.
Only you guys are willing to help.
Hey, Shin.
Aren't you done freaking out?
What's wrong, Ter? Get up and help us.
Get up and help us.
Right, Ter.
Go get an ax and help Puek.
Ask Nak where it is.
What the fuck?
I went up to Mak's house.
His house looks run-down and abandoned.
My mom once told me,
if you look at someone between the legs,
you can tell if they're ghosts.
Um, I...
I'm looking for an ax.
Do you know where it is?
Shin.
I did look between the legs,
but I didn't see anything.
So stop freaking out.
-Really?
-Yes.
How is that possible?
My god!
Shit.
Damn it!
I'm not even done yet.
Holy shit!
Shit. I saw a...
Ter. What happened to your face?
I saw a...
What?
There's a... behind the house.
What the hell is he talking about?
Thank you.
Oh, my god.
Nak is a...
What are you saying, Ter?
Are you talking dirty?
Nak
is
a...
What am I?
What is wrong with your face, Ter?
Did you get stung by bees, Ter?
My mom told me
to use limewater to heal bee stings.
Nak, can you make some?
I'll see what I can do.
Thank you.
Watch your step.
Nak is...
I saw her body behind the house.
She really is a...
Ter, stop being silly.
Right.
What are you saying?
I can't understand your nonsense talk.
NAK IS A GHOST
Guys, it's raining.
Come take cover inside.
Ter.
What happened to your face?
What paper is that?
Bee sting.
-Let me see.
-See what?
The paper.
What paper? There's no paper.
Ter.
Bee sting.
-I want to see the paper.
-It was a bee sting.
-Let me see it now.
-Hey.
-Ter.
He said "It's about to rain.
He has clothes drying outside,
so he'll go home now."
How did you make sense of that, Puek?
I don't know.
Let's go get the damn clothes already.
I can't take it anymore.
Gosh! I almost had a fling with a ghost.
What are you doing?
I'm packing my stuff to leave.
We can't stay here.
Are you sure, Ter?
Of course. I saw it with my own eyes.
The ruby ring is exactly like Nak's.
Is it a big ruby?
Jerk. That's not the point.
Then, how come when you looked
between the legs, you didn't see anything?
How would I know?
I looked between her legs and saw nothing
except her honey pot.
What?
I mean the honey pot in the kitchen.
-Oh, right.
-You idiot!
You're supposed to look
between your own legs!
Is that so?
Then, why didn't you say so?
What?
Do you think Mak got the message?
Of course.
He looked really shocked.
Look. He just went inside.
I know the truth now.
Why didn't you tell me?
Did you think I would be disgusted?
Who told you?
That's not important, Nak.
Didn't we promise each other
there would be no secret between us?
I didn't know how to tell you.
What if you couldn't take it?
I couldn't risk it.
How could I not take it?
I used to be like that too.
Hey. If he knows the truth,
how come he still looks so in love?
I know.
Shit. I know why.
It says Nak is "gross," not a ghost.
If she is gross,
then what's the big deal?
But if you're really gross,
that's disgusting.
You've never had an underarm zit?
I had one last year and it was--
Hey! What are you guys talking about?
Let's pack up and get out of here.
Let's go pack up now.
What are you lingering there for, Ter?
Hurry!
I can't abandon him.
What now?
Are we really going to leave Mak
with a ghost?
Can I not go?
No.
You're the one who saw Nak
with her long arm.
You have to tell Mak.
How can someone that beautiful be a ghost?
Anyone here?
Anybody home?
Hey, Ping.
Why are you crying?
Can anyone help me slaughter my cow?
I sympathize with you.
You must really love your cow.
But people can eat anything
when they're starving.
Don't worry about it.
-I once ate my own dog--
-It's not like that.
It's to feed people at the funeral.
Whose funeral is it?
My mom's.
Mrs. Priek is dead?
That day at the market,
she told Mak about Nak.
So, Nak got angry and killed her.
Her body had just surfaced this morning.
Shin and Ter.
Damn it.
Mak.
Hey.
What's up?
Mak.
I have something to tell you.
Do you know that your wife...
Your wife is--
Beautiful!
What?
Right. I wanted to say
that your wife is very good-looking.
She's like a pageant queen.
I just couldn't wait to tell you.
You guys are so sweet.
You didn't have to
make a big deal out of it.
Now, we have to tell you
about important stuff like this.
Next time, there's no need to rush.
My wife will still be pretty tomorrow.
-See you.
-Mak.
Why don't you invite your friends up here
to eat something first?
Make yourself at home, guys.
No need to be too formal.
Go ahead.
Everything is delicious.
Go on.
I saw your mouth watering. So, eat up.
We are full already.
-Really?
-Yes.
Yes. There was a buffet at the market.
That's too bad.
Nak will be sad.
She worked so hard in the kitchen.
-How about next time?
-Up to you, man.
I can eat by myself.
You guys are missing out.
We shouldn't have eaten so much.
On second thought,
it wouldn't hurt to have a bite.
Wow, this dish looks good.
I'll try some.
Go ahead.
Very nice. So delicious.
I told you.
You guys should try some.
-What?
-Try this.
-Try it.
-Puek, go on.
-Just try it.
-Eat up.
-Right. Just try it.
Where did you learn to cook, Nak?
Le Cordon Bleu?
Shin, why don't you eat anything?
Right, Shin. This one is yours.
Oh, that is Nak's signature dish.
Go for it, Shin.
Hey.
Big bite, man.
How was it?
Damn good!
My Nak is the best cook.
Hey! Does anyone want to hold Dang?
My Dang. My son.
Peekaboo! What's up, baby?
You want to play with Mr. Shin?
Right, Shin. You love kids, right?
Let's play with Mr. Shin.
Here you go, man.
Oh, dear.
Hey, Shin.
Dang really likes you.
"Kiss me, Mr. Shin."
He can't stop smiling.
Come here. Come to Daddy.
-Go back.
-"Go back" what?
Go back home!
What are you guys doing?
I know.
You guys...
feel like playing charades?
Like we did during the war, right?
Okay. I like that idea.
Nak, let's play charades.
-What charades?
-Let's do it.
Hurry up, Shin.
Just watch me.
Throw?
Javelin?
Athlete?
Throw?
Throw away?
Trout?
No?
What is it?
Kitchen.
Kitchen?
Oh, a cook?
A beautiful cook?
Damn. Then, what is it?
Nak's kitchen?
Mak's kitchen.
No.
Mak and Nak's kitchen?
No?
Will he ever guess it right
in this lifetime?
A pan?
A knife?
A spear?
-Correct!
-I told you so.
What spear?
Body?
Armpit?
Armpit hair?
-No.
-Sweaty armpit?
Smelly armpit?
No.
Bumpy armpits.
-Not that one.
-Not that either?
Gosh.
I wonder what Mak's IQ really is?
What is it? A bed?
A bed, right?
A bamboo bed?
-Correct!
-"A spear near the bed."
That's right!
-Yes!
-You're good, man.
Who the heck came up with this phrase?
Your dad must be Shakespeare.
That one was difficult.
-A bird?
-Flying?
A bat?
-A shirt?
-Correct!
-A shirt.
-We're almost there.
A dog?
A tongue?
Tonguefish?
Tonguefish wearing a shirt?
What the hell is that?
What is it, Ter?
-What?
-Damn.
-Nak?
-No.
Beautiful?
Sexy?
What is it?
A woman?
A wife?
I got it.
Dead.
Desert.
Correct!
It's so easy, Ter.
This is a shirt and that's a dead girl.
Dead shirt, pronounced as "desert."
No, that can't be right.
Shin's answer is wrong, right?
Yes. Shin is wrong.
How can it be wrong?
This is a shirt and she is dead.
So it's dead shirt, or desert.
"Yay" my ass.
What is going on?
So what is the answer?
Let me see the paper.
What are you doing, Ter?
I'm hungry again.
I just realized
I left the rice in the pot at home.
I better go check.
Yes. I meant to remind you.
Let's go before it burns. Quick. Let's go.
-What about the shirt?
-Forget about it.
Won't you tell us the answer first?
-What the hell?
-Hurry up, Shin!
-I already gave the right answer.
-"Right" my ass. That was close.
Hold on.
Shin, hurry up!
Shin, come on!
Wait up!
Holy shit!
Shin, hurry up!
Hey, wait up.
-Ter! Hurry!
-Ter!
She's right behind you!
-Come on, Ter. Hurry!
-Come on, Ter.
Untie the boat. Let's go!
Paddle hard.
Why the hell are we turning?
Shit! We're circling back around.
Go that way!
Why are you turning again?
Where are you guys going in such a hurry?
Don't you want to finish the game?
I didn't get a chance to play yet.
What phrase would you act out?
MYOB.
Puek, what does it mean?
It means "mind your own business."
Did you have to ask?
Just go!
Damn, I think Nak is on to us now.
She won't let us live for sure.
What's that?
You go check.
Get out of my aunt's house right now!
What's wrong with you, Mak?
You guys are no different
than the townsfolk
who think that my wife is a ghost.
You have to listen to us, man.
Your wife is really dead.
Everybody knows it.
My wife is not dead.
Ping lied to all the villagers.
They said when I was at war,
Ping tried to seduce Nak.
When I didn't show any interest,
he bad-mouthed me
by telling all kinds of lies.
Everyone believed him.
And now everybody hates me.
I get the picture, man.
You didn't have to change your voice.
So, that's it.
Ping fooled all of you too.
No, you're the one who is being fooled.
Watch your mouth!
Stop being an idiot!
Just listen to us.
We're trying to tell you the truth
because you are our friend.
I don't need friends like you!
Mak!
I think...
we need to take drastic measures.
I kicked all of them out.
What did your friends say?
I don't care what they said.
They cannot talk about you like that.
If you are really a ghost,
I should be able to go through you, right?
Let me try.
Hey!
Hey, I can go through you.
This is so cool.
This is super cool.
-Hey!
-Enough.
What did you do?
Look at you. You're all dirty.
So what else have you cooked for me?
Your cooking is as good as always.
Nak, my love, is so pretty.
How can you be a ghost, right?
Wait up!
A ghost.
Why don't you try to scare me?
Stick your tongue out.
Scare me.
You are no fun. Boo.
Damn fatso.
I'm going to smack you in the head.
Are you going to wear this mask all night?
Why not?
It's kind of funny.
Okay.
I begin to get sad
Looking far across the sky
It's nearly dawn, the light is faint
I know our time is coming to an end
My heart is breaking
But what else am I going to do?
I want to cry
And beg time to go by slowly
I need more time
Let's look at each other more
I want to stop the time
Before we say goodbye forever
Won't Dang cry if he wakes up
and doesn't see anyone there?
Don't worry.
Dang never wakes up
in the middle of the night.
Look, honey.
Ten cents per ball.
If you can knock them all down,
you win a doll.
Baby, watch this.
I'm just warming up.
This next one will hit for sure.
Almost.
This is the one.
Go.
Hit it.
Baby, look at the fireworks.
See that, Nak?
I told you I have good aim.
I'll go get you a doll.
Told you. I've had good aim
since I was a kid.
The line is so long.
I think we'll have to skip this ride.
Let's go get on other rides.
Hey.
-Is that her?
-Look.
The line is gone now.
You're right.
Nak.
Do you love me?
What kind of question is that?
What's wrong with that?
You don't love me anymore?
Of course I do.
Do you love me a lot?
Lots and lots.
You love me lots and lots like jelly tots?
Hey, baby. Look.
There's a haunted house too.
Let's go in there after this.
Aren't you scared of ghosts?
Who, me?
Where?
Come on out. Ghosts?
I'm not scared of them.
Baby.
If one day I die,
can you live without me?
Why are you asking me this?
Just tell me. I want to know.
No.
If anyone is going to die,
then let that person be me.
If I don't have you, I can't go on living.
But if I die first,
you'd be able to find a new husband easily
with that big butt of yours.
HAUNTED HOUSE
-Please keep the doll for me.
-Okay.
Let's go, baby.
What kind of a goddamn ghost goes
to a haunted house?
Who will be scaring who?
I brought some powerful magic.
What is it?
I got this holy rice from a monk.
-It's very sacred.
-That's good.
By the way, where is Aey?
Where is he?
Hey.
Where have you been, Aey?
Well, I had diarrhea.
You were gone for a long time.
Don't be scared, baby.
Come play with me.
I think I screamed too loud,
so I scared him away.
Sorry, Mak. This is for your own good.
-Come play with me.
-Shin, you keep watch.
-Hurry up, Ter.
-Puek, hold his legs.
It's stuck.
Shit.
She's on to us.
What are we going to do?
The door is stuck.
Shit.
It's too late. She is coming.
What now?
I have no idea.
Hey.
Why are you jumping?
That other boy was so damn energetic.
Come play with me.
Actually, you don't have to play.
Up to you.
You think Nak was really fooled by this?
What's with all these decorations?
What the hell is this?
Hey!
You guys aren't customers!
Or did you get off work already?
Why doesn't anybody tell me?
Damn it! Letting me hang
upside down that long
might give me a stroke and kill me.
Let's go home, then.
Come on.
You there. It's time to go home.
The one who dressed up as Nak's ghost.
What a trendy costume.
Are you new here?
Let's go home.
Ter. Where is the holy rice?
The rice. Hurry!
-Take it out.
-Come on.
Hey!
What the hell are you screaming for?
It's just a fake hand.
You freaked me out with your screaming.
Take a look.
-Hey. Untie him.
-Come on.
What is going on with you?
Nak is really a ghost.
What ghost? It's all in your heads.
Just like this hand.
Mak, come here.
What is it now?
Shit. You scared me.
Holy shit.
A lizard.
I thought you saw
her!
There are otters around here?
You guys still won't let go
of this nonsense?
We are telling you the truth.
If you don't believe us,
try looking at Nak between your legs.
I did, and I saw nothing.
Maybe you didn't do it right.
You have to look down
between your own legs,
not between Nak's legs.
Of course.
Who would be that stupid?
My wife is not dead yet.
Hey, Mak. Wait up.
Where are you going?
How could he look between the legs
and not see anything?
Mak!
Mak! Where are you?
Is this Mak's blood?
Shit.
Help.
Mak, is that you?
Are you okay?
Help me.
I'm hurt.
Help me, please.
Hey, Mak.
Help.
Help me.
Mak.
What's wrong?
My wound hurts.
Where?
Gosh. You're bleeding out.
You've had this wound for so long.
How come it's not healed yet?
Do you have something to pressure it?
Shin.
Something isn't right here.
You're right.
Isn't it way past the rainy season?
You idiot. Not about that.
I meant how Mak looked down
between his legs saw nothing.
So it means...
Nak is still alive?
But the body I saw in the backyard...
has the exact same ring as Nak's.
Shit. I remember now.
The ring that I saw is on the ring finger
on the left hand.
So what?
It's a wedding ring.
So that means...
Mak should be wearing one too.
Softly.
Ter, what are you doing?
What the hell are you doing, Ter?
You're hurting him!
Ter! Mak's wound is still raw.
Shit, Mak! You scared me.
I thought you had your ring on.
My wedding ring?
My hand hurts,
so I wear it around my neck instead.
These are the bodies of soldiers
who died in the war.
The cemetery is full now.
So we have to return the bodies
to their family to be buried at home.
You've had this wound for so long.
How come it's not healed yet?
I will make it back to see my wife
and my baby no matter what.
It's him!
-What's wrong?
-Run!
Ter, what the hell?
What's the matter with you?
Wait for me!
Hurry up!
Shit. That was Mak's body in the backyard?
We've been living with a ghost
all this time?
So Nak was really slandered, then.
What about when I saw Nak's arm stretch
to the ground to grab a lime?
Or...
Maybe Nak was just using a long stick
to get the lime.
It must've been that spear.
Damn it.
Are you sure
that Nak is alive?
We must take her with us, then.
Why do you even bother about that?
Come on.
How can we leave her like that?
She's all alone and so vulnerable.
I don't care. No matter what...
Nak and I will run away together.
What?
I mean run away with us.
You womanizer!
I want no part in this.
Hey.
Puek does have a point, though.
You too, Ter?
If one day
Nak is haunted to death...
We are all partly to blame
for not doing anything to help her.
The living can't stay with the dead.
Hurry.
Nak!
Nak.
It's been a while. How are you?
I'm so sick of those villagers.
Idiots.
How could they believe Ping's lie?
I tried to talk to them
but they wouldn't listen.
Just now, I busted more than a few lips
on your behalf.
Please accept our apology.
Now, we have no doubt
that you're really alive.
That's okay.
Shin. What are you scared of now?
Come here.
Try and touch her. Trust me.
Come on.
You can touch her. See?
What kind of ghost has such smooth skin?
Why does she eat dried leaves
for food, then?
Damn you.
She's health-conscious.
How do you think
she keeps her nice figure?
Everyone eats organic food now.
That's why you look like a model, right?
But there were worms too.
You idiot.
Organic means no insecticide
so there are worms.
That's how you know it's safe to eat.
Have you ever studied
health education in school?
Where is Pee Mak?
Well, the war front has made its way here.
It's very dangerous.
Mak told us to take you with us first.
That's right.
Why didn't Pee Mak come with you?
The path is very rough.
So he's preparing provisions for us
at the waterfront.
That's right.
Let me get Dang for you.
Let's get in the boat.
-Come on, Nak.
-Hurry up, Shin.
Not too far now.
Mak should be around here.
Puek, the boat is sinking.
Holy shit.
-It's carrying too much weight.
-What?
What should we do?
Just toss things we don't need out.
Okay. Throw it out, Shin!
-Sit still.
-Shit!
What now?
The water is getting inside the boat.
What else can we toss out?
Uh, is Dang necessary?
I guess he is.
-The paddles. Give me the paddles.
-What?
-Hand me the paddles now.
-Here.
How's that?
The boat isn't sinking anymore!
It's good that the boat stopped sinking.
But how are we going to paddle now,
you moron?
Why did you toss them out?
They are so far now.
Should we swim to the shore?
I can't swim.
Shit. It's Mak.
Pee Mak!
Where are you going?
Mak, leave us alone.
You're dead. Just let us go.
What are you talking about?
Mak died during the war
but he doesn't know yet.
Right. Forget about him, Nak.
You can find a new boyfriend now.
Am I not right?
What the hell is wrong with you all?
-Where are you taking my wife?
-Pee Mak.
Let's go.
-Hurry. There he comes!
-Mak.
-Shit.
-Come on.
Pee Mak!
Pee Mak.
-Where did he go?
-I don't know.
Help. Help me.
Pee Mak!
Hey. Can ghosts drown?
Don't let him fool you.
Pee Mak!
Help me! I have a muscle cramp.
-Pee Mak!
-He has cramps.
-Help me.
-Ghosts can have cramps?
Please help him.
He must have taken an acting lesson.
-Help me!
-His acting coach must be Ang Lee, then.
He's not dead. Help him!
Give me your hand, Mak!
-Come here.
-Mak.
Pee Mak.
-Calm down.
-Are you all right?
What the hell?
Why did you run away from me?
We thought you were a ghost.
Why did you scream
when we threw the holy rice at you?
You threw the rice right at my wound!
If it were you, you would scream too.
Shit! We got the same problem again.
The boat is sinking
because of too much weight!
Dang is still necessary, right?
Sure, he is.
Let's paddle to the shore.
Come on. Faster.
Come on.
Paddle. The boat is taking on water.
Hurry up!
Wait.
Wait for what?
The boat is sinking.
At first, I thought Nak was a ghost
and Mak was human.
Then, it turns out Nak is human
and Mak is a ghost.
And now Mak isn't a ghost after all.
He's just human.
So who is a ghost and who is human?
Ter, what the hell are you rambling about?
Right.
You lost me since your first sentence.
Plus, their names are so damn similar,
Mak and Nak.
That's right.
If Nak is still alive,
and Mak is still alive,
then, whose body is it in the backyard?
Aey.
Why do you have that ring?
Aey is a ghost!
How come every time we realize something,
there are always flashes of lightning?
Damn it, who cares?
Ter, kick him overboard!
Come on. Let's go!
-The boat is taking on water.
-Let's go.
-Hurry!
-Keep rowing.
Aey, I am sorry.
It wasn't me who kicked you. It was Ter.
Shake him off!
Come on!
Hurry!
Paddle harder. We're not moving.
-Faster!
Damn it!
Paddling with our hands
to escape is no use.
Here you go.
-Thanks.
-Give it to me. I will paddle.
Give me the paddle. I will do it.
Give it your best shot, Ter. Row.
Why don't you keep rowing, Ter?
Ter, why did you stop?
-Ter, keep rowing.
-Hurry.
Aey will catch up with us.
What's with you, Ter?
Don't stand up, man.
The boat will flip over.
What the hell?
Why are you standing, Ter?
Mak, move.
What's with you?
Shin, move.
-Me too?
-Yes. Move aside.
-Which way?
-To your right.
Fine.
-Only Puak?
-Shin, you move to the left.
Left? My left or your left?
Just pick one!
-Which side?
-It doesn't matter.
Whose left side?
The left hand that you use
to wipe your ass!
-Which way?
-My wound hurts.
Why did you move back, Mak?
-Move!
-Move where?
-To the right.
-Okay.
Shin, bend to the left. Left.
-Which way?
-Whichever way you want.
-Which side?
-What is this?
You idiots! Bend down!
Bend your head down to your feet.
Hurry. Bend lower.
I'm sore now.
Damn it!
The drums of war sound off
Like rolling thunder
As we set out to protect our homeland
Why are you singing now?
I know.
And why am I dancing along?
Roused to the point of release
I raise my white flag in sweet surrender
And polish my sword
Nak is a ghost!
Let's go!
Mak, jump! Hurry!
Mak!
Me too!
Mak! Come on. Let's go.
Let's go.
Ter, hurry.
Give me your hand, Ter. Come on!
-Hurry, Mak.
-Come here.
Mak!
Shin, jump now!
Hurry! Jump!
Shin!
Just jump, Shin!
Jump!
I told you, I can't swim.
Just jump now!
-Jump now, Shin!
-Hurry!
-Help me.
-Come on.
Didn't you say you can't swim?
You swam like Michael Phelps.
Nak!
Mak, let's get out of here.
I am not going!
Are you crazy? I'm sorry, man.
What the hell? That hurts!
How come you didn't pass out?
I see it always works in movies.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Puek!
-Is he dead?
-I don't know.
Just drag him away. Run. Hurry!
-Run!
-Hurry up!
Let's go.
What should we do now, father?
Remember, no matter what happens,
do not step outside the enchanted thread.
We don't receive a lot of donation lately.
We've been waiting for months
to get it fixed.
Father!
I almost shit my pants.
I just did.
Father, what's next?
Don't worry. I will handle this.
Nak!
Mak, don't!
Listen to me, baby.
Don't listen to her.
God, you're a ghost!
Stop with the sweet talk already!
Get rid of her, father!
Ter.
Hand me the holy water.
Don't hurt my wife!
Don't. Don't hurt my wife! Let me go!
Nak!
-Get her, father.
-Pee Mak.
Please help me.
-Mak, don't!
-Nak!
Nak!
Let me go!
Damn it, Ter!
-You spilled it all.
-It's okay.
Shin, hand me the holy rice.
Let me go!
Nak!
-Shin.
-Nak.
Guys, look. They're so tame.
They're eating out of my palm.
How about you have a taste of my feet?
This isn't the time
to go all animal-lover on us!
That's okay.
As long as we stay inside the holy thread,
we will be--
Father!
-What the hell?
-Whose hand is it?
Shit! Tell me which way to go.
Is that you, Shin?
What is this?
It's time for me to go.
The monk already made it over the wall.
Turn the other way.
I'm getting the creeps.
-Hurry.
-Nak!
-Pee Mak.
-Nak.
Pee Mak.
Jeez! Enough already!
This isn't some name-calling game.
Let's go that way.
-Aey!
Please let us go, Aey.
At least we used to be friends.
I didn't do anything to you, you know.
Ter! Why did you kick him off the boat?
I told you not to.
I'm not a ghost.
I don't believe you.
Don't come any closer.
Don't push me!
Nak!
What should we do now, Ter?
Puek, you are still wet, right?
Of course. Why?
Shin. Mak.
I will count to three,
then you push Puek towards Aey.
-One.
-Can we talk about this first?
-Two.
-Shit.
-Three!
-I hate you all!
-Everyone, jump on him.
-What's that for?
See? You said you were human,
but you screamed
once the holy water touched you.
I screamed because you guys are on top
of me and it hurts!
Disgusting!
Come on! Get up!
Get up!
Fuck!
How come the holy water didn't hurt you
like it did Nak?
I told you I am not a ghost.
How come you got the ring?
Well...
I needed some money.
I saw it with my own eyes.
The ruby ring is exactly like Nak's.
Is it a big ruby?
Where is he?
Where have you been, Aey?
Well, I had diarrhea.
I'm sorry.
I needed the money to gamble.
I was mistaken. I'm sorry, man.
I thought you were a ghost for so long,
when in truth
you're just a casino junkie.
You too.
You watch too many movies
and always make assumptions.
Are you guys forgetting something?
What?
That Nak is still standing here.
Nak!
Mak, let's go. Run!
Let's go.
The door can't be opened.
It's stuck.
This one is stuck too.
Jeez, Nak.
Please just let us go.
You are a ghost,
so stay in your own world.
You cannot be with the living.
It's unnatural. It's sacrilegious.
It won't work out. It's not okay.
Don't you understand?
Don't mess with me!
What's happening?
Nak disappeared.
This one is stuck too.
What are we going to do?
If I make it out alive,
I will donate a lot of money
to get this damn roof fixed.
Puek.
That isn't the roof leaking.
Mak, run!
Nak.
Please don't hurt us. We're scared.
I'm already scared as hell
when you come in your normal form.
Now you're hanging upside down
like Spiderman.
Why do you keep getting
between Pee Mak and I?
What have I ever done to you?
Because you are a mean ghost.
Why did you kill Mrs. Priek?
I didn't kill her.
She was drunk, fell in the water,
and drowned by herself.
I don't believe you!
You're beautiful,
but you're a big fat liar!
I told you, I didn't kill her!
Let's go.
I just want to be with the person I love.
Why do you guys have to get in the way?
This isn't love.
This is selfishness.
Right. Mak can't go anywhere anymore.
The townsfolk are all scared of him.
I am scared too.
Why don't you go
where you're supposed to go?
Yeah. Mak's aunt died
and she didn't come back.
Neither did Mrs. Priek.
They have probably been reincarnated
and got new husbands by now.
You're already dead.
How can you be with Mak?
If I can't be with Pee Mak in this world,
then Pee Mak must go with me.
What the hell are you standing
there for, Mak?
Mak!
-Let's go.
-Mak!
Are you that scared of me?
I am so sorry.
If I ever hurt you,
I wouldn't be able to live with myself.
Don't cry, baby.
You won't look handsome.
I am so sorry...
for lying to you all this time.
I just wanted to be with you
as long as I could,
even if it's just for one more day.
Do you still remember
what we talked about on the Ferris wheel?
I am sorry...
that you don't get to die before me.
Please promise me.
When I am gone,
you will have to carry on.
Nak.
You don't have to go anywhere.
You said you lied to me.
You didn't lie to me at all.
Even though I am a fool,
I'm not stupid enough
to not know that my wife is dead.
I will go see your friends off.
Nak!
What did you do?
Look at you. You're all dirty.
So what else have you cooked for me?
Your cooking is as good as always.
Nak, my love, is so pretty.
How can you be a ghost,
right?
I knew it
since when we were playing charades.
Even if all the townsfolk avoid me
and nobody wants to be my friend,
and even if I have to eat
dried leaves everyday,
I would still want to be with you.
Thank you.
But it is impossible.
Why not?
We can just pretend
that nothing has changed.
All this time, we did fine together,
didn't we?
But I'm dead.
The living and the dead...
can't stay together.
It's unnatural.
If that's so,
then love is also an unnatural thing.
When I was at war...
Mak, do you have any last words?
I should have died that day.
No one thought I would make it.
But I found my way back to you.
Help.
Pee Mak.
Even though you're already dead,
you are still able to come back for me.
You also used your powers
to help me hit those cans
and won a doll for Dang.
Is it wrong
that we love each other this much?
Aren't you scared of me?
You know I am terrified of ghosts.
But I am more terrified
of living without you.
Just one thing though.
Don't ever hang upside down...
like that again.
I almost had a heart attack.
Damn.
I am really moved.
I promise you.
No matter what happens,
we will be friends forever.
That's right.
If you all die and become ghosts,
I won't be afraid.
But I remember you kicked me off the boat.
Come on.
Love you.
Nak.
Do you love me?
I do.
How much?
I love Pee Mak lots and lots.
I love you
heaps and heaps too.
Nak.
Let's look at each other more
I want to stop the time
Before we say goodbye forever
Baby, I love you.
Give me your hand to hold
And to keep my heart warm
Let me look in your eyes
So I will never be lonely
Let me have your love to inspire me
To make my dreams come true
The roof isn't leaking anymore, father.
Let us know
if there is anything else we can do.
Keep up the good work, baby!
Watch your hand.
What?
Horn?
Hair?
You? She?
-Does she mean head?
-Oh, really?
-There is head in the phrase.
-Watermelon head?
-Exploding head?
-Potato head?
What kind of head?
Airhead?
Headless?
Headless. Pee Mak is correct!
This is the first time I got it right!
Shin!
Hey!
Hey, aren't you happy for me?
HAUNTED HOUSE
SCARIER THAN EVER
Come play with me.
Wow, that was so realistic.
I know.
Thank you.
Come on. Hurry up.
Watch this. I'll show you.
You'll never hit the target.
You throw like a blind man.
This time don't help me, okay?
Everybody.
WE DON'T WANT NAK THE GHOST
Mak has really gone too far.
-Yes!
We can't let this unnatural behavior
go on in our village.
-That's right!
-We can't allow it!
-No way!
Tonight, we will get rid of it.
Does anyone want to come with me?
-Yes!
I want to go too.
GET OUT
GHOST SHOULDN'T LIVE WITH HUMANS
Shit.
Better hurry before you miss out.
Go on. Hurry up.