Aod.
What's wrong?
Nightmare?
No.
What is it? Why don't you tell me?
-It's nothing.
-Aod.
Whoever takes what is mine
must die!
TOH MIN-JUN
Give me your hands.
It's already washed.
Is it true that your argument with friends
was the reason for the band's break-up?
I wouldn't ask that kind of question.
What is your channel?
Sky News.
Sky News?
-Sky News! Okay, go ahead.
-Sky News!
Very good. Great start.
Wait a second.
The company will announce this later.
Toh Min-Jun is very tired.
We really have to go.
-Come on, stay a little longer.
-No, he's very tired.
-He's very tired. She told you.
-We should leave now.
Please move.
Move. Make way.
Make way please, or I will spray at you.
-Don't push.
-I really will.
-No. Hold up.
-Please calm down. We'll announce later.
Go…
Where are you, Yot? Where is the van?
Hurry up.
An accident?
How are we going to get back?
Hurry up. Go.
No. Please. Stop!
Calm down!
Take it easy, keep your distance.
Please stop.
Hey! Why are you standing on the road?
You wanna die, you assholes? Huh?
What a chance!
Wait for me! Wait! Toh Min-Jun.
What the hell?
Just once, please take a picture.
Oh, please.
Stop.
Got you! I studied Korean, you see.
Awesome, First. Go get him.
Why? Just one selfie.
That is Toh Min-Jun.
I'm a Youtuber called Pampam.
I don't know.
Where are you going?
-You need a ride?
-Let's go!
Yes. Let's go!
Get in the van. Guard him.
Guard him…
Guard him!
Hurry up!
It was chaotic at the mall.
You won't pass the probation like this.
So many fans, Shon.
This place is worn-out.
-We tried our best.
-Are we staying here?
Here?
Wow!
Greetings, Luang Loong.
Be well.
We're here to visit Phra Nong
and attend Aod's ordination.
But…
we can't reach Phra Nong.
Phra Nong has gone to India
for about a month.
I'm taking care of everything now.
Didn't he tell you?
Yes, he did.
We were just on tours
and had just returned to Thailand.
Hey, Fahlan.
Where are Aod and Novice Nott?
They would have been
standing here making noise.
If it weren't from Phra Nong,
we wouldn't have known
that he would be ordained.
Well…
we have to hold off the ordination.
The thing is…
Aod is not well.
Will you watch your step?
Are you supposed to be a mom or a dad?
A mommy, of course.
We all have boobs and VJJs.
With a VJJ, you can't call us dads.
And that handsome man
behind you, is that your husband?
Don't say that in the temple.
No, Novice.
-I'm the bottom.
-Hey!
Stop joking.
Actually, the three of us
were ordained here.
You sure are ugly when you lie.
Hey, Novice.
You better grow up soon
and leave the monastery.
-So then, you can be my man.
-Let me see if you're ready.
Is your junk ready?
-Let me see.
-Let me.
Just a little.
Let me see.
Help! Novice Nott!
Nott…
-Come here.
-Hey!
What are you doing?
You grow fast, big thingy.
You said you'd die.
And here you are, Aod.
Hello.
Every time I meet you,
you always have a new nose.
My new series.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Did a shaman do it?
It doesn't go with your face.
Piss off.
And First,
how long do you have left to live?
You have the same old foul mouth.
I don't think you're ill at all.
But you're all still the same.
Cute as always.
Aww, aren't you sweet?
How have you been doing, Mr. Toh?
I'm fine.
Let me introduce you to someone here.
This is Shon, my manager…
and the boss of both First and Balloon.
I'm Min-Jun's friend.
We're friends.
-That's enough.
-We're friends.
That's enough. Keep your mouth shut.
Shut it.
Nott, these aunties were harassing me.
Who do you say were harassing you?
That would be enough.
Apologize to them.
Why should I?
Novice.
You should apologize when you did wrong.
Apologize to them.
-Come on.
-I'm sorry.
This is Novice Namnua.
His parents got divorced
and his dad moved to the city to work.
He was left to be ordained here.
I assigned him to take care of Aod.
How about the other novices?
They left the monastery
to continue their education.
Novice Nott just got accepted
at the Buddhist University in Bangkok.
Wait…
This is an ill person?
How? You don't seem ill at all.
What a crybaby.
Now he is really ill.
Yes, Aod is ill.
Aod is ill.
-This is serious, Aod.
-I think it's serious.
This is serious.
You have a serious issue. Damn. Go.
Ever since I found this anklet,
I've had bad dreams.
And these scales
started growing on my chest
until last month.
It's painful.
It feels hot and it burns
so I always have a fever and feel ill.
No!
Don't touch it.
I'm just curious.
Will it disappear
if you just throw the anklet away?
Or leave it where you found it.
Bury it, so this would end.
Why would Aod keep it if it was that easy?
You chatterbox.
Ouch! Luang Loong.
Aod found an anklet
and was cursed like Nak in the dream.
-Luang Loong.
-Yes?
What do you know about the anklet?
Giving anklets to Nak before ordination
has been the temple's tradition
since its establishment
which has been passed on
for hundreds of years.
Everyone, look closely.
What does it say?
I can't read it.
Looks like an ancient text.
-Pampam.
-Yes?
Can you blow up the image
and show it to Luang Loong?
Let me see.
You are the oldest here.
Can you read it?
I'm not that old to know this script.
I can't read it.
All right.
You stay together tonight.
I'm going.
Please, sir.
Please, Luang Loong.
And he says he's not that old.
ANCIENT PAMPHLET
"This ring which Nak takes off when…”
What's next?
The script on the back had already faded.
It can't be read.
I think the rest of the script
might give us a hint.
Novice.
Can you try to rub it?
You might see the rest at the back.
Can you?
There's nothing.
If we can't see it on this one,
let's look at the other one.
There's only one.
I agree with Novice Namnua.
If it's Nak's anklet,
it must be a pair.
The script might be perfect
on the other one.
Why is there only one then?
Aod, why is there only one?
It's just that.
I went back to dig many times
but didn't find anything.
Kiddee called me yesterday.
He said one of his relatives
went to ordination
at a temple by the Mekong.
At that temple,
their Nak also wears anklets
like we do here.
Aod and I decided to visit Kiddee in Ubon
and meet with his relative.
Let me go with you.
No, you can't.
And it's too risky.
What if someone takes
some footage of you again?
I have a van. I can take you there.
You are the worst and the weirdest.
You'd like to record
and post Min-Jun's clip on Youtube.
We have rules,
and you should respect them.
You can't keep filming everything.
It sounds strange
when you talk about rules.
We're professionals now.
Very well.
Song Hee.
I beg you.
Just a few days.
I'm really worried about them.
I'm sure you can handle it.
The sooner we go,
the sooner we can get back, right?
Please.
Okay.
But as a professional manager…
Take good care of Min-Jun.
If anyone attempts to record a video,
use extreme measures.
-Yes, madam.
Stop that.
I wish this merit reaches
all the spirits in the world.
I wish them to rest in peace.
I wish this merit reaches
all the animals in the world.
I wish all demons in the world
to rest in peace.
I wish the merit from this prayer
reaches all the spirits
that I have offended
from the past to the present
no matter where you are.
Please receive this merit,
forgive me for my sins,
and bless me with
the power of this good deed.
-Aod.
-Aod!
-What's wrong?
-What's happening?
Let's get him to bed.
Easy, Aod.
Does it hurt?
Be careful with his wounds.
Aod.
-Careful.
-Slowly.
I undertake the training-precept to
abstain from taking what is not given.
Are you all right, Aod?
-Let's get you to bed.
-Take it easy.
-Aod.
What?
A ghost!
Ghost!
Aren't you a novice? Perform an exorcism.
I can't.
I never succeed.
Who has stolen what's mine?
I'll kill you!
Shon, you bitch!
The anklet.
His ankle looks like mine.
-What the hell? I can't take this.
-I undertake…
-the training-precept
-Let's go…
to abstain
from taking what is not given.
Shit! Which way should we go?
Go this way!
Let him stand there like an idiot.
You come all the way from Korea,
and you're still stupid.
What the hell?
What should we do?
The door!
-Aod.
-Are you okay?
Luang Pee!
-Novice!
Novice!
Balloon.
Novice.
Are you okay?
You want the anklet so bad, huh?
Come and take it!
Aod.
They have nothing to do with this.
Aod, what are you saying?
Aod.
You want this?
Aod, what are you saying?
Why would you risk yourself for him?
You're not a part of this.
I took the anklet. It's my responsibility.
You let them go
and you come take it from me.
The four of you…
You have stolen
what's precious to me.
I'll kill you!
Namnua.
Novice, what are you doing?
Novice, why did you get in?
Your heart is full of grudge.
Don't come closer.
Novice, come back.
It's pulling me.
First.
Everyone, it's open.
What are you waiting for? Go!
Novice, let's get out.
-Let's go.
-Let's go, Aod.
Aod, go.
Pampam, go.
I can't feel my legs.
Pampam, hurry up.
My anklet!
Novice.
Wake up, Novice.
Wake up.
Go and wake up everyone.
Wake up. It's morning.
-First.
-Balloon.
No.
Balloon.
Shit!
In the chapel, really?
Well.
You were all over me last night, First.
Are you sure?
It's my period.
Let me ask you, Aod.
Is this Nak ghost
haunting you every night?
I can't do this every night.
No, it's the first time
since Aod found that gold anklet.
This is the first time I saw him.
It's the same ghost I saw in my dream.
And he mentioned all four of us.
Four of us?
Which four?
Is it me?
"Is it me?"
You're just a kitten.
Or is it me?
But I'm Korean.
You never know.
Where are you going?
I'm not involved in this.
It's my first time visiting this place.
"First time visiting this place."
That's what we thought.
And then?
Let me tell you this.
We are all here
because we might have met before
in the past.
We might have done something together.
I'm talking from experience.
Oh, there you are.
Luang Loong and I
looked for you guys everywhere.
-Luang Loong.
Why do you look worn out?
A ghost, Luang Loong.
There is a new ghost.
And a dead Korean…
Does this have anything to do with this?
Are you still awake?
Bitch!
Yes, perfectly.
Still alive.
And the dead Korean you mentioned…
Who is it?
It's all done.
-Thank you.
Is it Shon's body?
Can you call the office
and the police as well
to inform them about the body?
If news of this gets out,
it will be a big mess.
Hurry up, so we can go with Aod.
You still want to go with Aod?
That ghost just killed Shon.
That's right.
That ghost is evil.
He'd kill just about anybody.
I'm scared, Mr. Toh.
This is the reason
why I think it's best that
we stick together.
That way, we can help each other.
Give me that, Aod.
Here, one more.
I really think it's dangerous.
If Nak is looking for the anklet,
I should just go with Novice Nott.
It's dangerous everywhere.
Everybody might have something
connected to Nak.
We'll go together to support each other.
All right, everybody?
Yes.
When you said everybody,
can you leave me out of that?
You're in such a hurry to be excluded.
You were the first one who wanted to come
and now you want to leave.
You better be careful going alone,
or the ghost might just break your neck.
We still don't know
what he meant by "the four of us,"
like which among us are among those four.
Just come along so you can be safe.
Come down and film your stupid Oppa video.
Come on.
Let's go.
Please get off, Novice.
Novice!
I know!
Move.
Novice.
Get off.
No, I'm coming along.
Novice.
-Get off.
-Why not, Aod?
It'll be just a few days.
That's right.
It's dangerous and you know it.
Come on, Novice.
Wait.
Only you get off.
The Buddha statue stays there.
Novice.
They are taking my photos.
Yeah. Good morning.
I knew it.
-Pampam.
-Yes?
You posted about Mr. Toh
on social media, didn't you?
That's why everyone is staring at us.
Are you crazy? I've been driving all day.
Hold on.
I don't think they're Min-Jun's fans.
Is it me?
You and me?
They're pointing at something on the roof.
On the roof?
-Shit!
-Gosh!
-What?
-Are you possessed again?
-It's a leg.
-What?
Where?
-It's Novice.
-Careful.
-Novice.
Novice.
-Oh, my god.
-Novice.
How did you get here?
-Novice. Get up.
-Careful. Are you hurt?
-Novice.
-Get up.
My van. Wait.
Get down from there, Novice.
Get down from there, please.
Please get down from there.
I'm sorry.
Let me hang on to this, all right?
-Novice.
-Novice, get down here.
-Novice!
-Get him.
Go get him.
-It's crowded here. Get down here.
-Novice!
-No!
-Get down here.
-Get him.
-Get down now.
-No!
-It's crowded. Get down.
-Get down!
-No!
-No to you too!
-Novice, get down here.
Go away!
-Pampam. Hurry.
-Everybody.
Pampam, people are crowding around us.
Let's just take Namnua with us.
We can take him off our hands
once we get to Kiddee's house.
-Okay.
-Yay!
Thank you, Mr. Toh.
Be patient.
When we arrive at Wat Nak Nimit,
Luang Por can revoke the curse.
Who has stolen what's mine?
I'll kill you!
Klae, wait for me.
Aod?
What's wrong?
Calm down.
I had a bad dream.
I think you ate too much.
Aod's dreams are never good.
Hello, Kiddee. What's up?
Novice Nott, come on.
Why do we have to go to this cemetery?
It's spooky.
Kiddee's uncle just died,
so we have to meet him there.
Kiddee's uncle died?
What on earth is happening?
Under the seat, bitch.
I can't find it.
What do you usually ride?
I'm so tired. My VJJ is rocked.
Just a moment. Let me call Kiddee.
That kid?
Look.
It's fucking abandoned.
No…
Hello everyone.
Long time no see.
How are you, Mr. Toh?
I'm good.
And you, Aod?
You must be Pampam.
Annyeonghaseyo.
Nice to meet you.
Novice Nott.
Both of you
just forget it!
Did you know what we…
…were thinking?
Cute school boy.
I can hear your thoughts.
I'm single, here with friends on business.
You guys are brave,
risking yourselves to help Aod.
But I think
you're underestimating the situation
by coming here to fight Nak with nothing.
I think it's risky.
Yeah, he is worried about us.
I think he likes you. Don't blush.
One moment.
Why is he bending?
First, Balloon,
and Aod, please have a seat.
I think this is a really tough situation.
You guys should prepare
your bodies, minds,
and insurance policies
to guarantee your success.
I love you all.
I want you guys to be prepared.
But Kiddee, my friend--
Shut up, Balloon.
Go on.
This is what we're talking about,
getting a life insurance policy
so you can be insured.
But I don't have…
…a pen. You didn't prepare one. I know.
Here you go.
Go on.
-But I think it's quite…
-Quite dark?
Is this bright enough?
But I don't have…
…any cash.
Mobile banking.
That's satisfying.
Sign here.
It's done, First.
Now I think
you don't have to be worried about
getting hurt or dying.
Now you can die, First.
Come here.
I heard that my uncle's mother
put all of his belongings in the coffin
because he was very possessive.
I think his phone was in it too.
Who would go to get it?
CHANGSHUI MOUNTAIN
Why do they howl at this hour?
Mama?
Mama!
These shitty lights every time!
You've been here before?
Every movie is like this.
Dogs howl, lights go out.
Typical.
Run!
First! This way.
We are the chosen ones.
Let's go.
Smile.
Wow!
Hey…
There's a mirror at the entrance.
This is not the time.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, here.
What?
Jungle!
Jungle my ass. Uncle!
I'm Chinese.
Stop fooling around.
I'm sorry.
We mean well.
What?
Your face, I'm not used to it.
Bitch.
Quite pretty.
I just got back from Korea.
Come on.
Careful.
You know how to open it?
I've never been in one, you know?
Help me push.
It will be all right.
Put your back into it, First.
One, two…
First!
You pull and I push.
No. I push. You pull.
Careful.
You pull. I push.
So you push. I pull.
No. You pull. I push.
Bitch!
Listen to me.
I pull and you push.
One, two, three!
Did we get it? Did we?
Who are you? What are you doing here?
We have to wait for the guests to leave
so we can cry with the body in private.
It hurts. It damn hurts.
I see. You seem very upset.
Don't cry.
That's right, Uncle.
Listen to me.
Great-grandma and great-granduncle
never loved us.
First Aunty also had that bitch.
That bitch.
She can't take it that we are queer.
And you know what?
Do you know?
Third Aunty never supported us
with money or tuition fees.
And what about that bastard?
Big Brother.
Uncle!
So that means…
you must be Gim's children?
Yes.
It's okay. Don't be sad.
You can get changed into mourning attire.
All right, here.
The ritual is done.
Are you heading off now?
Can I stay with my dad
for the last time, Uncle?
I want to have a final moment
with my dad, Jungle.
Enough.
Take your time. I'll be right back.
You're so annoying.
Uncle!
Jungle!
Did you find the cell phone?
Did you?
Damn, he loved singing.
A pager? To call your fucking dad?
Dead people can't take anything.
Got it.
I got it, First.
Turn it on.
I can't.
Scan. Scan it now.
The newest model needs a retinal scan.
Open his eyes. Open them.
Then, you hold it!
Retina.
Pull him up.
Oh, shit.
First.
First. Hurry.
Hurry.
Take it.
Hurry. Help me pull him up.
Dad. I'm sorry.
Make sure they're open.
Got it?
Got it? Not too close. Damn it.
Not too close.
Are they aligned?
-Ready?
-Go!
One, two, three!
Enough! Close them!
Close them already!
Don't turn around.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
-Hey!
-Let's go.
Hurry, First!
Come on. Hurry!
What the hell were you lunatics doing?
-Stop. Don't run!
-Hurry.
Bring it back.
Damn these bitches.
Kiddee, here.
All right, First.
Why are you dressed like that?
To mourn your death.
Just drive. Stop asking.
Do we get the temple name? What is it?
Wait a second.
The temple's name, everybody…
What's the temple's name?
-Wat Nak Khum.
-Where is it?
Where is it?
Just a minute, Mr. Toh.
No, Kiddee. You have to find the location.
Okay.
Hurry up.
It's the fastest I can go.
Is that the fastest you can go, Pampam?
-It is.
-Guys.
I got the location.
I'll lead the way.
Okay, let's go.
Look. Here, Pampam.
Where are we going?
I'm looking at it.
-Stay away from it, Nott.
-What is it, Aod?
What?
-Stay away from it, Nott.
-What is it, Aod?
What?
What's that noise?
What's on the roof?
I don't know. What is it?
-A rock?
-What is it?
Pampam! Watch out!
Balloon!
Pampam.
-Aod, are you all right?
-My nose.
-Your nose, Balloon.
-You okay?
-How are you?
-Is everybody okay?
Okay.
Guys.
There's a main road.
Let's go that way.
-Help me.
-Aod, hurry.
Anybody. Help me.
-Anybody.
-Calm down. Watch out for cars.
What?
Snake!
Novice.
Can I have something to keep me safe?
Here.
A flashlight…
Why do you bring that?
Son,
come to Mama.
Who has stolen what's mine?
Aod.
Aod!
My anklet!
-Aod!
…must die!
-Aod, are you all right?
-Aod?
Aod?
Leave me alone.
Aod!
Aod?
Calm down, Aod.
-Aod!
Aod!
Help!
-Aod, where are you?
-Aod.
-Everybody, this way.
-Aod!
Aod!
Aod.
Novice!
First!
Balloon!
I'm here!
Is this the right direction?
-I think it is.
-Aod.
Aod, where are you?
Mama! Hurry up.
-Aod!
-Kiddee, wait.
Mama, quick.
Straight ahead, First, Balloon.
Help.
Wait.
Let me go.
They all left you.
Luang Por!
Aod?
Aod!
-Aod!
-Wait up.
Aod!
This is so strange.
What happened to him?
Why is he shaking?
-Aod.
-Novice.
-Aod. I'm tired.
Kiddee.
-Are you all right?
-Damn you.
Watch where you're going.
I'm sorry.
This is my flashlight, First.
I remember it.
It's mine. I've been holding it.
There. Yours is over there.
You're the youngest. Go get it.
I'm watching our backs.
It's calling for you.
Don't you love me that much? Bitch.
Do you see what I see, B1?
I don't, B2.
Aod.
-Aod.
What's happening?
Aod.
What the hell is going on?
First.
Kiddee.
Hold on tight.
Don't let anyone take me.
Hold on.
Yes, Balloon.
There's nothing out there, First.
You stay out of this.
Aod.
Don't let him possess you.
You'll end up leaving me.
Nobody is going to leave you.
I, for one, won't.
You got accepted in the university.
You'll leave him.
Even if everyone leaves you,
I won't.
Novice!
-Aod!
Aod, get yourself together.
That's Novice.
Novice!
Let go of him!
Why are you fighting with him?
I have to take the anklet from him.
Or I have to put him out.
Pampam, help.
Aod.
Novice!
Novice! Catch!
Pampam, help Novice Nott.
-You stay here.
-It hurts.
Just a moment.
Do something.
-Easy, Novice.
-It hurts.
Your hip too?
First. Balloon.
Where is Pampam?
In the building.
What? Hey!
Where is my anklet?
It's not here.
Aod, what's the matter?
I saw that you took it.
-I said I don't have it.
-Aod.
-It has to be here.
Aod. The anklet is here.
I wrapped it up. Nobody touches it.
I used to call you guys
troublemakers.
But right now,
I'm the troublemaker.
Aod…
It's because the ghost possessed you.
You are also unwell,
so your mind becomes weak.
And the ghost found it easy
to possess you.
Aod.
Listen to me.
We'll are worried for you.
We won't leave you.
Aod.
Don't worry.
Novice Namnua understands.
Novice.
You came back to your senses, Aod?
Do you feel better?
Does it still hurt anywhere?
Novice.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing to apologize for.
I broke your arm.
The ghost did.
Just worry about yourself.
Let's get going.
-Don't rush.
-Take it easy.
Stay still. Does it hurt?
Novice.
Kiddee called your mother.
She will be here soon.
But if I don't go,
who will help Aod?
I'll go with you guys.
Novice, it's too hard on you.
Don't push yourself.
If anything happens to you,
we'll be heartbroken
that we didn't stop you.
I'll come back to pick you up soon.
The sun!
Where is Mr. Toh?
He went to recover the van
with the old man who helped us last night.
It's Mr. Toh.
Hello, Mr. Toh.
Yes. Balloon…
Your voice!
Yes.
Faster…
Yeah, almost.
Excellent!
Excuse me.
Can we really take this vehicle?
Yes.
This is my Cyclone 100.
I don't use it that often.
You guys can take it
while I find a mechanic to fix your van.
Whenever you're done with your business,
bring it back to me.
Consider it an exchange, okay?
Thank you, Uncle.
-Can I drive it? Guys, let me drive!
-Sure.
Go ahead. I'll call the mechanic.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Good bye.
Come on. Let's go.
Get on. Come on.
Everybody hop on.
Mr. Toh.
-Hurry up.
-Don't be stubborn.
You're stubborn. Hop on. Come on.
Come on. Let's go.
-Hop on.
-Why is he so hyped?
I'm a fast driver. Hold tight.
Pampam, come on.
Guys.
I'm not going.
What now?
I'm scared.
Why would I take a risk with you guys?
If we meet the ghost again,
you'll all just leave me.
Pampam, I know that you're scared
and you don't trust us.
But we want you to come
because we're worried for you.
We don't want you to end up like…
like Shon.
Hey.
Come with us.
We're already on the same boat.
Together, we'll survive, Oppa.
Come.
Ready. Go!
-That way, Mr. Toh.
-Sorry.
Is that okay?
The temple is over there.
WAT NAK KHUM
Wat Nak Toom!
Hey, Nak…
That is Wat Nak Khum!
The temple in Gim's phone.
Thank heavens!
We're finally here.
Luang Por,
is there a tradition at this temple…
Look at how he said "Luang Por."
Just speak with a normal accent.
People struggle enough without the accent.
Don't bully him.
Luang Por.
Is there a tradition
about wearing anklets?
Yes, we still wear them.
We found a haunted anklet.
And we're here to study the legends,
hoping to revoke the curse.
Aod, show the anklet to Luang Por.
This one.
Luang Por!
Don't touch it.
It's cursed.
If you touch it, burning scales will start
growing on your body.
The ghost will come after you.
I'm warning you.
So you bring it to Luang Por
to revoke the curse?
Yes.
Luang Por, please help us.
Prin, bring the anklet for them to see.
All right.
Done.
This anklet is similar to
the one from our temple.
But…
there is no script on them like Aod's.
Wait a second.
Can you look at this photo?
Is there a temple
that has an arched entrance like this?
Something ancient like this
can only be found at the deserted temple
called “Wat Nak Nimit”
in the mountains.
Old people say that the Naga built it.
Now it's just a deserted temple.
Don't go there. You won't find anyone.
Mr. Toh, pull over.
-Mr. Toh.
-Stop.
-Let me find the location.
What did you say, Aod?
I think this is it.
What is it?
Just follow me.
Aod, you always get me excited.
Is there no better place to go?
You have any sunscreen with you?
-What else?
-This is it.
That's the rock field
where I saw Nak running
from something in my dream…
before he jumped off the cliff.
Be patient.
When we arrive at Wat Nak Nimit,
Luang Por can undo the curse.
-Klae, wait for me.
-You stole what's mine.
You must die!
Jook was washed up here…
and looked up the mountain…
before he saw fire.
Wait, guys.
Luang Por said that there is
a deserted temple on this mountain.
According to Google Maps,
the mountain is quite high.
From what I see,
I think it's upside down.
Sorry, First.
It doesn't seem so high now.
Quite low, actually.
Are you all right, Aod?
I think that in the past,
your anklet might have been around here.
Since we're already here,
let's try to find it.
Let's go.
All right, Aod?
Yes.
Aod.
My anklet.
-Aod?
What's wrong?
Nak is hurting me.
That means the side where it hurts
is the direction where the anklet is.
Let's hurry and find it.
Pampam, take Aod to rest in the shade.
The rest of us split up
and look for a recess.
It should be quicker that way.
The ghost chased me to
a recess in the high mountain.
Let me go.
I give up.
And I died there.
Do you remember that mountain recess?
What does it look like?
That's too detailed.
Just look for a mountain recess
with skeletons.
Are you scared?
Yeah.
You want to hold this?
Nah, you have an amulet.
Careful.
Get up, Mama.
I'm sure.
I know.
Over there!
Your nails are still beautiful, Mama.
It's not about my nails.
That skeleton right there.
A dinosaur skeleton!
We'll be rich, First.
-We'll be rich.
-Oh, fuck!
That's a human skeleton.
Hurry up, Aod.
Hey…
Aod?
Aod!
Are you sure?
Look at his eyes. Don't you remember?
There are no eyes there.
And that hairstyle
he wore when he was younger.
He literally looks like a monk
with a bald head.
Yes.
See? Now you can't argue with me.
You saw what I saw, First.
I didn't.
I just saw this. The anklet.
Pick it up.
You pick it up.
I can't.
You're closer to it.
How am I going to reach it?
Okay, I'll get out of the way.
You pick it up.
-You saw it first. You pick it up.
-Why should I?
-You saw it later. You pick it--
-You pick it, First.
I got it.
Get out! Novice! Hurry up!
Hurry. Shit! Let him go.
You stole what's mine.
You must die!
Hurry up.
Come on, Novice. Get out.
You must die!
Hurry up! Novice!
Novice!
Let's go. Novice, come on.
Hurry up.
What happened?
-Help!
-What's going on?
-What happened?
-Go, Novice. Just leave. Let's go.
-What? What's going on?
-My anklet!
-Let's go.
Nak's ghost is here. Hurry up, Aod.
Wait.
Aod, come here.
Let's go.
Is he following us? Let's go.
Run, bitch!
Who has stolen what's mine?
I'll kill you!
Aod!
-Novice.
-Novice. Are you all right?
I'm okay. I just lost my balance.
Aod?
-Be careful.
-Are you all right?
-I'm all right.
-Go.
I think we should take a rest.
Let's keep on moving.
Before the ghost catches up.
Don't worry, Novice.
We have a Buddha statue.
Pampam, show!
Here you go!
-The Buddha is gone!
Pampam!
Shit!
Where did you keep it?
Where did it go?
How careless of you!
Wait, where did it go?
You stole what's mine.
You must die!
-Run!
-Wait for Aod.
Aod! Hurry up.
-Aod.
-I know.
Wait for Aod.
-Aod.
Wait for me. Hurry up.
My anklet.
There's fire, guys. The fire.
Is that a ghost too?
Let's get there first.
-Go.
-Go, everyone.
Guys.
-It's the fire.
-Be careful.
Is it this way?
Balloon, be careful!
Pampam, watch out for the fire.
-Guys, let's go.
-Hurry up.
Aod, careful.
Aod, are you all right?
-Yes, I'm all right.
-Aod.
Come on, Aod. I'll help you.
Hold my arm.
Guys, this way.
Aod, come on.
It's itchy.
I don't want to be at the back.
Hey.
-Is that a monk?
-Hey.
I think you should ask, is that a human?
Are you a human?
I'm a monk…
on a pilgrimage and staying here tonight.
He really is a monk, First.
-Hurry up.
-Hurry up. Luang Por!
Luang Por! Please help!
Luang Por! Please help us.
A ghost has been following us.
Very well.
I think we should treat
that young man first.
Aod.
How are you?
Is it better?
I feel better.
Can I have a look at your anklet?
Just hand it over.
It's all right.
You know about this anklet?
It belongs to
the big temple on the mountain.
So, there is a temple on this mountain?
Yes, there is.
Long time ago,
there was a temple on the mountain.
And this mountain…
has been protected by the Naga.
He was quite mischievous
and had hurt so many people
until the villagers fled.
Then,
there came a monk
who accepted the invitation
from the villagers
to subdue the Naga.
It took him seven days and seven nights.
The Naga finally surrendered.
He promised to turn his life around.
He redeemed himself for hurting humans
and harassing the monks
by building a big temple
and dedicated it to that monk.
He also made gold anklets for Nak
as a merit to support Nak
to become a monk.
Although the temple is deserted now,
the Nak anklet tradition before ordination
is still practiced by temples around here.
Luang Por.
The ghost is still in my head.
I'm afraid that I'll still be possessed,
and that I won't be
strong enough to fight it.
The strength you have
is not only from yourself,
but also from your friends
for not leaving you.
You're not fighting alone.
But Luang Por,
we once had
a Buddha statue to ward off ghosts.
It's gone now, nowhere to be found.
Can you give us something
to ward them off?
You think the ghost is
scared of the Buddha statue?
If it's not because of the Buddha statue,
why doesn't it hurt us
when it sees the Buddha statue?
Or is he scared of something else inside?
All right.
I don't think you should overthink it.
Rest here tonight.
This is a sacred place.
No ghost will come across here.
Yes, Luang Por.
Aod, you have another story, don't you?
I think we should tell Luang Por.
I'll find Luang Por.
Just a moment.
Yeah, make yourself useful.
Luang Por.
Everyone!
Luang Por isn't here.
His belongings are all gone.
-All gone?
-All of it.
Everything is gone.
Everything is gone?
No. Nothing. No candles.
Luang Por, the temple, the monk…
The cave!
Are any of these real?
Am I real?
I'm sure you're real.
But your nose is fake.
That hurts, you asshole.
I'm sorry, Mr. Toh.
Well, you asked.
Maybe Luang Por went out
to collect the alms.
You sleep like the dead,
like you're rehearsing when you die.
Let's get Aod to the temple.
Let's go.
Go.
-Let's go.
-Thank you.
Do you know where we're going?
Head north, Balloon.
-You know the direction.
-North.
What is it?
This way, guys.
You go ahead.
-Mr. Toh.
-Are you all right?
I lost all my energy.
Guys, wait a moment for First.
Balloon.
Keep going.
Hurry up, First, before we get lost.
Watch your hands.
What about my hands?
Balloon is so loud.
I'm sure we can find them.
Falling for someone.
Not funny. Come on. Get up.
Holy smokes.
Oh, you do care about me.
Kiddee, are we lost?
This is the way, Balloon.
It's a shortcut.
Oh, gosh!
I could hear you before you even got here.
Hey First, how did you get here?
Kiddee!
What's the point of using a compass?
I'm sorry, Balloon.
I'm aching all over.
Is my back dirty?
Look, guys!
This is laterite.
It's not found naturally.
What is it?
Here, there's a block of it.
First!
You're so stupid.
Don't you know what laterite is?
Look at me.
I don't have a geologist for a husband.
That means
there must be an ancient site hidden here.
Is this the ancient arched entrance?
This is what I saw in my dream.
It looks like the entrance to our temple.
it's exactly the same.
Annyeong!
Can you revoke a curse?
Any promos? Like revoking the curse
with free exorcism?
-We'll take one.
Why are you fooling around?
Look at him.
-Aod.
-Let me help you.
-I'm okay.
Let's get inside.
Let's go.
Balloon, come on.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up, guys.
-You play football?
-Let's go.
First, there are some people here.
Make sure they are humans.
Maybe they can help Aod.
Go.
-Excuse me.
Please help.
Our friend is ill.
Can you help him?
How did you get here?
Here he is.
Aod.
The curse of the Naga's anklet.
-Nak Kham!
How are you?
-Is that the same monk?
-Yes.
Does the ghost still bother you?
Not anymore.
But my wounds still hurt.
It's like he's still somewhere near.
What's the deal
with the anklet, Luang Por?
And about someone called "Nak Kham"?
The deserted temple you saw
used to be a big temple.
It's called Wat Nak Nimit.
The villagers along the Mekong
celebrate their ordination
by having the monk at that temple
perform for them.
Nak Kham was an orphan.
Phra Kru.
Kham is burglarizing again.
I have to bring him in this time.
I'm an orphan. Who do I turn to?
Can you spare me some,
even just this much?
Phra Kru took you in and raised you.
And you still dare
to call yourself an orphan?
You bastard. Look at what you did.
You have no respect for him.
Please spare him.
I'm asking you.
I might not have taught you well enough.
That's probably why you're greedy.
To commit sins and make yourself
an excuse that you did it
because you don't have as much as others
does not give you the reason to do so.
It makes you go down even deeper.
Phra Kru,
we'll bind him with a plank
and drag him to the authorities later.
No, Phra Kru. Please.
During the next crescent moon,
there will be a big ordination
at the Naga temple.
Let me be ordained to repay
for what I did.
He is right.
For the sake of Buddhism,
let the Naga discipline him.
I think
it's better than convicting him.
But it didn't come from
his heart to become a monk.
He wanted to go to the capital
so he planned to steal
the gold anklets and run away.
That's why he was cursed
and it caused his skin to grow "scales"
as he suffered until his death.
This young man must have been cursed
for the wrongful possession.
Is there a way to revoke the curse?
There is only one way.
Return the anklets to the Naga.
How do we do it?
Isn't it written on the anklets?
Is there anything written on
the other anklet we found?
Yes.
-What does it say?
"The anklets that Nak is wearing,
when they are removed,
you'll become a monk."
The ghost has been harassing Aod
because it doesn't want
Aod to become a monk.
Because if Aod succeeds,
it will revoke the curse.
How about this?
Aod wears the anklets, becomes a monk,
-and revokes the curse.
-Yeah.
That is not possible.
You still have ties with him.
Ties of karma that you committed
with him in the past life.
If you can't remove those ties,
you can't be a monk.
The anklets are a symbol of
ties in the mundane world,
both good karma and bad karma.
If you can't let go of these ties,
you can't be prosperous in Dharma.
So that means
to take the anklets off,
we must let go of
the ties in our mind first
and be a monk?
No ties, no concerns.
Then you can be a monk.
I see.
At a cliff near the back of the village,
there is a holy reservoir.
Put on Nak's attire and the anklets.
Go wash your body there.
May you be victorious, as Buddha defeated
demons at the base of the Bodhi tree.
May you reach the apex of Buddhist bliss
and be content on the throne
where no demons could reach.
May all the righteous benefits
come to you.
Awesome.
Why don't we just go to the flower market?
It's an eight-day walk.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Please take this yellow robe
to make merit.
Of course.
Thank you.
We will pray for you. Sathu.
I have some gossip.
Don't you think this village is weird?
There are only young people
and no elderly people.
There is only one
that looks like a village chief.
On top of that, there are no kids.
That's good.
When Mama sees them,
like the Korean-looking guys around here,
I just love it.
Don't make me suspicious. Just stay put.
How are you?
Did you wash yourself in the reservoir?
I did.
That's good.
But it can relieve the curse
for just a while.
Aod.
Do you know
how we can take the anklets off?
I don't know.
But I feel sorry for Nak Kham.
Without you guys…
I might be just like him.
Hey, Aod.
He lived by taking advantage
and stealing from others,
so he's no different
from selfish criminals.
He only blames others
and never looks at himself.
Yeah.
I think those who
only think of the benefit
won't get sympathy from other people.
That's right.
We should not forgive ourselves,
but we should ask for forgiveness.
That's true. Even during the ordination,
there is a part that deals with
apologies to all vengeful spirits.
Right, apologize to a ghost then.
You'll get your neck broken
before you know it.
Why do you take it off?
If we are willing to apologize to him,
we should let him see our true intention.
I, and everybody here…
want to apologize
for stealing what's yours,
as I will be ordained.
I won't let you!
We are here in good faith.
We are aware of our wrongdoings.
You…
stole what's mine.
You will be like me!
But the anklets don't belong to you.
The anklets are mine!
You took them off from my ankles.
Don't you remember?
The Naga anklets.
Nak…
you should let go of those anklets.
Wherever you took them from,
take them back.
No.
I won't.
I will die…
with my precious anklets.
The anklet curse…
Nobody can help you
if you won't help yourself.
Remember that.
I ask for permission
to leave the monkhood.
Please recognize
that I'm now a layman.
Jook, Klae.
Are you stealing from corpses again?
We're not.
Let's go then. Get the boat.
-Yes.
What are you waiting for?
Get the other one.
You have stolen what's mine.
Whoever took what's mine must die!
You're already dying. Don't be stingy.
That thing on your ankle, give it to me.
Give it back to me.
Novice.
The anklet.
Jook.
Just give it back to him.
Give it to me.
-No.
-It's mine!
-Get up.
-Give it back to me.
The anklet is mine.
Jook!
Take it.
Hey.
How come the events from the previous life
affect us in this life?
Luang Por,
it's a different life.
What do you think about
yesterday, today, and tomorrow?
How are they connected?
They are all connected.
That's right.
It's like the same piece of fabric.
All connected.
Today is yesterday's future.
And the consequences of our actions today
affect tomorrow.
We have to accept the consequences
because you can't go back in time
to fix yesterday.
I won't let you
take off my anklets!
Please forgive us.
Please let Aod go.
No.
-Aod.
All of you have to die like I did.
Aod has admitted his wrongdoings.
We are asking for forgiveness
with good faith
-and we should--
-Stop it!
-We are asking for forgiveness--
-I said stop!
I will kill him
and make him suffer.
Stop this, Nak.
-Luang Por!
-Aod.
-Luang Por.
Luang Por.
When they are asking for your forgiveness,
why don't you let go of the ties
and forgive them?
Why am I the only one
who has to become like this?
Why do you help them…
but not me?
And you…
you performed the ordination for me.
I have helped you
but you didn't help yourself.
Please stop.
I'm asking to hold back
the extreme punishment.
Please give him a chance to repent
the same way it happened to you.
And you,
if you really accept your mistake
and apologize to the anklets' owner,
you will survive.
No.
I'm not giving them back.
You are unjust.
This one is real, First!
Those who wear anklets
who dedicate themselves to Buddhism,
the Naga will protect them.
Those who wear anklets…
if they ever dare to become
an enemy of Buddhism,
the Naga will destroy them.
Like how you've declared yourself
as a protector of Buddhism…
My anklet!
A long time ago…
the Naga accepted his mistake.
That's why he created these anklets,
to remind the later generations
to accept their mistakes in the past.
As for you…
after you take off the anklets,
you can become Nak, then a monk.
Come, the spirit of Nak.
Don't go around
admiring the beautiful mountains
high up in the clouds
and the goddess Mekhla,
or the writer at the base of
tall candle trees
aligning through the woods.
For the merit of my ordination this time,
I want to dedicate it to every Naga
and Nak Kham.
No ties, no concerns.
Be prosperous in Dharma.
And everyone too.
-Sathu.
Hello, I'm Pampam Oppa.
You are now at
the Wat Nak Khum temple fair.
Where's mine?
Here.
That's my boyfriend.
Sure.
Yummy.
So delicious.
Oops! Here you go. Thank you.
-Thank you.
-This one is delicious.
What are you doing?
Whose drone is this?
It's Kiddee's dad's. He brought it today.
-What is this?
-Grilled rice crisps.
Grilled rice crisps?
Can I try to make it?
Sure.
-I keep flipping it?
-Yes.
Oh, gosh! Marvelous!
Like you've never been to a temple fair.
What's so marvelous about it?
That guy eating meatballs there.
Where?
The grilled rice crisps are cuter.
First, this is why I'm here…
to see real Naga fireballs.
Why are you excited?
Fireballs, not guys.
Really. I want to see them too.
What?
-They're trying to commit suicide.
-What?
-Where?
At the rock field we went to yesterday.
Yeah.
Why are they doing this? Why?
Let's go help him.
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
Calm down, everyone.
-Don't get down there. It's dangerous.
-It's dangerous.
-Guys.
-Calm down. No.
Old man.
See you.
-Again?
Here, my brother.
I give it to you.
Are you sure?
I don't feel comfortable.
You should give it to him.
Take it, my brother.
Here, Pampam. Keep it.
Before you leave, bring this to Phra Aod
to pay homage to
the Buddha image at the entrance.
Yes.
Told you he's not old.
Luang Pee…
Novice.
Cut!
-Let's go.
-In my face.
What's in your face?
-Are you all right?
-Yes.
You're not.
Go. Come on.
Like that.
Okay.
Good.
-Novice.
-Are you hurt?
-No.
You want to see a snakefish?