Hey, gather up!
Anggun wants to say something.
Uh…
God damn, you guys! I'm blown away!
Totally speechless.
Uh, I'm a teary mess.
Let's pray for the awards night later.
-Yo, yo, yo.
-According to your faiths and beliefs.
Amen. That's enough.
Mata Hari hug!
Win or lose, let's party
at Rama's tomorrow night!
You should've paid more attention.
What's wrong with you?
Now, listen to me. Remember this.
When someone makes a mistake,
you gotta help out. Okay?
Excuse me, Tariq, may I go home now?
-My family's expecting me.
-What?
Your family?
Aren't we all your family here?
Not that I wanna.
Just that my mother really needs me.
I was messing up with you.
You're not staying?
I mean, for the awarding?
It's two hours.
Don't think I can wait that long.
But after the awards,
I'll update the website right away.
All right. Take care. Guys!
Lady Sur is leaving us and going home now.
-Goodbye, all.
-Take care, sweet Sur!
South Jakarta bound!
South Jakarta bound! South Jakarta bound!
Ma'am.
-My boss texted you the order, right?
-What order?
I can't find my phone.
Don't you remember the order?
-Peace be unto you.
-And unto you peace.
Sur, help me find my phone.
-I forgot where I put it.
-I'll try to call it.
-You can't. I put it on silent.
-Wait.
I thought it was here.
Damn. What's that?
High-tech stuff!
-Glad you're studying computer science.
-Hey.
Who's calling?
No, Dad. I just triggered the alarm
from my laptop.
-Why are you late?
-The play just finished, Dad.
Stop wasting your time.
It's not even your major in college.
The diner is busy now.
How was it? Did you win?
I should check.
Mom!
Congrats, dear!
So rice, liver satay and sauteed kale?
Yup, that's my order.
-Sur.
-Yes?
You seem busy with that.
What about your studies?
It's going well, Mom.
It's actually good for my CV.
It shows that I can make a proper website.
It's also good for my scholarship reports.
When's your next report due?
Day after tomorrow.
-How much?
-Twenty-eight thousand.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Mata Hari!
Why are you all skipping class?
Go back to your class!
After the triumph of the play,
Medusa et Perseus,
in the Student Theater Festival,
the faculty will continue to support
the Mata Hari theater group,
to join the Asian Student
Theater Festival in Kyoto next month!
I'm hopeful that our dynamic duo,
Rama, the playwright,
and Anggun, the director,
will bring more success to our university!
Attention, guys!
Everyone is expected to be
at Rama's house by 6:00 p.m.
So you guys won? Where's the feast then?
I'm just the website designer, Amin.
You made that website here.
-Pay my power bill then.
-Damn you, loan shark!
All right then.
I'll buy you lunch. What do you want?
Sushi?
You're going to Japan, right?
No way I'm going.
Only 15 guys will go, and I'm a nobody.
-Printing work, Amin.
-Go ahead, boss.
Printing another draft, brother?
Yup. I have to translate it.
I also need to take new photos
for the installation sets.
Anyway…
My dad's looking for a web designer
for a charity gala
with his fellow artists.
I showed him Mata Hari's website,
and he likes it.
Seriously?
I recommended you to him.
So please come to the party.
Bring anyone you want.
Okay?
Thirty copies.
-I can't get it done today though.
-No problem.
Amelia is overworked today.
Amelia?
Why do you call it Amelia?
No reason. Sounds pretty, right?
Find the meaning.
The poor thing works all the time.
-Keep the change.
-Thank you, boss.
Did you hear that?
-I can take anyone. Come with me?
-No, thanks.
See those piles? Like the Eiffel Tower.
There'll be free food.
I'll pay for the gas.
Rama's house is a bit far.
I knew it. You just need a ride.
I need this job offer.
I haven't gotten my scholarship grant yet.
We'll finish by 8:00 p.m.
Not a minute later, okay?
Help me copy these then.
The party's dress code
is the '40s. Do you have that?
No shit.
Are you new in Mata Hari?
Yes.
Don't go to that party.
Waste of time.
And why is that?
You'd better focus
on your scholarship report.
It's due tomorrow, right?
Stop seeking attention
and trying to be popular.
-Eight thousand for six copies, right?
-Yep.
What's her deal?
-I'm leaving, Mom.
-Mmm.
Your hand, please.
-Godspeed. Go get that job!
-Amen, Mom.
I'll come straight home after the meeting.
-I'll be home by 9:00 p.m.
-Hey.
-Where are you going?
-A job interview, Dad.
Huh?
Who will help your mother then?
It's okay.
I gave her permission.
Why would someone
schedule a job interview
after office hours?
We'll also have a small party
for the award we won.
-Is it a party or an interview?
-An interview.
If it's a job interview…
don't wear such a revealing dress.
But everyone will be dressed like this.
Put something under it.
Hey.
Promise me. No alcohol.
Yes.
Who was that senior back at the shop?
She was so rude.
Farah?
Just ignore her.
She was a member of Mata Hari.
The photographer, I think.
But she was kicked out.
Got into
many complicated flings with boys.
That's what I heard.
Name please?
Suryani, sir. I'm bringing my friend here.
Suryani.
Damn! This house is huge!
I know, right?
So many statues…
Rama's father is a sculptor.
Amin.
Tuck your shirt in.
-Tuck it in?
-Better that way.
First,
an important announcement.
So the news is,
our flights to Kyoto
will be sponsored by
Uncle Soemarno and Aunt Lilis,
Rama's parents!
Uncle, Auntie,
thank you for always supporting
the Mata Hari family.
-Anything for you guys.
-What do we say, guys?
Thank you, Uncle and Auntie!
I'd like to thank everyone
who has contributed to our show.
First, our production manager.
Tariq the badass!
Don't let it go to your head now.
You have to arrange for everyone's visas.
Also, thank you to our Medusa
for her divine performance,
Kirana!
Thank you so much.
Our visual art crew, Samsul!
Samsul, thank you.
And last but not least,
we had a full house yesterday,
thanks to our super cool website.
So big thanks to Suryani!
-Dad, this is Sur, our web designer.
-Hi, Sur.
-Hi, Uncle.
-What a cool website.
Thank you, Uncle.
I believe Rama told you about the offer?
Yes, he did.
-I'm glad you're on board.
-Thank you for the opportunity, Uncle.
Fill it up.
-Hi, Sur!
-Hi, Sister Anggun.
Here. Take this.
Careful.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Don't get tired working with us. Okay?
Let's toast.
No. Let's start again.
When toasting,
we need to make eye contact.
Otherwise, it's bad luck. Okay?
Look me in the eyes. All right?
Cheers!
Mmm.
What's with the look?
Behold!
Medusa is coming!
Whoever gets shot
by Medusa's gaze must take a shot!
Brace yourself! Brace yourself!
Oh!
Amin, my man!
Chug! Chug! Chug!
Give it to him!
-Bring me my copies, Amin!
-Isn't it fun? Let's stay a bit more!
Another round! Incoming!
Chug! Chug! Chug!
Take it!
Chug! Chug!
Bottoms up!
Oh!
Sur.
Come on, let's go.
Stay a bit more.
What're you gonna do?
Everyone's still here.
No one will be at your shop.
You promised we'd be back by 8:00 p.m.
Sur, sit here.
Sur. Sit here!
I have my scholarship review, Dad.
-Please, let her go!
-I want to talk.
-Let her do her report first!
-You stay out of this!
-It's because you gave her permission!
-I'm taking your shoes, Mom!
I'm late, Dad!
-Listen to me!
-I am late, Dad!
Just take
the public transit, Sur!
You got wasted last night?
Mind watching my phone for me?
You almost missed your appointment.
Good morning, sir.
Sorry I'm late. I was stuck in traffic.
Why are you wearing a kebaya?
It's not Women's Day.
Not your graduation day, either.
I'm sorry, sir.
I have an event after this.
The dress code is kebaya.
This is my report, sir.
-This semester, I made a website for--
-Hold it.
I want to ask you something.
Do you often go to night clubs?
No, sir. Not at all.
-Do you drink?
-What? No, sir.
Then what's this?
Explain this.
Why did you upload them
to your social media?
I didn't upload them, sir!
Then who did? Your assistant?
But you did go to
a party last night, right?
I see you're still wearing the same dress.
Let me explain…
She told us that she needs
to wear it for an event after this.
-But, sir, I'm wearing this--
-I am appalled.
Why have you been slacking
since last semester?
Drinking alcohol
is not Indonesian culture.
The alumni is paying for your studies.
Sir, first of all…
I never took those photos, sir.
And then, until now,
I still meet
the requirements for this scholarship.
My GPA is above 3.6
and I have perfect attendance, sir.
We know that. However…
Your academic performance
and your behavior
are both important, Suryani.
And we give the scholarship
so students may use it for good causes,
not for this kind of rubbish.
But, sir, I've always joined
positive activities.
The website that I made
helped the theater department to win, sir.
Wait a second.
As far as I know, this faculty
doesn't have any theater group.
Are you really a Computer Science major?
Let's get to the point.
We have to deliberate.
Whatever the result, we'll let you know.
Your session is over, anyway.
Look at yourself.
I don't think you're fully sober.
Farah Natia.
Amin.
Who pulled a prank on me?
-Amin.
-What do you mean?
Who took those selfies?
How would I know?
Why didn't you wake me up on the way home?
I didn't take you home.
I went home before you.
You left me there?
You told me to go home and so I went.
You were dancing like crazy.
-Wisnu Brata?
-Present.
-Xavier Wibowo?
-Present, ma'am.
-And lastly, Yanuar Joko?
-Present.
All right, class.
Now I will distribute…
Miss?
You haven't called my name. It's Suryani.
Have you completed
your registration for this semester?
I have, Miss.
But I haven't paid the tuition fee.
I'm waiting for my scholarship grant.
So please settle that first.
Because if your name's not here,
then you can't join this class.
Let's continue.
We'll start with the first chapter…
Watch it!
Attention,
ladies and gentlemen!
To control the dengue fever
outbreak in Indonesia,
the government is providing
free fumigation in this area.
Please remain inside your house…
Why did you close the diner?
Still waiting for the fumigation?
So from now on,
I have to pay for your tuition too?
"Terminated due to inappropriate conduct."
What does that mean?
This is a mistake, Mom.
Dad.
What are you doing, Dad? Dad!
You've broken the rule
by drinking alcohol.
You are no longer a member of this family.
Dad, let me explain.
Please stop. I haven't explained anything!
I don't need any explanation.
Our neighbors know
that you came home drunk.
A guy was carrying you along the alley,
and he knocked on everyone's doors,
he woke everyone up,
just so he could find our house.
Did you know what time it was? Hmm?
Three in the morning.
-Please, listen to me, Dad.
-Hey.
Since this morning, everyone
has been coming, asking questions.
"What was wrong with Sur?"
"Who was the guy carrying her?"
Your mom and I had to answer all of them.
Said you had a job interview,
you were partying instead!
But I wanted to celebrate
my achievement, Dad…
Achievement?
You lost your scholarship
because of your bad behavior.
You call that an achievement?
Who's going to pay for your tuition now?
Don't you feel bad for your mother?
Consider this your punishment,
so you may repent.
Chitra? Excuse me…
Do you know who took me home last night?
What time did you go home?
I left around 10:00 p.m.
Hey, Sur. Sobered up yet?
Anggun wants to modify
the Gorgon's costume.
Can you add beige to its color?
Damn, I must go to the thrift shop again.
-See what you can do.
-I'll let you know tomorrow.
-Tariq…
-Not now.
Hey, morons!
What have you done with the package?
Have you got no sense of urgency?
Do I always have to clean up
after your shit?
-Next time, do it right!
-Sorry, brother.
-Tariq…
-Sur, stop bugging me. I'm busy!
Do you know who…
-Rama.
-Hi, Sur.
Sorry, do you know
who took me home last night?
NetCar, right?
Did you order it?
-No, Anggun did. Why?
-Oh.
Stop. Anggun is rehearsing.
Wait, let me get her.
Anggun, uh, Sur's asking about the NetCar…
I'll be quick. Sorry.
Okay, Sur. So…
Everyone left in their own cars,
so I ordered a NetCar for you.
Did you lose anything?
No, but what time was that?
Let me check the order history.
Was I… Was I asleep or…
Last night you were really drunk.
I tried to wake you up,
but you were out cold.
So I'm really sorry.
I had to find your ID to get your address.
-Can you send it to me?
-Sure.
Uh…
Done. Hey, Ical.
Please take out the Perseus helmet.
It needs more aging.
-Okay.
-Uh… Got cigs?
Do you know who posted these selfies?
Didn't you upload these yourself?
I can't remember.
Well, the room was dark,
and everyone was dancing.
When the lights came on,
I saw you sleeping on the couch.
So I'm not sure what happened in between.
Do you remember laying down on the couch?
Mmm.
I remember I was very tired,
so I stopped dancing,
then I can't remember anymore.
What's wrong with these selfies?
Did they get you into trouble?
Well…
It's common to lose control
when we're drunk, Sur.
I once drunk-dialed my ex.
-Anggun?
-Hmm?
-Let's start again.
-Just a sec.
-Uh, did you find Tariq?
-No.
Bummer.
Sur, sorry, I have to leave you now.
If anything happens, you talk to me.
I mean it. Okay?
Rama, help her out. Let's start again.
Sur, if you lost something,
just call me and I'll help you find it.
Rama!
The revised installation set has arrived.
Okay. Please unwrap it.
-Text me. You have my number, right?
-Yes.
Turn it on.
-This one's a picture of the Milky Way?
-Otong, please copy.
Get me a kimono.
Here's your kimono.
Welcome to the Mata Hari family.
Anggun, do you need me?
-Where were you?
-Restroom.
Everyone was looking for you.
Stop fooling around!
What did you drink?
Blacked out like that.
I just had wine, and what was it?
And that one shot,
when we played that Medusa game?
Whiskey?
-What else?
-I forgot.
But your eyes seem open.
Doesn't look like you're sleeping.
That's just how I sleep.
Remember when I slept in class
in primary school?
I'm sure somebody pranked me.
But why though?
Look at this. The sizes are different.
Front camera compared to rear camera.
They used the rear camera.
I never do selfies with my rear camera.
-They're the same, damn it!
-It's different!
-I'll check if anyone posted videos of me.
-Hey!
Use the scrap paper!
Video one.
Gita's mirror selfie, 11:00 p.m.
Video two.
Udiarti's Boomerang
in the garden, 5:00 p.m.
Video three.
Dance floor in the living room, 11:30 p.m.
The videos are disappearing.
It's been 24 hours.
Take screenshots then!
Sur.
Learn your lesson.
The next time you drink, be careful!
What lesson, jerk? Here. Look at this.
They did this to the new members.
I knew it was part of their initiation,
but they wouldn't admit
that they did this to me.
12:15 a.m…
I need you, as the dean,
to convince the Board of Alumni.
How could I lose my scholarship
over some selfies?
I've already told you.
The faculty can't interfere
with the board's decisions.
From what I heard,
the board monitors the social media
account of every recipient.
Now think about it.
What would happen if your social media
was filled with your drunk photos?
But I didn't violate
any of my scholarship requirements, sir.
Nonsense!
It's obviously in the requirements.
The recipients
shall not commit immoral acts
and must maintain their integrity.
Now, how could we regain their trust
if you used their money to get drunk?
What the hell are you doing?
I'll stay here from now on.
I need to find out who did this to me.
What do you mean?
Starting tomorrow,
I'll hack into Mata Hari members' phones.
Are you nuts?
Playing detective, are we?
Must be the lack of sleep.
Poor Sur.
I see you haven't sobered up yet.
Sur.
This is my territory.
You stay over here.
Don't you come near my fish.
If they die, I'll lose money.
How long will you stay here?
We're living together now.
Man and woman, unmarried.
What if the campus found out?
They'd fire me.
Getting fired is nothing.
What if they shame us in public?
I'll try to find evidence
within three days.
The theater members will come here often
to prepare their visas.
I'll work as usual, okay?
Mosquito repellent.
MOM
BLOCK
Amin, print this.
Min?
Is the Wi-Fi off?
I can't log in to my email.
There's been trouble
since last night.
Where's your file?
You have it on your phone?
I have it.
Just plug it in then.
The Wi-Fi's never died before.
Ask the shitty provider.
Damn it!
-Amin, five pages. How much?
-Seven thousand.
-Thanks, dude.
-Yep.
What now?
He left before I finished copying.
What was I supposed to do?
Okay, listen.
Hey.
If I play some folk music,
it means I'm still copying.
Help me buy some time.
If I change to rock music,
it means I'm done.
You can let them go.
What a pain in the ass.
Come on, fix your damn Wi-Fi!
Yeah.
I heard there's gonna
be a student protest?
Who said that?
The dean came and told me.
Ugh. That's just a rumor.
Wait! Don't unplug it yet.
This computer has viruses.
-Let me install the antivirus first.
-Huh?
Damn it!
Who needs an antivirus for a phone?
You don't want to lose your data, right?
Let me do it.
I don't need it. Piss off.
It'll only take a minute. Wait.
Cut it out, Amin. I don't need it.
Gosh, stop it now!
I need to see my professor soon!
Stop your bullshit.
-Well, I won't be responsible then.
-Don't worry. It's fine.
I need to print this one quickly.
I'll email it to you.
The Wi-Fi's dead.
Just plug it into the PC directly.
Really?
Moses.
-What's for dinner?
-Just order something from NetFood.
Pick anything. It's on me.
Satay maybe?
Udiarti.
Rama.
How's it going? Find anything?
Only four guys came today.
There are 40 theater members.
Are you sure everyone will come?
-When will you ever find out?
-Shut up.
Starting tomorrow, would you consider
hacking non-theater students?
-Maybe it'll help.
-Yeah, right.
You wanna stalk people, you creep?
Or steal theses?
Just trying to help here.
I've stopped selling theses.
I'm not a sinner anymore.
I don't want any dirty money.
It's you who's a stalker now.
I'm only looking
at photos from the party.
Then why are you
looking at their old photos?
Hi.
You got booze?
-Still have some?
-No, I don't.
-Why don't you go home?
-Mmm. Home is a shitshow.
-I'm coming in.
-Stop. I have to work.
You have a girl over?
Yes, it's Amelia.
So Amelia wears shoes now?
Shut up. They're my sister's.
Sister, my ass.
Poor Amelia, she'll get jealous.
Just go to the canteen!
Go to your boy toy.
Don't tell me what to do.
Why are you acting so busy?
You let me hang out here all the time.
Hey.
Your friend yesterday, what's her name?
-Sur?
-Mmm.
How did she get so wasted like that?
No idea. I went home earlier.
How did she get home?
You weren't keeping her safe?
NetCar.
That was awful!
You let her go alone in a NetCar?
What's wrong with that?
She got home in one piece.
What's your problem?
Crazy!
Those idiots!
Can't even use their head.
Okay, Ms. Anggun, how can I help you?
I ordered a NetCar for my friend,
but I noticed the car arrived
at the destination so late.
It arrived an hour later than expected.
I'm afraid something
happened to my friend.
Um…
Did you experience any
unpleasant treatment from the driver?
Or did you lose anything?
I'm not sure. That's why we need to check.
Mmm…
-So were you the passenger?
-That's right.
Okay, then. Did you lose anything or…
That's why I'm not sure,
because I was asleep during the trip.
Can we just check it now?
-The computer's getting hot.
-All right, Miss.
Queue number 425…
So far,
the car's route was still on track.
Hold on. I need to make a call.
Queue number 430.
Anggun…
Have you ever been so drunk
you passed out?
I have.
But it happened because I skipped dinner.
Did you skip dinner that night?
No, I didn't.
Hmm.
Maybe it was your first time drinking?
But, Sur,
if you want to
share anything, I'll listen.
Do you feel like something's wrong?
I…
I don't feel any…
-It's just…
-Mmm?
Is it possible
that someone drugged my drinks?
Do you mean our guys?
That's impossible!
I know they are out of bounds
but I'm sure
they would never cross the line.
Silly.
Should I take a urine test?
Sur.
Are you sure?
Some guys were smoking weed at the party.
Did you take some?
Queue number 430.
-I don't remember.
-Hey.
Suppose you take that urine test
and it comes back positive?
Go on. Move it, sir! This is her.
Yes, she…
I drove her the other night, sir.
Well, if that's true, now explain.
How did you arrive
at the destination so late?
Well, yesterday I had
to stop at Kendil Park.
I had a flat tire.
And I had to change it.
I actually tried to wake her up.
But she wouldn't wake up.
So I continued to change the tire.
And, indeed, it took a while,
because I was alone, and it was raining.
Here. I took some pictures.
Take a look.
Can I take some photos, sir?
Oh. Yes, certainly. No problem.
I think I drove through
the nail traps on the road.
Did you change the tire
all by yourself? No one helped?
No, sir. I did it by myself.
And I'm sorry, Miss.
I had to help you walk home.
But when I was helping you out of the car,
you threw up.
It was all over the backseat
and my carpets.
Mmm. Really? Throwing up all over the car?
-Someone's been partying hard.
-We're good, sir.
That's it? Very well then.
However, Miss,
Mr. Burhan here is a good man.
The driver can actually
file the same complaint
if their customers
behaved inappropriately.
But he didn't.
Mmm-hmm. Shut up!
Uh, Anggun…
One more thing.
Hold on, Sur.
I need to take this.
Yeah.
I'm in the parking lot. Why?
Sprained ankle?
Have you called the doctor?
Why did you call me?
Hurry up and make the call!
Sorry. Come again?
No, just… Sorry for all the trouble.
-And thanks for the gelato.
-Anytime, Sur.
Promise to call me if you need anything.
I need to check on Tariq. What a crybaby.
-Take care.
-Thank you.
Dinner time, fishy-fishy.
Did you get the Medusa video?
Yes, Fouad and Gabriella were here.
-Did you steal any theses?
-Why can't you trust me?
I've been running up and down
all day long for you!
Come on! Anyone who catches
Medusa's gaze must drink again!
Who's next?
Okay. This can prove that
he intentionally aimed the Medusa at me.
-Any other videos?
-I think so. Just check again.
Chug! Chug! Chug!
See that?
He took the glass with a different color!
Damn! I knew it was him!
Sur! What's wrong with you?
-Are you okay?
-It's my low blood pressure.
From Gabriella's video,
I found out where Tariq was
before he came out with the Medusa.
From this dark room.
What was he doing
in that room for so long?
When is this gonna end, Sur?
You're broke.
I can't back you up forever.
-When will you go home?
-I don't want to go home.
-But at least if you go home, you--
-I said I don't want to!
I've sorted these files.
There are three theses here.
I'll help you sell them.
Hey, man.
I thought you were retired.
How many customers today?
Just three.
Shit. He's early.
-Adrian from downtown?
-Yes.
-Russian Literature thesis?
-Yes, correct.
Hey.
-Here you go.
-Wait.
Thanks.
Your cut.
So Amin's not here?
Yes, he's delivering documents.
He'll be back in half an hour.
I brought
this beef-nutmeg soup
and some money for my daughter.
Mmm.
She is Amin's friend.
-Her name?
-Sur. Suryani.
-Do you know her?
-Yes, I know her.
May I borrow your phone?
One-one-nine.
No answer, ma'am.
Let me know
if you hear anything.
-Here, save my number.
-Okay.
-Thanks, dear.
-You're welcome.
Why does he listen to this trash?
Your soup is downstairs.
These are what I've found so far.
These are last year's photos.
Mata Hari was holding
an illegal initiation.
Is there any photo that shows
you were part of that initiation?
Hold on, sir.
Can you see Tariq putting
the drug into his pocket, sir?
He suspiciously locked himself up
in this room for an hour,
and suddenly he brought these drinks out,
then set me up to drink it.
What if he'd drugged my drink, sir?
Because I passed out shortly afterward.
Well, this is
a serious accusation, Suryani.
But on top of everything,
your case is about the selfies.
Now where is the evidence
that your selfies were fabricated?
I'm still looking
for more evidence, sir.
If the faculty can help--
I know,
but if you can't show me real evidence,
I can't process anything. Hmm?
Such initiations are indeed
illegal on this campus.
I'll talk to the dean
of the Faculty of Arts &amp; Culture.
But for your case,
you'll need to find real evidence.
Now, I don't see any.
Off you go.
Attention,
ladies and gentlemen!
To control the dengue fever
outbreak in Indonesia,
the government is providing
free fumigation in this area.
Please remain inside your house
until the fumigation is finished.
We will get rid of Aedes mosquitoes
from your houses.
To stop the outbreak,
always take precautions.
I didn't share any photos!
Bullshit! Those were
last year's initiation photos
and you were the photographer!
But I never showed them to the dean!
Because of your photos,
the dean cancelled our Kyoto funds!
Why do you hold grudges against us?
-Just admit it.
-It's not me, you asshole!
I don't care if you get wasted
all the time, but don't drag us along!
Go drink with your boy toys!
But I lost my scholarship
because of the initiation!
Stay out of this!
Huh?
Tariq! Stop! Stop it!
We're fine. We are still going to Kyoto.
I told them that was not an initiation,
but that it was
part of our acting training.
But why did she have to leak those photos?
-It wasn't me, asshole!
-It wasn't Farah, you idiot!
Stop accusing her!
-Who then?
-The dean didn't tell me shit!
What's done is done!
Now we must regain our focus. You get it?
Farah, I'm really sorry.
We didn't mean to accuse you…
Farah!
Enough! Back to rehearsal.
-Wait.
-For God's sake.
What did you mean?
Losing your scholarship
because of the initiation?
Huh?
You drugged my drink, right?
What do you mean?
Tariq!
Come here! Stop hiding!
Medusa is coming!
What did you put in her drink?
Why did you give her the glass
with a different color?
What do you mean?
Why did that drink make her pass out?
-Where did you get these videos?
-From everyone's social media.
I saw you put some drugs into your pocket.
What was it?
Answer her!
Well, that's… That's…
Why would I drug her drink?
But then why did you
lock yourself up in here?
-I swear I didn't put anything!
-Stop! Enough!
Let's go check the CCTV at my house
and put an end to this.
Please, Rama.
It's 14 days before we go to Kyoto!
-I need to ship our installations!
-We don't keep any secrets here.
If you actually didn't do anything,
why are you so reluctant
to check the CCTV? Huh?
Go check it yourself!
I have to organize the shipping now!
I don't care!
I want everyone to come tonight!
So there won't be
any mistrust among us! Got it?
Damn!
Just grab any drink you want.
Okay, let's go to the night of the party.
Fast-forward until Sur
got the shot from Tariq.
Rewind a bit.
Just switch
to that dark room now!
Switch to the pantry cam.
Zoom it.
See if he put in any drugs.
No drugs.
No drugs. Just the whiskey.
Rewind again, Rama.
Why did he stay there for so long?
Here.
Drugs from my therapist.
Why do you all keep torturing me? Huh?
I always serve you, you, you!
If you all need something,
who's been helping you?
Who have you been whining to? Huh?
-And now my privacy--
-Okay.
We're sorry we didn't know
you've been under so much pressure.
All this happened because
you never shared anything with us.
I… I thought I knew you.
I didn't know that you've been
taking all of these medications.
We are your family, your safe place.
You can tell us anything.
Guys,
let's give Tariq a big Mata Hari hug.
What are you doing?
I am sick of you all!
I always have to look okay, always fine.
Everything has to be treated
as if we're family.
Just let me do my work and leave me alone!
-No, that's not how it works.
-You too, Anggun?
How long have we been working together?
How long have you known me?
How could you accuse me?
Just so you know,
we lost one working day by coming here!
Just to deal with a bullshit accusation
by a new kid
who doesn't believe she got wasted!
It's only two weeks before we go to Kyoto!
And after this,
who must clean this mess? Me, right?
You complain about shit
and who do you blame? Me!
"Tariq, do this! Tariq, do that!"
That's bullshit!
Family? What a fake family!
Damn!
Riq…
Let him go.
Okay, then…
Sur.
It's clear now.
Tariq didn't put drugs in your drink.
Okay, look.
Sur said someone fabricated her selfies.
-Let's fast-forward to check that.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Thirsty, Sur?
Slow it down, Rama.
Pause it.
For God's sake.
Why do you do this?
Why blame others
if it's your own doing?
Let's fast-forward until
Sur goes home, so it's clear.
Pause it. I took your wallet,
to see your address,
to order you a NetCar.
Just zoom it. That's not a phone, right?
Nobody touched your phone.
Yes.
Tariq went home.
Sur went home.
Jesslyn, Abu, Kirana went home.
After everyone went home, I took off
to take photos of the Milky Way,
for the installation sets' revision.
How is it, Sur?
Satisfied?
Brother…
Can I check one more time?
-I want to take notes, just to be sure.
-Come on, Sur.
Why so serious, guys?
My oxtail soup is ready.
Let's eat!
Yes, Uncle.
Come on, while it's still hot.
Here, Sur.
Do you know how to operate this?
Yes.
What a mess!
Why aren't you eating?
Here.
So you won't pass out.
Thank you, Uncle.
My husband is so pushy, isn't he?
Auntie.
Everyone who has finished eating,
please go back to campus.
I heard
about your faculty, Sur.
I can't believe you lost the scholarship
over some selfies.
Can't you appeal the decision?
Uh, I was told that I violated
the moral clause in the requirements.
What?
How do they measure someone's morality?
If I may ask you,
how much is your tuition?
4 million Rupiah.
And what semester are you in now?
I still have six more semesters.
This is only my first year.
Six semesters. Six times four million.
-It's around 24 million, right?
-Mmm.
I'll help you pay your tuition.
But next week,
I expect you
to start working on our website.
You'll still get paid, of course.
How does that sound?
I'm sorry, Uncle.
I don't want to trouble you.
You're a bright student.
Losing your scholarship
because of drinking is nonsense!
Uncle, Auntie, we're leaving.
We're ordering a NetCar.
No, please. Hold on. Rama!
-We're fine, Uncle.
-Drive them home, Rama.
It's hard to get a NetCar from here.
Last time was easy, Auntie.
Really? It usually
takes hours to get them.
This house is too far from the main road.
There are not many
NetCar drivers around this area.
Please,
let Rama drive you home.
Let it go, Sur.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Don't overthink it.
You've got money
from Rama's dad to pay your tuition.
You can relax now.
From the CCTV records, I've counted
how many drinks I had before I passed out.
How many?
Four.
Can you actually pass out
after drinking four drinks?
I think I have to try drinking again.
If I don't pass out after four drinks,
then someone must've
drugged my drinks that night.
Slow down, Sur.
Don't gulp it down like that.
I don't feel anything.
Lighting and ambience are important.
I'll set it up like Rama's party.
Sur.
It'd be nice to see the sea now.
I miss the sea.
Look…
I've had three more shots.
I'm still not feeling anything.
Try dancing along, Sur. Come on!
Get up.
I'm still sober.
Brands matter, you know.
Rama's drinks were all imported brands.
I'll drink more then.
I can change the music
if you don't like it.
Check this out, Sur.
In West Sumatra,
there's a photocopier monument!
Ooh.
I think I drank too much.
My face must be red!
No, don't use a mirror!
Use Amelia instead.
Go on!
Come on!
Your face!
Look at yours!
-Try your armpit!
-Really?
Foot! Your foot!
What the hell?
Just like Mata Hari's installation sets.
Only one portion?
My friend said she's not hungry.
If the car stopped here,
it might have run over the nail trap
on the previous block.
Is there a tire shop
near here that opens at night?
I'm not sure, man.
I'm only open in the morning.
What are you staring at?
I thought this was
the statue Rama's dad made?
It's not?
The signature on this is different.
But I've seen this statue before.
This photo was in Rama's inbox.
Someone must've sent this photo of
Kendil Park's statue to Rama that night.
But why?
Are you sure it's not one
of the statues at Rama's house?
This one's clearly different.
Not one of his dad's.
Did Rama go to Kendil Park that night?
Why would he go there at night?
He said he went in his car after the party
to photograph the Milky Way
for the installation.
We can't get a hold of him.
You guys should stop depending on Tariq!
So although Tariq
still hasn't joined us today,
I still expect you guys
to do your work well, okay?
Cross-check everything!
Yes, Sur.
What if we create
an official email for Mata Hari?
So on Anggun's business card, for example,
we can write anggun@matahari.com.
-How long will it take?
-Not long.
I'll send a link to everyone.
You type in your existing email
and sign up for the new one.
Fine. All department heads,
do what Sur just said.
Now let's go. Don't waste any more time.
Let's go.
-Samsul?
-Huh?
Rama said he modified the installation.
The Milky Way one.
Yes. Why?
Can I take a look?
You're too late. They're already packed.
The van will take them soon.
What do you need them for?
I want to take pictures of them.
For our website.
Oh. I'll just send you the raw files
that Rama sent me.
Before they were printed on the lightbox.
-Do you have them?
-Of course. I printed them.
I'll send you the link later.
Got loads to do now.
-Okay. Thanks a lot.
-Sure.
Your show's video is uploaded.
When you went home from the party,
was it raining?
Yes, it was. Soon after I left.
And I think it was raining
all over the city that night.
I'm buying some cigarettes.
You need anything?
Why did you close the door?
Okay.
Look this way.
Tilt your head up a bit.
If you can get
their passwords this easily,
why didn't you do this earlier?
It's not that easy.
We still need their login approval.
Wouldn't he be able to find out
if his email was being hacked?
That's why I need your help.
Lure him to print something in here.
So when he's logged in
with the computer downstairs,
I'll also log in
to his email from this laptop.
He won't realize
there are two devices logging in,
and he'll approve them both.
Are you sure about this?
Doing this shit again?
His dad's gonna help pay your tuition.
What if you're wrong again?
And you get caught?
I mean, what's wrong
if Rama actually went to that park?
Not everyone wants to harm you.
I promise this will be the last time.
Then I'll be out of your hair.
But I need to check his location history.
Sorry, Rama.
The script I was supposed
to print was accidentally deleted.
How come?
When I was removing
files from the computer,
your script also got deleted.
You can access your email now.
The Wi-Fi is fixed.
Okay.
-Done. Should I also print it now?
-No need.
-Shit!
-I'll take care of it.
You haven't paid your electricity bill?
I forgot.
Oh, well.
I've downloaded the files.
Just check the download folder, and…
Please log out of my email later.
I haven't logged it out yet.
Yes, I'll do that.
So what about the fish?
Uh, I still have some.
I have the red one. Do you want it?
Not that fish.
The fish in the drawer.
What do you mean?
Come on, Amin.
I need them.
I've been stressing out lately.
Lack of inspiration.
You know,
the fish in the drawer inspire me.
Let me know if you have new fish.
Sur, Rama left. Turn the lights on…
Open the drawer,
or I'll spread this photo
of you selling theses.
What the hell, Sur?
What's wrong with you? Huh?
What are you hiding in the drawer?
Drugs?
No! What the hell?
Then open it!
Or I'm sending this photo
to the dean, so you'll get fired.
Open it!
Yes, be patient!
-Do you see any drugs?
-What's this?
That's my hard drive!
What was Rama talking about?
You ungrateful piece of shit.
I was back to selling theses
just to help you.
Damn, Sur! What are you doing?
Why did you steal the data?
What are they for?
Sur… Sur!
Early this year, my sister got sick.
Dengue fever.
She was hospitalized. I needed money.
Rama came to me and asked me
to steal the students' data.
500K for every student,
but that's all!
I checked all the photos, Sur!
I make sure there are no nudes
or anything like that.
They are just normal daily photos!
Rama only needs them for inspiration.
That's all.
And you see the result,
you guys won the competition!
-You're going to Kyoto!
-Bastard!
I did nothing wrong, Sur!
Eight hours, please.
14,000 per hour.
KENDIL PARK
Did you have anything to eat?
I'll order for you.
I'm good, thank you.
Two iced teas
and another plate of noodles, please.
Coming.
Why are you hiding from your mother?
Did you run away?
Got some problems.
Your scholarship?
Earlier, you said you lost it
because of the initiation?
-Actually, I want to--
-I've told you from the get-go.
You shouldn't have joined them.
It's better to focus on your studies.
I actually
have something to ask you.
Did you ever model for Mata Hari?
What do you mean?
Is this your tattoo?
-What made you think that?
-But it is, isn't it?
Where did you get that photo?
Mine's here too.
This is a photo of my back.
Answer me. Where did you
get those photos from?
Have you been hacking me?
You leaked those
initiation photos, didn't you? Huh?
But this is your tattoo, right?
If it's really yours, we must report this
to the ethics board now.
Stop it. No use.
If we testify together,
we'll have strong evidence.
Please help me. Let's report this now.
Stop!
I'd like to submit this evidence.
Photos of Rama's installation.
The photos of my back.
And the metadata of those photos showing
that these photos were taken at 2:00 a.m.
The same time
that my NetCar stopped at the park.
Mmm.
Are you 100% sure
that these are photos of your back?
If you have more evidence,
it could be useful for our investigation.
-That's all, sir.
-All right then.
I will form a team for this investigation.
I'll call some of the university's
administrators to help us out.
Do you have any digital files
of this physical evidence?
Yes, sir.
-I'll send them to you.
-Okay.
Sir, could you keep
my identity confidential?
Yes. Of course.
It's part of our procedure.
To keep your identity in confidence
during the investigation.
Hello?
These documents, did you make them?
-Hmm?
-Rama Soemarno just called us.
He's on the way here with his lawyer.
He wants to report you
to the police for defamation.
Wait, what is this about, sir?
These documents you made
have gone viral in our campus.
That's why Rama
will file a lawsuit against you.
Sir, I never made them go viral!
I gave them
to the ethics board for investigation.
They should be held responsible for this!
Yes, yes.
But still, you're the one
who prepared these documents.
And listen,
I don't want the university to get dragged
into this case if this goes to court.
Our faculty is going to send
Mata Hari off to Japan soon.
We don't want this case
to jeopardize that.
I've also talked to Rama
to try to amicably resolve this issue.
Sir, please listen to me!
Sir.
Please forgive my daughter.
She makes mistakes. Please forgive her.
Please, take a seat first.
Please, sir.
Sir…
Let's just settle this here.
My daughter is out of line.
I'll punish her myself.
Sir, take a seat.
Let us explain everything first.
I never made those documents go viral!
I submitted them
to the ethics board for investigation!
If they've gone viral, it's their fault!
Miss, calm down.
You prepared those documents
and shared them with people.
Now Rama Soemarno is being
labelled as a rapist, a creep, a pervert!
She's ruined my client's reputation.
And you tried
to hack into my client's phone.
Everything you've done is against the law!
I have evidence.
-Please, forgive my daughter.
-Stop saying sorry!
See this photo?
This photo was used
for Mata Hari's installation sets.
It was taken at 2:00 a.m.,
when my NetCar stopped at the park.
And it's a photo of my back!
Sur, watch your mouth!
Sir, please.
Calm down.
Sur.
That's not your back.
I want to investigate these photos!
Let's take these photos
to the forensics team.
And we can check
the other installation photos.
These were taken without my consent.
I know you are still upset
that you lost your scholarship.
-It's true, I took the photos at 2:00 a.m.
-Please. Let me take care of this.
But if you want to know the truth,
I took pictures of the stars.
Those are the night skies. The Milky Way.
What's your proof?
It was raining all over Jakarta.
No way you could take those pictures!
Sur.
Weren't you drunk that night?
Or are you still hallucinating now?
That's why I need help
to investigate this, sir!
All right then.
If Sur still insists,
let's take this to court.
And if we go to court, Sur,
you will face everyone
mentioned in those documents.
-Including the NetCar driver.
-Sir.
Please, if possible,
let's settle this problem internally.
-Please, I'm begging you…
-Dad, stop it!
-Why are you on your knees?
-Shut up!
Shut up!
You've made mistakes,
and now you want to make another one?
Sir, please.
Stand up.
What I need is nothing more
than a clarification.
-Rama, please.
-Let me speak.
In the Mata Hari family,
we always support each other.
Rama, please let me take it from here.
And we still consider Sur
as a part of our theater family.
We prefer to solve
this issue like a family.
Moreover, we're currently busy
preparing a show for Kyoto.
That's why I just want Sur
to make a public apology
and clarification.
Then tomorrow,
we can go back to being
a family again in the theater.
Sir, ma'am.
Regarding Sur's scholarship,
my father has agreed to pay
for Sur's tuition until she graduates.
Also, she can still work for my father.
And receive her salary.
I want to proceed with the case!
Suryani, enough!
I, Suryani,
would like to apologize to Rama Soemarno
for making false accusations.
And if all my allegations,
or hypothesis,
have damaged Rama Soemarno's reputation,
and that of other parties,
I would like to clarify
that all of them were not true.
I deeply apologize
and I promise
that I won't do such things anymore.
Rama Soemarno's family and I
have agreed
to settle this case amicably,
outside the court.
I, Suryani, would like to apologize
to Rama Soemarno
for making false accusations.
And if all my allegations, or hypothesis…
Mom? Where are we going?
What's going on, Mom?
You're my daughter.
My daughter.
When you were holding
those photos earlier,
I knew for certain,
it was the birthmark on your back.
Sur.
Tell me.
What happened, actually?
It's been a week.
Yes.
So unobtainable?
Yati, Sur.
I just called the lab.
It's unlikely that they'll find
any trace of sedative in your urine.
Because it's already more than three days.
At the time,
I was scared to do the urine test.
There were drugs at the party.
The lab would never
disclose your test result.
So you wouldn't need to worry about that.
But if you and Sur
would like to stay here first,
while gathering more evidence,
you're very welcome.
Sur.
You stay here.
It's useless to be with your dad.
What about you, Mom?
I have to go home.
Who's going to run the diner?
He doesn't have
the right to kick me out anyway.
If anything happens, call me right away.
Siti, please take care of my daughter.
-I'm leaving you some money, just in case.
-Don't worry, Yati.
-I'll call some friends to help us.
-Hello.
Sur.
Those are my tattoos.
I'm sorry I didn't help you earlier.
I brought someone here.
His body was
in Rama's installation sets as well.
After my mother died,
my therapist told me
to do activities to distract myself.
Thank you, Miss Siti.
That bastard was like family to me.
I've never showed this scar to anyone.
That bastard must have taken a picture
of it when I got wasted.
And I was in denial because
I was afraid of losing a family.
Rama was the one
who invited me in to join Mata Hari.
The activities helped me
to get over an abusive relationship.
I went to Mata Hari's party as well.
I was their photographer.
I enjoy drinking.
But that night, I felt dizzier than usual.
After only two glasses.
I should've completely blacked out
if he'd drugged me.
But my drinking habit might have
made me more resistant to sedatives.
And I remember…
I was taken into a car,
and I saw someone approaching.
My clothes were stripped slowly…
then I heard camera shutters.
I wrote everything here.
Why didn't you ever
tell anyone about this?
I did.
They told me
it was all in a drunkard's head.
That what I heard
was the sound of bottles clinking.
"Wasn't it normal for you
to get laid after drinking?"
They told me that I was making things up.
And I decided to leave Mata Hari.
At that time, you…
And Tariq…
Did you guys go home in a NetCar?
I was told that I did.
Did you remember the driver or the car?
I didn't.
I didn't even know who booked the car.
-I have a picture of my NetCar.
-Let me see.
Here.
No. I don't remember anything.
Stop. Zoom in.
Komodo Parking Lot.
Do you think this NetCar
is somehow related to Rama?
Since Rama's house is far
and it's hard to get a NetCar there.
You mean a fake NetCar?
No, because the driver was from
NetCar, it made Rama seem innocent.
That driver could've been asked
to stand by near Rama's house.
So if a booking was made,
he'd get the order.
So far, I have these pictures
of Kendil Park's statue from Rama's inbox.
But I don't know who sent them to him.
The only way we can find more evidence
is by checking the driver's phone.
But you met him in the NetCar office.
What if he remembers you?
He might go and tell Rama.
I'll go.
I think nobody ordered me
a NetCar whenever I got drunk.
Are you sure?
Thank you, Miss Siti.
Feeling sleepy?
Go have some coffee.
How was your day, little one?
Ah. I'll go get some rest first.
Excuse me.
Burhan!
-Burhan?
-Mmm?
Ah. Good afternoon, sir.
I'm from the Mata Hari theater group,
Rama Soemarno sent me
to give this parcel to Mr. Burhan.
Are you sure it's the right address?
This is Komodo Street, right?
Oh-ho. Komodo is up there, not here.
Let me see the address.
There's no address written here.
Rama told me to go to Komodo Street
to give this to Mr. Burhan.
So I asked people around here,
where Mr. Burhan lives,
and they told me to come here.
Our group just won a theater competition.
And we'd like to deliver
gifts to our friends.
I see.
Thank you.
Sorry, ma'am.
May I borrow a charger for my phone?
My phone's dead and I need
to order a car to go home.
Didn't you drive here?
No, I…
My friends dropped me off
and went to deliver other parcels.
Where are you going?
Further south.
I can take
an offline order, if you want.
That'd be great, sir.
I can pay you with cash.
Okay.
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Bye.
Uh, sir, may I use your phone?
I need to call a friend.
My battery is too low.
I can't take an order if my phone's dead.
And I left the charger at home.
This looks bad.
May I use your phone
to call a nearby repair shop?
Don't worry.
NetCar Center can help us out.
NetCar's office is far, sir.
An hour from here. I'm in a rush.
This will do, sir.
I'll just call the mechanic,
no new tire needed.
Let me use your phone.
Well, let's just change it together now.
Can you help me lift this tire?
You said you could
change a tire by yourself.
Tariq?
What did you do to him?
What did you guys do to him?
Please watch him, ma'am.
We have to take this man to the police.
We must act quickly.
He texted Rama already.
Mr. Burhan, I'm done.
The mechanic is on the way here.
After you change the tire,
take Sur home immediately.
Yes, understood.
Okay.
So in this phone,
there are eight videos
he secretly recorded.
A video of you, Farah.
Of Tariq.
Of me, and five other girls.
It all happened in his car.
No, it could be more.
It might've happened
to everyone you saw in Amin's hard drive.
You call every victim in the video
and tell them to come here.
We'll go to the police.
And don't forget Burhan's car.
We'll bring it along as evidence.
The police?
Our videos would just go viral!
Sur, haven't you learned anything? Huh?
Didn't you see how rich Rama's dad is?
You stole data from people, Sur.
You hacked them.
We beat up and abducted that driver!
We'd all go to jail!
Then why didn't you follow the plan?
Beating him up like that.
We're not alone now.
If we do this together,
our evidence is strong.
What if we still lose?
And those videos go viral?
Our naked bodies will be out there
for people to see forever!
And the campus?
They'll certainly back the bastard up!
And see what our friends did!
They shared our videos
instead of helping us!
I've been holding this back for months.
It'll be even worse
to see that bastard walking free.
To see him every day!
Attention,
ladies and gentlemen!
To control the dengue fever
outbreak in Indonesia,
the government is providing
free fumigation in this area.
Please remain inside your house
until the fumigation is finished.
We will get rid of Aedes mosquitoes
from your house.
To stop the outbreak,
always remember to take precautions, DCB.
To drain, to cover, to bury!
Until this foolish satyr appears,
and ruins everything.
All because he can't
restrain his earthly lust.
This Pandora's box
holds unspeakable evils.
Perseus must banish it.
Attention,
ladies and gentlemen!
To control the dengue fever
outbreak in Indonesia,
the government is providing
free fumigation in this area.
Please remain inside your house
until the fumigation is finished.
We will get rid of Aedes mosquitoes
from your house.
To stop the outbreak,
always remember to take precautions, DCB.
To drain, to cover, to bury!
Attention, ladies and gentlemen!
To control the dengue fever
outbreak in Indonesia,
the government is providing
free fumigation in this area.
Please remain inside your house
until the fumigation is finished.
'Tis nothing but a beautiful dream.
Would any mortal
believe in your dream?
Those mortals will turn into statues
silenced by your deadly gaze.
For you are cursed…
to be Medusa herself.
Attention, ladies and gentlemen!
To control the dengue fever
outbreak in Indonesia,
the government is providing
free fumigation in this area.
Please remain inside your house
until the fumigation is finished.
We will get rid of Aedes mosquitoes
from your house.
To stop the outbreak,
always remember to take precautions, DCB.
To drain, to cover, to bury!
Tariq, Farah, take this medicine.
-Thank you, Miss Siti.
-Use the eyedrops.
This is
all the evidence we have left.
The rest is nothing but stories.
Do you think
they're going to believe us?
The tattoo on your back,
what does it mean?
"Even in the darkest hour,
I decided to carry on working."