Good evening.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You okay?
They didn't even let you clean up?
Sorry guys, can you get us some…
Actually you know what?
Do you mind if we do this first?
It‘s not going to take long, you know?
Then we can let you get out of here.
I'll take that as a yes.
Hungry?
Thirsty?
So, let's see.
Your section went out there to
locate some AWOL soldiers.
And now those soldiers
from your section are missing.
What happened?
You know,
there are some people out there
who believe that you are responsible.
They want to make this your screw up.
Listen,
I'm your only friend.
Trust me.
Hello.
Yes, sir.
Okay, I'll be right in.
Can I just know what the…
There you are.
I've been here all along.
I want to ask you a question.
When you called me up
and said "Come back to town,
"because there's a big family emergency,"
was it really because it was an AGM?
Because now that I'm back in this country,
the Army knows I'm back,
and they want me to do
a two-week reservist.
I'm not too happy about it.
So? It's just two weeks.
If you can't survive that,
how are you going to take over
Heng Technologies from me one day?
I don't want to take over
Heng Technologies from you one day.
Do I want your money?
Do I take your money?
Listen,
you can stop hiding in London,
stop running away
from your responsibilities.
Now come over and join us.
Sorry about that.
To the Army.
History teaches us many, many, many,
many, many great things.
But the problem is,
are we willing to learn?
And you.
Twice in a week,
still never learn your lesson.
Now if you want this back…
Sir, class is already over.
James, I thought this was our weekend.
My name's Alvin,
and just one call
and then no distractions, alright?
Hello?
Yeah.
Yup.
I'm busy, okay?
Who's that?
My wife.
So, do you want to buy this flat?
Okay, James.
Alvin!
What's this?
They won't suspect anything.
That's right.
Been a long time, June.
How's playing soldier
been working out for you?
I see you're in good form. You look great.
Sir, I wouldn't sweat it.
I hear she likes the strong,
silent, ugly type?
Sort of like, you know, Benicio del Toro.
So…
I don't have a chance?
But Rajah does.
What's so funny?
I don’t know.
You laughed so I laughed.
It's good to be back.
Not.
Corporal.
Alright.
Welcome to Pulau Hantu.
Home of insects, reptiles, coconut trees…
and AWOL soldiers.
AWOL?
No wonder they were
so secretive about the mission.
Three soldiers presumed AWOL in this area.
HQ hasn't heard from them in two days.
Charlie Company Second Infantry Battalion,
Section Seven.
Lieutenant Terence Teo,
Lance Corporal William DeSouza,
and Corporal Suppaiah.
Why would anyone go AWOL?
It's not like we're at war, right?
Now Singapore Army is very simple
yet they want to go AWOL.
Horrible.
Last time my army days
were really difficult, you know?
I had to iron my number
three uniform every day,
polish the boots until they were shiny,
even the vegetables had stones in them.
Wow. Many, many words.
These men are armed with live rounds.
Sir,
I have checked already.
This island has no humans
but has a lot of mosquitoes.
Alright guys,
we rendezvous back here
at two o'clock with Sgt. Han.
Yes, sir.
It’s 1400 hours. Not two o’clock, sir.
Two a.m. or 2 p.m. What do you all want?
Two p.m., sir.
2pm sounds good.
Raj,
Alvin, Frankie.
That way.
Hadi, follow me.
Wait, wait.
Hey.
How come I have to shave my head
and this Lt. Heng
can have hair like a girl?
You rich?
Nope.
You got connections?
No.
You mean Daddy didn't save you from
going to reservist for 12 years?
Hell, no.
Which is why you look like G.I. Jane
and that clown looks like Malibu Barbie.
That's not fair.
He’s fair what.
Last time his skin was dark.
Now it's very white,
like a Caucasian.
He talks with a slang too.
Better than that woman
who pretends to be like a soldier.
I think if she sees a lizard…
Mummy, daddy!
Up, up. Hey, let's go!
You done?
Yeah.
Wow.
Rajah,
you normally don't talk
but when you do, there's power.
Steady, Rajah.
Soldier, on your feet!
There are oil refineries right here.
Major shipping lines.
These guys are a security threat.
June.
Chill.
Sergeant?
Are we good?
Is there anything else?
Are we fine?
Because if we are, can we please move?
Because I don't feel good…
Why? You're scared?
Guys,
this place is called
Pulau Hantu for a reason.
Pulau Hantu.
"Hantu" is ghost in Malay.
Look, there aren't
any ghosts on this island.
-It's just a name.
-How do you know?
Because my company
just had a barbecue here.
Cheap bastards couldn't even afford
to pay for a proper restaurant.
There are two innocent spirits
on this island.
A mother and a daughter seeking revenge.
How come every forest we go to,
you have to come up
with another ghost story?
Alvin,
my father's batch, some 40 years ago,
they heard the same story.
Two NS men went missing
somewhere near this island.
Okay, I also heard the same story.
They never found those guys, right?
Alright.
There's nothing here. Alright?
We're done. Let's go.
Sir, I love it that you're back.
Kiss my ass over a beer later.
It's just a scratch.
Permission to fire, sir!
What do we do, sir?
Sir!
Load and ready!
Alvin, Frankie. Left.
Rajah, cover me.
Go, go, go!
Why are they shooting?
Sir, you're bleeding.
-Do you need help?
-Shut up and stay alert.
They could be anywhere.
You guys covered this area.
You didn't see them?
We checked.
Kind of…
Let's go.
Hey,
hey!
It's safer here.
Don't try to be a hero.
I said let's go!
Hey!
Why?
What did you see?
Don't be scared.
It's only a mountain chicken.
What's this?
Guys!
Guys, please.
Do not touch anything!
This is a burial site.
Please respect this place.
Don't get distracted. Let's move.
Looks like this must be what the
AWOL soldiers were after.
Yo.
Why did you bring that?
Think we're going on parade, is it?
Alvin,
this emblem here,
this one,
it's been blessed by
seven different religions.
It's for protection.
Who knows?
It may just save our lives.
Understand?
Frankie, Frankie.
Frankie, please.
Frankie, please don't take anything
that doesn't belong to you,
Frankie please.
This is a ritual,
where the more evil the spirits,
the more things they put to cover.
Rajah,
how to say ghost in Hokkien?
"Gui."
Frankie, this one got…
Downstairs got "ghost".
This one put to cover the "ghost" from…
You are the "ghost" right?
Sir,
help me, sir.
Help me on this.
DeSouza, Teo and Suppaiah
could be anywhere.
Stay alert.
Believe me or don't believe me,
I don't care.
But the spirits here are innocent.
If we don't disturb them--
Hadi, drop it!
This must mean something.
Of course it means something.
The question is, what?
Please stop.
No more.
Corporal DeSouza,
-Corporal DeSouza! Do you hear me?
-I'm sorry.
-Stand down.
I said stand down!
You're already in a lot of trouble.
Don't make things worse!
He could be leading us to a trap.
Waiting for an invitation?
Come on.
We are all going to die!
Relax, relax.
Give me my gun.
I give you this one to protect yourself.
It won't protect you.
Nothing will.
We're here to help.
We're going to die. Just like my men.
We have a boat, okay?
We're here to get you.
A boat?
Yeah. We have a boat.
We can leave?
Yeah.
I'll kill you!
Frankie!
It's evil.
This place.
You don't know.
You want?
-Want some water?
-Yeah.
What don't I know?
This place.
You don't know this place.
Where's Teo?
Suppaiah? Where are they?
We got to go.
-We got to go now. Now.
-Where's the boat? The boat.
-Relax.
-The boat. We got to go.
The boat!
Come on. We got to go.
-Alright, Frankie.
-Go back.
-Go.
-Hang on, let me pick up my gun.
Wait.
I can sell this for a lot of money.
Shit.
Frankie. Frankie!
What did you do?
He didn't do anything!
We need a medic. Radio Sgt. Han.
Two-niner, two-niner. Acknowledge? Over.
Acknowledge? Over.
Shit. Comms not working.
Shit!
What the hell is going on?
Goddammit.
What's going on?
Check your phones!
No signal!
What the hell is going on?
I'm not staying to find out.
Get Frankie down.
No. We have to leave this place.
Now! Come on, guys.
Now! Leave this place.
Come on!
Wait, wait. Stop!
This is the wrong way.
Shit, something's not right.
Keep moving to shore.
Sir, we're running around blindly.
We need a plan.
The plan is keep moving to shore.
Yeah. Let's go.
Let's get off this island.
How? Where? Which way?
We should hide.
-We're not hiding.
-Hiding from what?
Teo and Suppaiah are still here. Armed.
Woman, is your bra on too tight?
After what's happened,
you're still thinking about those guys?
Shut up before I twist your balls off!
Can you sit? You're making me nervous.
Told you not to touch anything…
Not to touch anything…
You guys think I talk rubbish.
Just don't listen.
You see what happened?
I thought my students are bad.
You guys are worse.
-You know you guys are a…
-Just a storm, bro.
It's just a storm.
-Where are you going?
-Take a dump. You want to help?
-Now?
-You want to go now?
I don't control the flow, bro.
Do you think this is what happened
to those missing soldiers?
Back in the seventies?
You know,
I shouldn't even be here.
I should have gotten
an excuse from reservist.
I should have broken my hand
or maybe even my leg.
You know what?
My wife said that we should go overseas.
She said we should go to…
What the hell man?! Rajah!
Sir,
Teo, Suppaiah, DeSouza are career soldiers
with no disciplinary actions.
So why would they do this?
Who knows and who cares?
Right now,
our best option is to get off this island.
But I don't understand.
Why would they go AWOL?
I don't know.
Maybe they were secretly disgruntled.
Like you.
But at least
I'm not Daddy's little White Horse, sir.
Trust me. I'm anything but a White Horse.
Really?
No 10 kilometer run, no guard duty,
and you still make officer?
Of course you're not a White Horse, sir.
Alvin.
I know it's you, you dumbass.
What the…
Can you stop being immature
and get back to the problem, please?
Don't react.
Listen.
Back, back.
Let's get back.
Where's Rajah?
Shit. They know that we're following them.
Hadi, Rajah. Let's go.
Where'd they go?
What's wrong with you?
He shot himself in the head.
What's that?
You seriously expect me to believe that
they all killed themselves?
Like what? Mass suicide?
And that this guy,
Private Frankie Low.
This big guy impaled himself on a tree?
Look, I know you want
to get out of the army but
is this really the way to do it?
Come on, just give me
the facts without all the drama.
Please.
All AWOL soldiers accounted for.
Can we go now?
You know what?
Shut up.
We should have listened to Hadi.
-He was right all along.
-I said shut up.
How did Suppaiah hang himself?
And what about DeSouza?
Why did he kill himself?
What about Frankie?
Did you ever think about Frankie?
Why don't you ask them
when it happens to you?
You think you're funny, is it?
Alvin, shut up.
He's got a point, you know.
How are we going
to explain this in the report?
Let me worry about that
when we get off this island, sir.
Hey.
What's that sound?
We're lost.
We're walking around in circles.
How long has it been?
My watch is dead.
Feels like five, six hours?
We should be at the shore by now.
We must have gone off course
and taken a turn somewhere.
What?
Did you see that?
There's something there.
I saw someone.
Alvin.
Something.
Don't mess with me, man.
Sir, he's losing it.
Maybe.
How come we didn't see this before?
What do you think, guys?
Who wants to find out what's inside?
You're asking us?
We should go in,
rest and come up with a plan.
Really?
'Cause every bone in my body says
dying out here is better
than dying in there.
Rajah.
Alvin.
No.
I'm staying out here.
Goddammit.
Did you see?
Tell me you guys can hear that.
Say you can hear it!
We're going in.
Hey,
hey.
Are you lost?
Who are you?
And why are you doing this to us?
Alvin, shut up and stop scaring her.
I'm scaring her?
You want some food?
Anybody has rations?
Nope.
Alvin, go get some food.
Yeah, sure.
What do you want? Some hamburgers? Or…
or maybe some nasi lemak?
Maybe some noodles?
How about I go to 7-11
and buy something for everyone?
Am I the only sane one in this bloody hut?
Why don't you shut your mouth
and use your brain instead?
The AWOL soldiers have fullpacks.
Go check.
Are you crazy? I'm not going out there!
Rajah, wait.
Look, this hut wasn't here before.
You really think it's normal to find
a little girl in the middle of nowhere?
Maybe she split up from her parents.
You said people
come here for barbecues, right?
Yeah, but…
Do you think she's not freaked out
by soldiers walking into the hut?
Why are we still even talking about this?
Alvin,
give me your weapon.
Now.
Hadi?
Hadi!
Is that you?
Hadi, quit messing about man.
You're freaking me out.
Where is that idiot?
Where's Hadi?
-June?
-Rajah.
Don't be the hero, June.
I'd give you some,
but it's probably older than you.
I was saving this for later.
But there may not be a later, eh?
Two-niner, this is one-zero.
You acknowledge? Over.
Lt. Heng, this is Sgt. Han.
Do you copy? Over.
One-zero. This is two-niner.
Do you acknowledge? Over.
Sgt. Han!
Sgt. Han! This is Lt. Heng.
This is Lt. Heng.
Do you copy? Over.
Sgt. Han! Sgt. Han!
This is Lt. Heng.
We're still on Pulau Hantu.
We are in need of immediate assistance.
Do you acknowledge? Over!
Dammit.
This isn't happening.
This is not happening.
Rajah.
June!
Rajah!
Hadi!
Alvin?
This is not happening.
Everything okay?
Hadi?
Alvin.
Rajah,
why didn’t you help him?
Why did Alvin kill himself?
Don't be upset.
Kill her
and burn this place to the ground.
Rajah.
Rajah, calm down and stop overreacting.
Calmly, I'm telling you,
we're all gonna die here.
One by one.
What the hell is wrong with you?
This is not what is happening.
This is what?
Don't pretend you know what to do.
We're all dying here.
We're killing her.
That's the only way.
Rajah,
stand down.
June,
I'm trying to save you.
Do you want to die here too?
Leave this place.
Leave!
-Give me your weapon!
-We will end this now.
-We end this now.
Kill the girl and we can end this now.
We end this now.
We end this now!
Sir, we end this now, sir.
-Rajah…
-We end this now.
Maybe she has something to do with this.
Maybe she doesn't.
But we can't kill her.
Lower your weapon, Rajah.
Lower your weapon,
or we all go.
Now do you believe me?
Move out.
Back to the burial site now.
June,
grenade.
Let's go.
Hadi.
Hadi!
They’re all dead.
Rajah?
He was just with us.
He's been here all the time.
Look, he was with us in the hut.
He tried to kill the girl.
He must have been trying to…
save us.
To warn us.
What the hell is going on?
The legend…
The legend was wrong.
I was wrong
about everything.
The bomoh,
the villagers,
they're innocent.
The mother…
She's evil.
And that sign.
It's an evil sign.
And she has it.
Anyone that has the sign,
is evil.
What do you mean?
All this,
around us,
she did this to make us scared.
We'll put everything back,
just as we found them.
No, no.
No negotiating,
no praying.
She's going to kill us off one by one,
till she finds the
perfect body to possess.
And after that,
it's finally over.
We're getting off this island.
Hadi, what?
Soldier!
June,
lower your weapon.
Hadi,
I guarantee you
we will get off this island.
June,
lower your weapon.
Now!
Hadi!
-Dammit!
-Hadi!
Hadi!
Sir, I don't remember this place.
Stay close to me.
He's around here somewhere.
Sir.
June!
Lt. Heng?
Hadi?
What happened, Hadi?
Some…
something pulled me.
Listen to me.
I found the shore.
I found our boat.
We're getting off this island,
Okay?
Let's go. Come on. Let's go.
Hold your fire! June?
Hold your fire!
I saw her. Did you see her?
Who?
I saw her. She was standing right here!
She was standing right here!
June,
look.
Hadi?
Hadi.
Give me your FAD.
Give me your FAD!
Hadi.
I saw the woman,
I shot the woman… I didn't shoot him.
I didn't shoot him!
I didn't shoot him! It's not me.
It's not me!
Hadi! Hadi, I'm sorry.
Hadi, I'm sorry.
Come here.
We have to go, June.
Stick with me on this one.
Hold it together.
We have to go now,
Okay?
It ends now.
Come with me.
Come with me!
June, keep on going.
I found it once, I can find it again.
Should have left a…
Left a trail.
Okay.
Don't give up on me, June.
We will find it.
We will find the boat,
and we'll get off this island,
Okay?
Alright,
you rest.
I'll keep watch.
June, what are you doing?
June.
No, June.
No.
Let's move.
June.
June!
June?
Try them again.
Lt. Heng, acknowledge? Over.
Do you copy? Over.
Sergeant, we looked everywhere.
There's no one here.
You heard him say Pulau Hantu, right?
If this is a bloody joke…
Hold your fire.
Put your weapons down!
Get him. Get him, get him!
Enough!
Enough of this crap about bomohs
and pontianaks and vampires.
We didn't find a single thing
on that island, okay?
There was no blood,
no shell casings, no bodies,
nothing.
-What do you want--
-We've been here all night.
You haven't told me a single truth!
-Sir…
-Just shut up!
You only open your mouth
if you're going to tell me the damn truth!
Now what the hell happened out there?
I told you.
All that shit really happened, okay?
All those people, they killed themselves.
And I killed June.
I admit.
I killed June.
Last chance.
Just you and me.
Give me a proper explanation.
Some things can't be explained, man.
Everything can be explained.
It's just whether
I choose to believe it or not.
You know what?
You're wasting my time,
and you're pathetic.
Call yourself a soldier.
No, I don't.
All I know is,
I come back home,
I get a phone call from your army,
saying that I have to step up
to the plate for two weeks
to fill a pair of boots
I have no interest in filling.
Then you send me off to
some crap-hole island
in search of some
lost AWOL soldiers
that I don't particularly care about,
let alone know.
And right now,
I'm stuck here,
in front of you,
trying to convince you what happened,
when all this time
I'm trying to think to myself
why I'm still alive.
Well done.
Seven soldiers are missing.
Your story is going to go down as folklore
among soldiers who say
they heard it from a friend of a friend.
Go.
You're letting me go?
Yeah, for now.
Your Daddy's outside.
He's surrendered your passport so…
we'll be talking again.
I've told you everything I know.
Yeah, yeah, you killed June
because you were protecting yourself.
Yeah got it.
Let's see what June has to say about that.
She's alive?
And if her story contradicts yours then…
you'll be seeing me again very soon.
Hey,
remember where you are, okay?
Guilty until proven innocent.
Get out of my face.
Sir,
he's sticking to his story.
Yeah, and if June backs it up then…
I’ll just bury the report
with all the others.
Listen, sir…
…just maybe,
there is something to what he's saying.
You alright?
Here's your passport.
You can go back to London.
So Master Sergeant,
are you going to give me
a straight answer?
What happened out there?
Whatever Lt. Heng said is true.
I know we can't explain it,
but it happened.
Alright, just start from the beginning,
okay?
Can I have some water, please?
Go ahead.