What are you looking at?
You're making me blush.
Something wrong?
No, nothing's wrong.
I love you, Tee.
Yes, I know.
You can go now.
Can't I stay?
Tomorrow is the weekend.
No, you can't.
I want to be alone.
Well...
I'll go then,
but I'm coming back tomorrow.
You don't have to.
You don't have to come here anymore.
I'm a guy.
I'm not gay.
Don't ask me why we did this
or bring up what we've done.
It was just sex.
I just wanted to cum.
And I think...
I can do it with anyone.
It doesn't have to be you.
And because you're always around,
I can't have a girlfriend.
All my friends have been asking
what we are.
"Am I gay"?
The fact is, I'm not gay.
Do you understand?
-You don't love me anymore, do you?
-It's not that.
I think...
I never loved you at all.
Asking myself if I'm tired
Asking myself if I'm hurt
Every time I hear that song
The song you used to play
When you left
You left all I've done from my heart
No matter how much I love you
How much I love you
TEE: ARE YOU FREE THIS EVENING?
TEE: LET'S MEET AT THE PARK
Hey, Wine.
Tee admitted to us that he is gay.
And he was telling us that he loves you.
Yeah, so he wants to meet you
this evening.
-Where?
-That abandoned building, street side.
Why that place? It's scary.
Well, maybe he wants some romance
with you. To do what lovers do.
Another thing is...
He said the view up there is stunning.
I think he wants to see it.
Anyway, you don't have to be worried
about us having found out.
We're fine with it. We won't tell anyone.
No matter what happens,
Tee's still our friend.
Hey. He said that he really loves you.
Do you think Wine will go
to that building?
I don't think he will go.
Too scary.
Someone committed suicide
hanging himself there.
It was on the news everywhere.
But I think he'll go.
He really loves Tee.
Forget the ghosts! All he cares about
is if Tee's going to stop loving him.
I don't think he'll go there.
He doesn't love me.
He doesn't really love me that much.
Really?
But when I told him that you loved him,
you know,
his face was like he was dreaming.
I guess he was probably chased by ghosts
and has jumped off the building already.
Why are you guys pranking him like that?
Why not? Are you worried about him?
Are you loving him for real?
You said it was for fun.
Now it's real, isn't it?
Real my ass. Fuck off.
I don't love him.
I don't care whether he lives or dies.
WINE
6 MISSED CALLS
OK, let's wait a second.
He will make another fucking call.
Don't you pity him and answer his call.
Otherwise, you lose.
I know you want to answer Wine's call.
If he calls again
and you want to talk,
answer his call, Tee.
You should answer his call.
If something really happens to him,
we're all screwed, you know?
WINE
Fuck! Tee!
You're the man!
I believe you now
that you don't love Wine.
Well... If it were me,
I wouldn't leave my friend hanging
like that.
-You're the real deal, Tee.
-Guys.
Can you all leave?
-I'm so sleepy. I need to sleep.
-Oh.
What the hell is going on with you now?
I'm not sleepy yet!
Then go back to your room.
I want to sleep now!
Go! Get out!
He wants to sleep now.
Don't be stupid. Hurry up!
Let's go.
I'm leaving now.
See you, man.
Hey, Tee. Do you need me to stay over?
It's OK. You can go.
MISSED CALL - WINE
Help.
I'm starving.
I'll pray for you.
But I'm leaving now. You're scaring me.
I'm not dead.
I'm not a ghost.
So, where are you?
Help...
Help.
I can't see you.
Now you can't really say
that you're not a ghost.
Help.
You!
Hey, you.
I'll get some food for you.
Thanks.
Don't be long.
I'm afraid of ghosts.
I thought you were not coming back.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Have some congee. It'll give you energy.
Eat it.
Hey!
Drink some water.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know.
Maybe you haven't eaten anything
for too long.
Your body might need time to adjust.
Let's try something else.
Eat this banana.
You.
Hey, you!
Wake up. Hey!
What's wrong?
Oh my God.
What should I do?
Should I get some help?
We need a doctor.
Ouch! It hurts!
Ouch.
Hurts...
Hey.
Ouch, it hurts.
What the hell are you doing?
Why are you sucking my blood?
It makes me feel better.
I think I can drink blood.
I don't throw up after drinking it.
Can I drink your blood a little more?
Are you crazy? What kind of human
are you, drinking blood?
Or maybe...
you're not human!
-Maybe you are...
-I am what?
In Hollywood movies,
a person who drinks blood for living is...
a vampire.
No way.
I'm not a vampire.
If I was a vampire,
I would have some kind of power
like in the movies.
But I have...
no energy.
I feel like I'm dying.
That's true.
-Do you have fangs?
-Do you see any?
See?
No fangs.
Since when did you start drinking blood?
I don't know. Why can't I...
Why can't I remember anything?
So, who are you? Where do you come from?
How old are you?
And what's your name?
Name?
What is my name?
Where am I from?
I don't know. I can't remember anything.
So, you're a vampire with amnesia then.
Can you stay here for a while?
I can't really take you back home with me.
What about a hospital?
But you will need blood after all.
Maybe the police?
But you have amnesia.
What should we do?
What if I share your photo
on some social networks?
In case someone knows you?
But that could make you a freak.
Not good.
What should I do?
I can live here.
But, would you come to see me every day?
I'll come to see you every day, of course.
Who else is going to feed you?
Are you gonna let me drink
your blood again?
Like, every day?
What if I drink it all?
Would it kill you?
I don't know.
I can drink just a little bit a day.
Just to get energy so I can move around.
And your body can take time
to produce blood.
Sound good?
I don't know.
How is it, Wine?
Do you like it?
Is it OK for you to live here?
It's a bit old.
It's fine. This room is huge.
I think it's too big for me, even,
but I like it.
It's old but also classic.
I'm happy that you like it.
What were you and your parents
fighting about,
that you wanted to live by yourself?
The same old problems.
My home is a gambling house. So boring.
There are always strangers everywhere.
And they are so loud. I can't study.
Besides, my mom always forces me
to buy stuff for them.
I don't like it.
I understand you, Wine.
But do you understand me?
Well... I do.
So, would you do it with me today?
You know that I have been waiting
for this. I love you, Wine.
I have loved you
since before anyone else did.
Before you yourself ever loved anyone.
Let me kiss you.
Can you get up and walk?
I can't.
Just moving...
makes me feel terrible.
Here.
You can drink my blood then.
Ouch. It tickles.
Come on, when is blood going to come out
if you're just sucking like that?
I've got no fangs.
I don't want to bite you.
I don't want you to get hurt.
What are you doing?
Does it hurt?
Of course it hurts.
But if I don't do this,
we'll never get out of here.
Suck it.
Thank you.
Is this your home?
It looks like...
nobody lives here.
No, it's not my home.
And nobody lives here.
That's why we moved in here.
Well...
is the owner OK with that?
What are you looking at?
You're making me nervous.
I like the color of your eyes.
Red, like rabbit eyes. So cute.
I really want to know...
who you are,
and where you come from.
How old you are.
Where you studied.
If you are seeing anyone.
If your lover is a guy...
or a girl.
Mm. I want to know, too.
I'm think your parents, your loved ones,
and the ones who care for you
are probably looking for you.
I think so.
Why can't I...
remember anything?
I feel like I have just been born
again into this world...
since I woke up in that building.
And you are the first one I saw.
And you are...
also the first one who saw me.
Have you ever had sex?
I don't know.
So...
can I have sex with you?
Whatever makes you happy,
I'll do it.
You saved my life.
Your blood is in my body.
You and me...
are like the same person.
Thank you.
So, let me call you...
Night.
-Is it OK?
-OK. I like it.
My name is Night.
-And what's your name?
-My name is Wine.
-We are boyfriends now.
-Mm.
I'm now your boyfriend, Wine.
Hey! Night!
Wine!
Wine! Wake up, Wine!
I'm sorry.
Wine! Wake up!
Wake up! Wine!
Why are you yelling?
I feel exhausted today.
Let's sleep.
-Hello, Boy.
-Are you back at our place?
Can I go see you tonight?
I won't be there tonight.
My mom called me to come home.
It's the weekend tomorrow,
so I have to stay home to help her.
OK, then.
So, if you're free tomorrow, text me.
I will pick you up.
I miss you.
I want to hold you. I want to kiss you.
Sure.
Do you miss me?
A little.
Boy...
My mom is calling me now. I gotta go.
PORK, CHICKEN, AND COW BLOOD
Come! It's dinner time.
Let's try the first type of blood.
It's chicken blood.
Drink it.
Wow, you can drink it.
How was it? Are you feeling OK?
It's OK, right?
Let's try the second kind. Here.
It's pork blood.
Taste it.
Well...
Let's try the last one.
Cow's blood.
Try it.
You might able to drink it.
Please try a little bit.
Come on.
Just a little.
Night?
Night!
Night! Are you OK?
Night?
Why did we have to come here?
You told me once
that you wanted to have sex
in strange places.
Don't you remember?
Yes, of course.
I didn't mean to make you remember
everything I said.
I remember everything...
whether you meant it or not.
Thank you.
-But...
-But if I hadn't told you
that I would post our photos
and clips online,
including our sex clip,
and the clip where you told me
you loved me,
you wouldn't have come to see me.
Why do you say that?
You're always like this. You always
make your own assumptions.
But you told me you love me the way I am.
At least, we used to love each other.
Do me a favor today.
So we have something good to remember.
Just one last time.
And then I'll delete all the photos...
and all the video clips.
I'll delete everything about us.
All right, Tee?
All right.
I used to feel good about you.
-Does it hurt?
-No.
It's exciting. I like it.
What are you doing?
I want to take your blood.
It will hurt a bit.
-Stay still. You might break the needle.
-No way. You can't take it.
Let me go! This is not funny. Let me go!
Tee! I said quiet!
Don't scream! Don't move!
Are you insane, bitch?
You're getting mad
just because I don't love you?
It hurts me, too, lying to myself.
Let me go! I love you, you know that!
Do you hear me? Let me go!
I love you, all right?
Liar.
I don't want this.
I don't want this anymore.
I'm tired.
I've lost all my energy.
Please let me die.
I don't want your blood anymore.
I promise...
I won't trouble you again.
Stop saying that.
I'm not troubled at all.
Please, try again.
I promise.
If this doesn't work,
I won't force you anymore.
Please, do it for me.
If you die,
all the effort we have put in
will be meaningless.
You mean so much to me.
I want to live for you, Wine.
Do you like it?
Like you, Wine?
I don't.
I love you.
No, I didn't mean me.
I meant...
the sex we've just had.
I don't know.
I don't know if I had sex before.
I don't know
what I should compare it with.
I just know that...
it was...
the best of my life.
It was the best of my life, too.
I love you, Night.
I will do anything
to keep us together forever.
Thank you...
for seeing a dying person
as worth something.
And the blood I just had...
what animal did that blood come from?
How come it worked with my body?
It was buffalo blood.
I stopped by a market
and saw someone selling it,
so I bought it.
Tomorrow, I'll go back to tell them
that I will need it every day,
so they'll prepare it for me every day.
That's wonderful.
The buffalo is the loveliest animal
on earth, isn't it?
Hey, Wine!
Have you seen Tee?
-No, I haven't.
-Did he call you?
-Why should he call me?
-We tried calling, but his phone's off.
His parents are looking for him right now.
Aren't you worried about him at all?
-Why should I be worried about him?
-Gosh!
What the fuck is wrong with you? Let's go.
If he doesn't care about Tee,
we will go search for him ourselves.
Eat something, Tee.
Please, eat.
Why are you doing this?
Are you angry at me?
Do you hate me that much?
I'm sorry for saying I never loved you.
The truth is I do love you.
But I don't know what to do,
because I'm not gay.
And I never saw you as a man anyway.
Please eat, Tee.
I can't let you die like this.
Wine.
My head hurts.
I got you some pills.
Have some, and you will feel better.
My arms and legs are hurting, too.
Maybe my blood isn't circulating well.
Can I change positions?
No.
Wow.
Looks like you're a great player.
You've done it so many times, haven't you?
"Great"? I haven't made any shots.
Come on. Just keep trying.
You'll get there.
Here. Drink this.
Cheers.
Please hold the glass for me.
I'll go to the restroom.
Wait a second.
Don't be long. I miss you already.
That's too sweet!
Excuse me.
My name is White.
You look familiar. Have we met somewhere?
My name is Night.
But... Have we really met
each other before?
Night...
Well... the person I know,
his name is not Night.
Never mind. Forget about the name.
I think I like you.
Can we be boyfriends?
Wine!
Come here.
This is Wine. He's my boyfriend.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I love you very much.
Ouch!
Wine!
Wine?
Wine! Where are you?
I'm right at the door.
Are you trying to surprise me?
I'm home helping my mom today.
She called me.
Oh.
Really?
See? Now you're upset
because you never trust me.
And you always think
that I don't care about you.
-Everything is always my fault, right?
-No!
I never thought like that.
It's my fault
I came to surprise you today.
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
I promise.
All right?
Don't be mad at me, OK?
All right.
But you need to promise me that next time,
you will wait for me to call you
when I'm ready.
Gosh... Wine!
You're so mean.
We can talk via chat like usual.
But to meet up, I need to make some time.
That's what I mean.
Mm, OK.
I'm feeling better now.
Boy, my mom's calling me now. I gotta go.
Just now...
there was someone knocking at the door.
It was like...
he was trying to break into our place.
I was about to open the door,
but I couldn't move.
The sun was burning me.
I never thought it could be that hot.
It was burning me out.
Remember this.
If it's not me,
don't open the door.
It's dangerous.
You can kill me, please.
This is painful.
This is torture.
I can't take it anymore.
All right.
I will kill you.
I will let you die...
only if you eat this first.
You should be happy for one last time
before you die.
Did you ever love me?
Never.
I never stopped loving you.
Liar.
You're saying that because
you want me to let you go.
I don't need to lie to you...
because I'm dying.
Do you remember?
In sophomore year.
Me and my friends were talking
at the back of the classroom.
We were so loud
that the teacher was yelling at us.
You...
You were sitting in the front row...
and you turned to see me
like in slow motion...
and you were stunned by my charm.
I knew that.
Honestly,
I felt like...
I'd fallen in love.
But deep down,
I was telling myself...
not to love you.
"It's impossible."
But I couldn't help it.
Every time you came close to me...
I knew that you knew...
because you loved me, too.
Am I right?
Night.
Why are you sitting here?
I saw you went out to buy blood,
so I wanted to follow.
But you were walking too fast.
I couldn't follow you.
So, I was waiting for you here.
Move over. Let me sit with you.
Next time, don't follow me.
You might get lost.
All right.
Hey...
I can remember something about me now.
-I was...
-Wait.
Don't tell me.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid that one day
your memory will come back,
and you will leave me.
I promise you,
no matter what my past was,
I will never leave you.
What about you?
If you know my past,
will you leave me?
I will never leave you.
So... you can relax.
What I can remember is...
I can sing and play a guitar.
Really?
Damn...
I was depressed!
I thought you were going to tell me
that you were married with kids.
How come?
I was just afraid.
Wine!
Wine?
Wine.
What are you looking for?
We've wandered around
too many garbage dumps already.
Have you ever believed in something
so strongly
that it really happened,
just like a miracle?
I used to believe that I would one day
find someone I really loved.
Loved like I could die for.
And that person would love me
the same way.
And then I found you.
But now I believe that...
if I keep looking,
I will find a guitar for you to play,
and you will sing a song for me.
And I found...
-this!
-Wow! You really found it.
But it doesn't have any strings.
Oh... you're right.
Wine.
I believe that...
if we believe in something strongly,
miracles will happen because of our trust.
That's why we met.
Because we think the same.
So...
even though this guitar
doesn't have strings,
I will still play it...
and sing a song for you.
And you will hear the guitar.
Do you believe me?
Yes, I do.
Please, don't ask me why
When your heart can't deny
Better let it be
Please, know that someone
Can do everything
Just for you
Because I love you with all my heart
Nothing can stop me
Even it's wrong, I'll still do it for you
Make it worth it
Rather that disappointing you
If love can make this world so beautiful
You are the clearest proof to me
No matter how much I lost, I would accept
No matter how they misunderstood
I would let them
Just don't go away from me
Let you and your heart be here with me
Surprise! Happy birthday!
Today is not my birthday.
You forgot my birthday.
No, I didn't. It's my birthday.
I had to break my promise
not to surprise you here.
If I have to guess
whether you'll remember my birthday,
this will never happen.
I called you.
I texted and left comments for you.
You never answered. You know
that it was driving me crazy.
Happy birthday, Boy.
I'm really sorry
that I couldn't remember the birthday
of the most important person.
I don't have any gift for you.
Lately, there is so much going on
at home and school.
-Can you forgive me?
-No.
I won't forgive you.
Until...
Until you have sex with me the way I want.
-OK?
-OK!
-Not here.
-Oh.
Why?
It's exciting here. I like it.
I don't want anyone to see us.
Ah... shall we go to our place?
No, Boy. Our place is boring.
I have somewhere else more exciting.
I guarantee you will like it.
So good, my dear.
You know...you're the best birthday gift
that ever happened in my life.
I love you, Wine. My little boy.
What do you want?
Tee has gone missing.
Don't you want to help search?
Yeah. You said you loved him.
He's been missing for days. His parents
said he'd come back in his own time.
The police didn't believe us
and never filed the report. Fucking shit!
Oh! Look!
Are you guys blind?
Who would care about
a bad boy like Tee now?
Let's go.
I want you to be happy, Wine.
I want you to rape me.
You just read my mind.
I've always wanted to rape you, Wine.
Let's do it for real now.
I like it.
It's so exciting.
What you just said is...
really turning me on.
So...
Boy!
Boy! Let's me go! Boy, don't do it!
Let me go, Boy!
Hey!
Wine! Stop!
Boy, stop it!
Boy, let me go!
Boy! Don't!
Please, be patient, Chart.
I understand the feeling.
When you or anybody sees me,
it's hard to resist.
It happened to everyone.
Wait for me.
Just five minutes.
Wine?
Wine!
Wine. Are you OK, Wine?
I'm starving.
The buffalo blood tastes funny today.
Maybe a different buffalo.
It shouldn't be much different.
It still comes from a different buffalo
every day.
But today it might just be...
an older buffalo.
Hey.
What's wrong? Did you have a nightmare?
Let me give you a hug. You'll be OK.
Wine.
What have I done wrong?
Why did you bring someone else
to our place?
-You said it was just for the two of us.
-Hey!
I don't know who the fuck you are
or where you're from.
I don't care
if this room belongs to anyone else.
What I know is, Wine is mine.
I love Wine and he loves me.
-We love each other, OK?
-Wine.
It's not true, is it?
Tell me the truth.
What I have done for you all this time...
-It never made you love me, did it?
-Wine.
Wine, tell him that you love me.
Tell him. Tomorrow I will tell my parents.
I will tell everyone at school
how much I love you.
I don't care what everyone says.
I don't care if they say I'm gay.
I just want you to tell him
that you love me.
Wine. I will ask my parents
to make a proper proposal.
We will get married. We will travel
around the world on our honeymoon.
If you want to go to university,
I will support you until you graduate.
Whatever you want in this world,
I will get it for you.
I will work hard for you, Wine.
Wine, don't listen to him.
You're not a money boy.
Don't you remember how we first met?
-Wine, listen to me.
-No! Listen to me!
Stop! Stop talking!
Night.
I'm sorry.
Night. Don't leave me.
Stay!
Wine.
What's wrong?
You're trembling.
A nightmare?
Yeah.
The worst nightmare.
I dreamt that you left me.
I couldn't take it.
I'm afraid that you're really leaving me.
I told you
that I will never leave you.
Trust me.
Sleep.
I will hold you all night.
Please let me die.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm sorry for what I've done to you.
But I've made a decision that...
I will go away with someone I love.
I will go somewhere...
far away from here.
Somewhere quiet.
I'll let you go...
if you promise me
that you won't tell anyone about this.
Can you?
Yes.
I promise.
Eat your meal.
When you regain your strength,
just run away.
Help!
Help! Help me!
Let me go.
Let me go!
Fuck you!
Listen to me.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I just want your blood.
Just a lot of blood.
Because I have to travel a long way.
But I won't hurt you.
I won't kill you.
I know...
how much you love me.
Let me go!
Thank you so much.
And I want to apologize
that I can't love you.
No!
Please understand me.
I'll remove the duct tape...
if you promise you won't scream.
So we can talk nicely...
and you will understand everything.
Can you promise me?
Listen up, bitch!
I won't believe anything you say!
I played the fool all this time,
because I loved you.
But you were using me!
Fuck you!
Help!
No!
Dad!
Why are you doing this?
Listen to me, son.
I have to do it.
I love you.
I can't let you die.
How am I supposed to feel?
I can live if other people die?
Dad, you can't kill others
to make me survive.
I'd rather die.
You lied to me the whole time.
You lied to me that it was animal blood.
Dad, you never let me go out
to see the world outside.
You never let me see anyone but you.
Was it because I'm different?
Because I drink human blood, right?
What do you want me to do?
I love you, son.
Even if I had to kill
everyone in the world to save us,
I would.
To me...
you're not "different".
-I don't believe you anymore.
-Nam.
Nam. Where are you going?
Nam. Come back!
Nam!
Dad?
Dad!
Dad, wake up!
Dad?
Dad!
Wine.
Why did you do this?
Night.
I'm sorry.
I love you. I don't want you to die.
But I can't live my life...
by taking the lives of others.
I'm sorry...
for making you do the wrong thing
for my sake.
I love you, Wine.
Don't look for me.
When I'm ready,
I'll find you.
And believe me...
we will meet again someday.
All right?
Please.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Night.
Night. I'm sorry.
And you're still holding that guitar?
Can you really play?
I can't.
But I believe that holding it like this
will bring you back to me.
Come on.
Let me play it for you.
Please, don't ask me why
When your heart can't deny
Better let it be
Please, know that someone
Can do everything
Just for you
Because I love you with all my heart
Nothing can stop me
Even it's wrong, I'll still do it for you
Make it worth it
Rather that disappointing you
If love can make this world so beautiful
You are the clearest proof to me
No matter how much I lost, I would accept
No matter how wrong they understood
I would let them
Just don't go away from me
Let you and your heart be here with me