[eerie music]
[zipper rasps]
[Jade] Scientists said
the world would end in 2036.
Climate change, pollution.
[security alarm hums, blares]
The oceans would boil.
[security alarm locks]
The air, you wouldn't
be able to breathe it.
Billions of people would die.
[eerie music continues]
But they were wrong.
The world ended a long time ago.
[theme music]
Three, two, one.
-Happy birthday!
-[chuckling]
-Yay!
-Are you having a good day?
-Uh-huh.
-Dad tried to make me waffles.
-Mm.
-Ooh, "tried"?
-[Arjun] Well, there was an incident.
-There was a fire.
-Small fire.
[whispers]
Big fire.
Mm-hmm.
[chuckles]
I remember when I was nine.
My sister and I, we, uh…
[inhales deeply]
…went to Disneyland.
What's that?
Oh, it's, uh… It was a pretty fun place.
[Bea gasps]
Can I go?
[Arjun] Uh, Bea, uh, why don't you go
get your present to show Mom, huh?
Ooh, presents.
[hands rubbing]
-[Bea] It's a book.
-[Jade] Okay.
-[Bea] I'll be right back!
-What kind of a book?
[Arjun] Shakespeare.
-The Complete Works.
-[Jade] Wait.
When I left, she was still working
her way through Wrinkle in Time.
[scoffs]
Well, it's been six months. Things change.
[sighs]
-Oh, hey, I… I didn't mean…
-No, it… It's fine.
I know I've been gone too long.
I miss you guys so much.
Jade.
Be careful.
[serious music]
[hisses]
[clacks]
[beeps]
[digital swish]
[grunts]
[rabbit whimpers softly]
[sighs]
[button clicks]
[beeping]
Come on. Show me something.
[wind blows]
[ominous music]
[distant grunting]
[footsteps rustling]
[thumping]
[faint growling]
[snarling]
[growling]
[grunts]
[gasping]
[all growling]
[furious snarling]
[teeth gnashing]
[swift exhale]
[all growling]
[sniffing]
[recorder beeps]
Day 167 of observation.
[Jade] Pack 2426 still shows
no sign of leadership structure
or higher brain function.
[recorder beeps]
[alert moaning]
[zipper rasps]
[flesh rips]
[Zeros sniffing]
[grumbling]
[growling]
[suspenseful music]
[Jade panting]
[teeth gnashing]
[grunts]
[growling]
[aggressive growl]
[groans]
-[teeth clacking]
-[Jade grunting]
[grunts]
[screams, grunts]
-[grunts]
-[security alarm beeps]
[security alarm buzzing]
[fire roars]
[panting]
[whimpers]
[all growling]
[sizzles]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[hisses]
[security alarm blaring]
[Jade coughing]
[Zero grunting]
[security alarm continues blaring]
[Jade coughs]
[panting]
[Jade] No.
Damn.
Six months.
Fucking stupid!
-[rumbling]
-[Jade exhales]
[soft groan]
[earth rumbles]
[ominous music]
[gasps]
[rumbling and cracking]
[Jade gasps, effort grunting]
[monster roars]
[Jade breathing rapidly]
[growling]
["Oxytocin" by Billie Eilish plays]
♪ Can't take it back
Once it's been set in motion ♪
♪ You know I love
To rub it in like lotion ♪
♪ If you only pray on Sunday ♪
♪ Could you come my way on Monday? ♪
♪ 'Cause I like to do things ♪
♪ God doesn't approve of if she saw us ♪
♪ She couldn't look away ♪
♪ Look away, look away ♪
♪ She'd wanna get involved ♪
♪ Involved, involved ♪
♪ And what would people say ♪
♪ People say, people say ♪
♪ If they listen through the wall ♪
♪ The wall, the wall? ♪
[message received tone]
♪ I can see it clear as day ♪
♪ You don't really need a break ♪
♪ Wanna see what you can take ♪
Shit. Stop.
[Albert] I really think you guys
are gonna love it here.
Oh, and the school,
they have an amazing STEM program.
Their team won Codefest last year, and…
they've got kombucha on tap.
[sighs]
["Oxytocin" by Billie Eilish
plays over headphone]
Hmm.
Watch it, man.
[indistinct chatter]
[mellow music]
[Simon] One more shot.
Hey, did you see those freaks in the park?
Oh, you mean the normal people?
Like, walking around?
[young Billie] Yeah, I saw them.
They looked fine.
-Too fine.
-"Too fine"?
And we're in South Africa,
but there's only, like, five Black people?
This place is fucking weird.
-[young Billie] The house is nice though.
-[young Jade] Yeah.
If I burn it down, can we go home?
[Carol] Albert.
-Ah! There you are.
-[Albert] Carol, good to see you again.
[Carol chuckles]
Aw.
Jade, Billie, it's terrific
to finally meet you.
-Fucking weird.
-You too.
[Carol] You're going
to absolutely love it here.
Once you've settled, I'll take you
for a tour around the town center.
I hope you love cupcakes.
We have five shops, and two are vegan.
-Cool.
[Carlol] I know the place is
a little smaller than what you're used to,
but Cape Town's just an hour away.
And, you know, last year, we were voted
best place to live in the world.
[Jade] By who?
Lulu Lemon whores?
Guys, that jerk off to CrossFit?
-[thuds]
-Elon Musk?
-I don't--
-It's… it's a joke.
Jade thinks she's funny.
[awkward chuckle]
All right. Come on.
-Can you just not?
-No. No.
So, on behalf of the Umbrella Corporation,
welcome home.
-Wow, so lame.
-Great, really great.
New Raccoon City
used to be an old factory town.
When Umbrella bought it,
it was almost deserted.
But with a little inspiration
and a lot of hard work, well…
it's just special here.
The sun's a little brighter,
the air's a little cleaner.
You can have a house
with all the latest bells and whistles.
And plenty of room to run and play.
Right.
I mostly just read Zootopia porn, so…
-[sighs]
-[phone ringing]
Oh, excuse me.
He's super important.
-[Albert] Wesker.
-[bag thuds]
No, I… I've been trying to work.
[Carol] Well, Saturdays are usually
my cheat days, but…
[sighs]
What the heck?
We're celebrating, right, girls?
[softly]
Christ. Tijuana? What happened?
Who wants a slice of ca…
[young Billie] You can drop it.
The bitch act.
Not an act.
[young Billie]
Do you think I wanna be here?
Don't you?
I mean, you were fine with moving.
[young Billie] Didn't have a choice.
And what was I supposed to do?
Yell and scream and break a plate?
-I mean, it worked for me.
-No, it didn't.
At least I tried. You…
What happened to the chick
that stole that beer?
That broke into bio and let the frogs go?
-She almost got expelled.
-She got fucking boring.
[sighs]
You know, sometimes,
it's not so bad to just… get along.
With Carol?
Just try.
[young Jade] I mean,
at least the guys are hot.
-Let's go say hi.
-Can't. I'm too "boring".
-Billie, I'm sorry. Okay? Come on.
-No, it's fine. I need to unpack.
Fine. Whatever.
[backboard thumps]
[young Jade] Hey.
-Hi.
-I just moved in down the street.
-I just wanted to say hi.
-Cool.
-I'm Jade.
-Simon.
[young Jade] Hi, nice to meet you.
[pebbles clattering]
[uneasy music]
[screeching]
[effort grunting]
[yelps]
[groans]
[panting]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[thwacking, grunting]
[growling]
[Jade screams]
-[loud crash]
-[groans]
[growling]
[roars]
[ominous music]
[snarling]
[screeches]
[gunfire]
[Maskey] Jesus.
-That's one big old bastard.
-Check the camp. The girl.
[Maskey] There's
gotta be 40 zeros over there.
They fried those fuckers.
But it going off,
must have woke that fucker up.
-How is she?
-Still breathing.
Looks like internal bleeding, probably.
Concussion, definitely.
[Yen] Fuck me.
She's a survivor.
[dramatic music]
♪ There is a scourge
In the guise of sanctity ♪
[muffled upbeat music]
♪ A perpetrator with a quill ♪
How much does she hate me?
No one hates you, Dad.
The move, I know it's hard, but…
I didn't really have a choice.
Umbrella gets what Umbrella wants.
[sniffles, winces in pain]
[Albert] I'm sorry.
All done.
How are you?
[phone ringing]
-I don't have to pick it up.
-If you don't, you'll stress.
[Albert sighs deeply]
[Albert] Wesker.
I don't want excuses. We have protocols.
-[young Jade] You forgot my sample.
-[Albert] Hold on.
I wa…
-You took that yourself?
-[young Jade] I can work a needle.
Gonna be awesome at heroin.
[tranquil music]
[young Jade exhales deeply]
Dad's worried about you.
Dad worries about everything.
We have never been sick, ever.
-But still, every two weeks, blood test.
-He's just…
-It's for our own good.
-Is it?
Or he's a vampire.
He's totally a vampire.
[both chuckle]
You should have come today.
The boys were cute.
-Dumb, but cute.
-Right.
-Cool.
-I'm an asshole. Okay?
I know.
[both laugh]
[sniffs]
[young Jade] You worried about tomorrow?
-New school.
-New everything.
[young Jade] So? New us.
I mean, these kids in this shitty town.
We're gonna own them.
No, I don't… I just want to be invisible.
-Why?
-Come on. You know.
Is this because of the frog thing?
No, and the… The other thing.
One, you were ten.
Two, Alex Ingles kicked a first grader.
So you broke his leg.
-[young Jade] Fair trade.
-I had to go to counseling.
You know, and everyone
thought I was psycho.
Including me.
I need to stop getting mad
and then doing stupid shit.
Hey.
Look at me.
You are not stupid.
You're Billie fucking Wesker.
[young Jade] You are nice and cool.
You've got a great ass,
a 1520 on the PSAT.
And you've got the best sister.
So remember that and say "fuck it"
to everything else, okay?
-Come here.
-[chuckles]
[squeaking]
[footsteps]
[uneasy music]
[uneasy music swelling]
[music intensifies]
[exhales]
[PA system chiming]
[kid 1] Yeah, plus one through ten.
[kid 2] It's pretty good, though.
[announcer] Good morning,
Raccoon City High!
The lunch special today
is whipped cream, medium meatballs.
Sign up form for Mandatory Fall Festival
sponsored by Umbrella.
[indistinct chatter]
[Simon] Hey, lads. Lads.
Sorry.
[announcer] Positivity is a bridge
between you and your dream.
Have a great day!
-Hi.
[scoffs]
[indistinct chatter]
[girl] I know, they're not welcome you.
[sighs]
-Hey.
-I'm, I'm--
-[young Jade] Billie!
Who's that?
My sister. Twin sister.
You're twins?
I mean, same dad, but our moms,
we had different egg donors,
but the surrogate delivered us
at the same time.
So, technically, yeah.
[breathes deeply]
Go science.
[chuckles]
So, you're, like, a freak?
No.
[chuckles]
What's with the shirt?
-Oh, I'm vegan.
-That's stupid.
I just don't eat animals.
My dad took me hunting last fall.
It was awesome.
[imitates gunshot]
Shot Bambi in the brain.
[chair rattles]
You know, when the end of the world comes,
we eat the vegans first.
Eat this.
[gasps]
[clattering]
[students clamoring]
Get off me!
-Just stop! Stop!
-[thwacking]
[all chanting]
Fight! Fight! Fight!
-Hey, get off! Get off!
-Up! Come with me!
-Get off! Scram!
-Out! Move! Back, everyone!
-Don't make me throw something at you!
-[Mrs. Morgan] Move back!
Billie, are you okay?
-[panting]
-Hey! Hey, I got you.
[panting continues]
[bright music]
[woman] I was lethargic,
unhappy, and unmotivated.
And then I found Joy.
[baby giggles]
[camera shutter clicks]
[man] A new product from Umbrella,
where our business is life itself.
I kind of…
[sighs]
I hate it.
[sharp exhale]
Joy helps people with serious issues,
chronic depression, OCD.
[Albert] That's why I developed it.
But this…
She lives in a great house,
she's got a family,
-why is she taking pills?
-We aren't doctors.
It's not our job to ask that question.
We're just giving people
the tools they need to be happy.
-We need to take a step back.
-[Bob] We can't.
-With what's happening in Tijuana--
-We booked the ad buys.
[Bob] We launch in six weeks.
Eli Lilly made three billion a year
off Prozac.
We could double that in the first month.
Billie, stop!
-[door closes]
-Where the hell were you?
Uh, here.
Then why weren't you
picking up your phone?
I was on a call.
-Fuck you!
-Jade! Jade! Jade!
-[young Jade] Billie!
-[door opens, closes]
Billie, come on.
[panting]
[phone vibrates]
[crowd in video clamoring]
[young Jade] Get off! Get off!
[uneasy music]
Billie, let me in. Please.
Jade, tell me what's going on.
[scoffs]
[door opens]
Go back to work.
[door closes]
[young Jade] Why
didn't you just sit with me?
You were with your friends.
Owning them.
-Hey.
-I didn't want to ruin it.
Hey.
I don't give a fuck about those assholes.
[young Jade] The only person
I care about is you.
You know what you have to do.
-Apologize.
-What?
-The fight, it was… It was my fault.
-[young Jade] No.
You have to go at her.
Why, so everyone can think
I'm psycho again?
-I mean, they… they think--
-They're laughing at you.
The entire school.
And you need to shut them the fuck up.
[gasps]
[groans]
[panting]
[machine sparking and whirring]
[moans in pain]
[grunts]
[button clicks]
[reporter] Papal States
move to wall off Sicily.
Last Alaskan Freehold goes dark.
…and our patented bionanite technology
stops 99.99 percent of known cancers
in their tracks.
Available now from Umbrella,
where our business is life--
Map.
-Where am I?
-[Tate] Brighton.
-[button clicks]
-You're in the Brighton Freehold.
-I'm Tate, by the way.
-I need to get back to my camp.
-[Jade] I need my gear.
-[Tate] Sure.
We can make that happen… tomorrow.
Now.
[door creaks]
-[crackling]
-[indistinct shouting]
Uh, slow down.
[metal whirring]
-You're scavengers.
-Something like that.
There's still a lot of old tech
around London.
The richies in Auckland and Oslo,
they want it.
[indistinct chatter]
We only take what we can trade.
-How'd you get me here?
-Helicopter.
-Where is it?
-Out. Another recce.
So we can drive?
No, we really can't.
[indistinct shouting]
[suspenseful music]
[explodes]
[sparkles]
[whooshes]
[Zeros grunting]
[Zeros growling]
[Tate] Like I said…
really can't.
-[PA alarm wailing]
-[grunts]
One punch. Right in the tit.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I… I should have just let it go.
Can we be cool?
-[squishes]
-[gasps]
[laughter]
[tense music]
[scoffs]
[gasps]
Wait.
Fucking bitch!
Billie.
[ominous music]
[Roth] This is the last footage
out of Tijuana.
[static]
[screaming and gunfire on video]
[screaming continues]
[in Spanish]
Why won't he die? Why?
[Roth in English]
Six injured, three dead.
[key clacks]
-Has anything gone public?
-Nothing we can't handle.
Albert, if it's happening again…
[sighs]
-[PA alarm wails]
-[door opens]
♪ It's nothing like I thought it'd be ♪
♪ It's not how I imagined ♪
[video game trilling]
♪ It's interesting to justify the action ♪
♪ It's left me feeling kind of weak ♪
♪ It's bleak, anticlimactic ♪
[thwacks]
♪ You don't mind if I lie for a moment ♪
♪ I tell myself these little myths
I don't even believe in ♪
[Mrs. Morgan] Billie.
♪ I think that flowers gonna spring up ♪
♪ Make this weather break ♪
♪ Close your eyes
Synthesize different versions ♪
Is this your locker?
Well, I don't…
-What happened?
-[Mrs. Morgan] Open it.
♪ Myself these little myths
I don't even believe in ♪
-[Dave] She's psycho, okay?
-[Mrs. Morgan] Mr. Isaacs…
-[Dave] She jumped my kid.
-No, I didn't.
And these days, everyone gets a trophy,
everyone's special, but…
I don't know what your problem is here.
Maybe the voices made you or… whatever.
It doesn't matter. We're pressing charges.
You, you're gonna spend
the next ten years in a cell!
[Mrs. Morgan] Mr. Wesker,
thank you for coming.
Sorry, I'm late. I got caught up. Work.
[softly]
Wesker. Shit.
You okay?
-[Mrs. Morgan] Mr. Isaacs was just saying…
-I heard.
-Thin walls.
-[Mrs. Morgan] Uh…
Now, I know that Billie has a history,
but we're all part of the Umbrella family.
-I'm sure we can work this out.
-You… threatened my daughter.
-No, I, I--
-What's your name?
It's Dave.
What do you do for Umbrella, Dave?
-I'm a server admin.
-[Albert] And, um…
how many people can do your job, Dave?
A thousand? Ten thousand?
[scoffs]
I guess?
[Albert] Well, I work for Umbrella, too.
And do you know
how many people could do my job?
[scoffs]
One. Me.
-Okay. Cool?
-It's not.
It means I work too much. It means…
I'm not much of a father. I try, but…
[sighs]
I'm not.
[scoffs]
Okay, but what… What does this--
And it means that Umbrella needs me. So…
what happens if I call the people
that own this town?
The people that pay you and me and her.
What happens if I call them
and I say that I'm going to quit unless…
they fired you.
[Albert] No, I'm sorry. I…
I don't want you fired.
I want you blacklisted.
I want it so that no tech company
ever hires you.
Not Apple. Not Google.
I want PornHub to shred your resume.
Now, if I say that…
what do you think
they're going to do, Dave?
Dave.
I, uh… Hey, man…
Look, man…
[nervous chuckle]
I didn't mean to…
I… I'm not gonna call the cops.
Okay? And, and, and you know…
This… Never mind… This, this whole thing?
-It… it never happened.
-What?
Mr. Wesker, this girl was attacked.
-By you?
-No.
I believe her.
-Then who did it?
-Oh, I don't care.
-Dad, this is stu--
-Tammy, just shut up.
[Albert] But…
you attacked my daughter twice.
So…
[sucks teeth]
I think you owe her an apology.
Just… just do it.
I'm sorry.
[Albert] No.
Again.
Better.
I'm really sorry.
I'll… never do anything to you again.
Ever.
Thanks.
I think Billie should take tomorrow off
and call it a mental health day.
[chuckles nervously]
Of course.
So, everyone happy?
Yeah. Totally.
And I was thinking maybe
you could come by the lab.
-We could do lunch.
-Okay.
I'll get the car.
Hey, what happened?
[panting]
[young Billie] I know what you did.
[dark music]
-Those zeros, how many are out there?
-[Tate] It changes.
A few hundred at least.
We got over a thousand last summer.
Not sure why.
They can smell you.
[Jade] Their eyes go first.
After about two or three years,
the cornea is fried.
Their hearing goes next,
but their sense of smell
it keeps getting better.
And in the summer, people stink.
-Smart fucking dead folks, huh?
-[Jade] They're not dead.
The T-virus doesn't kill people,
it rewires their brains.
Your groupies outside?
They're zero strain. Carriers.
All they want to do is eat
and spread the virus.
And when the T goes cross-species,
it triggers rampant cell growth.
It makes animals big and mean and--
Really fucking big
and really fucking mean.
-What were you doing out there?
-[Jade] My job.
I study zeros.
Watch how they change, evolve.
Zeros don't change.
They will… because the virus will.
[Jade] If we're lucky, it'll get weaker,
and the weaker it gets, the smarter,
the more human the zeros will become.
[inhales deeply]
We need to understand it. Them.
I get how to kill 'em. I'm good.
[laughs]
No, you're not.
There's, what, 300 million humans left
on this planet?
But six billion of them.
I don't think you can kill them all.
So we have to learn how to live with them.
Like we do…
AIDS or Ebola or anything else
that's trying to wipe out the human race.
And we made them, so…
[chuckles]
[pitcher rasps]
-I didn't make no fucking zero…
-[liquid sloshing]
-[bottle thuds]
-…and I didn't end the fucking world.
And, uh, I guess you know about that.
You're a survivor.
First wave, right?
Your ink.
[Tate] You were in New Raccoon
when the outbreak started.
That must have been something.
When the sick hit Glasgow,
my dad put me and my sister on a boat,
spent ten years in the Fair Isles
while the world went to fuck.
But you?
You were right in the thick of it.
Sorry.
Uh…
It's not easy to talk about, I imagine.
[Yen] Tate!
-They're 30 out.
-[Jade] Who?
-Umbrella.
-Umbrella's coming here? Why?
They've got a bounty on survivors.
Turns out,
you're their number one most wanted.
["Devil" by Two Feet plays]
♪ If I lie when I say
That I'm getting emotional ♪
♪ Emotional ♪
♪ Let me try to express all the things
That you want me to ♪
♪ That you want me to ♪
♪ One, I feel nothing ♪
♪ Two, I got something ♪
♪ Three, I need you near ♪
♪ You're the only one
That never fools around here ♪
♪ So you ♪
♪ Won't ever break ♪
[automated voice] Please state your name.
Billie Wesker.
[automated voice] Hello, Billie.
You have been granted
a three-hour visitor pass.
♪ I don't really know
How to let you know ♪
♪ Let you know ♪
♪ One, I feel nothing ♪
♪ Two, I got something ♪
♪ Three, I need you near ♪
♪ You're the only one
That never fools around here ♪
♪ So you ♪
♪ Won't ever break ♪
Introducing Joy for kids!
[giggling]
[indistinct chatter]
[serious music]
[Rhonda] Hey, Billie.
So can you come take a seat here
for a moment?
He won't be long.
[cart rattles]
Carl.
-[Carl] Hey.
-[Rhonda] Hi.
Are you going to that thing this weekend?
-[Carl] Yeah, it should be fun.
-[Rhonda] Great.
[Carl] And I'm assuming
you'll be there, obviously.
[Rhonda] What time are you thinking
of making an appearance?
-[Carl] Like, 7:00?
-[Rhonda] Me too.
-Actually, could you give me a ride?
-[Carl] Sure could…
-Thanks.
-[Rhonda] I have your number, so I'll…
-Oh, whatever.
-[Rhonda] You know I will.
[ominous music]
-Hi.
-Hey.
Cafeteria's this way.
[young Jade] Billie.
I'm sorry.
At school, no one's laughing
at you anymore.
And they don't think
you're a psycho either.
They…
[grunts]
They love you now.
Just please don't hate me.
I don't hate you.
-[young Billie] But you owe me.
-Yes!
Okay, anything. Anything.
Did you know Umbrella does animal testing?
No.
Neither does anyone else.
And they say they don't, but they do.
PETA gave them an award.
So?
Today, at Dad's office,
I saw these rabbits.
-And?
-And it's gross and wrong.
And I told you this place was fucked.
But… kind of not our problem.
You said "anything".
And you said, you wanted them not boring,
crazy, frog-stealing in my back.
-So you wanna steal the rabbits.
-If we can.
I just need to get pictures
and put them online,
and let people see what's really going on.
-You think Dad will be okay with that?
-I…
I don't care.
What happened to getting along?
No stupid shit?
Fuck it.
Fuck it!
There are no guards
'cause everything's automated,
but the main gate is voice-activated,
-and then there's cameras.
-No problem.
You know how to get past security cameras?
No. But the internet does.
[suspenseful music builds]
[suspenseful music]
[scooter hums]
[young Billie] The guy
was, like, almost crying.
[young Jade] Our Dad did that?
The guy who wears socks to the beach.
Who talks about escape rooms for hours,
and whose password
to everything is Spock21?
He was scary.
[automated voice] Please state your name.
[Albert's voice]
Hello, this is Albert Wesker.
[automated voice]
Good evening, Dr. Wesker.
Now commencing your one hour
after-hours pass.
[uneasy music]
[beeps]
[squeaks]
[helicopters approaching]
You don't wanna do this.
You play with Umbrella, you lose.
-Always.
-I'm not playing.
I just happen to have something they need.
-Is this about money?
-Money is worthless.
Then what the fuck do you want?
A life. I hand you over,
and I get a pass to Umbrella territory.
They'll never let you in.
You're damaged goods.
[helicopters approaching]
[Zeros growling]
[helicopters whirring]
Watch her.
[tense music]
[muffled indistinct chatter]
[gun clicks]
[tense music]
[gasps]
Mr. Tate.
Mr. Baxter.
Your girl's over there.
Cool.
-[gunshot]
-[groans]
-[gasps]
-Go.
-[gunfire]
-[groaning]
-[thwacks]
-[grunting]
[tense music]
[bullets ricochet]
[animal noises]
[foreboding music]
Dude.
[young Jade] Fucked up.
If they're hiding this,
what else are they hiding?
[camera shutter clicks]
[squeaking]
[foreboding music]
[notification tone]
No signal.
[young Billie] Oh, um, that computer,
is it online?
Okay.
[trills]
[camera shutter clicks]
[monkey panting]
[mouse clicks]
-[screaming]
-[gunfire]
[animal whimpering]
Oh, my God.
[whimpering continues]
[trilling]
[beeps]
[door unlocks]
[monkey chitters]
[electricity buzzing]
[animal screeching]
[grunting]
Billie.
-[young Jade] Billie!
-No. I just need to get pictures.
-[young Jade] Just… hurry
-[animal sniffing]
[screeching]
[dog panting]
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[growls]
[tense music]
-[dog snarls]
-No.
No.
[growls]
It's okay.
Okay.
[both shrieking]
[barking]
[both screaming]
-[alarm wailing]
-[both panting]
-What the fuck?
-I don't know.
-[loud thud]
-[both gasp]
[dog grumbles]
-Come on.
-Let's go!
[intense music]
-[young Billie] In here. Hurry.
-[young Jade] Go, go, go.
[door opens]
[both mumbling and panting]
[dog grumbling]
[dog sniffing]
[paw steps running away]
[suspenseful music]
[clicks]
[clacks]
-[gasps]
-♪ Introducing Joy for kids! ♪
[giggles]
♪ I've got the joy, joy, joy, joy
Down in my heart ♪
♪ Down in my heart, down in my heart ♪
♪ I've got the joy, joy, joy, joy
Down in my heart ♪
♪ Down in my heart to stay ♪
♪ I've got the peace
That passes understanding ♪
♪ Down in my heart ♪
♪ Down in my heart, down in my heart ♪
♪ I've got the peace
That passes understanding ♪
♪ Down in my heart
Down in my heart to stay ♪
♪ I've got the joy, joy, joy, joy
Down in my heart ♪
♪ Down in my heart, down in my heart ♪
♪ I've got the joy, joy, joy, joy
Down in… ♪
-[growling]
-[screaming]
Go! Go, go! Go, go!
Wait. I can't find it!
It's locked.
Help! Come on. Come on.
I just need to… Okay, okay.
-[Albert] Hello, this is Albert Wesker.
-Play it again.
-I'm playing it.
-Come on. Play it again.
-Okay.
-You got this.
-[Albert] Hello, this is Albert…
-[glass shatters]
-[shrieks]
-[gasps]
-[snarls]
[screams]
-Help!
-Oh, my God!
[both screaming]
-[dog snapping]
-Wait, wait!
I'm coming!
-[thwacks]
-[dog whimpers]
[dog whines]
[extinguisher clangs]
Billie.
[young Jade grunts]
Billie, come on.
Billie.
[sobbing]
Billie, you need to wake up.
Billie, you need to wake up now.
You need to wake up.
Please wake up. Please.
Come on.
[cries]
[dramatic music]
[gunfire]
[fire roars]
[panting]
Oh, hey, Jade.
Your sister's been looking for you.
[breathes heavily]
[Zeros growling]
Stay the fuck away from me.
[dramatic music intensifies]
[Zeros growling]
[music stops]
[closing theme music]