[unnerving music]
[suspenseful music]
[loud clang]
[groaning]
[coughing]
[Zeros grumbling]
[inhales, coughing]
[sniffing, snarling]
[panting]
[tense music]
[panicked grunt]
[aggressive snarling]
-Keep her alive.
-[gunfire]
[growling]
[gunfire continues]
[panting, grunting]
[gasps]
[Baxter] Yo, Jade!
We stop shooting, you're dead.
So how about you just come with us, huh?
Come on.
Sometimes, it's better
to eff the devil, you know, right?
[Zeros snarling]
[vehicle approaching]
[gasps]
[loud clank]
[tense music]
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[engine revs]
[Jade] Stop! Please!
[all snarling]
[tense music]
[grunts, thumps]
-[knocking loudly]
-[Jade] Drive!
[yelling in fear]
[Zeros roaring]
[gunfire]
[loud clonking]
[engine roars]
[rapid gunfire]
[trilling]
[security alarm wailing]
[panting and crying]
[crying continues]
-[gasps]
-Hey! Hey!
Are you okay? Hey! Are you okay?
Are you okay?
[young Jade cries]
-[young Billie] I'm okay.
-Are you…
I don't think I'm a dog person anymore.
-Well, that's okay.
-[both laughing]
It's okay.
[whimpers]
Ow!
You need a doctor, okay?
-Okay.
Now I'm gonna get…
It might hurt a little bit. Okay, ready?
-Careful.
-One, two, three.
-[groaning]
-Okay.
I need… I need help.
I know. And we're gonna get you help.
[suspenseful music]
[sirens wailing]
[both panting]
It's okay.
[both breathing heavily]
-[flesh rips]
-I'm sorry. I…
[young Jade] It's gonna be all right.
-[door opens]
-[both gasp]
Dad.
[Albert] Did the dog bite her?
Yeah.
Jesus.
[flashlight clicks off, clacks]
-Is she, is she gonna be okay?
-Billie, look at me. Look at me.
She's in shock.
Hey, Bill?
-[grunts]
-[pen clacks]
-[young Billie breathing in panic]
-[rips]
[breathing heavily]
You're going to have to take her home.
-What?
-Keep pressure on the wound.
Her vitals are fine.
No major arteries were hit.
Are you fucking…
She needs a hospital.
Just go before Umbrella sees you.
Okay.
No. Not okay.
At the end of the hall, the door is open.
Cut through the backfield.
-But why?
-Now!
Jade.
Okay, okay.
-Jade.
-Come on.
Come on, come on.
That's it.
[alarm sirens wailing]
[sobbing]
[breathes deeply]
[clicks]
[digital trilling]
[suspenseful music]
[clicks]
[sharp exhale]
[suspenseful music continues]
[thrilling music]
[engine rumbling]
Stop!
-[loud thumping]
-[Jade grunting]
Hey!
[swishes]
No. Wait, wait! Stop!
[Jade] Wait! Wait! No!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Please!
Please! Stop!
[tires screech]
[panting]
[whooshes]
-[Jade exhales]
-[Yen] Move!
-Move!
-[Jade] Oh, my God.
[Yen] I got you out of there.
Now get the fuck away from me!
Umbrella's after you.
You got a big fucking target on your back,
and I don't want one on mine.
It's too late.
What, you think
they're just gonna let you go?
Run off and tell people that…
That they shot up a freehold?
[Jade] No chance.
They will hunt you down.
But I can help you. Okay?
I can get you away from Umbrella.
I save you, you save me.
[panting]
Okay, good.
-[loud thud]
-[both gasp]
-[gasps]
-[bones crackle]
[tense music]
[snarling]
[gunshot]
[grunts]
-[panting]
-[footsteps approaching rapidly]
[Zeros grunting]
[panicked groaning]
-[grunts, screams]
-[blood splatters]
[Yen] No.
No!
[tense music]
Grab my hand!
[Jade] Grab on!
[effort grunting]
[panicked scream]
-[Yen screaming in pain]
-[Zeros gnawing]
-[thumping]
-[flesh ripping]
-[grunts]
-[glass shatters]
[engine starts]
[engine revs]
[tense music continues]
-[tires screeching]
-[sirens wailing]
[cop 1] Move! Move, move, move!
-[cop 2] Coming.
-[cop 3] I need a probe, searching team.
[cop 4] Go out through the back door.
[suspenseful music]
-[cop 1] Right there.
-[cop 2] Contact, forward. In the back.
[cop 3] Contact!
[cop 4] We see your hands!
[cop 5] Don't move!
My, my name's Albert Wesker. I work here.
There's been an incident.
[door closes]
[young Jade] We should have waited
for an ambulance.
-[young Billie] No. Dad…
-[young Jade] Dad…
-[young Billie] Dad said…
-Fuck Dad.
What do you think was wrong with that dog?
[young Billie] I don't know.
-It looked dead.
-[young Jade] Yeah, well…
You looked dead too, Billie. I thought…
[somber music]
I should have stopped you from going.
-[sharp inhale]
-What?
[grunts]
It just hurts.
[soft ringing]
Where is Dad?
[metal clangs]
One minute, things were fine,
and the next…
every screen in the place went red
and all hell broke loose.
[metal clonks]
[Evelyn] Marcus.
Evelyn Marcus. I run this fucking company.
-[guard] Ma'am, without a badge, I--
-Move!
Clear the room.
[clanks]
Evelyn?
How bad is it?
I wasn't bitten. It's not my blood.
Fire that guard.
He's new.
[Roth] He's gone.
[pensive music]
What happened?
We got hacked.
I was working late when the whole system
went down and the virus…
It must have overridden our security.
The cage unlocked, the dog got out.
Whoever did this
wiped every hard drive on campus.
Research, security cameras, everything.
We have backups of the research.
Still a pain in my ass.
An attack like this,
usually, it's ransomware,
but this was just burn it all down.
Why?
I thought you were in Tokyo now.
I split time.
When I got the call,
I was already on my way here.
Thanks to you.
Joy?
[sighs]
I'm right about this, Evelyn.
The drug has side effects.
-Minor side effects.
-[Albert] "Minor"?
Did you see the fucking monster
in the lobby?
So we fix it. We make it better.
What happened in Tijuana,
we're taking it seriously.
That's why I'm moving
the Joy production line here,
so I can keep an eye on it.
And, you know, tax breaks.
Al…
[sucks teeth]
You and me.
We're gonna drive this one home.
Just like the old days.
I'm tired.
Can we talk about this tomorrow?
Sure.
-[footsteps receding]
-[sighs]
[chimes]
Ev! Oh, thank God.
What are you doing here?
I heard the sirens,
and you weren't answering your phone.
[sighs]
Diana, this is Albert Wesker,
one of my scientists.
Albert, my wife, Diana.
What happened? Was there a break-in?
It's being handled.
What does that mean?
-Diana, you know I can't talk about work--
-No.
I'm not one of your employees.
You've been gone for weeks,
and I have to hear from your assistant
that you're back.
[Diana] You drag us
around the world for this job.
Then we might as well leave.
-You don't care.
-No, Diana.
I should go.
[footsteps receding]
Al?
Say hi to the girls for me.
[unnerving music]
-[sharp inhale, groans]
-[young Jade] What?
-Billie? Billie?
-[door opens]
-Where were you?
-[light switch clicks]
She needs stitches.
[paced breathing]
[groans]
The bite's deep.
There's not much bleeding.
Get me the first aid kit.
What bit me?
A dog.
It had a rare genetic disease.
I was trying to help it.
[young Billie] It was sick.
Am I gonna get sick?
-I don't think so.
-You don't think so?
Will I have to quarantine?
No, it's not like Covid.
Why were you even there?
[dramatic music]
Let me guess. This was your idea?
No, no. It was mine.
I saw some rabbits in cages
when I was at your office.
I just…
[young Billie] I thought
Umbrella was doing testing.
We're not.
We're just trying to cure…
[sighs]
It doesn't matter.
If I hadn't woken up
and realized you were gone,
that you'd taken my keycard…
[Albert sighs deeply]
You can't tell anyone.
Why? What would happen?
[young Jade] And why can't we
take Billie to the hospital?
-If Umbrella knew you were there--
-What, you'd get fired?
-We'd be arrested. All of us.
-What, for trespassing?
And breaking and entering
and destruction of property.
[breathes deeply]
Look, some of the things
in that building are classified,
government projects.
Umbrella can…
[exasperated sigh]
We'd never see each other again.
Right now, I can fix this,
but it stays between us.
I need you to say it.
I promise.
Okay.
[dramatic music]
[young Jade] It's okay. It's okay.
Just breathe, just breathe, squeeze me.
[young Billie] Ow.
[breathing heavily]
[indistinct chatter]
[somber music]
[announcer] The following is
an Umbrella security announcement…
[indistinct chatter]
-[engine turns off]
-[gear shift cranks]
[keys jingle]
[indistinct announcement]
[serious music]
[machine whirring]
[marketplace chatter]
[whirring]
[indistinct announcement]
[fire roars]
[indistinct chatter]
[fire whooshes]
[drone humming]
[melancholy music]
[knocking on door]
[distant dog barking]
[door unlocks]
-[door opens]
-[Melinda] Yes?
[Jade] It's Melinda, right?
[Melinda] Do I know you?
Yeah. We… we met about six months back.
Your husband, Barry,
he got me here from Cairo.
Can I talk to him?
I'm sorry. Barry's not home.
-I can wait.
-[Melinda] Uh…
[exhales]
[squeaks]
I'm afraid Barry's in Selsey today.
When will he be back?
Um, I never really know.
[cats meowing]
[Melinda] Sorry. It's feeding time.
[chuckles]
This is, uh, Rocky.
Or maybe Sonny.
I can't keep them straight.
[grunts]
What did you say your name was?
The last time I was here,
there was no Umbrella.
-Now they're everywhere.
-[Melinda] Yes.
The city signed a security contract
with them last month.
It's been incredible.
We haven't had
a single infection since then.
I feel so much safer,
what with all the patrols and the cameras.
[Jade] Yeah.
That's Umbrella. Always watching.
Well, I have nothing to hide.
[chuckles]
Right.
I, uh, need to make a call.
Can I use your sat link?
Uh, just one, and then I'll leave.
[device beeps]
[pensive music]
[warbling]
[zipper rasps]
Arjun.
Jade. I, I've been trying to call.
The, the perimeter alarms
at your camp went off.
I, I didn't know if you were dead.
Not dead.
-[Arjun] What happened?
-Scavengers.
[Arjun] Oh, they took your equipment?
That's fine.
That, we can replace.
[Jade] They tried to sell me to Umbrella.
The company, they, they know I'm here.
Where are you?
Dover.
But Umbrella's everywhere.
They've taken over. I heard.
You need to get to Calais.
"Calais"?
That, that's Brotherhood territory.
And that's still better than Umbrella.
[Arjun] The Brotherhood hate Umbrella.
Get across the Channel,
I'll, I'll send a team to come meet you.
[Jade] Get across, how?
[pensive music continues]
I, I… I don't know.
Hey, hey, I'll be okay.
Uh, is, uh… Is Bea there?
Can I talk to her?
[Arjun] She's at ballet practice.
Good. Yeah, that's good.
Hey, uh, tell her I, um…
I will.
[emotional music]
[Arjun] Get home to us.
[inhales]
[door opens, squeaks]
[meows]
-All done, then?
-[zipper rasps]
[sighs deeply]
I need to see Barry.
I could call the authorities.
-[Melinda] Umbrella.
-You don't want to do that.
Oh, watch me.
[object clatters]
-[exhales nervously]
-[suspenseful music]
[loud thump]
What was that?
[meows]
Yeah.
[breathes heavily]
One of the cats must have
gotten locked in the bathroom.
-[meows]
-[soft thud]
Not a cat.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music]
[thuds]
[thumping continues]
[gasps]
[thumping]
[ominous music]
-[growls]
-Oh!
-[thuds]
-[cat squeals]
[snarling]
What the fuck?
When Barry came home
from his last trip, he…
He wasn't feeling well.
The next morning,
I found him chained in the bathroom.
He did that to himself.
You can't keep him chained up in there.
We both know how this ends.
He gets out, and he will kill you.
[breathes heavily]
Marriage is complicated.
Fine. You do you.
But I need to get to France,
and I can't take the ferry.
I need someone to smuggle me out.
Why? What did you do?
Well, I didn't keep
a fucking brain eater in my bathtub.
Let's start there.
[sighs]
Okay.
Did Barry know anyone who could help me?
I, uh…
Oh, maybe.
Charon.
Okay. Where is he?
Why, I, I… I don't know.
I mean, Barry kept all
that sort of thing in his pocketbook.
-Okay, and, and where's the pocketbook?
-[loud thump]
[sighs nervously]
[thuds]
In his pocket.
[suspenseful music]
[thumps]
[Barry growls]
[Melinda] Barry.
-She's not going to hurt you.
-[growls]
[grunts]
[Jade] Easy. Whoa!
-[curtains rattle]
-[flies buzzing]
Oh, my God!
Seriously, Melinda?
Cats carry disease.
[sighs in disgust]
-[growls]
-[thwacks]
[roars]
It's not in here.
His other pocket!
-[bones crackle]
-[flesh ripping]
-Yeah, yeah.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it.
-[blood splatters]
[growls]
[grunting and thumping]
[Melinda] Barry.
-[Jade] Melinda!
-[Melinda] Barry…
-[thumps]
-[growls]
-[shrieks]
-[panting]
-[object swishes]
-[teeth clacking]
-[grunts]
-[blood splatters]
[panting]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
-[breathing heavily]
-[cats meowing]
[Melinda sobbing]
[grunting]
[helmet clacks]
You…
You killed him.
-Wait…
-You promised.
[Melinda sobbing]
Get out.
-Get out!
-Yeah. Yes, that's the plan.
[Melinda sobbing]
Oh, and by the way, Melinda?
The cat thing? Super fucked up.
[Albert] Billie?
[muffled knocking on door]
Come in.
-[soft ringing]
-[door opens]
[high-pitch noise]
[door closes]
How are you feeling?
Sore.
Did you sleep? Look at me.
[groans]
Not really.
[Albert] Look right at me.
[young Billie] Why do you keep doing that?
The whites of your eyes, your sclera,
they're good indicators of health.
If the color changes,
it could be an early sign of infection.
[young Billie] So I'm getting sick?
[flashlight clicking]
No.
[sighs]
-[exhales]
-[squishes]
[young Billie groans]
[somber music]
[uneasy music]
But let's just be on the safe side.
["Beautiful Liar"
by X Ambassadors playing]
♪ You, beautiful liar ♪
♪ Your world is on fire ♪
♪ Look at the mess you've made of it all ♪
♪ All your desires ♪
♪ They creep like a virus ♪
♪ In perfect decay ♪
Hey!
How's Billie?
She's staying home today.
It's just a precaution.
I gave her something to help her rest.
-I can stay too.
-[Albert] No.
Both of you missing school would…
People would notice.
What does that even mean?
The car, in 15. No excuses.
♪ Lie to me now ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Don't lie ♪
♪ Don't you lie to me now ♪
[squeaking]
♪ Oh, oh ♪
[squirting]
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
[music stops]
[door opens]
[young Jade] Billie.
[somber music]
Bill.
[suspenseful music rises]
Thank you.
For saving me.
[exhales]
[suspenseful music]
[swishes]
[squeaking]
[suspenseful music continues]
[alarm beeps]
[beeping continues]
[Albert grunts]
[intense music]
[grunts]
[pierces]
[moaning]
[tense music]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
-[watch chimes]
-[sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, sorry!
What's going on?
Simon's got the new Deca-Dence.
It's the super-hard-to-get anime.
Not that hard. It's on Nyaa.
Not here. Umbrella blocks torrent sites.
Simon's, like, the only one
that could get around the firewall.
[murmuring]
-Hey.
-Cheers.
See ya.
[video plays Japanese]
[indistinct chatter]
Impressive.
You'll have to be more specific.
Cute.
The comment's cute, not you.
-You're disgusting.
-Oh, thank you.
I need your help.
Do you normally go around
asking disgusting people for help?
-Not if I can help it.
-You're saying the word help a lot.
I wanna get past Umbrella's firewall.
[sighs]
Why? Porn?
I can't tell you.
[chuckles]
So it's porn.
[zipper rasps]
What do I get?
What do you want?
I like your necklace.
[Jade exhales anxiously]
Hey, chill.
-[keyboard clacking]
-[sighs]
Where did you learn how to do this?
I, uh, taught myself.
I've lived in Umbrella housing
pretty much my whole life,
so, you know, fuck 'em.
[Simon] All right. I'm in.
[suspenseful music]
This is crazy.
He's talking about a dude who…
Animal bite turned him psycho,
like eating people psycho.
How did you hear about this?
A friend. From back home.
-Oh, get off. Give me. Give me.
-What?
[keyboard clacking]
-Dude.
-What?
[young Jade] It's a joke.
-Like you said. The guy's crazy.
-[sighs]
What? No thank you?
[Simon] Okay! Bye!
[suspenseful music]
[cats meowing]
[Melinda chuckles]
Hope you like oatmeal raisin.
My favorite.
Who needs delicious chocolate,
when you can toss a couple
of shriveled up grapes in there?
[chuckles]
[snickers]
[cracks]
[plate clanks]
If I'd known I was having company,
I would have tidied up.
No. No need to fuss.
One of our drones spotted
a person of interest in the area.
Just a few questions and…
We'll be out of your…
hair.
-Can I use your bath--
-No?
[chuckles]
-Have you seen--
-[Melinda] Oh, yes.
Horrible woman.
She was looking for my husband.
He's not home, you see.
[inhales]
[cat meows]
Cool.
Did she say why?
[door closes]
[rock music plays loudly]
[squeaking]
[clinking]
[indistinct chatter]
[rock music playing]
[woman] Ta, Charon.
Next.
-[grunts]
-Oi, get in the back of the queue.
Barry sent me.
A minute.
Barry still hasn't paid me
for the last transport.
-Where is he?
-Dead.
I need to get to Calais
without Umbrella knowing.
Yes, love. You and
half the people in this pub.
I hear you've got a way.
If I did, it'd be safe, secure,
and not cheap.
[sighs deeply]
[clinks]
It's not enough.
It's more than enough.
Fee's double for any friend of Barry's.
Next.
[indistinct chatter]
[sips, gulps]
[man burps]
[rock music playing]
Hey.
-[mug clacks]
-[man] Huh?
To the end of the world.
[man] Ta, love.
[music fades]
[Evelyn] Al.
You wanted to see me?
I always wanna see you. You know that.
How's your wife?
Diana and I are fine.
Thank you so much for asking.
You find out who hacked us?
Not yet, but we'll figure it out.
We always do.
What do you want, Evelyn?
[Evelyn] Like I told you.
Joy.
New and improved
and on shelves in two months.
That isn't possible.
[scoffs]
Sure it is.
[taps]
You're a genius!
Think of all the people
you could help, huh?
Cutters, the spastics.
Hey! The chronic masturbators?
What about us?
On that schedule, we'll make mistakes.
The last time
we made mistakes, people died.
Thousands of people. You were there.
[Albert] And that was barely contained.
This, if it goes wrong,
you're putting billions at risk.
[sighs deeply]
I won't do it. I'm out.
[scoffs]
-[inhales]
-[dark music]
You're not out.
I'm the only reason you were ever in.
[dark music continues]
You used to inject once a week.
Now how often? Every other day?
[gasps]
Every day?
Stop talking.
I get it. I do.
You need them.
Your cute little blood bags.
And I need you. So we all need each other.
Right?
-[Evelyn] Now get to work.
-[sighs]
[dark music]
[young Billie exhales]
[eerie music]
[soft ringing]
[sighs]
[squelching]
[breathes heavily]
[eerie music continues]
[music intensifies]
[retching]
[spits]
[Pablo whimpers]
[Pablo whines]
[young Billie] Okay.
Let's go for a walk.
[barks, growls]
-[Pablo snarls]
-Seriously?
[snarls, barks]
[phone chimes]
[indistinct chatter]
[dramatic music]
[man] Who are you?
-[young Jade] Who are you?
-[man] No, no, no, no. You contacted me.
How do I know you're not with Umbrella?
Well, for starters, I'm fucking 14.
-This was a mistake.
-[man] No, wait, wait.
Your message.
That someone was bitten. Was…
Was it real?
[young Jade] I don't know. Maybe.
What you posted on your site,
was that real?
[sighs]
Listen to me. If this is happening--
I'm not gonna talk to you
if I can't see your face.
[dramatic music continues]
-[light switch clicks]
-[sighs]
My name is Angel Rubio. I…
I was an investigative reporter
at The Baja Post.
But you're not anymore?
I've been looking into Umbrella's
health and safety violations for years.
Okay, people die there.
"Die"? How?
Last week, a worker at the Umbrella lab
went on a rampage,
and he killed nine people.
And when I talked to his wife,
she told me he was bitten
by an animal in the lab.
Within 72 hours,
he became erratic, violent.
He saw things. He heard things.
Where is he now?
Dead.
[Angel] But when I tried to publish,
well, Umbrella got me fired, hmm?
[inhales]
But people need to hear the truth.
And if this is happening again,
you need to tell me.
Have you seen the bite?
Was there a… a red rash around it?
I… Yeah.
Jade Wesker! Class!
-"Wesker"? No, wait!
-[Ms. Underwood] Now!
[dramatic music]
[young Billie] Dude, slow down. Slow down.
What's wrong with you?
[uneasy music]
-Hey, stop!
-[whimpers]
Pablo!
Whoa, whoa, hey, watch it!
-You okay?
-I'm sorry.
[tense music]
[Pablo barking]
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, my God. Thank you.
-He slipped out of his collar.
-You should really have him on a harness.
[snarling]
-Is this your dog?
-Yeah.
Pablo, come here. Come here.
Okay. I'm gonna need to see some proof.
What? Like a DNA test?
Like a picture, on your phone.
[Pablo snarls]
I left my phone at home.
[snarling]
[jogger] Look, he clearly
doesn't want to go with you.
I'm gonna take him to the shelter.
They'll sort it out.
You can't do that.
I really can.
[tense music]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
What the fuck?
[gasps]
I'm sorry.
-What's wrong with you?
-[young Billie] I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
-Hey. Hey. Okay. Hey, hey, hey. Okay.
-[barking aggressively]
[suspenseful music]
[indistinct chatter]
I swear I…
I had a token.
It's here somewhere.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no. No. Come on, where is it?
Come on!
[suspenseful music]
-[ferryman] Listen up!
-[chiming]
Listen up!
This way, people.
We board as soon as she docks.
[groans]
[gasping]
[vehicle approaching]
[engines revving]
[gunfire]
[drone voice] Halt!
You are engaged in illegal activities
under Umbrella jurisdiction!
Do not resist!
[rapid gunfire]
[tense music]
-[gunfire]
-[clamoring]
[fire roaring]
[thunderous gunfire]
[people clamoring]
[grunts softly]
[suspenseful music]
[moans]
♪ Oh, the loneliest girl in town ♪
♪ Is bought for pennies of prize ♪
♪ We dress her up in lovely gowns ♪
♪ She's easy on the eyes ♪
♪ So take what you want
Take what you can ♪
♪ Take what you please,
Don't give a damn ♪
♪ Ask for forgiveness, never permission ♪
♪ Take what you want, take what you can ♪
♪ Take what you please,
Don't give a damn ♪
♪ It's in the blood
And this is tradition ♪
[squeaking]
[thumping]
[bones crackling]
[hissing]
[glass shatters]
[ominous music]