[eerie music]
[somber music]
[brakes squeal]
You have marketing at 11:15,
accounting at 11:25,
and product development at 11:40.
-Tokyo's on the line.
-Tell them "no".
-Who?
-All of them.
Albert.
What happened to your pretty face?
It's, um, last night. He fought back.
-But you got…
-Nothing.
-Fantastic.
-But there might be another way.
Joy.
[Albert] At the right dosage,
it lowers inhibitions.
-If we mixed it with scopolamine--
-The Alzheimer's drug?
Well, they use high doses for Alzheimer's,
but it was developed
as a truth serum by the CIA.
If I'm right,
that combination could act like, uh…
a sodium pentothal on steroids.
And if you're wrong?
I don't know,
but we're running out of options.
People could know he's here.
They could start asking questions.
[sighs]
[doors close]
[beeps, clacks]
Hello, Angel.
How are you feeling?
[snorts, spits]
I'm a doctor.
Not the kind
that works with patients, really,
but I do know when someone's in pain,
all they really want
is for that pain to end.
Is that what you want?
Because I want to help you.
[scoffs]
[Albert] I'm your friend.
-[swishes]
-[sighs]
-Wh… what's that?
-[Albert] Help.
This can take all your pain away.
I just need you
to answer a question first.
Who told you what happened here?
[Albert] Well?
-You don't have to do this.
-I wish that was true.
-[Albert] Answer my question or I leave.
-[sighs]
And the person that replaces me?
He'll be worse.
He'll be nothing but pain.
And we won't be able to help each other.
Like we can now.
No one.
[rustles]
[Albert] Wrong answer.
But, hey…
[sniffles, moans]
-Let's try anyway.
-[Angel] Wait.
Tell my father I'm sorry.
[groans]
[chair rattling]
[dramatic music]
[doors open]
What just happened?
I told you it might not work.
[clacks]
-What do we got?
-I can't get a pulse.
[defibrillator hums]
Clear.
-[med guy 1] Charging.
-I was looking for a mole.
[med guy 1] Clear.
[Evelyn] You maybe just killed
the only person who could give him to me.
Is it you?
Evelyn.
If I wanted to ruin you, ruin Umbrella,
I could have done it a thousand times.
So fuck off.
Don't.
[Albert] Why? He won't do anything to me.
Because hurting me hurts Umbrella.
And let's face it, Umbrella…
is all you have.
Mr. Roth.
[fingers snap]
[dark music]
[sighs]
[trilling]
[serious music]
[woman] I want it all packed
and ready to go. Understood?
Move it.
You heard the orders. Go.
[ominous music]
[prisoner] We're the same. We're the same.
-[trooper] Get in!
-[prisoner] Say it again.
Souvenir?
Pack this to go. In my personal stash.
-So how are things?
-[Jade] "How are things"?
-You took my blood.
-[Billie] Sorry. Protocol.
[Jade] I thought you never left
Umbrella territory.
Hmm. Can you blame me?
Evelyn sent me to bring you in.
[Billie] I told her
it was a waste of time,
but she thinks you could be useful
in the world to come.
"The world to come"?
[Billie] You should know she's not asking.
She doesn't have to.
[Jade] She sent
her little toy to do it for her.
Her pet project.
Last I saw you, you were 18 and pregnant
with two busted-out front teeth.
Where's the kid?
I lost it.
-[Jade] How's Dad?
-Died asking for you.
[Billie] Yeah. That Albert,
he never minded playing favorites.
[Jade] I wasn't the favorite.
Maybe not at first.
But then, working on the fringes,
killing yourself to make up for your sins.
Sound familiar?
Our father was a psychopath.
Sure, but we've all got stuff.
Jade, it's time to come in.
Aren't you tired?
[Billie] Since the last time I saw you,
you did six months in Tokyo,
nearly a year in Greenland.
Until you get caught on the run
with a head in your bag.
Which, I mean, talk about psychopath.
Where were you gals going?
The University.
That's where you were headed,
no pun, right?
[Billie] Yeah, Baxter
was an efficient weasel.
We've been looking for that place.
Where is it?
-Fuck off.
Twins. Jinx.
Clear it out.
[dripping]
Billie, what the fuck is this shit?
I'm not giving you the University.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
And Umbrella,
they don't care about a new world.
They want control.
And you, of all people, should know that
because it's been our whole lives.
I will die before I go back to that place.
That's what I wanted you to say.
[emotional music]
Jade, when I chose Umbrella,
I chose wrong.
I should have picked you.
And now,
I guess I just wanted to say goodbye.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-[Billie] The virus.
-You're immune.
-I'm not.
Sure, it moves slower,
but the clock's still ticking.
Right down to zero.
[Billie] I just wanted to see you again.
I like to think of you as a happy,
working hard partner who keeps
trying to talk you into having a family.
But then, I worry.
That just feels
a little too settled for Jade Wesker.
We intercepted a signal.
There's a University team looking for you
less than a mile to the west.
[chains rattle]
You could leave too.
Just because I'm not chained up
doesn't mean I'm free.
[Billie] There's just one thing
I need you to do.
Punch me in the face.
-What?
-Oh, and…
-[rips]
-[Jade shrieks in pain]
[Jade] Stop…
They put a tracker in
when we took your blood.
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[panting]
I never stopped being your sister.
♪ Everybody thinks that we're insane ♪
♪ Just because we do not think the same ♪
♪ They wanna see us go our separate ways ♪
♪ No way ♪
♪ I am happy just to hear you breathe ♪
♪ The only medicine I'll ever need ♪
♪ All I wanna do is get out ♪
♪ I wanna do is get out ♪
♪ All I wanna do is get out of here ♪
♪ All I wanna do is get out ♪
[gun clicks]
[gasps]
[suspenseful music]
-Jade.
-[Jade] Gideon.
We've been looking for you.
[panting]
[waves crashing]
Amrita.
-I missed you.
-Same, love.
[Gideon] Oy, we need to move.
And we will move. Very quickly.
Tongue.
-[Amrita] Find a new best friend?
-[chuckles]
It's a specimen.
[Jade] Amrita, I think this
is what we've been looking for.
[Amrita] Come on. Let's go.
[action music]
[engine roars]
[bright music]
-[Amrita] Take it to the lab. Tell no one.
-Mm-hmm.
Go.
What's up?
[Paolo] My love.
[grunts]
Hey.
-Where's my welcome home committee, huh?
-Oh, right behind me.
[Bea] Mommy!
[Jade] Bea.
Mom.
Are you okay?
On the phone, you sounded scared.
I know. I know. But I'm better now. Yeah?
[exhales]
-[Arjun] Are you real?
-[Jade] Are you real?
Are you okay? Is everyone okay?
-[Bea] Uh-huh.
-Yeah, we're good.
Mom. I'm playing piano in the talent show.
"Piano"? What happened to ballet?
[Arjun] It's actually pretty impressive.
You're gonna love it.
Yeah, I'm sure I will.
Dad, I have to go.
[Arjun] See you at dinner.
Rehearsal.
Right.
-[Arjun] What?
-[Jade] What?
I've been gone for six months,
and that's it?
[Arjun] You wanted her
to break down sobbing?
-Rend her clothes?
-[Jade] No.
Tsk. All right, fine.
Yeah, just a little rending, maybe a tear.
Mm.
I missed you.
Yeah, you better.
[emotional music]
[ominous music]
[door opens]
[sighs]
I have been fantasizing
about this for months.
-[Arjun] Oh.
-[door closes]
-Well, that's very…
-[groans]
-[Jade] I'm so…
-…flattering.
[giggles]
All right. Tell me what I've been missing.
-[grunts]
-Uh…
It's been smooth.
We've had a record crop.
There's been a baby boom.
And, oh, Terrence's group brought back
about half a library from Istanbul.
And what about our
10-going-on-35-year-old daughter?
Uh, well, Bea's progress has been…
It's exceptional.
-I think she might be a bit of a genius.
-[chuckles]
She does well in mathematics.
She's a natural at science and sports.
But, you know, recently,
the one thing she can't get enough of…
is literature.
Yeah. She's playing the piano now.
-Somebody must be thrilled.
-Yeah.
You know, just be careful.
My father was one of those parents
who tried to raise their kids
to be just like them.
And, uh, he only went one for two.
[moans]
You sure about that?
[Jade] Hmm?
I mean, come on.
[Arjun] Tell me you don't want
to be in the lab right now.
I'm not like my father.
-Jade, I wasn't--
-[Jade] No, I…
When my father did what he did,
he only cared about himself.
When I was out in the field,
for six months, I…
I had nothing to show for it.
So I told myself, stay, finish the job,
so you don't have to leave again.
Yeah.
-And then I found this zero.
-Oh, the head?
You would not believe.
I knew I couldn't just run away.
I knew I had to go back and get it.
Otherwise,
it all would have been for nothing.
And I didn't do that for me.
I did that for her.
You… went back?
What do you mean, "I had to go back"?
At the bunker.
What, the Brotherhood bunker?
The one full of monsters?
[groans]
You don't get it. It…
This zero could control other zeros.
Okay. It could make them do things.
If I could figure out how,
do you understand what that means?
We… we talked about this, right?
No more unnecessary risks.
No more Kamikaze Jade.
-No. It wasn't like that, okay? I had to.
-No, you didn't.
-No, I did.
And if you think you did that for Bea,
you're lying to yourself.
Of course, I did that for Bea.
Why else…
-Okay. What if she lost you?
-She didn't.
-This time.
-[Jade] Don't do this.
-I'm the parent here. Me, her mother.
-And I'm what, huh?
The babysitter?
Look, just because I'm not
her biological father, doesn't mean--
[Jade] Just… just stop.
[door closes]
[sighs]
[shower runs]
[somber music]
[rustles]
[bottles clinking]
[somber music continues]
[Arjun] So…
[grunts]
How did it go?
Ms. Kyoko asked
if I wanted to have dinner there.
[Bea] Thursday, like usual?
[Arjun] Well, maybe
take this week off, huh?
On account of mom being back.
She'll be working. She won't care.
[gulps]
Hmm.
Hey, remember when we read
A Midsummer Night's Dream?
And Shakespeare wrote that,
"The object of art
is to give life a shape."
-Yeah.
-[Arjun] Yeah.
Well, your mother's work is her art,
and it gives shape to her life.
And she'd be lost without it.
Is that why she's always gone?
When Mom was young,
her daddy tried to fix the world.
But, instead, he made it much, much worse.
[Arjun] And your mother, she's spent
her whole life trying to make up for that.
For him.
That's not fair. She didn't do anything.
No, she didn't.
But it's the second most important thing
to know about her.
What's first?
[Arjun] She loves you more than anything.
[emotional music]
-[Jade] Hey, team.
-Hey, Mom.
-You're not eating?
-We're waiting for you.
Good.
Because I'm going to have
all your portions.
What do you think about that, huh?
We're gonna get all the hot stuff.
[door closes]
She went down fast tonight.
Mm. Must have been all of the excitement.
Arjun.
Hmm?
[clacks]
What I said earlier…
That… that doesn't matter.
[chuckles]
No, it does.
Listen.
The day you came into my life…
into Bea's…
I love you.
[tender music]
Wait, wait. Hold on. Wait, wait.
[Jade laughs]
[teeth brushing]
[mug clinks]
[sighs]
-[Arjun gargling]
-[Jade sighs]
[Arjun spits]
My father is dead.
My sister told me.
Umbrella sent her to bring me back,
but she let me go.
Well, do you…
I mean, can you trust her?
She said she's dying.
[Arjun] Jade.
I'm so sorry.
Part of me is…
[exhales]
…playing memories in my head
like home movies.
But the other part of me wishes
I'd killed her when I had the chance.
[alarm wailing]
Ghost ships drifting, off starboard.
[crew] Ghost ships acknowledged.
Suggesting intercept course.
[propeller whirring]
[burbles]
[clacking]
[beeps]
[faucet running]
[distant retching]
-[distant coughing]
-[toilet flushes]
[sniffles]
Sorry.
-How far along are you?
-I…
Two months.
[Amrita] We haven't really told anyone.
I'm a bit terrified.
Good. That fear, the adrenaline?
You're gonna need that
through the 2:00 a.m. feedings,
changing diapers.
I mean, have you ever been peed on before?
Once.
-College.
-[Jade] Okay.
[chuckles]
Well, expect a lot more of that.
You make it sound amazing.
It is.
I never wanted kids.
I was… young and alone.
It was the hardest, best thing.
[Jade] Amrita.
I'm so happy for you.
-So, ready to bust it out?
-Let's do it.
-What's so special about this lovely lady?
-She could control other zeros.
How?
Well, we always knew
the virus would evolve.
But zeros can't see. Most can't hear.
So if she was communicating…
It was through smell.
A pheromone maybe. On her breath.
This gland, right here.
I've never seen anything like it.
Don't let me get too lost in it, okay?
I've got Bea's piano thing.
I've set an alarm. You'll be there.
[serious music]
[squelches]
Okay. Observing the epithelial tissue.
[Jade] All right, the zero's cells
are putting out two distinct enzymes.
But…
Oh, shit.
[sighs]
Exposure to oxygen breaks them down.
Maybe they have to be mixed
with something?
Like?
[Amrita] If they're going
into her throat, her mouth.
Spit?
[Jade] Okay. And what's that?
Uh, water, electrolytes, mucus…
[Amrita] Amylase, lipase,
IgA, and lysozymes.
But the ratios…
There are thousands
of possible combinations.
Trial one.
[failure notification tone]
[Jade] Trial 11.
Trial 22.
[failure notification tone]
Trial 35 .
-[clacking]
-[failure notification tone]
Trial 44.
[failure notification tone]
[sighs]
And that is the end of trial 55.
[exhales]
I'm calling it.
-We'll start again tomorrow.
-Just… No. One more.
We're almost out of precursors.
We'll need to trade
with one of the other labs.
-We could steal them.
-Jade.
[both laughing]
[Jade] Um…
[spits]
That's disgusting.
-[clacks close]
-But it's trial 56.
[frustrated sigh]
[sighs]
[serious music]
[trilling]
[chimes]
[hopeful music]
Disgusting worked.
[Jade] The sample.
It's stable.
Fuck me.
[chuckles]
[both laughing]
-I…
-[timer beeping]
-Bea.
-[timer clicks]
-Go. I'll start isolating them.
-But…
-I'll page you the second they're ready.
-Okay. But, you know, they're delicate.
-You have to be careful when--
-Jade. Go.
-[Amrita] Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah.
-[Jade] Thank you.
-Go.
-And… and get samples!
-[Amrita] Yes! Go!
[door closes]
[violin playing]
[door opens]
[indistinct chatter]
-Where is Arjun?
-Forget him. Where's my wife?
-Working.
-Of course.
Did you even stop for lunch?
-She needs to eat.
-Yeah, for two.
-[applause]
-Like she wouldn't tell me.
[laughs]
I want to welcome friends,
family, and parents
to a celebration of arts and culture,
into which I can tell you
we have poured all of our hearts.
[clapping]
So why teach children poetry,
Shakespeare, dance, and music now,
at this point of our history?
Well, I think we're all dedicated
to collecting everything we can
from our past
and preserving it
in our collective memory,
because that is what the arts were
in their most ancient beginnings.
It was a way to imprint deep,
emotional stories on our souls.
Stories we didn't want to lose,
because even in times like these,
we are the stories we tell.
[applause]
Bea?
[approaching footsteps]
-Ooh!
-[gasps]
["Symphony No. 5"
by Ludwig van Beethoven plays]
by Ludwig van Beethoven continues]
[gasps in disbelief]
-[chuckles]
-[device beeping]
[muffled "Symphony No. 5"
by Ludwig van Beethoven playing]
[eerie music]
[Jade grunts]
[lid closes]
[mysterious music]
[squirts]
Introducing the first enzyme
to a sample of the T-virus.
I mean, the virus
is going nowhere near this enzyme.
[Jade] Pass me the other one.
[suspenseful music]
And it's as if this enzyme attracts it.
-[Amrita] So if it went airborne…
-"Airborne."
And then, you could mark a target
and send zeros after it.
-[Jade] But with the red…
-Keep them away.
[gasps, chuckles]
Jade.
If this is right, we need to test it.
On a real zero.
[Amrita] We just have
to get permission first.
Dock the ship, and wait two weeks.
And we will.
If I don't get you back to Paolo
at a reasonable hour,
-he's gonna kick my ass.
-[sighs]
Here you go.
[vials clacking]
[ominous music]
[swishes]
[splashes]
[grunts]
[panting]
[growls]
[flesh pierces]
[panting]
[zipper rasps]
[heaving]
[woman clears throat]
-[Serene] Hey.
-Oh, shit!
Serene.
-Hey.
-[chuckles]
-Hey. Uh, you're up early.
Yeah, you know,
it's just so loud in the field,
-I think you get used to it.
-Hmm.
-[Serene] Need help with that?
-Oh, no, it's all right. I got it.
-All right.
-[Jade] Thanks.
[sighs]
[stretching]
[grunts]
[Bea] Mom?
Bea.
I came to bring you some…
What did you do?
Hey, it's okay. Everything's okay.
You're with me, so you're safe.
[snarling]
I've got this all under control.
[chair rasps]
She just came out of the cold water.
What happens to zeros in the cold?
-They slow down.
-Exactly.
[softly]
Does Dad know?
Here, I'm gonna show you something.
But you have to stay way over here, okay?
When I was away, I found a zero
who could talk to other zeros.
-Zeros can't talk.
-Not with words.
[Jade sighs]
Now, you see this?
This is a pheromone.
It's like a… a smell.
And when zeros smell it,
they can't hurt you.
If we put this on people
on the ship, on entire cities,
we could build a whole new world,
make things like they used to be.
Dad said when he was a kid,
he could have ice cream every day,
not just on New Year's.
Well, you can have ice cream
and you can do anything you want.
That's the world I want for you, Bea.
-Okay.
-Yeah?
But right now,
I gotta figure out if this thing works.
You stay right there by the door.
[sighs]
[spraying]
Okay.
[eerie music]
-Mom?
-It's okay.
She won't even know I'm here.
[uneasy music]
[uneasy music continues]
[chuckles]
It worked!
-[growls]
-[snaps]
Bea! Get out! Go!
-[roars]
-[snaps]
-[Bea shrieks]
-Run!
[thuds, groans]
[Bea screams]
[Bea] Help!
[squeals]
[growls]
Help!
[panting]
-[Amrita] What's wrong?
-Over there! There!
-[growls]
-[shrieks]
-[munching]
-[Amrita screaming]
[tragic music]
[ominous music]
-[gunshot]
-[body thuds]
[Jade] Bea? Bea?
Bea?
[crowd panicking]
[door opens]
-[clicks]
-No!
What was it?
[man] Oh, God.
-No.
-Paolo!
-Bea?
-[Bea] Dad!
-[man] Are there more?
-I don't know.
[Jade] No.
It's…
It's my fault.
I brought it on the ship.
-I was trying to test.
-It's your fault?
I… I didn't think that I…
[stammers]
We… we were working…
[Paolo] You killed her.
[gun fires]
-[breathing anxiously]
-[helicopters whirring]
-[man 2] It's coming! Heads up!
-[man 3] You see them?
[man 4] Choppers incoming.
[ominous music]
[music intensifies]
[technician] Here we go.
-I want to know what killed him.
-Yes, ma'am.
[flesh rips]
[technician] Let's take a look.
-[gasps]
-[metal rattling]
[snarling]
[loud internal thumping]
Interesting.
[Albert] This is insane!
[thumps]
You can't keep me here.
[muffled rustling]
[clacks]
[man] Since when are you
such a scaredy-cat?
[suspenseful music]
[dramatic music]
Hey, bro.
[dramatic music continues]