Hello, Papa.
Did you find work?
Rent's late again.
I'll take care of it.
How? With your work?
I have work.
You know, I've lived here my whole life.
I've watched these corporations come in,
and build their factories
as if we don't exist.
They say they're giving us opportunities
by creating jobs.
And when things go bad,
when people get hurt,
our "saviors" disappear.
They don't care about us,
unless we do something.
Yes?
Tell me about your husband.
What was he like?
He was funny.
He loved baseball.
He loved his job.
Was that where…
it happened?
He was…
running a test,
and the cage was left open…
and the rat bit him.
He told me…
that it was so fast.
You mentioned…
a rash.
Were there any other symptoms?
Yes.
He complained about flashing lights,
loud noises,
even the baby would bother him,
and then…
he would get angry all the time.
He became very aggressive.
And these symptoms,
they lasted for three days?
They said he killed people.
You don't believe me, do you?
Of course I believe you.
I found this.
In his things.
People need to know the truth,
because them,
they lie.
Heretics.
Why?
To rid the apple of the worm,
it takes the knife.
Another.