[unnerving music]
[chiming music]
[reporter] Umbrella.
A company besieged by legal scandal
and falling stock prices
is now trying to reinvent itself
with a major push
into direct-to-consumer drugs.
Critics say that the company's operating
at a dangerous burn rate,
but Umbrella's betting big on the move.
Brainchild of newly minted CEO,
Evelyn Marcus.
Tell me about Joy.
Well, they say you can't put a price
on happiness, but sure you can.
-If you bottle it.
-[reporter chuckles]
[reporter] You sound like your father.
He founded Umbrella
before being… pushed out.
He did.
And I still like to think of this
as a family business.
[reporter] Still, I have
to ask you about the past.
Raccoon City.
It was an unimaginable tragedy.
A horrible accident
that no one could have seen coming.
Don't get me wrong.
The old Umbrella, my father,
made his share of mistakes,
but this is not that company.
[Evelyn] The things
we're working on today…
they're gonna change the world.
[tense music]
-[gunshots]
-[alarm wailing]
[people scrambling, screaming]
[bullets ricochet]
[clacks]
[clacks, creaks]
[grunts]
Those are rubber bullets, right?
[gunshots continue]
[tense music]
[clanging]
[Liam] Help!
Help!
Mom?
[gasps]
[Jade] Come on.
-Over here.
-[door creaks]
-[moaning in fear]
-[bullets ricochet]
[trilling]
[indistinct muttering]
[trooper] Sir, we lost her.
So, you find her.
Chase down the runners.
I want a team along the outer docks,
another in the trees.
[man wincing in pain]
Dude. Ouch.
[giggles]
[hopeless music]
[sighs]
-[gasps]
-[door opens]
-[Enya] No!
-[Mark] Don't shoot!
-Don't shoot!
-[Liam] Mom?
Mom!
[Enya speaks softly]
Liam, come here.
[sobs]
I'm sorry.
We thought he was gone. We…
I don't know how to thank you.
[haunting music]
[young Jade] Billie.
[suspenseful music]
Billie?
[young Billie] Go away.
No! We have to talk.
[squelching]
[young Jade] I just wanna know
you're all right. Billie.
[door opens, closes]
Oh, you're home. Great.
I'm starving. What's for dinner?
What?
[sighs]
How's your sister?
She's…
good.
Catching up on school, I think.
When she's done…
-tell her I'll be right back.
-Yes, sir.
[tense music]
[sighs]
Billie, come on.
It's fine.
[soft ringing]
I'm fine.
[lights click]
[ominous music]
[rat squeaking]
[vials clinking]
[suspenseful music]
-[rasps]
-[Mark] Who the hell sent that drone?
Umbrella.
"Umbrella"?
-They wouldn't.
-[Jade] Oh, they really would.
You have a family.
You should've taken the ferry.
We can't.
Why not?
[uneasy music]
[bottles clink]
You're smuggling contraband.
Forty-year-old contraband.
[Mark] The Black market on these
will keep us alive while we resettle.
We've got people in Calais.
My sister, her girls.
He's been through so much.
[Enya] We just want
to raise him amongst family.
Give him something that feels… normal.
There's gotta be another way across.
There is.
[Enya] The "chunnel."
Traffickers run people through
to the other side,
and they don't ask questions.
-It's too dangerous.
-And if we stay here? What, then?
We spent most of our money on the boat.
Okay, so we pull what we've got,
and we go together.
No offense, but why should we trust you?
She saved Liam.
Look, the only way you can trust anyone
is when they need you.
And right now, we need each other.
[somber music]
[squeaking and munching]
[squirts]
[clinks]
Jesus, are you okay?
Hey.
[exhales]
Good talk.
Nice sister moment.
♪ Still ♪
[panicked breathing]
♪ Falling ♪
♪ Breathless and on ♪
♪ Again ♪
♪ Inside ♪
♪ Today ♪
♪ Like two strangers ♪
♪ Turning into dust ♪
[chimes]
[sighs]
[ticking]
-[soft ringing]
-[heart pounding]
-[woman] Eat it.
-[whooshes]
So where are you down from?
'Round York.
I heard it's beautiful around there.
Why'd you leave?
Didn't have any choice.
[Mark] The walls kept the zeros out, but…
didn't stop the virus from getting in.
That's…
I'm so sorry.
Everybody lost somebody, right?
[melancholy music]
[breathes deeply]
[eerie ringing]
[static scratches]
[loud flickering]
[sighs]
-[clanks]
-[young Jade] Hmm!
[Albert clears throat]
So how's the new school?
They have kombucha on tap.
[footsteps descending]
-Hey, morning.
-Billie.
[Albert] What are you doing?
-Going to school?
-Uh, no.
We should give it a few days.
Dad, I'm fine. And I'm missing classes.
-I don't think you should--
-[young Jade] I think she looks great.
I mean, you said it yourself.
If we miss too much school,
people could notice.
Billie.
Come here.
Okay, look at me.
[uneasy music]
And?
It's better.
So can I go?
Uh…
-That's a yes.
-Thanks, Dad.
[Albert] I… No, you, you…
[sighs]
Call me if anything doesn't…
feel right.
Jade.
Keep an eye on your sister.
[agitated breathing]
Do you feel like, weird?
Mad?
I'm mad that you keep asking me
asshole questions.
[indistinct chatter]
Because I'm good.
And after everything…
everything that happened,
I just want things to be normal.
Okay?
[wheels rattling]
[heart pounding]
[loud rattling]
[echoing]
Billie?
Billie.
[exhales]
[Simon] Jade, hey.
Hi, I'm Simon.
I'm gonna be late.
Stay.
"Stay"?
Hey.
-Hey!
-What?
What do you mean "what"?
The fuck just happened back there?
Dad… Dad just gave me these drugs to sleep
and I just… I think I have a hangover.
Yeah, I don't know.
He's cute.
-[young Jade] He's okay.
-[young Billie] He likes you.
So what? Like, I miss one day,
and you have a boyfriend now?
-No, he just helped me.
-[young Billie] With what?
Homework.
[young Jade] Look.
You'd tell me
if something was wrong, right?
You should go.
Your boyfriend's waiting.
[sharp exhale]
I don't think your sister
likes me very much.
Why do you care?
[sighs]
She doesn't know you.
You literally just met.
I don't know, it's just a vibe.
I'm quite good at reading people.
And you think I'm super-hot.
Charming as shit.
[chuckles]
I think you're full of shit.
The files you sent me
were only half downloaded.
I need the rest.
-I thought you said that that was a joke?
-[young Jade] It is.
It's super funny.
[hazy music]
Umbrella does shady shit.
-Like Facebook shady, but--
-So you can't get them.
-No, I can.
-Then do it.
You know, you're not like, bossy at all.
[young Jade] You love it.
Yeah.
[fire crackles]
[doors open]
Four to cross.
[Dodger] Well, you've come
to the right place.
I don't know what you've heard,
but since our outfit's taken over,
passage is much safer.
Only three people died last month.
"Three"?
Well, if you want repeat business,
you've got to put the customer first.
[Dodger] You sure you want to take a kid?
-Whole team.
-It's your call.
Right, all that's left then
is the dirty business of business.
[clinking]
[Dodger laughs]
This will get you one.
[keys jingle]
That'll do.
[Devil-horns] All right, everybody in.
My advice.
Keep your eyes on the floor
and your hands
and your feet tucked in tight.
And we'll get you through,
quick and quiet.
This is safe, right?
Sure.
[man] Come on, come on,
let's go, let's go, let's go.
Hey.
It's okay.
-[man] Going up!
-[door squeaks]
Okay, let's go.
[engine starts]
[dark music]
[Evelyn] Italian leather.
Fancy.
[beeps]
Come on, honey. You think I'd miss
your world-famous lemon salmon?
I'll be home by eight.
Promise.
Love you, too.
[beeps]
Sounds like things are better at home.
I'm a great lay.
Let's have some fun.
[Evelyn] Now, I'm not gonna lie to you.
Tijuana was a setback.
But Joy still represents
the future of this company.
For most of its history,
Umbrella's been a contractor
for the US government.
But if we're gonna survive,
we have to look elsewhere.
Outward, to the people.
That's why you put me in charge.
[Janet] But I understand Dr. Wesker
wants to suspend this project.
Oh, you heard wrong.
Right, Al?
[Albert] Prescribed in the correct dosage,
Joy can be a miracle pill.
An antidepressant that lowers anxiety,
increases focus.
But the drug contains
a derivative of the T-virus.
A pathogen we originally developed
for the American military.
That project was, um…
ill-fated.
And while we thought
we'd solved the problem,
in larger doses, the viral load
not only activates the T-virus,
it becomes transmissible.
Usually through a bite.
[Janet chuckles]
So we just tell people
not to bite each other.
[all laughing]
It's, um…
-not that easy.
-[zipper rasps open]
[squeaking]
[Albert] This is what happens
when you overdose on Joy.
The subject becomes desiccated.
Violent.
For rats, it takes a few hours.
For a human…
three days.
But the end is always the same.
The T-virus makes monsters.
Joy, could be a billion-dollar drug,
but we need to delay the launch
until we can stabilize it.
[Evelyn] Well, I don't
see this as a problem.
Wait, did you… Did you say
you don't see that as a problem?
[Evelyn] It's an opportunity.
Yes.
We need to rethink Joy.
That gives us a chance to make it better.
See, in our trials, we found
that slightly tweaking the virus
does something unexpected.
This subject was given, let's call it,
a souped-up version of Joy.
[aggressive barking]
-[alarm sounding]
-[dog whimpers]
[cage door clacks open]
[meows]
So this is our billion-dollar idea?
-Dogs?
-[Evelyn] No.
Our team anticipates
a similar response in human trials.
Which means,
it goes beyond the "feel good."
The new Joy would allow us
to influence attention, behavior,
all through a series of triggers.
So imagine that same pattern
on a website or an app.
A Joy user wouldn't be able to look away.
So we're doing mind control now?
[chuckles]
Of course not, Janet.
But hey, who hasn't popped a Xany
and gone hunting for Louboutin's.
Right, Alan?
Joy will make Umbrella
the biggest company in the world.
Fuck Google, Fuck Zuckerberg.
They deliver eyeballs.
Umbrella will deliver minds.
That's not a billion-dollar drug.
That's a trillion-dollar drug.
None of which eliminates the danger.
How much would I have
to take to turn into…
that?
Let's see.
Three?
No?
Ten?
Am I getting close?
-Al?
-[thumps]
Twenty thousand.
So we know what goes on the warning label.
Right?
[indistinct chatter]
[announcer] Attention, students.
This is a reminder
that all personal items,
including purses, helmets, and cellphones
should be kept in your locker.
Thank you.
[tense music]
[muffled chatter]
[gasps]
[roars]
[panting]
Can't help you, mate.
[suspenseful music]
So you haven't seen her?
Well, even if I had,
which I'm not saying I have…
I've got principles.
Standards. Criteria and such.
I…
Is… is he for real?
I have no idea what you're saying.
What I'm saying is fuck off, Umbrella.
-[laughs]
-[vehicle approaching]
[chuckles]
[squeaks]
[ominous music]
Nice ride.
[forced chuckle]
[chains rattling]
[uneasy music]
[Enya] Where you headed?
Home.
And where's that?
The University.
Like, a school?
No.
The University, it, uh…
preserves the old world.
[Jade] Books, art, history.
It's like a… a backup disk
for civilization.
It will help us rebuild
when all of this is over.
If it's ever over.
What's it like?
Peaceful.
"Peaceful."
Do you know what it was like to be… bored?
I try not to think about it.
The world that we had.
[sighs]
The one they never got.
[metal creaking and clonking]
Okay, next leg of the trip.
Everyone keep your mouths shut.
And I mean super glued.
You hear me?
[growling]
[eerie music]
[rips]
[clinks]
What?
Lickers.
[Jade] They hunt by sound.
[Lickers rattling]
[clicks]
[siren wailing in distance]
[softly]
The hell?
[man] Warning! You are engaged
in illegal activities
under Umbrella jurisdiction!
Do not resist!
[laughs]
[tires screech]
[suspenseful music]
[man] Do not start your engine.
Do not exit the vehicle.
You are under arrest.
[trooper] Move out.
Pull them out and line them up.
Yes, sir.
Let's go. Round them up.
[Lickers rattling]
Where's that coming from?
The heck?
-[squelches]
-[groans]
Contact!
[gunshots]
-What's happening?
-[shushes]
-Mom, look.
-[gasps]
-[glass shatters]
-[roars]
[flesh rips]
[gasps, screams]
-[tongue whips]
-[screams]
[screams]
-[tongue whips]
-[screams]
[Devil-horns] Move.
No, no, let me go. Let me go!
-Hey, over here.
-[shushes]
-There's another way out.
Here.
-Go, go.
-Come on. Right this way.
Go, go, go!
-[metal clonking]
-[Licker snarling]
-[roars]
-[gasps]
[clonks]
[groans]
[panting]
Come on!
-[tongue whips]
-Help me!
[woman screams]
[fire roars]
[switch clanks]
Service door. Down there.
Go, go! Go!
[panting]
Come on!
[humming, clonks close]
-[all screaming]
-[Lickers screeching]
-[ticking]
-[fire crackles]
[rat squeaking]
-[Evelyn] Like I said…
-[scratches]
…fun.
Mickey was a nice touch.
-The Board decided.
-For you.
It's a trillion dollars, Al.
I'm offering them a bright shiny future,
and you've got, what?
A fancy pen?
[sighs]
[Evelyn] How you doing?
You seem edgy.
Top off today?
We took behavioral modification
off the table.
I changed my mind.
You're risking millions of lives
for what, money?
A spot on the DOW?
If this scales,
can't you see where this is going?
It's not about the stock price.
It's about changing the world.
[Evelyn] Just…
think about it.
Global warming, gone.
World hunger, not anymore.
Fuck.
We can turn the world vegan if we want to.
And who gets to decide any of that?
Oh, I do.
[Evelyn] My friend at the FDA
agreed to rush human trials.
-[cage thuds]
-[Albert] Because you bribed him.
Because I'm such a charming lady.
But I need you to stabilize the formula
and bring production online.
[sighs]
What happened in Raccoon City,
we'll take precautions.
The only precaution is a cure.
-We don't have one of those.
-So let me find one.
-Look, get me a team.
-I need you focused.
[Albert] I can do both.
And, look, if something does go wrong,
and the virus gets out of control…
imagine how much money
Umbrella makes if you own the cure?
[dark music]
After hours.
[Evelyn] And Joy come first.
-Fine.
[rat squeaking]
-[Albert] Wait, Evelyn, don't do that.
-Oh, and, Al?
No more surprises.
I don't like surprises.
[squeaking]
[flesh rips]
[Ms. Foster] Viral modulation.
Think of it as Darwinism
on a molecular scale.
Virus has literally changed
the cells of their host
for their own survival and reproduction.
And as a virus alters
or modulates its host,
what does that look like to us?
[keypad clacking]
[Ms. Foster]
Symptoms from the everyday stuff.
Sweating, vomiting,
to the extreme cases where viruses
attack the blood-brain barrier,
causing hallucinations.
Changes in mood, behavior,
violent outbursts,
until the body can fight it off or…
not.
[anxious breathing]
Dude.
-[paced breathing]
-[heart pounding]
-[groans]
-[soft ringing]
[dark music]
[announcer] Attention, students…
Sorry.
[heart pounding]
[door opens, closes]
[young Billie retches, coughs]
[dripping]
[ominous music]
[gasps, panting]
[echoing voice] Breathe.
[splashes]
Where are we?
Service tunnel.
Which way to the surface?
[Devil-horns] Up.
[ominous music]
[suspenseful music]
[Liam] Mom.
[Enya] Come on, just a bit further.
[Jade] What's wrong?
[Enya] Just a little further, yeah?
Come on, Liam.
[Mark] He's fine.
-[Mark] You've got to get up. Come on.
-Get him up. We gotta go.
[snarls]
-He's infected.
-No, no, he… he isn't.
[snarls]
When did bright light start bothering him?
Loud noises? When was he bit?
-No, it… It's not--
-Three days ago.
That's why you couldn't take the ferry.
[Enya] We had to get to Calais.
There were rumors.
The Brotherhood has a cure.
The Brotherhood skin people alive.
They don't have a cure! There is no cure!
Fuck this.
[Liam retches]
[Enya weeps]
[cries]
No.
No!
You love him. I get it.
But the minute someone is infected,
they don't care about you anymore.
They don't love you anymore.
[emotional music]
[Devil-horns yells]
Run!
Fucking run!
[monster roars]
Run!
-[gun fires]
-Run…
[growls]
[Enya] Come on, run. Come on.
[screeches]
[exhales]
[tense music]
Here. Here. Through here.
-[Jade] Come on.
-[Mark] Go.
Come on.
Fuck. Fuck!
What now?
[monster roars]
[emotional music]
Mark?
Count ten…
then go.
[Enya] No. Mark.
[cautious breathing]
[softly]
Come on.
[soft crackling]
[thwacks]
[Mark] I got it.
Come on.
-[Mark] I got it.
-Go.
-I fucking--
-[flesh pierces]
[blood splatters]
-[rips]
-[Enya screams]
[screeches]
[gunshots]
-[yells]
-[clicks]
Shit.
[exhales]
[heavy thumping]
[effort grunting]
[crunches]
[panting]
[somber music]
[young Jade] You get the rest yet?
The firewall's been updated.
Okay, so?
So Umbrella hasn't updated
their security in two years.
Jade. What's going on?
I can't tell you, but…
-I don't know.
-Jade, seriously.
[young Jade] Simon, get off of me.
[Simon] You can't just
keep telling me what to do
-without telling me what's going on.
-Get off.
-Don't touch her.
-[groans]
-Shit. Billie.
-[Simon groans]
[soft ringing]
[panting]
[young Jade] Billie, wait!
What is wrong with your sister?
[Simon] Jade.
Jade, can you just hold on?
[Jade sighs]
[Evelyn] Jade?
Jade Wesker?
Hi, Mom.
Jade, you don't know me, honey,
but I've been watching you
grow up in pictures for years.
Your dad and I go way back.
[Evelyn] He's a brilliant man.
-You want a ride?
-I'm good.
Billie…
[uneasy music]
[young Jade] Billie?
Billie?
I think…
I think something's wrong with me.
This whole time…
I thought…
maybe if I just ignore it…
then it would all go away…
and everything would be normal.
I hurt you.
[young Billie] I hurt people.
I've been hearing things.
Seeing things.
[chuckles]
Lights…
they feel like…
like drills in my brain.
And sounds.
Sounds just hurt my bones.
I can feel all of that.
But I can't feel this.
What's wrong with me?
The dog…
might have been sick.
What does that mean?
[young Jade] I found this thing online.
Same kind of thing happened
in an Umbrella factory.
A guy got bit, and three days later…
[young Billie] What?
[young Jade] He went crazy.
He killed people.
What?
But it's… It's fucked up.
And it's not true.
This is just the drugs.
Like you said earlier.
And if it's not?
It is.
Billie, look at me.
[young Billie weeps]
No.
[young Jade] Look at me.
Don't cry.
[shushes]
Everything's gonna be fine.
♪ Maybe I'm foolish ♪
♪ Maybe I'm blind ♪
♪ Thinking I can see through this ♪
♪ And see what's behind ♪
♪ Got no way to prove it ♪
♪ So maybe I'm blind ♪
[Jade exhales]
♪ I'm only human after all ♪
-[Jade sighs]
-[Liam clacking]
[Jade] Enya.
Leave him.
He's not yours anymore.
I can't.
[sighs]
♪ Don't put your blame on me ♪
♪ Some people got the real problems ♪
♪ Some people out of luck ♪
♪ Some people think I can solve them ♪
♪ Lord heavens above ♪
♪ I'm only human after all ♪
♪ Don't put your blame on me ♪
[Baxter] Took you long enough, huh?
Ha, it got pretty crazy back there, right?
Like, "Ah, brain monsters."
[giggles]
-[grunts]
-Let's, uh…
Let's not.
[panting]
-[gunshot]
-[groans]
[man 1 yelling in French]
[man 2 yelling in French]
[indistinct shouting]
[man 3] Don't move!
You're surrounded.
[man 4] Don't move!
[clicks]
[man 5] Take them now!
Drop your weapon.
[in English]
Dude.
Ouch.
[Baxter panting]
You know who we are, huh?
[in French]
We know you.
Umbrella.
[sucks teeth]
[groans]
Fascist.
[in English]
Come here.
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa. No, no, no.
-I'm… I'm not--
-[thwacks]
[ominous music]
[somber music]