[eerie music]
[Jade] I found it on a beach in Cypress.
Then why is it… like that?
[exhales]
I've implanted an electrode
into its thalamus
which delivers a focused ECT pulse.
You put it to sleep.
And…
I can wake it up.
-[clicking]
-[zaps]
[snarls, thumps]
[gasps]
This was your idea?
I made a few tweaks,
but this sort of research
is more my sister's thing.
The procedure is too complicated to scale.
It's literally brain surgery.
But… it could be interesting
with a few specific cases especially if…
If what?
We go bigger.
[ominous music]
[trilling]
[engine revs]
[Roth] You got five minutes to pack a bag.
No games, no drama. In and out.
Then I take you back to your dad.
Jade?
We don't wanna go back.
Not your call.
Or maybe when we get out
of the car, we'll scream.
See what happens.
[light tap]
Do it. See what happens.
[ominous music continues]
[Evelyn] I warned you
about the outside world, Bert.
I told you, you weren't ready.
But you didn't listen,
and people got hurt.
You could have been hurt.
I… I had to help my family.
-My brother, he--
-What, Albert?
[scoffs]
Please.
When has he ever helped anyone
but himself?
Hmm?
He thought I was dead.
Did you tell him that?
Of course not.
Look, l understand loving your family.
I love my family.
I'd do anything to protect them,
but Albert's not…
He's…
[sighs]
[inhales]
I'm the one who's taking care of you.
[Evelyn] For all these years,
I'm the one that's kept you safe.
Uh… But what about the girls?
I'm keeping them safe as well.
Right now, they are in my office,
having ice cream.
Rocky Road?
It's their favorite too.
[Evelyn inhales]
And they keep asking about you.
Uncle Bert, the great scientist.
But I, I thought I scared them.
No. I told them you're a good man.
Smart.
Funny.
Helpful.
We need your help.
[suspenseful music]
We've got a new project.
An important project.
And if you do a good job,
maybe the girls can even come
and stay with you.
Maybe it will get you
a house all your own.
Green grass, white picket fence.
Happy family.
[breathes deeply]
[suspenseful music continues]
What's the project?
[chimes, beeps]
Him.
[uneasy music]
[burbling]
[uneasy music continues]
[Roth] Five minutes!
[door closes]
[sighs]
Dad's a clone.
[young Jade] I know.
And we're science experiments.
Hey.
This can't be real.
Fuck it.
Fuck them.
Jade, you can't pretend
like this isn't happening.
I'm not.
Actually, I feel like
I'm going crazy, okay?
I wanna scream and cry,
and Dad is a psycho.
His boss is some Cruella de Vil bitch,
and there is a guy
in our living room with a gun.
So I know this is happening.
I know that everyone is lying to us
about everything.
[sighs]
Even me?
[uneasy music]
[young Billie] And what if Dad was…
[sighs]
What if I'm not okay?
No, you are.
You're, you're good, right?
[suspenseful music]
[young Jade] We just need
to get out of here.
Away from Dad, this town,
Umbrella, all of it.
How?
The bag.
It has money, passports, everything.
And then what? We just…
run?
We run really fucking fast.
[tense music]
[young Jade clears throat]
[young Jade] This is Pablo.
We have to take him with us.
[skids]
No. We'll send someone
to take care of him.
Okay, but…
he's high maintenance.
[suspenseful music]
-[soft ringing]
-[deep breathing]
He likes salmon and chicken, no beef.
[heart thumping]
[breathes heavily]
He gets treats every night.
He hates walks,
and he takes, like, giant shits.
I'll let them know.
-[breathing deeply]
-[thumping intensifies]
You're gonna be okay, buddy.
[snarling]
[heartbeats slow down]
-Sorry. He doesn't like assholes.
-[whining]
Get your sister.
[clicks]
[tense music]
[tense music continues]
[window opens]
[young Jade] Hey.
You and me, right?
[tense music]
[grunts]
[Roth] Girls.
What did I say about playing games?
Run! Run!
[yells]
Hey!
[heartbeat intensifies]
[young Jade] Billie?
[dark music]
Shit.
[squeals]
[yells]
-[groans]
-[screams]
[thuds]
-[coughs]
-[sirens wailing]
[whooshes]
Go.
What? No.
Get up.
[young Jade grunts]
[Roth] Goddamn it!
[tense music]
[brakes squeal]
[grunting]
[Roth] Come here!
[young Billie] Go! Get help!
[both grunting]
Find her!
[indistinct chatter]
[grunts]
What are you?
[tense music]
[muffled gunshots]
[growling]
[tense music continues]
Whatever you did, stop it!
I can't.
-[thwacks]
-[groans]
[sighs, groans]
[rapid gunshot]
[growling, munching]
[tense music]
-[thumps]
-[panting]
What's happening?
[chimes]
[sucks teeth]
Nothing.
[Billie] A lot of people are about to die.
Maybe you.
No.
You need me.
[Evelyn] Without me…
what are you?
[sighs]
[droning, whooshing]
[indistinct chatter]
-[yelling]
-[growling]
Fall back!
[snarling]
[squishing]
[splatters]
[skids]
[grunts]
-[thwacks]
-[groans]
[snarling]
[tense music]
[gunshot]
-[somber music]
-[whooshing]
[indistinct chatter]
[rapid gunfire]
[droning and humming]
[shots firing]
[tense music]
[bullets ricochet]
[effort grunting]
[scoffs]
[rapid gunfire]
[chuckles]
[tense music]
[Arjun] Jade, come on.
[Gideon] Set sail!
[snarling]
[suspenseful music]
[munching]
[tense music]
[woman] Come on!
[clonking]
[Jade] Wait!
[gasps]
[tense music]
[yells]
Wait!
Jade!
[Arjun grunts]
Move, move, move!
Wait!
[grunts]
[clanks]
[Jade] Throw it!
[grunts]
[dramatic music]
[dramatic music continues]
[grunting]
[both panting]
I…
[breathes heavily]
How?
[breathing heavily]
[Jade grunts]
-What's our speed?
-Fifteen knots and climbing, sir.
[Jade] Saqim!
-[Saqim] Jade?
-Press the fucking button.
-Too close.
-It doesn't matter.
It won't go for us.
It will go straight for them.
[exhales]
Okay, Saqim.
I know I fucked up before.
But I won't fuck this up.
[suspenseful music]
[exhales]
They get one chopper up in the air,
and we're dead.
[serious music]
[grumbles]
[exhales]
[serious music continues]
[breathes deeply]
[clicks]
[clinks]
[rattling]
[suspenseful music]
[clicking]
[alarm beeping]
-[beeping continues]
-[buzzes]
[ominous music]
[beeping]
[clonks]
[burbles]
[humming]
[grumbles]
[serious music]
-Are you sure?
-[Roth] I'm sure.
She's been bitten.
[breathes heavily]
It was you.
That night.
[Evelyn] The dog.
My dad says I'm fine.
Are you?
That animal was sick.
If it infected you,
it makes you dangerous.
To others, to yourself.
Have you had any symptoms?
[Evelyn] Hallucinations?
Rage?
Pounding heart?
[serious music]
Why should I believe you?
[sighs deeply]
I know you don't like me much, Billie.
I don't like me much either,
most of the time.
But I've never lied to you.
Can you say that about your father?
[serious music continues]
You're a fucking bitch.
I'm the fucking bitch
who's telling you the fucking truth.
[Evelyn] And isn't that what you want?
The fucking truth.
[serious music]
If I am sick…
can you help me?
I'm the only one who can.
[Diana humming]
[upbeat music]
Mom, what are you doing?
It's your mother's favorite.
Mm…
Wait, weren't we…
She's not even here.
We just had
this exact same dinner with her.
[humming]
-Mom, are you alright?
-[doorbell chimes]
[light music playing]
[insects chirping]
I need your help.
[Pablo whimpers]
Jade, what's wrong?
-I, um…
-[Diana] Who's this?
Uh, this, this is Jade,
she's a friend from school.
-We were just…
-Homework. Math.
Look at the puppy.
[chuckles]
[Diana] Hi.
We're just going to go out
by the pool, all right, Mom?
Have fun. Hi.
[eerie music]
-[Simon] You're fucking with me.
-[young Jade] I'm not.
-There are clones in this story, Jade.
-I know.
And, and you saw
this weird shit in my house.
I need to get into Umbrella.
-To get your sister?
-Yeah.
-Because my mom kidnapped her?
-Yes.
Jade, what am I supposed
to say to that? It's, it's insane!
I know.
But, Simon, they're,
they're going to hurt her.
[dramatic music]
I was there.
I've seen what they do.
Their secret labs
and their stupid Joy pills.
What?
[Simon] You saw these?
Yes.
♪ Bring in this face to my ♪
[humming]
[Simon] Mom?
Mom? Mom?
-[rips]
-Oh, my God.
Shit.
-It's just a scratch.
-[Simon] No, it isn't.
I barely feel a thing, really.
Mom, are these yours?
Of course not.
Western medicine just treats
the symptoms, not the cause.
[gasps]
Oh, I love this song.
♪ Cross out his name on the page ♪
[dark music]
You're being very brave.
Am I sick or not?
[dark music continues]
Well?
The virus is…
It's just not infecting the cells.
I don't know why.
It's still viable?
Maybe.
[phone ringing]
Find out.
[phone clacks]
Get creative.
[footsteps receding]
[rustles]
Simon, it's late.
Are you drugging Mom?
[chuckles, inhales]
What?
[Simon] I found the pills. The Joy.
-Those are mine.
-Cut the shit, all right?
She has just cut open her hand,
and she can't even feel it.
-So what did you do to her?
-Simon.
Tell me.
Your mother was having trouble adjusting.
We both agreed that she take medicine
to help with her anxiety.
Just stop lying!
Simon!
I did what I had to,
to keep our family together.
[Evelyn] And, and she's,
she's better. She's happier.
She's a fucking zombie.
And you're a fucking child!
Okay. You have no idea how hard I work.
This company was stolen
from your grandfather, and I rebuilt it,
and your mother she never, she never…
[sighs]
[Evelyn] She wanted to leave.
She wanted to take you away.
I did all of this for you.
I don't want it.
You don't know what you want.
[sighs]
You…
Fuck you.
-Simon--
-[beeping]
[sorrowful music]
[breathes heavily]
[Simon sighs]
[sorrowful music continues]
[sighs]
[light flickers]
Just one more test. Sorry.
-[young Billie] What's that?
-[tech] Just relax.
-No. No, what are you giving me?
-No, it's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. Relax, okay?
Everything's okay.
-[heart pounding]
-[groaning]
Everything's okay.
Oh, shit.
[yells]
[opera music]
[muffled gunshots]
[splatters]
[opera music continues]
[groans]
[music ends]
[wind blows]
[earth rumbles]
[gasps]
[ominous music]
-[splashes]
-[thuds]
[roars]
[tense music]
Fuck.
[distant roar]
You had to.
I know.
[emotional music]
[exhales]
[door closes]
Bea?
[ominous music]
She's not in her room.
Maybe she's on deck.
Bea?
[suspenseful music]
[tense music]
[uneasy music]
All right. I can override the doors
and jam the system,
but that only gives us about ten minutes
before they notice.
[beeps]
So do you know where you are going?
Yeah.
You don't have to come with me.
Mm, I know.
[clonks]
[suspenseful music]
Come on, then.
Hey.
Thank you.
[dramatic music]
[clanks]
-[rapid breathing]
-Calm down. Just calm down!
My sister?
I gave her a shot of adrenaline.
She's in v-tach and seizing!
[yells]
I want my sister!
[tech] The cart. I need the sedatives!
[grunts]
-[flesh pierces]
-[tech screams]
[groans]
[unstable music]
Calm down, okay?
You lied to me!
-[flesh rips]
-[groans]
[tense music]
[panting]
-[dog growling]
-[alarm wailing]
[hazy music]
[young Billie squeals]
[panting]
-[dog barks]
-[screams]
[blood splatters]
[dog barking]
[tense music continues]
[cries]
[barking]
Breathe. Hey. It's okay. It's okay.
-Breathe.
-[young Billie breathing]
Hands above your head.
[panting]
How did you… how did you know about that?
Albert.
[somber music]
You weren't eating ice cream, were you?
What?
[sighs heavily]
[young Billie exhales]
[somber music continues]
[soft sigh]
[gasping]
-I need to get out of here.
-Okay.
-We'll find your dad.
-No.
I don't care about him.
He doesn't care about me.
Yes, he does.
When he was locked up,
all he wanted was to help his girls.
Because we're his medicine.
He needs our blood to stay alive.
So?
"So"?
[Bert] My dad needed me
and my brothers too.
So he kept us locked away for a long time.
We didn't even see the sun
until we were all grown up.
[Bert] But Albert's not like that.
He gave you a life.
And maybe…
I'm not saying he was right,
or even good, but…
he could've been worse.
So that makes… that makes it okay?
No, but…
Well, maybe there's no such thing.
Maybe life's just a bunch of accidents
and tragedies and…
[Bert] No one's really okay.
We're all just doing our best.
In a world where it's way too easy
to do your worst.
Your dad loves you.
Well, maybe
it's a messed up kind of love, but…
Well, they kind of all are
when you think about it.
[somber music]
But, if you want, we can leave him.
If we do…
what happens?
[inhales slowly]
Nothing good.
[somber music]
[clanks]
[breathes angrily]
[beeps]
[sighs]
-Jade?
-[young Jade] Don't get excited.
Where is Billie?
She's not with you?
-Hi, I'm…
-Evelyn's son.
What happened?
We tried to run, but…
they took Billie.
I think they know she got bit.
-We need to find her now.
-You're not coming with us.
Just tell me where she is.
-Jade, I…
-[door opens]
Hey, family reunion.
[emotional music]
Hey, bro.
-Oh, we're…
-Clones.
-Did they hurt you? Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
I have the bag,
and I left Pablo with Simon's mom.
We have to go.
[young Billie] He's coming with us.
-What? Why?
-Because we can't leave him here.
[sighs]
[beeps]
[timer beeps]
Ten minutes.
[energy hums]
-What's happening?
-They're locking down.
[locks clanking]
This way.
[monster roars]
[thudding]
[tense music]
[helicopter whirring]
[drones humming]
[gunshots]
-[gasps]
-[clanks]
[screams]
[slaps]
[groans, gasps]
[tense music continues]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[explosion]
[slaps]
[whistling]
[splashes]
[somber music]
[engine roaring]
This is all my fault.
Jade, don't.
We're gonna bring her home.
There. There.
[somber music continues]
Hey.
She couldn't have gotten far.
[slithers]
Arjun!
[splashes]
[burbles]
[ominous music]
[ominous music continues]
[thumps]
[ominous music]
This way.
[panting]
[softly]
Hide. In there.
-Right, everyone in there.
-Okay.
-[soft ringing]
-[groans]
[tense music]
[young Billie breathing in panic]
[Simon] Shit.
Okay, okay.
-[soft ringing]
-[young Jade] Yes!
[breathing heavily]
[beeps]
You!
None of you would even be alive
without me.
So I think it's time for a "thank you."
[yells]
A little fucking respect!
-[soft ringing]
-[heart pounding]
It's…
[echoes]
Hey.
You're okay.
[clanks]
All right, this way.
[young Jade echoes] Come on.
-[dog barks]
-[groans]
Jade? Billie! Billie!
Billie, stop.
-[munches]
-[Simon screams]
Let go!
Southwest Hall.
[Simon groaning]
[tense music]
No.
[guard] Halt!
[tense music continues]
[tense music]
Simon?
[Simon] Mom.
No.
She bit me.
[dark music]
[dark music continues]
[Albert] Evelyn.
Evelyn.
I can fix him.
I'll find a way.
But…
you have to let my girls go.
You know it's his only chance.
Mom?
[dark music]
-Mom--
-[gunshot]
[screams]
No!
[weeps]
[Jade wailing]
[dramatic music]
[gunshots]
[both grunt]
[rapid gunshot]
[groans]
[cries]
[hazy music]
[young Jade] Dad!
No!
No! No!
-[gunshot]
-[shatters]
[thuds]
[muffled gunshot]
[tense music]
[music fades]
[emotional music]
[coughing]
[coughs]
[retches]
[inhales]
Arjun. Arjun.
Arjun… Arjun!
Arjun.
Ar… Arjun.
Arjun!
[Jade] Arjun!
-Oh.
-Hey.
-Oh, God.
-[groaning]
-Can you move it?
-[groans]
No.
[grunts]
You have to go.
Find her.
Jade, go.
[Arjun] Go!
[tense music]
[growling]
[gun fires]
[humming]
-[pilot] Let's go! Let's go!
-Go!
Let's move it!
[roars]
[whirring]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[ominous music]
[loud thumping]
-[monster grumbles]
-[shrieks]
[tense music]
[grumbles]
[squeals]
[exhales]
[groans]
[grumbling]
[squelches]
[glorious music]
[gasps]
[clicks, whistles]
[explosion]
-[explosion]
-[splatters]
[panting]
[Jade] Bea?
[Bea] Mom!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Where's Dad?
I…
-[footsteps approaching]
-[indistinct chatter]
Stay close.
[suspenseful music]
Hey, Mama.
And here I thought
I was the best liar in the family.
Kid's cute.
[Billie] What'd you do to her?
Oh, 'cause Lyle the Crocodile back there,
he could have ripped her
in half, except didn't.
That's weird, right?
It's weird.
[Billie] You mess with her DNA?
Give her the old Wesker special?
-Mom?
-It's okay.
Of course, it is. Hi, sweetie.
Stay the fuck away from her.
[guns clink]
[tense music]
[wind gusting]
No.
[Billie] It's always gonna be no.
And you should have known that.
I mean twins, right?
We're the same.
No, we're not.
Ever since that night, you are heartless.
[Jade] Hopeless.
[Jade] That night was
the worst night of my life.
-That was when I lost my sister.
-No, it wasn't.
[Billie] See, that's what you never got.
The T, it stripped away all my…
Fucking bullshit.
The fear, the anxiety.
It didn't make me somebody else.
It let me be who I always was.
I was just too scared to admit it.
[dramatic music]
That…
was the best night of my life.
[dramatic music continues]
What are you?
I'm the future.
And you?
You're a fucking virus.
I mean, you ever notice
how everyone around you somehow…
dies?
[Billie] Simon?
Bert?
Kim? Hiroki?
Dad?
I can keep going.
You keep telling yourself
you're trying to save lives,
but your hands, Jade,
they're covered in blood.
Because you're selfish.
Because you only care about the mission
about fixing what you started.
So people die, but you keep going.
You don't stop
because that's what matters. You.
It's still always the fucking Jade show.
[cries]
[somber music]
[sobs]
-[somber music continues]
-[sniffles]
Fine.
[sniffles]
Take me.
[Jade] Just…
Please just…
[emotional music]
Let her go.
[emotional music continues]
[sobs]
[tense music]
I don't need you anymore.
-[gunshot]
-[flesh pierces]
[Jade groaning]
[Bea] Mom?
Hey, Mom?
-Bea!
-[Bea] No! No!
Bea!
Mom!
[suspenseful music]
[tense music]
[inaudible wailing]
[siren wailing]
[tense music]
-[whooshes]
-[siren wailing]
[gasps]
[young Jade] Go, go! Go, go, go!
[tense music]
[door squeaks close]
They're everywhere.
[all breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music]
[wheels rattling]
What are you doing?
Making a bomb.
Evelyn won't stop unless we make her stop.
[sloshing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Albert panting]
Bert, get them somewhere safe.
What? What about you?
Someone has to set it off.
[emotional music]
[young Billie] Dad?
You don't have to do this.
[breathes heavily]
[sighs]
[emotional music continues]
I love you.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to.
I'll do it.
No.
You deserve a life, Bert.
[emotional music]
-[sirens wailing]
-[tires screech]
Let's go!
[suspenseful music]
[rips]
Go out the back.
Find her.
[suspenseful music continues]
[sobbing]
[suspenseful music]
[door opens]
[guard] There he is!
[clicks]
-[gunshot]
-[Albert groans]
[gasps]
Come on! Come on!
[Albert groaning]
[Evelyn] My son.
I loved him.
You killed him.
-[gunshot]
-[screams, groans]
I was protecting him
from becoming a monster.
[whimpering]
[chuckles]
But when this is over…
All of it…
Everything I sacrificed…
[chuckles]
…I'm gonna change the world.
[panting]
I have the future.
What do you have?
I have a pen.
-[pen ignites]
-[fire roars]
[whooshes]
[light music]
[loud explosion]
[loud explosion continues]
[light music continues]
♪ When I was older ♪
♪ I was a sailor ♪
♪ On an open sea ♪
[wincing]
♪ But now I'm underwater ♪
♪ And my skin is paler ♪
♪ Than it should ever be ♪
I didn't mean to hurt you.
[young Billie] Or Simon.
I, I… I just…
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
[pensive music]
[breathing heavily]
You and me, right?
[pensive music continues]
You and me.
♪ But now I'm underwater ♪
[engine roars]
♪ And my skin is paler ♪
♪ Than it should ever be ♪
♪ Hmm ♪
[grunts]
♪ Dreaming of a time and place ♪
♪ Where you and I
Remain the best of friends ♪
♪ Even after all this ends ♪
♪ Can we pretend? ♪
[whirring]
♪ I'm on my ♪
♪ I'm on my back again ♪
♪ It's seeming more and more ♪
♪ Like all we ever do
Is see how far it bends ♪
♪ Before it breaks in half and then ♪
[exhales]
♪ We bend it back again ♪
-[indistinct chatter]
-[man coughs]
♪ Guess I got caught in the middle of it ♪
♪ Yes, I've been taught
Got a little of it ♪
♪ In my blood ♪
[man yelling]
♪ Memories burn like a forest fire ♪
♪ Heavy rain turn
Any funeral pyre to mud ♪
-[rumbles]
-[growling]
[pensive music]
♪ I'm watching movies back to back
In black and white, I never ♪
♪ Seen anybody do it
Like I do it any better ♪
♪ Been goin' over you
I'm overdue for new endeavors ♪
♪ Nobody lonely like I'm lonely
And I don't know whether ♪
♪ You'd really like it in the limelight ♪
♪ You'd sympathize with all the bad guys ♪
♪ I'm still a victim in my own right ♪
♪ But I'm the villain
In my own eyes, yeah ♪
[engine zooms]
♪ When I was older ♪
♪ I was a sailor ♪
♪ On an open sea ♪
[light music]