MAY 20TH, 1997
We are going to record our demo
in two days.
The label company is waiting.
Are you leaving us?
You guys know I have a reason to leave.
The board exams are important for me.
I need to be a civil servant
and support my family.
Enough! Can you guys stop fighting?
We're going to perform in a minute.
Grow up!
Ju, where's your guitar?
I'll just use the guitar that's here.
Ju, that guitar is damaged.
It's a cheap guitar
and it has a bad pickup.
Don't worry about that
as long as it performs.
But the sound is awful, right?
-What?
-What's with you and your nose hair?
What happened?
Am I the only one
who cares about this band?
Are you saying I don't care
about this band?
Don't block my way.
You scream like a girl.
Move, move. Move aside!
You fatso!
All right, you guys are Mabok Edan?
Kagok Edan.
Okay, can you move please?
Okay, you're next. Get ready!
Let's give a big applause
to the next band!
Tabok Edan!
Good afternoon, Zenithers!
We are Kagok Edan.
ZENITH HIGH SCHOOL
MUSICAL PERFORMANCES
Hey, your guitar is too loud and noisy!
Don't worry, nobody cares about us.
Can you turn it down?
You want to fight?
Fight!
They're fighting!
Why isn't it coming out?
What's happening?
Kou, kou, kounaon, eh?
Your water pump broke? You can't shower?
Use Suzumi!
BUY NOW: 1080-1920
It sprays just right!
Suzumi, the king of pump.
Acclaimed film director Joko Anwar
is on the search for a lead actor
to be in his new colossal horror film
"Kabayan and Satan's Slaves."
How is the progress of
"Kabayan and Satan's Slaves"?
I'm looking for a star currently.
This film is a mix of horror,
art house, and some religious elements.
So I have to find the right actor
for this role.
Where are you taking the monkey?
This? We are going to put it to sleep.
Isn't that too cruel? Why?
This one is carrying a deadly virus.
If we don't kill it,
the virus can spread to humans.
The speaker is dead. We need
classical music for the monkey to be calm.
My battery is low.
Do you have any classical music
on your phone?
-Do you have any?
-Just Indonesian songs.
Is it Koplo or a remix?
No, forget it.
Can you find someone
who has classical music on their phone?
I'm going to charge my phone first.
Excuse me.
I'm taking back the bowl.
Where is everyone?
Hey, Monkey. What are you doing here?
You want to come home with me?
You're so cute.
What do you want? You want to eat?
You are so cute. Why are you so cute?
That's not nice.
You're lucky you're inside there!
If I see you outside,
I will turn you into meatballs!
UJANG MEATBALL
ORDER HERE FOR FEASTS
ZENITH HIGH SCHOOL REUNION
ACCEPT
Will we always be together
Despite the distance between us?
-What's up, Dip?
-Instead of going to that reunion,
I have lined up an MC job for you.
It's good money.
Are you taking a dump while talking to me?
What are you talking about?
Ju, there are few offers.
You just need to choose.
I can't. I confirmed I would go.
Come on.
You just want to show off
in front of your high school friends.
Dip, instead of arguing with me,
why don't you try to get me
an audition for Joko Anwar's movie?
He's making Kabayan and Satan's Slaves.
I think I would be perfect for the role.
Jimmy and Reza are getting too old.
Do you remember your last three films?
They're all average.
Joko Anwar will not give that role to you.
An actor who is known for his line
"Ku, ku… Kunaon, eh?"
You're wrong. Its Kou, kou, kounaon, eh?
If you don't get me an audition by Monday,
I will start looking for a new manager.
Come on, Ju.
I know grandpa uses a strong cologne,
but can you just bear with it?
Stop screaming. I want to talk to Wina.
Wina, don't put the slime
inside your brother's pants.
You can't put the slime or the sand!
Don't do that.
Why are you crying now? Hello, Wina, wait.
-Jef, can you talk to your children?
-Wait, I just got a comment.
Shit, asshole, idiot!
What do you know about art?
You have no idea what's good talent.
I have been playing guitar
since you were still in your diapers.
Think before you make a comment, idiot!
Wait, another comment just came in.
IS THAT YOUR MASTURBATING FACE?
What does her picture look like you?
-Is this your account?
-Yep.
Good comment. Very constructive.
Hurry up. It's getting late.
Can I erase the comment, honey?
ZENITH HIGH SCHOOL REUNION INVITATION
ZENITH HIGH SCHOOL
-Kagok Edan!
-Shit! Are you crazy?
I didn't know celebrities get scared.
Ju, do you still remember me?
Do you? Come on.
I'm Erwan.
I don't care if you are Erwan or Erwin.
You scared me.
Ju, what's your famous line?
Just once, all right?
Kou, kou, kounaon, eh?
That's so you!
Ju, can we take a picture together?
-I want to show my wife.
-Can you just tell your wife to come here?
-Hey, Ju, aren't you shooting?
-I just finished a project.
Are you guys dating?
I thought you broke up.
Hi, Ju? How are you?
Twenty years,
and you haven't changed a bit.
I have, Ju. Seriously.
-Ku, ku, kunaon, eh?
That's wrong. It's, Kou, kou, kounaon, eh?
Can I have a picture with a movie star?
I didn't see you coming.
-Hi, Ju. How are you?
-Hi, Lulu. I'm fine.
I miss you.
Honey, you were talking
about him in the car. He's here now.
Stop it.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Ju.
-Where are your kids?
-With their grandparents.
Everything is still the same.
Who is this?
-This must be Mansur!
-We meet again.
Look at my finger.
If we give you a wedgie, you'll enjoy it.
-Please, no!
-Are you still poor?
-No.
-Why are you so smelly?
-You stink!
They still like to give wedgies.
-They are your friends, right?
-Jeffri's friends.
You must be kidding.
Isn't that…
The one who likes to…
-Mansur!
I'm married.
Hey, don't tell me that after 20 years,
my sex is the only thing that changed.
You guys haven't changed?
Are you still fighting?
No, they're fine now.
Honey, how are you?
I'm fine.
I'm so happy to see you this way.
It's like you've lost weight.
I haven't lost weight.
In fact, I have added more weight.
Is this all built up, Sur?
Yes, I'm still going back and forth
to Bangkok.
A little touch up here and there.
And from now on, my name is Marina.
So if you call me Mansur,
I will cut off your balls.
Let's party.
Attention everyone.
All of you over there,
please line up. Stop pushing.
Everyone will get a name tag, okay?
Wait.
Let me guess.
I know this one.
A famous star. Jupiter, right?
Jupiter? That's a planet. It's Juhana.
All right, Juhana. Here.
Welcome.
As I remember,
you guys are in a band, right?
Mabok Edan!
Kagok Edan.
I was close. Lulu, right?
Yes.
-How are you?
-I'm fine.
This must be Jeffri.
Hi, Raina.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
And you must be…
Who are you?
Marina.
Previously Mansur.
-Mansur?
-Yes.
-Okay, Mansur.
-It's "Marina."
Mansur?
It's "Marina!"
Why am I getting chills?
CLASS OF '97
I don’t know who this girl is,
but I'm going to get her.
Tonight, she will go back home with me.
She will enter my room.
And sleep with me.
Cupi!
-Hello.
Hello.
I'm Jody.
Marina.
I'm Cupi.
I'm Tyo.
Marina.
Jody, weren't you a science major?
-How do you know?
-Yes. How?
How do you know?
Who are you? I can't recall you.
Maybe you don't know who I am,
but you know who I was.
-You know her?
-No, I don't.
So you're divorced?
It's been three years, Ju.
Too bad. You guys were the ideal couple.
Rudy and Nining were like
the legendary Anjasmara and Dian Nitami.
Well, this is real life.
Not as good as soap operas.
So, are you dating anyone now?
The toilet stinks.
Ju, this is Febby. Febby, this is Juhana.
He's working in the entertain industry.
-Entertainment.
-You're in the entertain?
Entertainment.
But as far as I know,
Juhana is very typical with his line…
-Ku, ku…
-Kou, kou, kou naon, eh?
That's the one! It's spot on.
How are you able to imitate that guy?
Why can't I remember which class
you were in or who your friends were?
Try to remember.
You used to give me wedgies.
-What?
That's not possible.
I would never forget pulling the underwear
of a beautiful girl like you.
You're perfect.
Besides, you always gave wedgies
with us, didn't you?
Wait. You must have been doing this
alone without telling us.
-Right.
-That's my own underwear.
I know. You're Erik's friend, right?
You dated Erik, the basketball player.
But I didn't.
I have to go to the restroom.
One of our friends
used to pull their nose hair.
-Who is it?
-Nose hair?
I know Ridho
who use to pull his chest hair.
If it's a chicken feather,
he's a chicken butcher.
Why do I even bother to ask you?
-By the way, I'm a model.
-What kind of model?
Cover model.
-Magazine covers?
-Crossword book.
-Crossword book?
-Do you know a crossword book?
I'm the lady on the cover.
Now I see it. It's good sideways
and better going down.
Yes.
Ujang…
Shit!
-What's wrong with you?
-I'm fine. I'm just exhausted.
-One meatball soup. No bean sprouts.
-Noted.
I'll have the same.
Hi.
Are you sure, Prill?
What do you mean?
Why? It's just meatballs.
I mean about… sitting next to me.
Wouldn't Mandy be mad?
Mandy is not that bad, Afuk.
All right.
Thank you.
I'm starving.
Excuse me, Afuk. Can you move?
-Afuk, can you move a little bit?
-Hi!
-Sure.
-Yes!
Can I have this meatball soup?
I'm really hungry.
That's mine!
Prilly, we promised
to go on the Keto Diet.
This must be because of Afuk.
-You're a really bad influence.
-It's not…
Let's just eat this, okay?
Ujang, please make one for me.
-One for me.
-No tomato sauce.
Can I have some space?
Afuk, please be careful.
Check first whether there is enough space
before sitting.
Anyways, thank you.
Now my clothes are a mess.
Let's eat.
Afuk…
What is that green stuff on the meatball?
It's the new green tea meatball soup
that is getting very popular in Singapore.
Is there such a thing?
-That's your meatball.
-This one?
Thank you.
-This is Prilly's.
-That's mine.
Don't be like that.
Hilbram!
Hilbram, right?
How are you?
Sorry, I'm married. We can't shake hands.
What are you talking about?
You were a drunkard.
-What happened?
-But I'm not Hilbram anymore.
I'm Abu Umar.
Abu Umar. Why?
Hilbram got a heart attack…
when he was getting a massage
from masseur 228.
From that time,
Hilbram has been reborn as… Abu Umar.
Jeffri, right?
-Hey, how are you?
-Good. Thanks.
-Who are you?
-Budi.
I used to copy your work.
-Yes, I remember. How are you?
-I'm good.
-I couldn't recognize you.
-Yes.
Your hair used to be so thick
during class.
Your hair is still good.
Well, I'm blessed.
I think it's good genes.
-What are you up to now?
-Regular work.
-I work from nine to five.
-I see.
-But I have this.
-What?
I have that too. I have two of them.
This one is for work,
and this one is for fun.
No, I mean I own a YouTube channel.
Youtube? I use this one
for YouTube, Path, and Instagram.
I like the camera on this phone.
It's nice, right?
What do you do?
Well, I'm a housewife.
I take care of my husband and children.
Very good. That's very noble. Keep it up!
But I also sell food on social media.
Oh, dear.
You shouldn't do that.
That's how problems arise in the family.
You should stay at home
and let your husband provide
for your family.
Hilbram.
-Hi, how are you?
-Sorry.
Congratulations, your wife won
the Marketer of the Year!
-That's good.
-Yes.
Your wife's hard work finally paid off.
She's lucky to have a husband
who takes care of the children.
What's wrong with him?
-Hi, Ju.
-Hi, Ning.
-How are you?
-I'm fine.
-It's been a while.
-Yes, when was the last time?
-More than three years, I think.
-Yes, I think so.
-Hold on, I have to take this.
-Sure Ju.
Hi, can I take a picture with you?
-Just one, please.
-I have to take this call.
Just a second.
Say, "Cheese!"
One more. Wait!
Rudy, if you still allow
the kids to watch Awkarin,
I will have your parental rights
terminated.
-What is wrong with Awkarin?
-Everything.
I don't want the kids to dress up
all sexy like her.
Come on. Awkarin is really cool!
Look at her figure.
She represents kids today.
What do you want?
This is only for invitations.
You haven't paid yet.
Here. You can go now.
This is only for alumni.
Marina,
what are you doing after this?
Shall we go out for dinner?
Let's eat each other.
I'm so dirty.
Every time I see your lips, I want to…
I even scare myself.
I have never seen a body like yours.
Your heart, liver, pancreas, intestines…
Why am I getting hungry now?
Marina,
you have something…
that I have never seen in any other women.
And that something is…
A penis!
It's "Marina"!
My name is Marina, not penis.
I currently work
at the National Land Agency.
This is my business card.
In case you need any help
extending house papers,
exchanging certificates,
or exchanging wives.
-What?
Exchanging what, you said?
Exchanging what?
-Exchange…
-Exchanging business cards.
-I'm Budi. You still remember?
-Yes.
Jeffri says he does not have
any business cards.
The office should give him one.
Juhana? Our celebrity!
How are you? "Ku, ku, neon, eh."
That's wrong.
It should be, Kou, kou, kounaon, eh?
Get out of my way! Move aside!
-Calm down. What's wrong?
-Shit!
Hey, easy.
Shit. Asshole.
-What's wrong?
-Why?
Idiot!
-Relax.
-Yes, but what happens?
That beautiful girl, with the red dress.
I was after her.
-The one…
-The sexy one!
-I thought she was my only love.
-Who is she?
I don't know who she is.
-So?
-I found out, she has…
-What? Boxing gloves?
-A big fist?
What?
-She has…
-What?
A ring?
-A ring. She's old? Is that it?
-Menopause?
She… has a penis.
-What? A penis?
I just found out from Raina,
that the girl with the red dress
and big boobs is Mansur!
Mansur of Kagok Edan?
Exactly.
The one who liked to pull his nose hair.
Did you bring the video?
-I have it.
-The one we recorded last time?
Mansur…
Hey, boy! Put this on.
I can't. I have to follow the rundown.
You've got some nerve.
You want me to mess up your face?
-Do you want that?
-No.
Make it flat?
Yes. I mean, no!
With some powder on your face?
-Why do you say that?
-I thought it was funny.
Put it on now!
Thank God my career has been picking up
in the past 20 years.
Twenty years, huh?
In the past 20 years,
have you ever thought of your old band?
Stop it.
It's fine, honey. I just want to know
if he realizes how he destroyed our dreams
just to fulfill his dream
of becoming a civil servant.
What are you trying to say?
What are you guys talking about?
I want in.
Let's give a big welcome
to our next band! Tabok Edan!
Jef, that's you!
I can't forget that thick hair.
That music. It's very annoying.
The guitar part was improvised. Great.
The sound of Satan.
It disturbs the purity of the soul.
And creates chaos in our hearts and mind.
My God.
Ju, you were awesome!
You guys are legendary.
In a negative sense!
I have to record this.
This is so good. Jef? Where are you going?
Piece of shit!
SAY "YES" TO ACHIEVEMENT!
SAY "NO" TO DRUGS!
Jef, cut it out. What's wrong with you?
That was 20 years ago.
Class of '97!
What do you think of Tepok Edan?
For our next performance,
I'm sure the song will bring
all of you back to your high school days.
Okay,
let's give a big applause
to Zhe Zhe Cheers!
If you were not egoistic,
maybe we would be rock stars by now!
Maybe we would have made many albums!
I wouldn't need to work
with my annoying boss!
I wouldn't have to go around
with my secondhand car.
Maybe I wouldn't have
to live in my small house.
Those are all hypothetical, Jef.
Your YouTube channel might get
a million subscribers.
Okay, you might win an award
for your movie!
Your hair might grow back!
You might get a wife soon!
You might grow up and move on
from all of this.
-Impossible!
Bro, is pedophilia allowed in Indonesia?
If it is, I'm in.
Don't their parents…
get upset…
When… they dress up…
What's all this rubbish?
They think they're hot.
-Baby, look at me!
-What?
Why are you looking at them?
I'm sexier than them, right?
Yes, you are sexier than them.
I'm going home. I'm mad at you!
If you want to be a rock star, go ahead.
Just don't blame me
for Kagok Edan's failure.
See? You never had any faith in our band.
What band are you talking about.
Kagok Edan is no more.
-You wanna fight?
-Do you?
Cut it out!
Jef, let's go home.
Home? He will go back
to his glamorous celebrity life.
And us? We go back
to our normal dull life. Is that fair?
You're right.
Going back home with your wife,
meeting your adorable kids,
in your very small home.
It's not fair.
-Honey.
-Forget it.
I don't want to see your face
for the next 60 minutes.
Take care of this.
Take care of the purse!
It fits you!
Move!
Mandy, what's wrong with Intan?
Maybe she's improvising.
It's like breakdancing.
-It must be their new move. Breakdance.
-Fantastic!
Wow!
He gets a girl in no time.
The charm is still there.
That must be nice.
She's giving him a hicky.
There is also lap dancing.
How do you get your neck bitten by a girl?
I'm scared.
-They're ill, Raina.
-It's bad.
-What's wrong?
-Is this for real?
Hey, get up!
Is this for real?
Prilly!
-Prilly!
-What?
Mandy!
Hey, don't be naughty.
Prilly!
-Why are you pushing it?
-She's coming!
Hey, don't push me there!
-Don't push me!
-Why are you holding this back?
CLASS OF '97
Mansur…
-It's "Marina."
-Mansur!
I have already repented. I have repented.
Forgive me. This is a warning from God.
The end is nigh.
We are all ungrateful.
This is God's way of punishing us.
I have warned all of you. Nobody cares.
Nobody wants to listen.
You have to repent right away.
Oh God.
Not me. Please, I have children.
I have a wife.
Please, not me.
Him. Take him.
He's unemployed and has sinned.
Help the government reduce unemployment.
See? Even Satan knows
who has repented and who has sinned.
Help me!
KEEP IT CLEAN
Shit!
Aren't you the one who asked for a selfie?
Let me tell you… What's your name?
Why do kids today
have such difficult names?
Let me tell you.
There are some ethics you have to follow
when you ask for a picture.
Don't come closer. Don't worry.
I will let you take a picture.
I'm not that kind of actor
that only takes pictures during promos.
If someone else sees the both of us here,
it will become hot gossip.
All right?
What are you doing?
What's wrong? Don't be mad.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Lulu, this girl!
What's wrong with her?
Lulu, hit her!
-No, I can't.
-Hit her!
Raina!
-It's good I saw you.
-Are you okay?
Go straight.
Go straight to the front!
Oh my God!
Come on, hurry up!
-Turn right.
-Oh my God!
-Oh God.
-Come on! Run faster!
-Shit.
-Budi! Hey!
Did you see my wife?
Your wife? I don't know.
Don't go out front.
They're eating everyone!
Let us just finish all of them then.
Don't go there. You'll get killed, Mansur.
"Marina."
You call me Mansur one more time,
you're dead!
-So? Where should we go through?
-I know, Uncle!
Aunty. Follow me!
We're going back? Are you serious?
Shit.
-Come on.
-Bring it on!
Mansur.
I'm sorry, I hit a girl.
What is this thing?
My hair?
I knew it! We're almost the same age.
Your hair can't be thicker than mine.
Let's leave this place.
It's locked.
Everything is locked.
How would they get a proper education?
-This one opens!
-Your stomach is too big.
-This door doesn't close.
-Let me hold it. Wait.
They're gone. It's good. We're safe.
I'm so tired.
-Your phone.
-Turn it off!
It's Dipa.
Dipa, help me! Dipa!
-Ju, I'm with Joko Anwar now.
-I don't want to die! Help!
Dipa, help me!
I still want to live. Help me!
Stop that!
I don't want to die.
I don't want to be eaten by my friends.
He's ready for casting now.
Joko, listen to this.
Jump. What?
Hello. What is this?
I mean, here.
Yes, hello.
Dipa, I still want to learn how to pray.
Please, help me!
I promise if I live through this,
I will promote all my films always.
I will post on all the social media…
This is fantastic.
…unlike the other actors!
Amazing. And with a price less than Reza?
Yes. It's just a quarter of Reza's!
-Dwi?
-Dwi? Far below.
-Tora?
-Way below Tora.
Kabayan is you.
I'm a fan of Juhana now.
I don't want to be eaten by my friend.
Dipa, help me! Please!
I should have taken the MC job
instead of coming here.
Ju, start praying. Maybe it will help.
Hurry up, Ju, pray.
I can't do that
when I’m exhausted. Why don't you pray?
I also don't remember
my prayers when I panic!
Ku, ku, kunaon, eh?
You have a long life Ju.
Follow me. This way!
This way! There's no one here.
Faster, Mandy!
Mandy…
Please! Help me!
-Prilly!
-Latuconsina?
Afuk.
-This way.
-Faster!
Open the door!
Help!
Baby, I have to make sure
I still look good.
Where's my mirror? Where is it, Baby?
My mirror?
I don't know. You had it with you.
I still look very beautiful.
I should be at home with my kids.
Not here with this bimbo
who only thinks of her looks,
make-up, and mirror.
Baby, are you going to let her
talk like that to me?
Help me, Baby. I'm not in Bimbo.
They're old.
I didn't mean Bimbo the band.
You understand English, right?
Baby, help me!
Nining, please.
Just say sorry to her.
I'm not a kid, Rudi.
You're a kid when you act like this.
Who keeps getting tempted by new toys?
Is it me, or is it…
Rudi.
Hey you, beautiful.
I have to take care of you.
Your eyelashes.
Oh my God, they're amazing.
I can't let my fake lashes fall off.
I have to always look beautiful.
I'm so tired.
Excuse me.
Ju, look at them. They're everywhere.
What do they want?
What's wrong with them? They look dead,
yet they walk around.
They are neither human nor ghosts.
We really need to find a name for them,
but what?
Half-dead humans.
Not catchy enough. Too long.
Humans who neither want to die nor live.
It's too dramatic.
Or…
Too American.
I know. I think they're called…
Si… si…
Singles!
-Singles?
-Because nobody wants to be with them.
How do you know
nobody wants to be with them?
It seems so.
Maybe someone does.
Do you want to be with them?
-Well, they're not my type.
-So they are singles.
That's Jeffri!
Thank God he's safe.
And he still has my purse.
Shit.
Juhana.
What's wrong with his phone?
Ju, where is your phone?
I dropped it in the classroom
when I was panicking.
-What about you?
-I left my bag in the main hall.
I just brought… this.
-Mr. Erwan?
-There.
See? I have come out as the hero
in such a critical situation.
You're out of credit.
What kind of hero has no credit
on his phone.
Hero without credit.
Right, Baby?
Why is everyone so quiet?
Baby, what do you think?
Baby!
What's wrong with your face?
You should use your night cream.
Listen to me. Look at your face, Baby!
Hello, police headquarters.
Can I help you?
Hello, officer. I'm calling
from Zenith High School.
We are having a reunion…
when suddenly my friends died.
Then, those who died ate my other friends.
Officer, please send help.
Are you sure you want to involve
the police?
I'm sure, Officer. I can't involve
my father in law, right?
Don't you want to settle this
between yourselves?
We Indonesians always value friendship.
The only settlement for this
is with the grave.
What do you mean? They are all…
Dead. D.E.A.D.
Finito. Kaput.
I see. And they still bite other people?
Man, this is so difficult.
Help me, Officer!
They're going to rape me!
Be the rapist.
Come on.
Yes, I'm the rapist.
I'm going to rape you.
I'm going to open the… shoes.
Please send someone now. Please!
Hey, can I record the rape scene?
To make it more believable.
We're dead.
We're so dead.
Do you want to die that badly?
Then let's go out there and die together.
Let's do it!
Shit.
We're dead.
I'm just a regular housewife,
while my friends are successful.
Including you. A famous event organizer.
What are you talking about?
If I could choose,
I would rather not be an EO.
It's very tiring
and very difficult at times.
When you're busy at work,
who takes care of your children?
I don't have any kids.
My uterus is as dry as the Sahara desert.
That's the reason my husband left me.
I'm sorry, Raina.
It's all right.
I actually envy seeing you and Jeffri.
You both have everything
that I have always dreamed of.
You're blessed, Lulu.
Afuk.
So, which one is it?
Both. I mean,
thank you for helping me and…
For not joining your band
since I joined the cheer squad.
Don't worry about it.
But honestly… I miss you.
I mean, I miss being in the band with you.
Okay. So, which one is true?
You miss me or you miss
being in the band with me?
Well, I think both.
I just feel that you have a lot of talent
and you should not waste it on cheering.
Okay, try to moving it now.
Don't put too much pressure.
It still hurts…
but it's much better.
That's good.
Please, tell me next time
you're going to do that.
-Now do it again.
-Stop it.
25 million for one breast?
That's expensive.
I got a very special deal and I took it.
That's insane and very weird.
Wait, when you wanted to do the surgery,
who was your reference?
Look-alike, but her boobs…
are not…
that big.
I know. It's two cups difference.
Very good.
Why didn't you cut the thing below?
That's even more expensive.
I have to save for two years
to get that much money.
That much? Crazy. Just to cut that thing?
-Bud?
Bud! No!
No! Mar!
Mar, help me! Please, help!
Here, Jody!
-I can't hold that!
-Let me hold his hand.
I'm sorry, Bud.
Rest in peace, Bud.
Have a good life there, Bud.
Please ask God for thick hair, okay?
-God bless you.
Jeffri!
-What?
-This…
"Jeffri" here. Isn't that you?
Which one?
There is Lulu, Juhana, and Mansur too.
"Kagok Edan."
Isn't that the band
that was on the video screen before?
Yes.
I’m sorry.
If I knew the video
was going to cause problems,
I wouldn't have put it in.
That's okay. My friend said
that the band is gone.
-There's another one.
-Where?
-Did you write this one as well?
-Yep.
So, which one is it?
The band or the affair with Lulu?
The reason I made the band
was to get close to Lulu.
-And did you get her?
-I did. Inside and out.
She's my wife now.
That's so cute.
Even though the band is gone,
you still have your soul mate.
Ju.
Ladies, please get up.
Look at the monitor.
What's that? Look.
-Where?
-There.
It's the police.
Officer!
Hello Mar, take Jody and Budi to the lab.
Now. The police are here.
What happened to Budi?
All right, you and Jody come here.
Hurry up. We can get out
of here once it clears up.
-Jod.
-What?
-Now is the time for you to hold a weapon.
-True. I agree.
Jod!
This is perfect for a macho guy like me.
Give it to me.
-This is for me.
-What about me?
I thought it was a rape case.
Why is it so empty?
It might just be hoaks.
Hoax.
Hoaks. I have been taught
that it is hoaks since I was a kid.
Did they already have the word hoax
when you were a kid?
Of course not.
The word hoax only started now.
You just said, "hoax."
-Hoaks.
-Hoax.
I don't care if it's hoaks or hoax.
This can create problems among our team.
Move forward!
Check everything first!
I see one victim there. Let's ask her.
You ask her. I'm shy with girls.
Are you serious? Hurry up.
-I'm nervous.
-Don't be. You do it.
You do it.
Just go and ask her.
Okay. We'll do it.
Miss, where are you going?
Yes, kill all of them.
It's a pity we haven't given them a name.
There's more of them!
I don't think they are human.
Shoot them!
Take that!
Finish them off!
Kill them all!
-Shoot them!
-Back up!
Shit!
Oh, God!
There goes our only chance.
-Jody.
-What?
-Your fart smells really bad.
-Just a little.
-Wait.
-What?
They can't see us.
I take back my word.
Your fart is a blessing.
They think we're garbage.
-Jod.
-It's our principal, Mr. Is.
Let me kill him.
Wait! Hold on, Sir.
He might be an annoying teacher,
but he's still our teacher.
Who we are today is all because of him.
Please wait, Sir.
Very stubborn. Don't kill him.
People like him should be preserved.
All right, Sir. Don't be naughty.
Just stay here.
Scratch the walls if you want.
-Thank you, Sir.
-Thank you for everything.
Look at that.
Not only the living hate our songs,
but the dead too.
Now I know it's really bad.
Shit. Just lost another lifeline.
-Why?
-Hold on. Don't make too much noise.
-I'm not making any noise.
-Quiet.
Hey, Jod.
Isn't that Hendrik?
-Hendri.
-From Class 1A?
Hendri who…
I'm not scared of this one.
-Hey.
-Nice hair.
Hey, beautiful.
-Come here.
-Let's go.
Who is the cute one?
What do you want?
It's time for you to…
Now it's my turn.
-I never thought I would use this.
-Take that!
Mar!
Jod!
Mar, they got me.
Your band members are all still here?
Why don't you guys perform?
That's not possible.
Two of us are here.
Jeffri and Mansur are outside.
And if we want to perform,
we have to go to the hall.
I don't want…
I don't want to be like them.
-I don't want to end like that.
-I know.
I'm sorry, Mar.
All this time I have hurt you.
If you do go through the surgery,
remember that to me you will always be
the one with the biggest balls.
You've always been the brave one.
I know.
Not now. There are too many of them, Ju.
They are talking to each other.
Talking?
Mar.
Jod.
-Mar, my hand really hurts.
-Easy, Jod.
-My body is shivering.
-It's okay.
Relax.
Kill me now, Mar.
I'm here, Jody.
Don’t worry about anything.
What are you doing, Sur?
-I'm Marina.
-What are you doing?
-Don't kiss me!
-Don't worry.
I don't want my last moments
to be like this.
-Jod.
-No way!
Jod! No!
Go to sleep, Jod.
Good bye, Denok.
-Who is Denok?
-My car.
Hurry up.
Look at that.
-Where is Jody?
-Jody…
-Jef.
-Lulu.
I'm sorry I yelled at you before.
I'm sorry too.
I have realized that you
and the children are my pillars.
Nothing can take that.
So sweet. So dramatic. So romantic.
Are you guys done?
We have to go to the hall.
-Hall?
-I'll explain later.
Let's go. Hurry up.
If they do anything, we fight them!
Mr. Erwan!
-There are so many of them.
-Are you scared, Ju?
If you're scared,
I will face all of them alone.
You guys go there.
Ju, remember.
Your next movie must be a big hit.
Come on. I'm not scared of you.
I will fight all of you alone!
Come on!
Ju, I'm tired. Let's rest.
Anyway, the hall is still far away.
And they're everywhere.
If I knew there would be a lot of running,
I would have worn my track suit.
Let me do it.
Let me clear the way to the hall
for you all.
I will try to lure them to come to me.
Are you sure?
I…
have no one left.
No one to really worry if I'm gone.
But you…
Many people need you.
Jeffri, and the kids
who are waiting for you at home.
They all need you.
Okay.
-Raina?
-Where are you going?
Good evening, Zenith!
Welcome to the reunion
for the class of '97!
I can't hear your voice!
What happened to your leg?
Please go to the doctor
and get it checked.
Class of '97! Come on, I can't hear you!
There is a surprise performance tonight!
A really cool band will perform!
Don't you guys want to hear it?
I'm sure…
this band will remind you
of your high school days!
Do you know the name of the band?
This will be our performance for tonight
from our own class of '97.
Okay.
Let's give a warm welcome to…
Kapok Edan!
Let's call to the stage…
Budi, Jody…
Mr. Iswadi.
And now Raina.
I'm sorry, it's out of battery.
She's still alive.
Let's give a big applause to Kagok Edan!
They will destroy your eardrums!
Come on, all of you!
Jef!
Be careful.
I haven't used these sticks
for a long time.
Ju, what's the title of the song?
I want you to know that I want…
What is it?
I want you to know that I want you.
Why do you have to make
the title so long and difficult?
We'll be all right.
We'll get out of here alive.
How do we play this? I forgot.
You forgot the song that you wrote?
I'm busy.
I don't have time to think about it.
You must have a lot of spare time.
Making videos for your YouTube channel.
Does anybody even watch it?
Why are you saying that?
Let me tell you, songs are art.
Art is in our blood.
And our blood is our children.
Children? I don't even have a wife.
Then find one. Stop jerking off.
I don't care. I like it!
Let's just play. I'm sure we'll get it.
-The chords are B-D-A.
-Okay.
-Are you sure?
-C.
Let's just play.
Come on.
Guys, they're coming!
We're dead.
They're coming.
Why don't they die?
It's not working, Ju.
Something is not right.
-Look at me.
-We're going to die!
-How do you know?
-I just know!
They will die. Trust me.
-No. You don't know that.
-We'll find a way out.
We will find a way out.
Afuk, you don't know that.
Ju, where is your guitar?
I'll just use the guitar that's here.
Ju, that guitar is damaged.
It's a cheap guitar
and it has a bad pickup.
Don't worry about that,
as long as it performs.
I know what's missing.
Ju, 20 years ago,
you used a broken guitar
provided by the school.
-The strings are made of…
-Cheap wires?
That's it. Different strings
mean different sounds.
You should use the same guitar
you used back then.
That old guitar was from
the music department.
Do you think it's still here?
That was 20 years ago.
-It is unlikely!
-Yes, it is.
Hello. The guitar!
Boy, the guitar I used 20 years ago
from the music department?
It's there. I know where it is.
-Let me get it.
-Hurry up.
Afuk, are you going through the front?
Don't worry. There is a back door here.
All right, hurry up.
What are you guys doing?
Stop fooling around.
Stay away from me!
Help!
Why is he taking so long?
I got it.
Afuk!
-They bit me.
-Please, Afuk.
My hand hurts a lot.
-It really hurts.
-Are you okay, Lulu?
-I'm not sure.
-Did it bite you?
I don't know.
Are you okay, Afuk?
-Don't worry about me.
-You're gonna be okay.
Please, tell the children
I really love them.
Don't touch it. It hurts.
-I have only one request.
-That hurts.
Sur, are you crazy? What are you doing?
Honey, that's just a sprain.
Stop being a drama queen.
And next time you call me Mansur,
I'm going to kick you in the balls.
Honey, will you fix it
if my balls are uneven?
Afuk, how is he?
-They got him.
-He'll be okay.
Should we just kill him?
So the virus doesn't spread.
Just kill me. I'm going to die either way.
You're going to be fine. I know that.
Prill…
you have to know this.
I would be happy to see you in the band
for the last time before I die.
What do you mean?
You're the only one
who can play the bass here.
Please, if you don't want to see me
die in vain,
play the bass now.
-You're not going to die.
-I…
Tie me up now.
Afuk, just when you got a date,
you have to die.
Poor Afuk.
I'm really sorry I have to do this.
The chords.
Hurry up. Come on.
It's bad.
They're almost in.
Kou, kou, kounaon, eh?
Die, you all! Die!
Research conducted
by Professor Oto from Zigot lab
proves that the guitar used by Kagok Edan
emits new frequencies
that can actually affect the human brain,
which had never been discovered.
I told you my song is good.
I'm sure there will be more research
saying that your song is terrible.
You always envy me.
Ju, I have a friend.
Her name is Cindy. She's beautiful. Look.
Prill, what do you think?
-She's all right.
-"All right"?
Five out of ten.
-She's not bad.
-She's beautiful.
-I think Marina is more beautiful.
-Seriously? Thank you.
-Not bad.
-You want to get to know her?
Next month, she's getting
gender reassignment with me.
Kids are out of the question then.
Five out of ten.
Five out of ten and I can't have kids.
-She's pretty.
-Isn't she?
You got an extra stick for free.
By the way, Kagok Edan got an offer
for an album.
-Really?
-They want your song as the single.
I told you. This song
doesn't just kill, it sells.
Let me reply to their text. Okay.
Prilly!
What now?
Look. Look at it.
-What?
-What is it?
Look at that.
Does it remind you of something?
Don't eat it!