There is a story about an ordinary food stall
that found overnight success as the best-selling food stall
in the school cafeteria.
And it is said
that there was a secret hidden in the food stall's soup.
Hello, I'm Kong, or Click, the Hardcore Truth-seeker.
HE'S HERE
Today, I'm going to review a food stall…
RIGHT ON TIME
…that became a sensation…
WHAT'S UP?
…overnight.
I'M A BIG FAN
It went from shitty…
THE LAST ONE WAS SO FUNNY
…to amazing.
Here's the story.
This lady used to serve rice with soups and curries.
When she switched to serving spicy pork bone soup, bam,
things got better for her.
It really is good.
-HAHA, HE SLURPED -IS IT THAT GOOD, KONG?
I'VE EATEN THERE. IT'S SO GOOD
Her food stall has no name.
EPIC
But the whole school calls it "Aunty Jong's place."
Let me tell you something. The most important point here
is that
the son of the stall owner
is a drug dealer.
In our school, the drugs that Jong's son sells the most
are probably amphetamine and weed.
He comes after school.
He and I usually meet behind the toilets.
Aunty Jong knows all about it.
Remember, she may look like a nice person,
but looks are deceiving.
It's possible
that she put weed
in her soup.
You know, I'm not sure.
I've eaten some, and I thought it was good.
I liked it.
I don't know.
But I think other stuff must be in there. That's why it tastes this good.
Shit.
There's other stuff?
Of course there is, dumbass.
Here you go.
TASTY SPICY PORK BONE SOUP
SOLD OUT
UNIQUELY DELICIOUS
The coast is clear.
TIME TO START DIGGING
START DIGGING NOW, KONG
Let's go.
Right now, everything is going our way.
It seems like the soup is sold out for the day.
That means
we are all about to see what's at the bottom
of her pot.
Let's check it out.
SOLD OUT
SHOW US
Here we go.
DELICIOUS
HURRY UP
THIS IS HELLA FUN. I CAN'T WAIT FOR THE PLOT TWIST
THEY SAY SHE PUTS DRUGS IN HER SOUP
-IS SHE BACK YET? -GO ALL THE WAY
Yeah!
That's what we hardcore truth-seekers do.
Watch, everyone.
Today, I'll show you what's really in here.
Don't go anywhere. Stay tuned.
What? Shit!
My dear, what are you doing in my stall?
Well? Please leave.
Well, Aunty, I am live streaming about how delicious your food is.
I won't be long.
Can I see what's in this pot?
My dear, stop it.
Don't do this.
Please leave, dear.
Wow. You're acting so fishy, Aunty.
See, everyone?
Look, everyone.
You're acting so fishy, so there must be something in the pot,
or you wouldn't mind sharing.
Move aside, Aunty.
SHOW US
Move!
-Don't. -Move, Aunty.
AWESOME
Ouch.
What bones are those?
-Shit. -Shit!
Fuck!
What?
A dog's head.
-Shit, a dog's head. -Kong!
-Hey. -You okay?
-What is it? -Hey.
-It's a dog head. -A dog's head.
Aunty, why did you do this?
It's a dog.
-What? -Aunty Jong fed us a fucking dog's head.
-Shit! -Shit!
-You guys, look. Look. -Take a picture.
-Take pictures. Go on. -Sure, Kong. I'll take pictures.
-Shit, I just ate that. -Take photos.
-Take photos. -You're gonna get it for sure.
Take photos.
What the hell?
How long have you fed us dogs' heads?
-Yeah. -How the fuck could I eat it?
How could she do this?
Shit.
Damn dogs' heads.
Aunty, how the fuck could you do this?
It's a dog's head in the pan too. It's clearly a dog's head.
What the fuck?
I think it's…
Aunty Jong, how could you do this? Well?
I'M GOING TO BE SICK
THE BITCH MUST GO TO JAIL
I WON'T EAT HER SHIT ANYMORE
THE SCHOOL NEVER CHECKS SHIT
THE WHOLE COUNTRY KNOWS YOU NOW
POOR DOGS
Look.
-Shit. -Show him too.
Let me see.
Which one?
Let's see.
Shit.
-Clear as fucking day. -Yeah.
Aunty Jong is fucking done for.
Where did she get dogs and cats to cook?
So many still live behind the building.
Right.
But I think the point is not where she got dogs and cats from.
The question is, how long has she fed us fucking dogs and cats?
Ew.
-Shut the fuck up. -I'm going to throw up. Shit.
So where is the skull we found?
I heard the school director had Mr. Pob, the science teacher, take it away
in case it can be used to prove that Aunty Jong fed dog meat to students.
Shit, I think this is a good thing.
If it had gone on any longer… Who knows?
You and the whole school could end up barking like damn dogs.
We ate dogs.
-Shit. -Fuck.
Kong, you're the hero of the hour.
Move.
Well, then,
can I have a cigarette, Mr. Hero?
It hurts! I'm hurt!
-What hurts? -What?
Ouch. Don't touch me, guys.
-Where? -It hurts here.
Here.
-Shit! -Shit!
-Hey. -Awesome.
Hey, can I take a photo?
Shit.
Shit, you're my fucking idol, man.
I'll get a tattoo too.
Which tattoo place did you go to? Do you guys want to come too?
Sure.
How cool.
-I'll get my neck inked tomorrow. -Kong.
Where's my cigarette? Don't pretend you didn't hear me.
-Just a sec, for fuck's sake. -Hurry up.
-You're so slow. -Just take it.
I HOPE SHE GETS FIRED SOON. SHE CAN WORK SOMEWHERE ELSE
DID SHE EVER EAT HER OWN FOOD?
BARF! EVIL!
KONG DESERVES ALL THE CREDIT
KONG, KEEP US UPDATED ON THAT DOG SOUP BITCH
MORE POWER TO ALL THE LITTLE GUYS WHO EXPOSE EVIL. KUDOS
IT'S TASTY, BUT IT'S A NO-NO
Kong, thank you so much.
KONG, YOU'RE BLOWING UP
THEY'RE GONNA TALK ABOUT THIS ON CLUBHOUSE TOMORROW
I LOVE YOUR QUEST FOR TRUTH
Kong, thank you so much.
ACCORDING TO SOME INSIDERS, AUNTY JONG'S SON IS IN A DRUG CARTEL
KONG MUST HAVE KNOWN. THAT'S WHY HE STARTED EXPOSING HER
What the hell is up with Aunty Jong's son?
How dare you bump into me?
Who the fuck was that?
Hold on!
What?
Fucker.
What do you want?
Well? Acting all shady like this?
Tell me what you want.
You're not answering? You wanna be mysterious?
I'll film you and post it online. Come at me if you dare.
I'll get you.
Show your face. Who the fuck are you?
Shit!
Fuck.
Don't! No!
Don't, motherfucker! Don't!
Shit!
Did you see that? Did you see that just now?
Did you see that?
Fuck!
Did you see it? He was going to kill me.
I don't see anyone.
I know who sent you.
You think you can threaten me?
I'm not afraid of you, motherfucker!
TASTY SPICY PORK BONE SOUP
Is the old bitch here?
Hey, the old bitch is fucking here.
Hurry up.
All right, I'm trying.
She's looking this way.
-Let's go. -Okay, let's go.
YOU MADE SOUP OUT OF DOGS, YOU EVIL BITCH!
Aunty.
What is it, dear?
You paid someone to stalk me, didn't you?
You think you can threaten me?
I see.
Are you afraid I'll expose you on Clubhouse tonight?
Fine.
You're dead. I'll fucking expose you.
Wait, dear. What are you talking about? I know nothing about that.
Shit. Jod.
Come over here.
Film it! Go on!
Hi, everyone.
Ever since the incident at this stall, I have been stalked.
HER DAMN SON DID IT
Aunty.
You tell everyone.
Keep filming.
Who did you pay to stalk me?
What do you mean, dear?
Look, everyone.
She's the one who put dogs and cats in her food and fed it to us all.
And when she got caught, she paid someone to stalk me.
-No. -Aunty, admit it.
-I didn't. -Confess.
I've never used dogs and cats to make soup, sweetheart.
You're still lying? We have evidence. The whole school saw it.
Well? Why are you lying?
-My dear… -There he is!
-There. Look. -Wait.
Wait. Please.
-There's really someone in there. -What do you mean?
Where is he?
Wait, dear. What do you mean? There's no one. I'm here alone, dear.
I beg you. Don't cause trouble for me.
I LOVE KONG
I'm not causing trouble. I'm seeking the truth.
Instead of begging me, speak to the camera and to everyone.
Just confess what you've done. Well?
Everyone wants to know the truth. Aunty, move aside. I'll prove it.
-Hey. -Look, everyone.
Look at that picture there.
Here.
I'm sure this is the person stalking me.
Wait. Hey.
I didn't see his face, but I think it's him.
No.
This is my son.
WE FOUND THE SECRET
I see.
TERRIBLE SON
This is your son?
He's your son, right?
DO DRUGS, DO TIME
She finally confessed.
EVIL FAMILY
This is her son
who is rumored on the Internet to be a drug addict and an ex-con.
You got your son to stalk me, right?
Just admit it.
-THE COPS WILL GET YOU -WHY IS SHE CRYING?
Why are you crying?
Well? Do you feel guilty?
EVIL FAMILY
Jod, follow me.
All right, everyone, today, I'll show you the truth about Aunty Jong.
What's behind her stall? Let's find out.
Hey, kid.
LEAVE, AUNTY!
That's enough.
There's no one else here.
Jong has worked here by herself all this time, I'm telling you.
-WHO'S HE? -HER NEW HUSBAND? HAHA
-Follow me, everyone. Jod. -What?
-What are you up to? -Follow me, everyone.
Let's look inside. Where are you?
Jong, calm down. Don't cry.
-Where are you? Film it. -Where?
Come out! You can't get away! You can't get away, motherfucker!
-No one's here. Let's go. -Hey!
Enough, you little shit!
That picture is from his funeral.
Do you hear me? Jong's son died over a month ago.
I'll tell you something. Come here.
Look. The urn is right here.
Open your fucking eyes, won't you?
Can't you see? His mom has worn black for weeks.
I'll tell you something.
Her son was decapitated.
His head still hasn't been found.
Can you imagine?
A mother had to cremate her own son whose body was missing its head.
How much pain must she have endured?
And you keep harassing her.
You little shit!
What are you waiting for? Get the hell out!
Go and apologize to Jong right now.
-I can get out myself! -Go!
-All right! -Get out!
Get outta here, you punks!
-I can fucking walk myself. -So damn nosy!
Last time, he barged in and hurt her.
Here he goes again. Who the hell does he think he is?
Yeah, he's such a clout chaser.
Hey, go and apologize to her right now.
Why should I?
I did nothing wrong. She really made food with dog meat.
If I hadn't exposed her,
we'd all still be eating dogs.
She didn't cook dogs or cats or anything like that.
There's only one way to go in and out.
We stall workers here can see
that she buys food from the market every day.
You're just spewing nonsense, you punk.
Go!
But the other day, everyone here saw it.
That really was a dog's skull in the soup.
Right?
That's enough, Kong.
What you found, which you claim is a dog's skull,
actually came from a chicken.
I had the so-called skull tested at the university's lab.
They said the bones look similar.
You have to look closely to see the differences.
Mr. Pob, listen to me.
You see,
someone said that they saw Aunty Jong put a dog in a sack and hit it.
I'm telling the truth.
Can you bring that person here to confirm this story?
It's someone on the Internet.
You can read the comments. Everyone is talking about this.
Sir, I'm not lying.
Kong.
It's the Internet.
That person may not even be real.
Apologize to Aunty Jong now,
then go see the principal.
I won't apologize to her.
I did nothing wrong.
Aunty Jong really cooked dog meat for all the kids here.
I'm trying to help everyone.
I knew it. She's a good person.
She wouldn't do that.
So true. Besides, she's so old. She's too slow to catch dogs or cats.
Well, how do you explain why her cooking suddenly tastes better?
-Enough. -She put something in it.
That's enough, Kong.
Apologize to Aunty Jong, then we'll go to the principal's office.
Hey, Mr. Pob, let me go.
I won't apologize.
There must be something, sir. Let me go.
MOVE THE CAMERA
-WTF, KONG? -THE TABLES HAVE TURNED
Is this what you want?
I saved you all from eating dogs, right? And you're doing this to me?
Kong!
-Come back! -Wait.
What? Let me go!
Hey, wait!
-Hey. -Hey.
How did it go, Kong? What's your punishment?
-A parent meeting, dickhead. -Damn.
And I gotta apologize to that bitch at the assembly tomorrow
so that she won't press charges, or I could go to jail.
Shit, man, I'm so fucking mad about this.
You know, right, that I did this for everyone?
I think you should apologize to Aunty Jong and end this.
Why should I? I did nothing wrong.
You're one of them now?
It's okay.
Today, on Clubhouse, I'll keep exposing her dirty secrets.
She'll be ruined.
Damn, Kong. What fucking Clubhouse?
They've canceled it.
And now
they've set up a room to bash you, you know that?
"What an epic fail."
"I knew it."
"Something felt off."
"Just another clout chaser."
"For all we know,
he could be the one who put the bones in the pot
and made shit up."
-Shit. -Shit.
Shit, those fucking assholes…
This morning, they supported me. You saw that, right?
And now they've switched to bashing me?
Fuck them. And…
I'll expose all those trolls on my page.
And you guys have to help me, okay?
You'd better apologize to Aunty Jong and end this.
You'd better apologize via live stream before you get witch-hunted for real.
That's true. I agree with him, dude.
Why the fuck should I? I did nothing wrong.
Look, I'll show you how it's done.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know what I was doing.
I didn't mean it.
-See? You can cry too. -It's not funny, assholes.
Do you see me laughing?
Fine.
I'm gonna find proof
that the old bitch put some shit in the soup.
I'll fucking destroy her.
Will you really do that?
If you do that,
I, for one, won't be a part of it.
You're on your own.
What?
You asshole. Jod, seriously, are you…
are you ditching me?
Honestly, Kong,
you're just…
using social media to bully people.
If you still can't see it, that's your problem.
I'm done with you.
-Let's go, Song. -Okay.
You guys are fucking…
Fucking what?
You're fucking assholes!
Fuck you. How could you say that?
Are we still friends? Well?
Break them up! What are you waiting for?
-How could you say that? -That's enough.
-How could you say shit like that? -I told you to stop!
-Are you all right? -Hey!
-Calm down! -What?
Calm the fuck down!
Enough, okay, guys?
Use your head.
You were filming for me this morning. How can you say that, Jod?
Let's just fucking go.
Is this what friends do?
He's fucking annoying.
Okay, assholes, fuck off, then! I'll be fine by myself!
I don't need shitty friends like you!
Piece of shit.
-Really? -How can she do that?
You're gonna get it. You're done. Take photos.
What the hell?
How long have you fed us dogs' heads?
How could she do this?
Shit.
Damn dogs' heads.
Aunty, how the fuck could you do this?
Jong's son died over a month ago.
Can't you see? His mom has worn black for weeks.
Enough, Kong.
Apologize to Aunty Jong now.
I won't apologize.
There must be something, sir. Let me go.
Last time, he barged in and hurt her.
Here he goes again. Who the hell does he think he is?
Yeah, he's such a clout chaser.
You'd better apologize to Aunty Jong
and end this.
Hello, I'm Kong, or Click, the Hardcore Truth-seeker.
-Hello. -Hey, Kong. Check your Facebook right now.
Everyone's shitting on you, asshole.
Song bashed you for hitting him today.
Damn, now everyone is shitting on you.
What are you gonna do?
Hey, Kong?
-What? -Are you okay?
-Calm down, okay? -Well…
-Okay. -Are you really okay?
Fine, then. I'll send you the link, okay?
Call me if you need anything.
-All right. -Okay?
Okay.
DEATH BY TRUTH
I'm telling you, this prick is a clout chaser.
-HE SHOULD PAY -SERVES HIM RIGHT
He messed with her life to get views.
Anyone could see that they were chicken bones,
but he said it was a dog's skull.
Even when we had proof that they were chicken bones,
he still kept lying.
He wouldn't own up.
SHAME ON YOU. WTF?
-DOGS? BULLSHIT -OWN UP TO THIS
-IT'S CHICKEN, NOT DOG -MORON
It's a dog's head.
How could you do this, Aunty?
What the fuck have you fed us?
-YOU'D BE CRAZY TO BELIEVE HIM -DOG, MY ASS
Motherfucker!
Let me go! What the fuck?
Shit!
-WHAT A MORON -WTF IS WRONG WITH HIM?
SO FUNNY, HAHA
Shit.
HE'S FIGHTING WITH A SHADING NET
-Fuck you! -Is this what you want? Well?
Break them up! Kong, come with me! Damn asshole.
Calm down!
-IT'S JUST HIM -CHANGE SCHOOLS, KONG
I saw all your comments, so I had to make another video.
I bet he's getting a shit ton of flak.
I'm sure he's made a video to apologize to Aunty Jong.
He's all like,
"I'm sorry. I didn't know better."
"I'll learn from this mistake."
"Blah, blah." Piece of shit.
I bet he'll release a video like that.
Kong is such a pussy.
Fuck you!
Why did it turn out like this, fucker?
I'm leaving now.
-See you tomorrow. -Okay, see you. Get home safely.
Jong, are you all set for tomorrow?
Why are you done so soon today?
No, I'm not done yet. I'm still missing some ingredients.
I have to go to buy chicken at the market.
They said they'd deliver it today, but they haven't.
I'll get the chicken and come back to stew it.
That's just it. That's what I'm wondering about, Jong.
You serve spicy pork bone soup. What do you need chicken for?
Mr. Pob also said that you use black chicken.
Why do you have to use black chicken?
This recipe is quite strange, isn't it?
Honestly, Jong,
what do you put in it?
Come on.
You're not answering me.
It must be a special secret recipe.
That's amazing.
Well, you're quite something, Jong.
By the way, are you really leaving this place?
Well, I have to stay till the end of the month,
then I'll go.
You poor thing.
What school are you going to work at next?
Nowhere, I suppose.
I doubt any school would hire me now.
My goodness.
Are you going now? We can leave together.
-Yes. Let's go. -Okay.
Get home safely. See you tomorrow.
It's nothing.
Just my imagination.
I'd better go home.
It's creepy in here.
All done.
I'm out. Man, it's been so hot all day.
What the fuck?
Damn it, Jong.
Are you a cook or a witch?
Compared to this,
a dead cat in my bag is nothing.
This shit is way weirder.
I'll get you, Aunty Jong, you bitch.
I'll film everything.
What?
Shit. Why is it acting up now?
What do you want?
Well?
You think I'm scared?
I'll get you.
Let go of me!
You're Jong's son, aren't you?
Didn't they say you died by decapitation or some shit?
You and your mom are dicks.
You fooled the whole school, and they all believe you.
Damn, you're not just a drug addict. You're a horror film addict too.
Right, asshole?
Show me your face if you dare!
Well?
Fuck!
Everyone, have you seen this?
-What is it, Miss? -Kong has lost it.
Many people say he's a clout chaser.
This comment is interesting.
"Kong, what stuff did you take? Tell me."
As in drugs?
Yes. I guess we have to watch him closely.
Mr. Pob, please help me.
Mr. Pob.
Mr. Pob, please help me, sir.
Open the door, sir. Mr. Pob!
Sir, open the door!
Sir, listen to me. Please, sir. You have to help me.
There's a ghost, Mr. Pob.
It's the ghost of Jong's son. He's trying to kill me.
He just tried to kill me over there.
What are you playing at, Kong?
I'm not playing, sir. There really is a ghost.
He broke down the door. He just tried to kill me.
Take a look. If you don't believe me, let's go.
Come on.
-He was down there. -Let go.
Let's go take a look. Go out there. Here. You go down there. You'll see him.
He's there, I swear. Sir, please believe me.
If you're making it up to get more views online,
go do it somewhere else.
Stop causing trouble for others.
I'm starting to believe what they said about you
being high out of your mind on drugs.
There really is a ghost. I'm serious. He's in that bitch Jong's kitchen.
If you don't believe me, go and see. Why don't you go and see?
And at this hour, what were you doing inside Jong's kitchen?
I asked you a question. What were you doing inside Jong's kitchen?
What have you done to her now?
-Damn. -What?
What's wrong with you? Why are you taking that bitch Jong's side?
-What? -You're being very rude, Kong.
I've had enough of you.
Social media users already know the truth about Aunty Jong.
Why won't you stop this?
I see.
Now you believe what's on social media?
Pointing is rude.
Fine.
-Kong. -Kong.
What is it with this kid?
So full of himself.
Whatever the fuck you are, come at me.
I'll cut you to pieces.
Come on.
Who the fuck tied this? Fuck you, Jong.
Shit!
Her son was decapitated.
His head still hasn't been found.
Shit!
Ghost! Shit!
I'm scared. Stop it.
Enough, son.
That's enough, son.
Aunty.
Aunty Jong.
Aunty Jong, I'm… I'm sorry.
Aunty Jong, help me. Please, Aunty Jong. I'm sorry, Aunty Jong.
I'm sorry,
but this is the truth, and I've felt bad about it all this time.
I just want to make a living.
I'm sorry, Aunty Jong.
I promise not to tell anyone about today, Aunty Jong, I promise.
But you have to help me, Aunty Jong.
Please listen to me.
I'm sorry.
Please, Aunty.
I understand you.
You have nothing to worry about.
Don't worry.
I promise not to say anything about today
and about
how you
made soup with a human head.
I promise I won't tell anyone.
I promise, Aunty Jong. Please help me.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have chosen this path.
Okay.
Then let's leave together, Aunty Jong.
Let's go.
I was planning on leaving here quietly at the end of the month.
I didn't want any trouble with you.
Aunty, I'm so sorry. I promise I won't mess with you anymore.
But you wouldn't stop trying to hurt me.
You were trying to use a dead cat
to hurt me.
Aunty Jong, listen to me. I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
-I can explain. -Get out!
What's the point?
I did everything…
for my stall to survive.
I did everything
to be with my son forever.
to protect my beliefs from whoever would destroy them.
But you…
you stuck your nose in my fucking business.
I'm sorry.
Those things you always wanted to know,
you know them now.
Are you happy now?
Well? Are you happy now?
-Aunty. -My son's bone broth…
How was it?
-Was it good? -I'm sorry.
Fuck.
Why is Aunty Jong's soup extra good today?
I'll have three bowls for sure.
Oh yeah. What the fuck is wrong with Kong?
He's missing school again. He's missing something tasty too.
He wouldn't dare show up.
He was supposed to apologize to Aunty Jong during the morning assembly.
You're right.
He must be avoiding it.
I don't think he'll show up anywhere for a while.
Hey, last night, some people saw him hanging around at the cafeteria.
-He doesn't know when to quit. -Shit!
You should ask Aunty Jong. Maybe she saw him.
Damn. The soup is so fucking tasty today. It's so goddamn good.
You guys.
-Shit! -Shit!
Son of a bitch!
Hey, what's going on?
Wait.
TASTY SPICY PORK BONE SOUP
TASTY SPICY SKULL SOUP
Hello.
I'm Kong,
or Click, the Hardcore Truth-seeker.
Today,
I'm going to apologize for…
I'm going to apologize for what I've done.
Honestly, maybe it's all my fault because…
It's because I'm such…
a clout chaser, and I…
and I…
I didn't know any better, and I'm…
I'm sorry.