Every school has a story.
It is said that
the school library
houses more than just books.
Although it is a harbor of knowledge,
it may also conceal some secrets.
And, one day,
you may get a chance to read them.
THE BOOK OF CORPSES
Once upon a time,
there was a girl
who wished for a friend who would understand her,
one who would stay by her side like a true friend would do.
JARIYA SUETRONG, PRINCIPAL
STUDENT RECORDS 1972
I saw them threatening another student.
STUDENT TRANSFER REQUEST
Kaew and her friends tried to give their cheat sheet to her.
I heard Kaew say
that she should write down the right answers
and share them during the exam
or Kaew would get her.
Get her?
Yes, ma'am.
She looked terrified. Her arms were bruised from being squeezed.
It seemed serious, so I came to tell you.
Thank you very much for telling me.
After this,
I'll properly consider those students' punishment.
Excuse me, Madam Principal.
I need to show you something urgently.
FAMILY BELIEVES TEACHER WAS ABDUCTED, KILLED
Saiparn, you may go, dear.
Goodbye.
Hey, have you seen Saiparn?
-Hey, have you seen Saiparn? -No, I haven't.
Hey. Have you seen Saiparn?
Kaew, I don't see her anywhere.
Maybe she's already run home.
Look inside again.
Saiparn.
Well, well,
you sure wasted my time, Saiparn.
-Let me go! -Such a snitch, aren't you?
This is the library.
Be quiet in here.
If you must be so loud, please go outside.
I don't wanna be here anyway.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine, miss.
All right, then.
NARIN PINTONGKAM, LIBRARIAN
Um…
What is it, dear?
Shall I help you arrange the books?
Start with that pile behind you, then. Put it in the other room for me.
Yes, miss.
Thanks, dear.
CHECKOUTS AND RETURNS
THE BOOK OF CORPSES
It's getting late. You can finish this tomorrow.
I don't mind, miss. I can stay.
POTASSIUM CYANIDE
Don't you get lonely all alone in the library?
Not at all.
But it's nice that you're here to help today.
FAMILY BELIEVES TEACHER WAS ABDUCTED, KILLED
Miss.
Is that our school in the news?
Yes, it is.
His family told the police that he'd gone to work as usual that day,
but he never came home in the evening.
Many teachers said that the last place he visited
was probably this room.
Then people started speculating that he might have died or gone missing.
Actually, this rumor made some people scared of using the library.
Do you think
that teacher
died in this room?
Does that frighten you?
I've been here for so long,
and I haven't seen anything scary.
People keep spreading rumors of strange things, though.
Haven't you heard any tales about this school?
No, I haven't.
I just transferred here.
So what happened here?
They say that 20 years ago,
a female student named Ploypoom
was bullied by her classmates and locked up in the toilets.
And no one knew.
She endured that torment in there for three months
until she decided to kill herself
in the toilets upstairs,
right above this library.
Before she died,
she recorded her intense pain and torment
in a book.
A book?
Friends
were all she wanted…
but they ended up killing her.
It's so tragic
for a defenseless person to die from bullying.
It must be some sort of hidden pain you can't tell anyone about.
But sometimes,
it's about who you choose to tell.
Don't let that happen to you.
If you have any problems, you can tell me.
Think of me as a friend.
Let me help you.
It's all right.
What is that? It smells so strong.
A kind of chemical
used to preserve tissue, I think.
Lately, the science department has used lots of it.
But how come I could smell this at the library?
Well…
Uncle Daeng.
Yes, miss?
ACCEPTING NEW STUDENTS
Do you have a moment?
Yes, miss.
Can you look at this ceiling?
There's a hole, so there's water leaking out.
Of course, miss.
KUNAKORN GIRLS' SCHOOL
Twenty years ago,
on the last day of the semester, a female student named Ploypoom
was bullied by her classmates
and locked up in the toilets upstairs,
right above this library.
Hey. What?
Come here.
Go inside.
Get inside, Saiparn. Come here.
You almost got us expelled.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but I'm not going anywhere.
I'll keep you company
for a very long time.
Quit being a bitch, Kaew.
Just own up to your mistakes.
Don't preach at me!
How dare you stick your nose in my business?
I'll stay away from you guys from now on.
You stay away from me too.
Step aside.
I told you to back off.
Stay here and repent, Saiparn.
Nosy bitch!
Let's go!
Kaew!
Kaew, let me go!
Kaew! You--
Saiparn!
They did that to you?
Why didn't you tell anyone?
I can help you.
It's okay, miss.
You wouldn't be able to help anyway.
Nosy bitch!
THE BOOK OF CORPSES
Before she died,
she recorded her intense pain
and torment…
THE BOY WHO CRIED WOLF
…in a book.
THERE WAS A SHEPHERD BOY WHO LIKED TO FOOL…
THE VILLAGERS RAN OUT TO CHASE THE WOLVES AWAY, BUT…
THE BOY CRIED FOR HELP AND LOST HIS VOICE…
THE LION AND THE MOUSE
THE MOUSE GNAWED RIGHT THROUGH THE ROPE AND SAVED THE LION'S LIFE.
"In a lonely, desolate land,
there lived a girl."
IN A LONELY, DESOLATE LAND, THERE LIVED A GIRL.
EVERYONE ELSE TURNED HER INTO A LOVER OF SOLITUDE.
"Everyone else turned her into a lover of solitude."
"They forced her to be
where nobody wanted to be."
MEET US IN THE TOILETS. WE GOT YOU A BIRTHDAY GIFT.
FROM SUDA.
Ploypoom.
This is a Western dessert.
Maybe you've never had one…
AESOP'S FABLES
…so we got it for you
as a birthday gift.
"One day,
someone came forward, destroyed that land,
and gave her something called 'friendship.'"
Close your eyes and make a wish.
Do you like it, Ploypoom?
Just like the lion and the dead mouse
in your story.
Where do you think you're going?
Stay in here with your dead mouse!
No!
Open the door!
"But then she discovered
that having friends like those was the worst gift in life."
"They were like vipers
that would bite their helper
and destroy the trust she had in them."
Let me out.
She endured that torment in there for three months…
"Friends… who never valued me."
"Friends…
who looked down on me."
who wanted me dead."
"Friends?"
"With friends like you, I'd rather have none."
THE BIRTHDAY GIFTS THAT THIS WORTHLESS…
WITH FRIENDS LIKE YOU, I'D RATHER HAVE NONE.
"The moral of the story is
even if you're mightier than a lion,
when you become a rotten corpse,
you're just food for the mice."
"Your dead bodies are the birthday gifts
that your worthless, mouse-like friend
wants the most."
LIBRARY
Excuse me, miss.
Can I ask about Ploypoom, the girl you talked about the other day?
The girl who was bullied to death?
Yes.
I want to know
what happened to her bullies after that.
I heard
that they were arrested
and extensively interrogated.
After that,
they killed each other in the cell.
Rumor has it
that they died
just like Ploypoom wished for in her book.
Does that mean whatever gets written in the book
will come true?
I believe
that these school tales are true.
If they weren't true,
nobody would have written about them.
Why are you so interested in this all of a sudden?
I'm just curious
about what happened at this school.
SHE HELPED THEM CHEAT…
THEY BETRAYED HER.
"GOOD FRIENDS TAKE YOU TO HEAVEN. BAD ONES DRAG YOU TO HELL."
Saiparn.
KUNAKORN GIRLS' SCHOOL
Rumor has it that they died
just like Ploypoom wished for in her book.
Does that mean whatever gets written in the book
will come true?
I believe
that these school tales are true.
ONCE, AT A BORING GIRLS' SCHOOL,
A GIRL COULDN'T STAND SEEING INJUSTICE HAPPENING IN FRONT OF HER,
SO SHE DECIDED TO INTERVENE.
Students, please thank the teacher.
-Thank you, teacher. -Thank you, teacher.
UNITED WE STAND
Saiparn. What's your hurry, bitch?
What are you hiding?
-Give it to me. Get her. -Give it back, Kaew!
Stay still.
-Let go! -Will you stay still?
Don't move.
Let go of me.
Jeez, stop moving.
YOU'RE SO ANNOYING!
"Kaew, I hate you."
"When will you just die?"
"Evil bitches like you
won't die in peace!"
Aw, Saiparn.
You hate me so much, but all you can do is write in this silly ghost book.
You really believe this nonsense?
Poor Saiparn.
Apart from being a snitch,
are you delusional too, you lunatic?
Everyone, look at this nutcase.
She has no friends,
so she has to befriend a ghost.
-Let go! -Hey!
-You crazy bitch! Hold her! -What the hell are you doing?
-Stay still! -Get off me!
-Come here! -Let go!
-Will you just stay still? -Stop.
You bitch!
-Come here. -Hold her still.
Let go of me!
-Hold her still. -Sit down.
-Hey. Stay still. -Let me go!
Stay still.
-Stay still. -Kaew.
What are you doing?
Kaew!
This is payback, stupid!
If any one of you tells a teacher,
you're fucked!
Go!
Let's go, girls.
Kill her.
"When will you just die?"
"Evil bitches like you
won't die in peace!"
Kill her.
She must die.
-She deserves it. -Kill her.
Kaew.
Kaew, what is it?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Saiparn.
-Kaew! -I'm sorry.
Kaew!
-What happened to Kaew? -Kaew!
Wake up, Kaew!
Kaew, wake up!
-Kaew! -No.
How did this happen?
Kaew!
Kaew! Wake up!
YOU MADE THIS SCHOOL WORSE!
Kaew, I hate you.
Evil bitches like you won't die in peace! I hope you hurt 100 times more than me!
"Karma's a bitch, and then you die."
Shit, where is it?
THE WISH BY NARIN PINTONGKAM
THIS BOOK'S WHISPERS SHOWED ME THAT HE DESERVES…
YOU'LL PAY FOR WHAT YOU DID TO ME
NARIN PINTONGKAM, LIBRARIAN
Miss.
You've read my story, haven't you?
A young woman who just graduated…
was determined to be a good teacher.
But she ended up being isolated
because her colleagues didn't like her.
She was slandered
day after day…
until…
NARIN PINTONGKAM, LIBRARIAN
…she met a male teacher…
who offered her friendship.
She thought she had found a true friend.
-Stay still. -But he assaulted her.
He hurt her body
and her soul.
She wanted to die…
but she couldn't.
The moral of the story is…
that the one who deserved to die
was that bastard.
I wrote that the son of a bitch died here.
Isn't it great, Saiparn?
Didn't he deserve it?
Why do you look so upset, Saiparn?
You hated that girl so much, you wanted her to die, right?
But I didn't want Kaew to die.
What happened to you and the others who wrote in that book?
I had to trade my body
and my soul
for the wish I wrote in the book.
THE BOOK OF CORPSES
I'm glad
you decided to write down your wish
and leave it to someone you trust.
If you have any problems,
I can help you.
It's what you wanted!
I never wanted it to turn out like this.
You lying bitch!
I know you wanted revenge! You wanted her dead!
Karma's a bitch,
and then you die.
We just helped you fulfill your wish…
and made it come true, that's all.
A hundred times more pain.
You must die!
Let's stay friends forever, Saiparn.
No. I'm scared. No.
In the end,
that girl got her wish…
…and found friends who would stay by her side
forever.
THE BOOK OF CORPSES
Give this book a try. It's worth it.