They say
a senior once put the curse of death on all her classmates
before killing herself.
That senior
was hiding a secret
in a box of curses.
And it's hidden
somewhere in this school
and no one knows about it.
Everyone, please help me.
It won't stop following me. I don't know what to do now.
I don't know what else to do.
If and when it's opened,
it will bring death
to this school again.
PANYAPHORNWITTAYA SCHOOL
I'm so damn sleepy. I was up so late last night.
Did you watch the live stream last night?
What happened? Spill it.
It's Mint from Class Two. She was raving on Facebook,
saying someone was gonna kill her, and then the live stream got cut off.
That attention seeker must've had a fight with her boyfriend as usual.
Bitch, if she heard you say that, she'd be mad at you for sure.
You think I'm afraid of her? Come at me.
Yeah.
Hey, that's Mint. Did you watch her live video last night?
-Shit, it must be her. -Yeah.
Let me take a picture.
Hey, please don't take pictures.
Please put your phone away.
No pictures. Put your phones away.
Put your camera away. Hey, do you have permission?
We're at the scene of the incident now.
I can't show you more because the teacher's keeping us back.
Shit, guys. Look. It's so freaking scary.
HAS ANYONE TAKEN MINT'S BODY DOWN?
The teacher said we have to wait for the cops.
If anyone knows more, leave a comment.
SUN'S EX WON'T LEAVE HIM ALONE.
HE DOESN'T LOVE HER ANYMORE.
HOW SHAMELESS IS SHE? SO ANNOYING.
A GIRL WOULDN'T KEEP CALLING HER EX SECRETLY IF SHE WASN'T A SLUT.
MINT
CLASS 5/3
NO ONE COULD HAVE IMAGINED THIS WOULD HAPPEN. REST IN PEACE, MINT.
Hey.
I heard the teachers checked the school's security cameras,
and it looked like Mint was alone.
Plus, they saw Mint jumping on her own.
Why would Mint kill herself?
It'll be okay. Don't worry about it too much.
THE PLAY CURSE OF CIRCLE
The script is almost done, Mr. Director.
Well done.
Okay.
JINNIEZZ WRSRZ LIKED YOUR COMMENT.
SHE SHOULD JUST DIE.
Here.
Wow, it's green tea.
How did you know?
-It's your treat? -Yeah.
Is this low sugar?
Yes. Why?
It's so sweet. Should I go deal with them?
No, don't bother.
Are you sure?
I would if you didn't stop me.
Oh, right.
Everyone in my class was talking about Mint today.
It's so shocking.
I walked past her yesterday.
I watched the video from the livestream.
It's so scary.
You watched it?
I didn't dare. My friends said it was horrifying.
If this scares you, how can you be a horror film director?
It's not the same, my dear Pleng.
I guess that's true,
since even cuties like me can write scripts for horror plays.
Yeah.
You really are cute.
We need to finish.
You mean the script?
Yeah.
All right. I won't tease you anymore.
I'm off to the bathroom, okay?
Can we take a picture with you?
Sure.
Thank you.
-Thank you. -I'm rooting for you.
JINNIE
Pleng.
Where are you going?
I have an emergency.
I'll write the rest at home. It's almost done.
BOY CALLING
MISSED CALL FROM BOY
Come here.
Don't try to win me over. You're sleeping outside tonight.
Bad dog.
All right, just this once. But that doesn't mean I'm not mad anymore.
Want some?
Don't make that face.
I brought flowers for Mint.
Oh, the other day, I saw you with Boy.
Why? Do you like him too?
Or are you gonna steal someone I like just like your friend stole my boyfriend?
Don't talk shit about my friend.
How lucky for Mint
that her best friend's defending her.
You know what?
You're boring.
That's why Sun got tired of you
and went to my friend.
There's one more thing.
It's a secret, actually.
Boy and I
have been together for a long time.
I hope you understand, Pleng.
Where are you?
I don't feel like studying. I'm skipping class.
SUN'S EX WON'T LEAVE HIM ALONE.
HE DOESN'T LOVE HER ANYMORE.
HOW SHAMELESS IS SHE? SO ANNOYING.
So true. She should just die.
Pleng.
FROM DAY ONE IN CLASS 1/1 TO THE END, PRAEWA WAS MY FRIEND.
MY DEAR ING-ORN, YOU'RE AT PEACE NOW.
UP THERE, NO ONE CAN FOLLOW YOU TO COPY YOUR HOMEWORK ANYMORE.
"If you want to curse someone, write their name under your foot
and chant this ground-stomping spell."
"Ohm jakka jakka winas moranang
jakka jakka namapata ou ou."
Hey, that's Mint. Did you watch her live video last night?
Girls, move back. Hey, please don't take pictures.
Please put your phone away.
MINT
You love your friend, so go be with her, Jinnie, you bitch.
JINNIE
Ohm jakka jakka
winas moranang jakka jakka
namapata ou ou.
-…an idol shooting a story. -Beautiful.
-Wow. -Look at that.
-Isn't she hot? -What a model.
-Nice. -Here she goes.
-Yes. Excellent. -Does it look good?
Just a little more. One, two…
Good.
-The famous pose. -Looking good.
Jakka jakka winas moranang
jakka jakka namapata ou ou.
One, two…
Ohm jakka jakka winas moranang
jakka jakka namapata ou ou.
Ohm jakka jakka winas moranang jakka jakka namapata ou ou.
Ohm jakka jakka winas moranang
jakka jakka namapata ou ou.
Stop it!
What happened?
Winas moranang jakka jakka namapata ou ou.
Shut the fuck up!
Ohm jakka jakka winas moranang jakka jakka namapata ou ou.
Ohm jakka jakka winas moranang…
Stop it!
Stop!
Jinnie.
Get it out!
PANYAPHORNWITTAYA SCHOOL
STORAGE ROOM
MODELING.
Why did you follow me here?
If you want the script, check your email.
I sent you everything.
Wait, Pleng.
What's wrong?
You didn't pick up my calls. You didn't text me back either.
Is there a problem?
I don't have one.
But you do.
What's wrong?
You have a girlfriend.
No, I don't.
It's Jinnie.
Why did you lie to me?
Hold on, Pleng.
Jin is actually my little sister.
She's my sibling.
Why have we never heard of her?
There are no pictures of you together on social media.
Jin wouldn't let me post them.
She said that her man might get the wrong idea.
Jin is always like this.
Last time, she stirred up trouble with my female friends too.
My friends almost dumped me.
Wait a minute.
How do you know my sister Jinnie?
We went to the same cram school.
We didn't get along.
Oh, so that's what happened.
Now that you know the truth,
can you stop being mad at me?
Are you still mad?
Perhaps you're not mad after all.
Are you jealous?
No.
I'm not that close to Jinnie,
so I didn't know you were siblings.
How was I to know I'd be messed with like this?
Well, that's that.
I believe you're not jealous.
So what are you doing in here?
I don't feel like going to my last class.
To be honest,
when I walk past this room,
it always sends shivers down my spine. I…
Because you're afraid of ghosts.
No way.
Who's afraid?
Not me.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Don't you know this room's story?
They say the students in this class
all died
because of a classmate's curse.
And that person killed herself afterward.
Then the room was kept locked
and turned into a storage room, as you can see.
But…
isn't that
the plot of the play that you wrote?
Yeah.
It is.
Well, I used this story for inspiration.
Well.
I don't have any more classes. Should we go get some food?
Are you buying? I don't have any money left.
Okay.
Then let me go get my things first.
Why don't you stay here until the traffic is lighter?
Okay.
Is no one home?
No.
My mom's out of town for work. She isn't back yet.
I see.
So…
are you an only child?
I played alone when I was little. It was kind of lonely.
It would've been nice to have a brother like you.
Are you and Jinnie close?
Yesterday,
I didn't know what was up with her.
She locked herself in her room and wouldn't eat anything.
It's going to be okay, Boy.
I'm sure she'll be better soon.
Thank you so much, Pleng.
When I'm with you,
I feel so at ease.
Pleng.
I…
like you.
JINNIE
What the hell?
Why did you write Jinnie's name?
Boy, calm down.
It's nothing, Boy.
Then why did you write it?
-Boy, calm down. -Why did you write it?
Answer me.
-Why did you write it? -Boy, please.
-Calm down. -Why did you write it?
Boy, help me.
Jinnie.
-What's wrong? -Boy, help me.
Hello?
Boy.
Can you hear it? It's back again.
-LOOK AT HER. SO CREEPY. HAHAHA. -WHAT ARE YOU ON? SPILL IT!
Look at it. Look.
CLOUT CHASER.
What is this weird sound?
-GO GET YOUR MEDS. -WHO ELSE IS CONFUSED?
Help me. I can't take it anymore.
No. I can't take it anymore.
I don't want to hear it.
JINNIE
Can you hear it?
I'm scared.
No! Don't!
No, I don't want to hear it. Get out!
I can't take it.
Come off!
-IT FROZE. -LOST CONNECTION?
PRIM
What's with you, Jinnie?
If you're so scared, die.
If you can't go on, die.
You can't even bear this?
Yeah, just die.
Just die.
Get out!
What a loser!
Do you dare to die?
You should just die.
Since you're going to kill yourself,
just die already.
People like you are such losers.
That's not enough to kill you.
You need to do more.
Is that all you can do?
You need to do it harder.
Just die, Jinnie.
Die now. Do it again. I told you to do it harder.
Just die already!
Jin!
JINNIE HAS PASSED AWAY
JINNIE
"Once the curse is cast, no one can stop it
until the cursed person dies."
"But if the curse reflects back upon the caster,
burn everything in this box
to reduce the curse and all the vengeful spirits to ashes."
PLEASE TAKE OFF YOUR SHOES
STORAGE ROOM
I didn't mean it.
I didn't mean to put the curse of death on you and Mint.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
BUSTED. SHE HAS NO SHAME AT ALL.
WHOA! PLENG IS THE WORST BITCH IN OUR CLASS.
I'M SO SCARED. WHAT OTHER NAMES DID SHE WRITE?
HER CONDOLENCE POSTS ARE LIES.
I'M SO ASHAMED WE SHARE A SCHOOL.
You want to do this, huh?
Get the hell out!
Come at me, you bitch! Come here!
STORAGE ROOM
Thank you, Pleng, for being a part of my life.
I'll always think of the good times we shared.
I don't have any more classes. Should we go get some food?
Are you buying? I don't have any money left.
Okay.
Then let me go get my things first.
Boy.
IF YOU WANT TO CURSE SOMEONE, WRITE THEIR NAME UNDER YOUR FOOT…
PLENG