If you are my junior
I will be scolding you harshly right now
But if you are my lover
I won’t say a word of complaint
So, what kind of relationship do you want to be in with me?
Your lover
I’m meeting my friends tomorrow
I’d like you to come with me
So he lets you dangle around him already
So, do you like my friend?
I like Sky
Then, if one day I no longer look cool
you mustn’t abandon me
Understood
Um!
I want to ask you something
Are you free this Saturday?
Where are we going?
Let’s meet my father
Huh!?!
Starring
Billy – Patchanon Aounsa-ard as “Nuea Nimman”
Seng – Wichai Saefant as “Toh Thima”
Heng – Asavarid Pinitkanchanapan as “Sky”
Surprise – Pitikorn Siripornsawan as “Kaojao”
Opp – Weerapong Aodherng as “Intouch”
Nut – Witsarut Khakum as “Daisy”
Freen – Sarocha Chankimha as “Khongkwan”
Becky – Rebecca Patricia Armstrong as “Fon”
Dew – Nitikorn Pankram as “Tor”
Looknam – Orntara Poolsak as “Som”
Ging – Areeya Ponfutrakul as “Prao”
Punch – Tipanan Nilsiam
Paper – Peerada Namwong
Anda – Anunta Teavirat
Guest-starring
Saint – Suppapong Udomkaewkanjana as “Thep”
Pete Thongchua
Chanokwanun Rakcheep
Inthira Charoenpura
Siwadol Janthasaewee
Adapted from novel – “Stalker: The Secret Crush” by Darin
Directed by Thanamin Wongsakulpach
Secret Crush On You, The Series
[Comedic music tunes play]
Cock-a-doodle-doo
Doo
Doo Doo! Doo Doo!
- Hey
- What
- Look at him
- Oh
- Argh!
Give it back here
[Still continues to chuckle and cackle with a piece of chicken]
Cock-a-doodle…
Toh
Doo!!!!
- Toh!
- Ah!
[Endlessly making chuckle and cackle noises with fried chicken]
- Grrrr!
- Ah!
- Damn it!
- Huh?
What’s with you, Toh!? You keep fighting with the chicken nonstop
- Yeah. You still looked happy yesterday
- Yeah
Who’s happy!?
I’m super stressed out right now
Why is that?
You must tell me what’s stressing you out
so we can help solving the problem
- Um
You know…
Nuea asked me to go to his house tomorrow
Ahhhhhh
[Som and Daisy screaming loudly]
- House
- His house
- Shsh!
- Oh shit!
- They’ll kick us out, you ass
- So sorry
- I’m so sorry
Hee hee
What’s the problem?
You’ve been there before, yeah?
- That’s true
- Aha
Think about it
- Aha?
- What?
Last time
I went there as his junior from the university
Aha
Yeah
But this time
I’ll go there as a….
His wifey
- Hmphhhh
- Hmph
Let’s think about it
Who were the people he invited to his house up till this point?
And…
if Nuea’s dad meets me this time,
won’t he black out?
I don’t think it’ll be that bad, maybe
Don’t you agree?
True
- Right
- Um!
I think you should be more confident
Regardless of what’s gonna happen, you’re now Nuea’s lover
- Yeah
- Right?
- Right
Um
Toh
you said Nuea only invited
those hot and glam people to his house
But who says you can’t be one of those hotties, huh?
[Rock music tunes play]
It’s been 2 weeks
Tor hasn’t come for 2 weeks…what does this mean?
I said the weather is nice today
- Hello, everyone
- Hello
- Hello, Jao, Som, Daisy
Hello
Hey, on the count of three
Tadah!
[Romantic and gentle music tunes play]
Here
Come here
Hello
Toh, what did you do today?
You look nice
So cute. Can I kiss you on the cheek, please?
Er…
well…
Hmph!
You can’t…
because Nuea hasn’t kissed me yet today
Whooooo!
[All are making noises to cheer and tease]
Serves you right, Kwan
Khongkwan, stop teasing him already
Then, may I kiss you on the cheek instead, Fon?
Whoa whoa
Too sweet
Hee hee
But I really think you look cute today
Thank you
- Come with me
- Eh?
Oh! He’s dragging him out
- Byeeee
- Go go
Why did you have to tease him so much?
- He’s already crazy in love as he is
- He’s funny
As far as I can see,
Nuea is kind of possessive. Right?
Yeah. He’s so fierce
Yeah. I wanna have a moment like that, too
Did you three purposely do that [makeover for Toh]?
- That’s correct
- Ha ha ha. Yes
What about you, Jao? Would you like to know
if I’m possessive or not?
Ooh
[“Like a Star (My Stellar)” melody plays]
Oh!
One more time, Sky
- Ah! Oops
- Wanna try again, Sky?
Ha ha ha ha
Bye bye
Then…
“our couple”
Our couple will take our leave as well
- Oh, sure!. Yes, of course
- Bye bye
Bye
Oh?
Hey, I’m heading off first
- Where are you going?
- Touch just texted me
- Byeeee
- Hey
Who primped you up like this?
Tell me right now
Erm…er
- Tsk [Nuea clicks his tongue in frustration]
- Nuea…
You don’t like how I look?
[Soft dramatic music tunes play]
Toh
I know I shouldn’t do this
It doesn’t look good on me
I only end up embarrassing myself
Toh, that’s not true
Not only you don’t look bad
but you also look very cute like this
You’re so cute that I’ve become so possessive right now
Are you…
possessive of me?
Damn right
You are my lover
[Nuea’s voice echoes “my lover”]
You suddenly dress up so fine turning heads around you
Hmmmm. There’s no way that they look at me, Nuea
They most likely
look at you, Nuea
Why are you saying such things?
You’re cute the way you are
[Nuea’s voice echoes “You’re cute the way you are”]
If you’re not cute
will I like you?
Hm?
Don’t be ridiculous, Nuea. I’m not cute. I’m actually handsome, you know
Pft
One more thing
The reason I do the makeover is
I want to impress your family
Also…I bought a manner book that teaches how to talk with adults
I’ll master the skills by practising in front of the mirror tonight
You’ve been trying so hard. But have you got the outfit for tomorrow yet?
[Soft dramatic music tunes resume]
Hmph. Not yet
In fact, I’m here to ask you
what’s best to wear
Come here
Here. Open it
Is this for me?
That’s right. I bought it for you
[“SCOY” Ost plays]
Do you like it?
Yes, I do
Thank you
Secret Crush On You, The Series
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
Hello. My name is Toh
Secret Crush On You, The Series
Colla-AC, 1 tablet a day to reduce facial and body acne
[Fantasy music tunes play]
[Sounds of main doors opened]
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello
Hello
[Sound of Nuea’s father footsteps approaching]
My name is Toh
[Intense music plays]
You came to take photos on Lan’s birthday. Is that right?
I remember you
Yes, sir
You don’t need to take a lot of photos today
Make yourself at home
I have quite a few photographers today
[Intense music continues to play as footstep sounds fade]
Nuea
Uncle is so handsome!
Chill, Toh
That’s my dad
[Entertaining music plays]
Toh!
Slow down. Mummy can’t keep up with you
- My son! Muah!
- Mum
Hm! You look pretty good today
Look at your sister’s dress. Isn’t it gorgeous?
- Yes, it is
- This is the dress I wanted to wear but I couldn’t squeeze myself in
Mother
- Hello, auntie
- Oh, hello
Hello
I’m Toh
Toh
I have a question to ask
Yes, ma’am
I heard you’re close with Nuea, right?
Yes. We’re seeing each other right now
[“We’re seeing each other right now” repeated]
What did you just say?
Er…
I mean…
we’re close
Ohhhh, I see
It’s good to know you’re on good terms
Toh is adorable
Just like Nuea told me
Thank you so much
- Hello
- Oh!
- Hello there
- Good to see you
- Hello. Hello
I’ll take care of the guests first
Yes, mum…I mean auntie
Hello
- This way please
- Yes
Show me
Oh, thank you so much
Nuea
Do you think…
uncle knows about us?
Actually, I told my mum already
But I don’t know
if she told my dad or not
Nuea!
How come you didn’t tell me sooner? I freaked out a lot
Come
Let’s have a seat at our table
Let’s go
- Quick
- Coming now
- This way
- Yes
[Intense music plays]
- Ahem. Toh
[Toh blowing raspberries]
[Toh continues to blow raspberries while playing with food]
What’s the matter?
Nervous
No need to be nervous. Okay?
Nuea
I haven’t seen you for ages. It’s as if you vanished into thin air
I’ve never gone anywhere
I just…need to spend time with my lover
Lover?
Please excuse me. I’ll go take photos
Where are you going, Toh?
It’s time to eat
Why must you take photos now?
Excuse me
May I have this one?
Yes, of course Master Nuea
Try this one. It’s good
You’re generous, Nuea
You even allow the photographer to sit here and enjoy the meal together with us
[Soft dramatic music tunes play]
You were saying that you have a lover
Who is the person? I’m so curious
Pie, you’re here already!
You look so beautiful. Hello
Hello
Wait a minute. I heard the word “lover”
Whose lover? Hm?
[Soft dramatic music melody continues]
Toh
You know who Nuea's lover is, don’t you?
Right
I’m also curious to know who Nuea’s lover is
who Nuea’s lover is
[Voice echoing]
Well…
why are you asking me this,
uncle and auntie?
I have a reward [if you tell me who that is]
[Intense music plays]
That’s right. There’s a reward
[Voice echoing]
A reward!?!
There’s a reward. There’s a reward. There’s a reward
[Intense percussive music plays]
I, Thima
[Fantasy and romantic music melody plays]
promise to cherish and respect Nimman
for better or worse,
in sickness and health
I will love you and honour you
all the days of my life
till death do us part
[Crowd clapping]
[Romantic music melody continues]
Whoo!
Kiss kiss kiss!
Whoaaaaaa! Bravo!
[Nuea’s mum and the crowd screaming joyfully]
Hmph!
[Sound of firearm magazine foley]
Dad!
[Crowd screaming]
Secret Crush On You, The Series
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
Dad, no! Please don’t
Move aside!
Bang!
[Sound of fired bullet]
Secret Crush On You, The Series
Kiss kiss kiss!
Whoaaaaaa!
[Nuea’s mum and the crowd screaming joyfully]
[Romantic music melody continues]
Hmph!
Ahhhh!
[Sound of firearm magazine foley]
Dad!
[Intense and dramatic music plays]
Dad, no!
[Sound of crowd panicking in the background]
Please don’t!
Move aside
Dad, don’t!
Arrrgh
[Sound of fired bullets]
[Intense and dramatic music continues]
[Sound of firearm magazine foley]
[Sound of fired bullets]
Dad
Hello
- Hello
Pie, please do me a favour and lead your father and mother to their seats
Wow, I love the scent of your perfume
You’re gorgeous today
Thank you
You’ve met Pie already, correct?
Yes, sir
I’ve met her
At first
I planned to match her up with Nuea
but I just learnt that
Nuea already has a lover
[Intense musical buildup music plays]
You know
who the person is, correct? Toh?
I…
well…
erm…
It’s me
Hm?
I’m Nuea’s lover
[Toh’s voice echoing “I’m Nuea’s lover”]
What if I tell you to break up?
What are you going to do?
I will break up with him
[Intense musical buildup music fades]
[Soft dramatic music tunes play]
Everyone
I’d like to thank each and every one of you
for coming today to celebrate my father and mother’s anniversary
I’d like to ask all of you
to raise your glasses and make a toast for my parents
All right
Hip hip Hooray!
And, because today is an important day for my family
I’d like to take this opportunity to tell everybody here
that I have a lover now
My lover
is Toh (table) right here
[“SCOY” Ost plays]
Eh?
Toh (table) ?
Which one?
Which table?
My lover
is called “Toh”
[The crowd applauds]
Come take photos together
Thank you
So, if I tell you to break up
will you break up with him that easily?
In fact
it will be tough
But
I can’t continue to date Nuea
if his family doesn’t approve of our relationship
Besides
uncle and aunties have raised Nuea so well
You’ve given him nothing but the best
I think…
if you think I’m not suitable for him
I will accept it and leave
Hey, be more confident
Let me tell you something
As Nuea’s dad
I don’t like choosing anything for him
He’s pretty fussy
He prefers making his own decisions
[Gentle and romantic tunes play]
I don’t think we should intervene in love and romance of the younger people
It’s better for old people like us
to just cheer them on from afar
Hm
Does this mean…
you approve of our relationship, uncle?
This is Year 2022
Stop calling me uncle
and start calling me dad already!
Call me mum, okay?
Say it
Yes, mum
Let’s take pictures together
So…
what do you think about my dad?
[Toh whistling gleefully]
What the heck is he doing?
Who is he smiling at?
Yeah
What happened?
Who is he waving to?
Well well well
Since you’re smiling from ear to ear like this
it can only mean
things went well last night, huh
Do you wanna hear?
Of course, we do
Tell us
Tell us quick
Well…
I went to Nuea parents’ anniversary yesterday
Aha
And…
I took pictures together with his family
Ooh
Your hubby’s dad
is soooo cool
He also said that…
that…
he’ll take me along for a holiday trip abroad
during the semester break
Aaaaaahhhh
Your scream is louder than mine
Don’t tease me, Som
Toh
You took photos with his family, right?
Um!
You didn’t bring back anything weird with you, right?
That’s right!
Did you take anything back with you?
No
[Sighs of relief]
What a relief
No way I would ever miss the chance!
[Lively music plays]
- Pig’s head
Damn it!
Did Nuea see it?
Nope
The pig’s head, Jao
[Energetic music tunes play]
May I sit with you?
[Uplifting music tunes play]
Woah! What the hell!?
What’s happened, Daisy?
Wh-why do you look like this!?
Yeah
Exactly
I think something must have happened
Tell us
Right
Speak up
- Quick
- Hurry up
- Speak up
- Now
Aaaarrrgh
There’s nothing
All you need to know is
from now on
I am
Oh!
“Day”
the manly masculine
I’m no longer the feminine Daisy you used to know
[Phone rings]
Ah!
Mm…
[Phone continues to ring]
Yeah, so tough of a guy
It gives me chills
Yes, Day
So manly
But if I know
it’s related to what happened
I will hunt for the truth
It’ll be over for you
So over
You’ll be done
You won’t make it
Ahhhh
Whatever
Let’s head to class
or we’ll be late
Fine
Right
Hurry
Follow my lead
Yes, sir
He changed the subject
- So scary
- I think something must have happened
Hey hey
Huh?
That way
The elevator is that way
Oh yeah
I was going that way anyway
Right
Follow me
Is he possessed by a demon spirit?
How can he act like this?
- Agree
- Is he gonna be all right?
Hello, students
- Hello
You don’t sound so lively today, hm?
Those in the back rows
Submit your assignments over here before the class starts
As for the front rows, I can tell you haven’t finished
So keep doing it
This way
Come here
You wanna re-submit?
Correct it and re-submit, so you pass
- Come in
- Hello, professor
Nuea
[“SCOY” Ost plays]
Hello
- I hope you are doing fine
- I’m good
May I borrow your microphone please?
This?
Have it your way
Hello
Whose name is Thima?
Please stand up
Secret Crush On You, The Series
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
It’s time to tell us
what’s happened to you
this is unbearable
Secret Crush On You, The Series
Hello
Whose name is Thima?
Please stand up
Thima
[Uplifting music tunes play]
- Thank you so much, professor
- Sure
- Er…
- Hello, Nuea
- Hello
Why are you here, Nuea?
I’m here
to make a delivery for the desserts
Fon baked some for you to share
I see
Thank you
Oopsie...too bad you got overly excited for no nothing
Hmph!
[“Like a Star (My Stellar)” music plays]
And I’m here to see my naughty kid
Are you studying hard?
🎵 I pointed my eyes towards the wide and empty night sky 🎵
🎵 Still, there is a star 🎵
- Professor
- Yes?
- May I borrow the microphone one more time please?
- Yes, of course
Thima
Study hard, okay?
Oohhh....
Your guardian really cares about you
He’s our friend
Students, settle down
Thima, sit down
Next row, come. Having a guardian doesn’t mean you’ll pass my subject. Understood?
Argh!
Oh. I dropped it again. Ha ha
Hey there
Let’s dig in
Come on
Ummm. Yum
Hey
if you dropped your spoon
take mine
Here
[Melodramatic and sad music tunes play in the background]
If you drop it again, you can take mine
You can also have mine
Daisy
if you want to try to be Day
go ahead and do it
We’ll be right here to support you
- Jao
- Hm?
You know him better than that
Daisy is a transgender woman. She doesn’t catch a cold
She doesn’t need to be cured. Taking painkillers like paracetamol is not needed
If
you wanna try a new look or new style
I have no problem with it
But this…
Even someone like Toh can tell you’re lying through your teeth right now
- Som
- It’s true, isn’t it?
So
it’s time to tell us what’s happened to you
this is unbearable
[Melodramatic and sad music tunes continue]
Er…
- If you’re not telling us, I’ll call Touch right now
- Don’t
- Toh
I get it! Actually…
the day I went to have noodles with Touch. I overheard the conversation he had with his friend(s)
His friend(s) said I was girly
I’m afraid Touch will be…
embarrassed…So, I try to change myself like this
Why must you be ashamed?
Daisy, you’re ashamed of yourself because Touch’s friend(s) said those things?
Hey
So what if you’re girly?
Touch likes you for who you are, doesn’t he? That’s why he’s going after you, right?
Why bother listening to what other people say?
[Melodramatic and sad musical build-up continues]
Daisy
If you want to be Day or Daisy
it doesn’t matter
All of us, Jao, Toh, and Som, are always by your side
Everything will be okay
You’ll always have me
Thanks so much, you all
Daisy, listen to me
I’m saying this out of concern, not anger
I don’t want to see you not acting like yourself like this
Me too
But if you really think you want to change yourself
I’m ready to give you the support you need
But you have to promise me one thing
don’t force yourself [to be someone else or to do what you don’t want to]
Can you give me that?
That’s the only thing I ask for
Mm
Um
[“You’re the Magic in My Life” melody plays]
You’ve promised. Don’t push yourself too hard
Don’t force yourself
I’m so exhausted
Daisy
If you’re exhausted, tell us
We’re with you. Doesn’t matter which versions of you that you choose to be
Urgh! Stop being so melodramatic already. Look at my face! All messed up
Urgh! Enough!
I’m done. Let’s eat
Yeah
- Let’s eat
- Hurry. I’m hungry
Eat up
Argh! Check this out
[Caption: Ugly & The Pig]
(t/n Playing with the movie title: “Beauty & The Beast”)
- What is it?
- Hey
Let me see
Shit! So many people have commented
- Is it good?
- Very
Nuea, look at this
What?
What are you gonna do?
I think this is harsh
Just ignore it
But that’s your lover!
True. Aren’t you gonna do something?
[Jao’s phone vibrating]
Hmph
- Sky is calling
- Pick up the call, then
- I don’t wanna
- Hey, pick it up for him
- No
It’s connected
That face means you’ve seen the post, right?
I have
But I think you look adorable in every photo
Sky, you silly. Why are you joking around like this
[Dramatic musical stings]
[Comments]
- Disgusting
- What even are they?
- They’re bloated
Sky
Well…
Has Nuea seen this?
Yeah, he has. He’s sitting right here
You don’t have to worry about it, Jao. If it bothers you, I’ll take care of it
Thank you
Bye bye
Goodbye
- Hey
- Hm?
Does Sky know about this already?
Yes, he does
Oh? What about Nuea, then? Is he furious?
As far as I can tell, he’s not
He seems pretty calm
What the hell?
[Comments]
- He doesn’t deserve to be with the star of the faculty
- With a face like this?
- What the heck?
Urgh, Toh! Would you just stop reading the comments!?
They are all horrible. Why did you even bother reading them?
Well…
I read so I know about them. I have to get used to it as well, right?
- Get used to what?
- Right
Well…as long as I’m with Nuea and look like this
nobody can accept me [as Nuea’s lover], right?
I’ve been thinking
it’s quite normal they loathe me. It’d be weirder if they don’t
What the fuck is wrong with you all!?!
Secret Crush On You, The Series
- Too much!
- We’ve seen much worse before
- This is the one that goes out with Sky
- So fat
He was so plump back then. Take a look
I don’t wanna see it
Is your name Kaojao?
- Someone asked me to bring you the flowers
- Hey, wait!
How much was the flower bouquet yesterday?
Wasn’t it you who ordered it?
- Not me
- Not me either
- Heh!?
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
Directed by Thanamin Wongsakulpach