We’re not upset or anything. We only ask for one thing
Please don’t come around us anymore
It’s better that you know now so that I can do what I want to take Nuea
But isn’t this before we’ve started dating, right?
I love you, Nuea
I love you too, Toh
You all must go to Suphanburi with me
I wonder…if it’s a good idea to take Nuea with you
Your father is as fierce as a tiger
Are they all your upperclassmen from the university? Why are there so many of them here!?
Starring
Billy – Patchanon Aounsa-ard as “Nuea Nimman”
Seng – Wichai Saefant as “Toh Thima”
Heng – Asavarid Pinitkanchanapan as “Sky”
Surprise – Pitikorn Siripornsawan as “Kaojao”
Opp – Weerapong Aodherng as “Intouch”
Nut – Witsarut Khakum as “Daisy”
Freen – Sarocha Chankimha as “Khongkwan”
Becky – Rebecca Patricia Armstrong as “Fon”
Dew – Nitikorn Pankram as “Tor”
Looknam – Orntara Poolsak as “Som”
Ging – Areeya Ponfutrakul as “Prao”
Punch – Tipanan Nilsiam
Paper – Peerada Namwong
Anda – Anunta Teavirat
Guest-starring
Saint – Suppapong Udomkaewkanjana as “Thep”
Pete Thongchua
Chanokwanun Rakcheep
Inthira Charoenpura
Siwadol Janthasaewee
Adapted from novel – “Stalker: The Secret Crush” by Darin
Directed by Thanamin Wongsakulpach
Secret Crush On You, The Series
[Intense music plays]
Let’s put everything here
Toh
Seems like your dad is not so fond of me
Shush!
Shushhhh
Aren’t you thinking too much? My dad is only stern on the outside
I’m with you. The way he stared at you
actually gave me chills
Toh
I think your dad surely knows about us
Yes
[Intense music continues]
In fact…I think my mum told him
[Sky slaps his knee loudly]
I knew it
That’s why he glared at you like that
Tough job for you this time, Nuea
Get your spirits up
Well then…
- I should go give mum a hand. Hey, let’s go
- Right right. I’m going
- Som
- Yes?
- Me too, me too
- Come come
Are you coming along?
- Som, wait for me as well
- Hurry up
Jao, where are you going? I’m coming with you
- Daddy
- How are you doing?
[Lively music plays]
- You look more handsome
- So true
- Hey hey. Enough already with your sweet talk
- Whoa…
- Mum, can’t I just tease him a little?
- No can do. He’s mine to keep
- Oh, it looks so yummy and pretty!
- Are you thirsty? I have some fresh coconuts ready for you
- Yes, mum. I’m so thirsty
- Daisy
- Come come. Let’s eat some snacks first
Oh, wait. Let me put a flower behind your ear
The flower makes you look even more gorgeous. I picked them from our front garden
Daddy, I brought this for you
[Groovy music tunes play]
Good good. Make your dad dance with you. The kid of this household is so lively
Oh, let me join as well. I wanna dance, too
Come join us, everyone. Move your body a bit. Quick
- So, you don’t really wanna dance, huh?
- Not really
- Toh, hurry
- Argh, slow down. Dad is gonna lose his image here
You keep insisting you wanna eat. You’d better finish it or I’ll make sure you regret it
Ah, perfect timing. Come on, move your body
[Groovy music continues]
Yeah, keep moving your body
Don’t just sit here and eat. Take them and eat with your friends
- Go now
- Okay
- Move move. Bring them along as well
Kids
I’ve prepared some sweets for you. Come eat quickly
Absolutely. Thank you so much, mother
Let’s have some sweets for appetisers. I’ll prepare today’s dinner main dishes
- Let me know if you have anything you wanna eat. I’ll cook it for you
- Understood
As for this one, it’s our first time meeting each other. I don’t know what you like. Do you have any allergies?
Can you eat spicy food? My dishes are known to be quite spicy
- Er…I can eat spicy food
- Yeah? What about prawn? Are you allergic to prawns?
- Mum, he’s mine
Dear me, can’t I just touch him a little?
Mother, then allow me to be your kitchen hand today
Perhaps I can add some culinary skills with me
Why do you need cooking skills? Everybody here is no longer available. Am I right?
I mean, just look at Toh. It’s beyond my wildest dream that he’s sold. He has zero skills!
Mum, I’m your kid
[Intense music grows louder replacing groovy music]
Of course you are. That’s why I’m happy you have a lover
- Er, mother
- Yes?
Actually, I want to come here to properly introduce myself
to father and mother
Even more so, I’d like to
apologise
to you both for shocking you with the unexpected relationship between me and…
Toh
Erm…
[Toh's father slams the speaker down]
[Awkward silence and intense music continues]
[Nervous laughter among the group]
I’m not, my child. I’m not weak hearted. This is nothing to be surprised about
What era are we in now?
Why should we be stunned or surprised about this [same-sex relationship]? I totally embrace it
Really, I’m not stressed out or anything. You’re overthinking. Don’t assume what I think about this
Toh opened up to me about everything
[Soft cheerful melodies play]
Whoa! Mother, you’re such a cool mum
Besides looking young, your mindset is also modern
Good-looking, smooth talking, and understanding old people. You’re a true sweetheart, huh
Tsk
[Tongue clicking sound]
Oh, he’s clicking his tongue in dissatisfaction
They’re together, mum
You don’t keep your composure at all, hm?
- Mother, are you not gonna tease me too?
- I could do that if you don’t mind
Bro! Why are you saying this!?
[Music stops abruptly]
That’s it. No more drinking for you
[Entertaining music plays]
My dear, Som. Have you got enough coconut water? I have more than plenty. It will calm you down
I will go tease that one
The one stands sulking right there. My old man
Honey, can I touch your cheeks?
- Sulking. He’s sulking
- He’s jealous because I touched your cheeks
- Everyone, raise your glass
- Cheers
Yeah
[Sound of meat sizzling on the BBQ-topped stove]
Your turn now. Let’s go
- Like this? This?
- Yeah
Hurry hurry
[Som, Sky, and Toh are singing and cheering Daisy to dance]
Well…
- I…I’ll get more ice for you
- Huh?
[Soft melodramatic music plays]
[Touch breathes out softly]
I should follow [Daisy]
["Like a Star (My Stellar)" music plays in the background]
Hey, can’t you wait just a minute, Som! What’s with the rush!?
Ahem
[Touch clears his throat]
Oh, Touch. Is there something we want?
Truthfully, I don’t want to back away
But it pains me you’re not being your true self
I’m a trans. Don’t you think it’s weird?
Even if you’re a man and ask me to be your wife
I’m willing to do it for you
So that means I can go back to being my normal self, right?
Like the real bitchy one
Aye!
[Daisy screams in happiness]
Cheers!
[Cheerful music starts to play]
Bottoms up, everyone. Bottoms up
Hey…stop
Daisy is back!
Woohoo!
Let’s go
Music!
My buddy is back [to herself]
Hey, I’m heading to bed now. I’ve exceeded my limit
Out of my way. I’m going
- Hey, I’m coming with you
- Yeah
- Touch
Wait for me
I’ll go check how Som is doing
- Jao! Where ya going!? I’m coming with you. Hurry
- Are you still breathing?
- Easy. Only this can’t bring me down. I can do 10 glasses
- Arghhhh
- Jao, mind your steps. You almost fell
- Oh, they leave in pairs/as couples
Yeah. And we're sitting here as a couple as well
[Toh giggles and talks gibberish]
Oh, they’re all gone. I’m going too
- Hey, you all
- Toh, don’t be so loud
- Nuea
- Toh
Toh
- Lower down your voice
- Hmph
Your parents will wake up
Wake up?
Who’s gonna wake up? Aren’t they all asleep?
And…
How come you’re still awake, Nuea?
It’s because I have to look after my little monkey here
- Come. Get up
- Hmmm, Nuea
- Lower your voice, Toh
- Are you scolding me, Nuea?
- Toh, let’s go to bed
- Argh
- Hm
- Toh
Toh
Today is Friday. Are you not gonna “tutor” me?
[Entertaining music tunes play]
Please please please
We can’t, Toh
Be careful
- Toh
- If you’re not doing it, I’m gonna jump into the water
- Toh. Toh
All right. All right
I’m here. I’m right here
[Soft rousing music tunes play]
[Thrilling and suspenseful music plays]
Bam!
[Wooden doors shut loudly]
Toh!
Ah
Stop yawning
Remove the chilli pedicles. I want the small and red ones. Make sure you remove both the pedicles and calyxes entirely
And, this. The tamarind is too soaky
Separate them and squeeze them for the juice. All the good stuff is in here. Don’t waste it
Here. You can use the spoon to break it apart
Now, what are you doing? Everyone has a task already
I’m fanning and giving you a massage, of course
You’re only squeezing my legs and you call it a massage. This silly kid
Are you good there, everyone at the back?
Do you know how to light up the stove?
- All good, mum. Easy
- Easy, yet, I don’t see any sign of a flame
- Plenty of smoke here
- Okay, that’s a pass
Don’t play with raw food. I’ll turn you into food itself if you don’t eat it
Do it nice and clean
Hey, you. Pay attention
[Brooding music tunes plays]
I think one more should be enough
[Everyone’s chatting in the background]
[Brooding music tunes continues]
Toh
How’s your headache
My head doesn’t really ache
But I feel the pain on my body, Nuea
Did I fall down last night?
Er…last night…
Hmph. The better question should be “how many times did you fall down”
You were so drunk you gave the ghost in the room a headache
- That’s true
- Yeah
Very much
Mum, I’ll go take care of the garden
- Eh!?
- Oh
- Well, let’s continue
- Ah, right
Jao, remove it. Do it nicely
Oops
[Sombre music plays]
(t/n Sine Intira – Toh’s mum here – is best known for her prominent/groundbreaking role as “Nak” or “Mae Nak” from the movie “Nang Nak” (1999) adapted from the best-known Thai urban horror story based on true story)
[Sound of arm muscle stretching as music continues to play]
(t/n Here, they’re playing with one of the most iconic/haunting scenes where “Nak” dropped a lime and stretched out her arm to pick it up from under her house)
Mum!
[All shout in unison in fear]
Get me the lime. I dropped it
Ohhhhhh
[All sigh in relief]
What’s with you? You’re so young
Why do you still watch “Nang Nak”? It’s been over 20 years since the film was released, you know. Enough already
Well, the movie is a real horror
Toh
I’ll be back
Okay
You can take a break. We have to wait for this kid to finish
Mum. Here, it’s melting. Huh?
- Come. Let’s go
- Okay, mum. Let’s go. Jao, come
Ah…
[Soft melodramatic music tunes play]
Father
About last night…
I’m sorry
Why are you apologising?
It’s normal for young people these days when they’re in a relationship
But next time
do it inside the room. Understand?
Yes, sir
[Soft melodramatic music tunes continue]
I’ll be careful next time. I won’t let this happen again
I’ll take good care of Toh so we won’t shame you
Good
Er, father
Now what?
I really love Toh
If you have anything else you don’t like
please let me know anytime
I hate that you’re handsome
[“You’re the Magic in My Life” music starts playing in the background]
Erm, father. I promise you
that I will not flirt around. I will not cheat on Toh
I will only have him
Doesn’t matter if you’re a playboy or not. I don’t care about that
because, at the end of the day, you’ll still be handsome
Er, well…
My turn
- I agree
- Please take care of this situation, mum
- Go for it, mum
Dad, my honey
What more do you want, hm?
You’re scaring the kids off so much
Come on. We’re so old that our hair is turning grey. Why are you still in such a foul mood?
- Isn’t it your fault that I’m like this!?
- Huh?
Here
Nuea, look at my phone wallpaper screen. You can go ahead and look. There’s no passcode or anything
Eh? Mum!
You cropped me out again!
[Comedic tunes play]
Well, you’re not as good-looking as Nuea. Be better looking so I don’t have to crop you out, my dear
See, my screen only has Nuea’s picture
Hmph, mum!
- Why?
- Er…
what’s this about?
Actually…my dad is not upset about you, Nuea
He’s jealous of his wife
since his wife…
is crazy for good-looking men
Toh, what nonsense are you talking about? Who’s jealous? I’m not
Look at this old woman. She grins from ear to ear whenever she sees good-looking people
Oh
She should have been more reserved when her son-in-law pays a visit. She’s ruining the system here
Am I right, Daisy?
Ah, yes dad
I mean
you really are jealous
- You’re right, Daisy
- Absolutely
- I’m jealous
- Yeah
- That’s absurd
- Urgh
Father, I actually heard Sky said earlier that you’re so good-looking
Whoa
Hey, this one knows how to talk
Then, I’ll let this one sleep inside the house. Let the rest sleep outside
- Heh!?
- Don’t you dare. You old man
Let the good-looking ones sleep inside the house. We can sleep outside
Who was the one that complimented him? You can accompany him and sleep outside. Toh, you come as well. Let’s all sleep outside
Such an annoying bunch
Secret Crush On You, The Series
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Timing @breathejsmile @SaintChannel
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7
- Jao
- Hm?
Are you free this Saturday?
Is there something you want, Sky?
Let’s meet my mother
What?
Secret Crush On You, The Series
Colla-AC, 1 tablet a day to reduce facial and body acne
["SCOY" Ost. plays]
Shall we play a game and see which team can get the coconuts first?
The losing team mustttt
pay for the meal
Woohoo
We’re good. This is easy peasy
- Argh
- Wanna do it?
- You wanna start right away?
- On the count of 3… 1, 2, 3. Start!
- Let’s roll
- Hey, shall we put this down?
- What do we do?
- Hey, hurry up
[Incomprehensible ongoing shouts]
Yay!!!!
- Got it. Got it!
- Toh
(t/n This scene refers to the iconic “coconut-grating” scene from the well-known Thai erotic & drama novel, and later film and series, titled “Mae Bia”)
[Romantic music plays]
Um!
What kind of crazy person would bring 2 hats with him?
Your crazy lover
Since I’m your lover, I should always be mindful, right?
Yes
- Thank you so much
- My pleasure
What are you doing?
I’m grating the coconut
Umm
So…what do you think about this place, Nuea?
Pretty or not?
Yes, pretty
What are you smiling about, Toh?
[Comedic music tunes play]
Well... you said... pretty
Right?
I’m talking about the banana trees
Oh…hahahaha…banana trees
Didn’t you tell my parents you wouldn’t play around?
Hmph!?!
Hey!
- Hm!?
- Toh!
Toh…
I’m sorry
I didn’t know you’d be jealous even of the banana trees
I don’t discriminate. I’m jealous of everything
- No exception
- Ouch ouch ouch. Easy, Toh!
Calm down. Put it down first
You’re pretty. You’re the prettiest
Put it down, okay?
All right
Toh
I really want our parents to meet
[“Like a Star (My Stellar)” music plays in the background]
Let me know when your parents plan to go to Bangkok
Of course
But…
before that
Hm?
Can I take a photo of you as a keepsake first?
Please. This way
Come here
It won’t be a keepsake if you take only a photo of me. Both of us should be in it
Huh!?!
[Shutter sounds]
Hey, you didn’t even count. Do it one more time
- Not like this
- Check it out
Geez. Let’s do it again. I’ll do the setting myself
Hey, not yet. Ah, count first. Hmph!
Toh
[“SCOY” music plays in the background]
- Yes?
- Let’s hurry up. Mother and father are calling us
- Yeah, come quickly
- Quick quick
Okay, let’s go
- Yes. Yes. Let's go
- Go go
- Hurry and go
- Faster
- Come on
- Argh!
- Careful!
Hurry up
🎵 No matter what you do 🎵
🎵 No matter what you think, and no matter who you’re with 🎵
🎵 I keep my eyes on you 🎵
🎵 Every little thing about you 🎵
🎵 Be it good or bad 🎵
🎵 I also know it all in secret 🎵
🎵 I’m right here (been watching you all this time) 🎵
🎵 Where I belong 🎵
🎵 I dare not meddle with you 🎵
🎵 Just by doing so (been watching you always) 🎵
🎵 Makes me feel so blissful 🎵
Let me do it for you
🎵 Please, this is the only thing I ask for 🎵
Sure
🎵 I can’t let you know that I secretly watch you every day 🎵
🎵 Things might get out of hands if you notice it 🎵
🎵 There’s someone who’s been watching you 🎵
🎵 It’s me right around the corner 🎵
🎵 Being “secretly” in love with you 🎵
🎵 Secret crush on you 🎵
[Sighs]
You’re all grown-ups
Would you like to stay longer?
- Ah…
- Now you’re asking them to stay?
- A day or two longer maybe?
- Come come. Sit down
- Surely, I’ll be lonely when you leave
Father, Mother. We’ll have to excuse ourselves and return to Bangkok
Right. Before you leave, we’ve talked and agreed that
we’d like to do the handfasting for all of you
- Yes
- Take this as our blessings to you, okay?
(t/n In brief: “handfasting” ceremony is a traditional ceremony held to console and bless a person by having adults binding their wrist with a holy thread)
Bring out your arm, Nuea
Have a safe trip, my child
Please take care of him for me
He’s still very much a kid. Should there be any issues, please talk them through
- All right?
- Yes
Toh
- You keep fidgeting. You just don’t know how to stay still
Don’t be self-conceited. Take care of Nuea as well
As lovers, you should always talk things through calmly
Use less emotions. Use more reasons
- All right?
- Yes
I wish you both happiness
- Thank you so much
- Always
Come here now
Nuea
I know that you’re serious about this
But there’s a whole lot more in life
So, do not rush into tying down everything right now
The string that makes us suffer the most is the one we attach to ourselves
["You're the Magic in My Life" music plays]
The tighter you tie the knot, the more uncomfortable you’ll feel
When you feel uncomfortable, you will want to escape from it
Let the love relationship develops by itself
No need to promise or put pressure on anything
Just make sure you’re happy when you’re together
You understand what I’m trying to say?
Yes, I do
Toh knows who come with good intentions and who are the bad ones
Hmmmm
If he chooses you, it means you’re a good person
That’s why I trust you both
All right?
Whoaaaa
Thank you so much
- He’s in your care now
- Yes
Take good care of him
Go pay respect to your dad
I’m worried about this one, really
Come here. What about the other couples?
- I'm here
- Mum, I want to do it
Sure. Come here. Come here
Excuse us
Right, I’m not touching your cheeks now. I’m binding your wrist instead
Take care of each other. Learn to forgive and forget
Try not to make faces at other people when you’re not happy with them
Try not to overthink
Don’t play around too much or people will misunderstand you. That will bring unnecessary troubles, you understand?
- All right. Gather here
- Okay, next
Make sure you bring this one next time. I don’t want to remember new names anymore
- Go easy on me
- Right. I’ll go easy on you
Come come come
- The colour of your shirt is so pale
- Oh, seriously?
- Yeah, I think so
- Too pale, right?
- A little maybe. Come here
How much coconut water will these 2 need?
- Go easy with her, okay? She’s a headstrong one
- Understood
Talk calmly and be as cool as ice when you talk
- Be as cool as the coconut water you had the day before
- Oh. Haha
So you don’t snap so easily
Please tell mum to go easy on me
Go easy on them
Right. Come here
Don’t be a hot-tempered woman. Don’t make scary faces. You’re scaring your man
- If there’s anything that upsets you, sort it out between yourselves calmly
- Yes
Come on
- There there
- Thank you
- Good luck. Good luck, kids
- Best of luck to all of you. Good luck
Ah, let me give you a hug first
Oh, there there
Come here, my child
- Let’s hug
Jao, I’ll put your stuff away for you
Okay
There. Done
- Jao, wait up
- Hurry
- Come here
Huff. Okay
Was that everything?
- There’s one more
- Hand it to me, Jao
- Som, do you need a hand?
- No, it’s fine
Sky
Hm?
What is it, Jao?
Did you see them, Sky?
See what?
Toh and Nuea, of course
It’s so nice
that Nuea is accepted by Toh’s parents, isn’t it?
Were you cheering for them on the side?
No, I wasn’t
I’m just…happy
that Toh’s family now welcomes Nuea
- Jao
- Hm?
Are you free this Saturday?
Saturday…
Um! Yes, I am. What is it, Sky?
Let’s go meet my mum
Huh!?
Jao
Hey, let’s go
Quick
- Right
- Come quick
- Jao, hurry
- Hurry up
- Right, hurry
- Come. Let’s hurry back to Bangkok so we can see my mum
- Get in
- Sky!
- Hurry
- Come on now
- Get in
Sky
Hm?
Where are you taking me?
I’m taking you to all the places where my memories lie
I used to play hide and seek with my friends here when I was young. I still remember
[Sky, the handsome]
You’ve remained the same all this time, Sky
- Sky, the handsome
What handsome
Tell me where I’m not handsome, hm?
Just you wait. Just you wait
What’s up? You’ve finally come, huh
Yeah. This is my lover, Kaojao
These are my friends since elementary school – Attaphon and Wichean
Hey, that’s my dad’s name. You shithead
Hello
My name is Win. And this is Pol. We’ve been friends with Sky since elementary school
Then, he moved to a different school for secondary school. He followed a girl there
I moved because the basketball team was popular, damn it
Jao, you must be careful. Don’t trust his words too much
He’s been a player since he was young and tiny
Ouch!
Are you a player?
But but but but…ever since he has a lover, he hardly comes out these days when we ask him to come drink with us
Why are you smiling?
Don’t let me catch you
Catch me on what?
Being a player!
Anyway…whenever you want to hang out or have a meal
you can take Sky with you. I’m not stopping him
You give me the permission
- but I no longer want to go
- Eh?
I want to be with my lover more
Oohhhh. Lover, he says
- Sky
- Hm?
Sky
Erm…what’s the plan for today?
Shsh
Don’t ask just yet. Just hop in first. We have quite a few places to go today
Hey, I gotta head out first
Yeah, go ahead
I have big surprises
for my wifey tonight
- Oh
- Whoa
Really?
- I think it is
- Yeah
- See ya
- Yeah, sure
- Yeah yeah
Please don’t listen to him. I’m not a wifey
- I’m really not
- Come quick
Erm
[Uplifting music tunes play]
- Sky
- Hm?
Where else are you taking me?
You’ll know soon enough
Right there, Jao. That’s the restaurant I told you I loved to go when I was young
- That, too!
- Sky, come here quick
- Whoops!
- Jao!
Come on, Jao
- What are you doing!?
- Whoa
Whoa whoa whoa
[Sky laughs]
Jao!
- There
- Ah
Are you tired?
Um
- Come this way
- Oh
1, 2, 3
Smile!
One more, one more. Pucker up
1…2
Hey, you all
- Wassup
- Hello
- Hi hi
- Hello. Hello
- Jao, come sit down
You look cute today
Hello
Have you eaten yet?
Oh, I already have
You can have some more
Arghhhh
Isn’t that too much, buddy?
I’m eating Kao(Jao), yeah?
(t/n “Kao” (n.) means “rice, meal, or food” in Thai)
Ayeeee
- Hello hello hello
- Hello
- Hi there
Hi
Surprise!!!!
- Yay!
- Woohoo!
Why are you all here?
Of course, we have to be here. That’s because…
3 equals to 4
Wherever 3 goes, all 4 tag along!
Ouch
Sky, have you told Jao about Tew yet?
Khongkwan!
Who is Tew?
The one that sent you flowers, of course
But, don’t worry about it. My friend has already taken care of him. He won’t appear ever again
- Ohhhh
- Good job
- Well done
Why did you have to do that?
Sky
I don’t want anyone to pursue you
- Urghhhh
- Whoa
He sure knows how to talk
Right, Sky, have we been to all the places for today?
Not yet. There’s one more place we have to go
🎵 You’re the magic in my life 🎵
Sky!
What is it?
🎵 You’re the magic in my life 🎵
🎵 You’re the one that makes my heart 🎵
Wow…so beautiful
🎵 feel love since the day you walked in 🎵
What is this place?
🎵 You’re the one that changed my life 🎵
This is my house
🎵 You make me realise 🎵
Your house?
🎵 when I wake up the following day, I will spend all my time for you 🎵
Why are you bringing me here?
No need to be nervous, Jao
I already told my mum I’d bring her in-law to visit
🎵 I don't dare to keep dreaming like this 🎵
🎵 because in reality you are too high up for this person right here to reach 🎵
🎵 But you are my destiny 🎵
🎵 I will treasure the moments I share with you in my heart forever🎵
🎵 You’re the magic in my life 🎵
🎵 You’re the one that makes my heart 🎵
🎵 feel love since the day you walked in 🎵
🎵 You’re the one that changed my life 🎵
🎵 You make me realise 🎵
🎵 when I wake up the following day, I will spend all my time for you 🎵
Ouch
🎵 to have today is like a dream come true 🎵
Does it hurt?
🎵 You’re the magic in my life 🎵
No
Thanks so much
🎵 You’re the one that makes my heart 🎵
🎵 feel love since the day you walked in 🎵
Let’s go together, shall we?
🎵 You’re the one that changed my life 🎵
Yeah
🎵 You make me realise 🎵
I’m more than ready
🎵 when I wake up the following day, I will spend all my time for you 🎵
🎵 You’re the magic in my life 🎵
Shall we?
🎵 You’re the one that makes my heart 🎵
🎵 feel love since the day you walked in 🎵
Yeah
🎵 You’re the one that changed my life 🎵
🎵 You make me realise 🎵
🎵 when I wake up the following day, I will spend all my time for you 🎵
Secret Crush On You, The Series
But…
there’s another place I’d like to go
Where is it?
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Timing @breathejsmile @SaintChannel
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7
Secret Crush On You, The Series
🎵 I thank you for staying right here every single day 🎵
- Nuea
- Yeah?
I’m sure Jao must be passing out right now
because it’s the very first time Sky takes him to his house
You know, Toh
Yes?
Nobody can be as shocked as I was when I met your dad
Really? Anyhow, I really appreciate that you said yes to go everywhere I want to
Yeah
But, there’s another place I really want to go
Where is it, Toh?
You need to promise me first that you’ll take me there
Of course
I promise you. I will take you to wherever you want to go
- But before that
- Yes?
I need a reward
[Toh smooches Nuea’s cheek]
Here, an extra bonus
- I’ll take you there
- Yup
[Lively music tunes play]
- Wow, the sound of waves is so refreshing
- Agree
Toh
You sure know what you’re doing, huh
You literally book the same resort we stayed
and even the same room
That’s some skill you have
- Oh
- Hey
- Nuea
- Come on
["SCOY" Ost. plays]
- Oops
- Dear me
Hey, let’s play beach volleyball
🎵 No matter what you do 🎵
- Come on
- Sure
🎵 No matter what you do 🎵
- Come on
- Sure
🎵 No matter what you think, and no matter who you’re with 🎵
- We’re on the same team, right?
- Sure
🎵 No matter what you think, and no matter who you’re with 🎵
- We’re on the same team, right?
- Sure
🎵 I keep my eyes on you 🎵
🎵 Every little thing about you 🎵
🎵 Be it good or bad 🎵
🎵 I also know it all in secret 🎵
🎵 I’m right here (been watching you all this time) 🎵
🎵 Where I belong 🎵
🎵 I dare not meddle with you 🎵
🎵 Just by doing so (been watching you always) 🎵
🎵 Makes me feel so blissful 🎵
🎵 Please, this is the only thing I ask for 🎵
🎵 I can’t let you know that I secretly watch you every day 🎵
🎵 Things might get out of hands if you notice it 🎵
🎵 There’s someone who’s been watching you 🎵
🎵 It’s me right around the corner 🎵
🎵 Being “secretly” in love with you 🎵
🎵 Secret crush on you 🎵
Now what?
You ask me to watch the stars with you, but how come you’re only looking at my face
I’m good-looking, right?
Do you have something in mind, Jao?
I’m thinking
[“Like a Star (My Stellar)” plays]
🎵 I pointed my eyes towards the wide and empty night sky 🎵
I don’t need to look up to see the stars anymore
because my only star is right here in front of me
🎵 Still, there is a star shining radiantly as always 🎵
🎵 Like you 🎵
🎵 You are the beauty in my eyes 🎵
🎵 You make me realise what I have been searching for all my life 🎵
Oh, right. Just a minute
Here
Unwrap it
Jao
Thank you so much
for always being so patient with me
Also…
I’m sorry that I tend to think too much at times, and that I may annoy and bore you of
You’re never boring for me. And you’re never annoying to me
- You have been thinking about this, all right?
- Yeah
I love you, Jao
I love you too, Sky
Love you
Let’s watch our stars, okay?
Yeah
- Let’s go
Hmmm, one couple is down
Oops
Woah
Kiss. Just kiss on the cheek already
- Oh
- Ooh
Khongkwan, you’re joining them as well?
[Sounds of laughter]
And…what about the two of us?
Urgh, don’t make me rant, Tor
There. Look at that
Look over there
Um
Can you recognize the stars you have taken photos of?
Of course, I do
It’s the North (Nuea) Star
(t/n As said from the beginning of the series, the word “Nuea” in Thai means “north”)
Nuea
do you know that the North Star is so cool?
How so?
Well
It leads people the way
When we’re lost or have no idea which direction we should take
what we need to do is simply look up
It will lead us home
And do you know
that the North Star
is also loyal
because it always waits for us
to look back at it [when we need it]
[“You're the Magic in My Life” plays]
🎵 You’re the one that changed my life 🎵
Nuea
Yes?
What makes you like me?
Must there be a reason?
You’re strangely unique, I think
Hmph
Well
Normally
when we like someone
we would want to be as close to them as possible, right?
But that wasn’t the case for you
You always looked at me from afar
Ironically
it was me
who ended up searching high and low for you
If there was a day
that I didn’t see Van Gogh
I would feel
so empty like something is missing
Right now especially
I must have you with me all the time
Nuea
do you know
how lucky I feel
that you love me
The lucky one
is me
Without you in my life
I wouldn’t have known
what real happiness feels like
Thank you
Ooh my. Hey, you all
- I dare you to slap me on my face if this one doesn’t feel sensational
- Hmph
🎵 No matter what you do 🎵
🎵 No matter what you think, and no matter who you’re with 🎵
🎵 I keep my eyes on you 🎵
🎵 Every little thing about you 🎵
🎵 Be it good or bad 🎵
🎵 I also know it all in secret 🎵
🎵 I’m right here (been watching you all this time) 🎵
🎵 Where I belong 🎵
🎵 I dare not meddle with you 🎵
Quit peeking already
- Argh!
- Ah
- Oh
Who’s peeking?
We’re here to watch the stars
- Yeah true
- See? They’re beautiful
Come over here
Okay, let’s go
- Let’s go, Tor
- Absolutely
- Come quick
- Jao
- I’m here. I’m here
- Where should we stand?
- Well
- Take the front row
- Come take photos
- Sit here
- You’re blocking me
- Hmph
- Tor
- Excuse me
1, 2, 3
Yay!
🎵 With those eyes looking my way 🎵
🎵 Though I don’t know the meaning behind them 🎵
🎵 They continue to shake my world 🎵
🎵 ST right here! 🎵
🎵 No need to overcomplicate things 🎵
🎵 I’m not thinking too much. I'm just following my heart 🎵
🎵 That’s more than enough. It’s quite okay for me 🎵
🎵 Secret crush on you. This is the way I am 🎵
🎵 Umm you just continue being you 🎵
🎵 Yeah. And I’ll always look at you from the distance 🎵
🎵 Please, this is the only thing I ask for 🎵
🎵 Come on, Come on, Let’s go 🎵
🎵 I can’t let you know that I secretly watch you every day 🎵
🎵 Things might get out of hands if you notice it 🎵
🎵 There’s someone who’s been watching you 🎵
Secret Crush On You, The Series
🎵 It’s me right around the corner 🎵
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
🎵 It’s me right around the corner 🎵
You said there’s a surprise for me
What is it exactly?
Hm?
Are you ready?
I am
Secret Crush On You, The Series
[Text on doorknob hanger: “Here on Samed Island, we don’t leave till we finish. Please Do Not Disturb”]
1 tablet of Colla-AC as advised by the doctor
Clear skin, no skin breakouts. Nuea will be head over heels for me
[Toh breathes in and out as a sign of preparation]
[Soft rousing music plays]
Toh
What are you doing?
May I do it?
I want to give it a try
And what do you mean by that?
Please
Of course
[Rousing music plays]
Toh, keep your eyes closed
Yes!
You said there’s a surprise for me. What is it exactly? Hm?
[Nuea laughs softly]
Stand right here
Keep your eyes closed
Yes, they’re closed
Toh
Yes?
Before you open your eyes
there’s something I’d like to tell you
I have always felt
happy and assured
every time
that you are by my side
So, here is everything
an ordinary man can do
for a person named Toh
Are you ready?
I am
🎵 Is this real or am I just dreaming? 🎵
🎵 The one standing right next to me is you…the one [I’ve longed for] 🎵
🎵 We’ve been side by side through the thick and thin 🎵
🎵 And you choose me as your one and only. Please tell me this is real 🎵
🎵 I’m not as good as anybody else, but you didn’t look past me 🎵
🎵 You hold me close to your heart and prioritise me whenever I need you 🎵
🎵 You are the one who always stands right beside me even when nobody does 🎵
Nuea
🎵 I thank you for staying right here every single day 🎵
From now on
🎵 It’s like a dream 🎵
neither of us has a secret crush
🎵 that I dare not to wish it come true 🎵
🎵 Everything that happens 🎵
because right now
🎵 Every warmth. Every embrace 🎵
🎵 How you say you love me dearly with all your heart 🎵
our feelings are mutual
🎵 it matters not what kind of person I am 🎵
🎵 You always stand by my side 🎵
I don’t know what to say
I feel like the luckiest person in the world
It’s beyond my wildest dream
to think that
a person like me who only had secret crushes
🎵 I’m not as good as anybody else, but you didn’t look past me 🎵
could be with the person I fell in love with
🎵 You hold me close to your heart and prioritise me whenever I need you 🎵
🎵 You are the one who always stands right beside me even when nobody does 🎵
🎵 I thank you for staying right here every single day 🎵
It’s only natural for people who have secret crushes, right?
🎵 It’s like a dream 🎵
Nuea
🎵 that I never imagine it could happen in reality 🎵
Don’t tease me
🎵 Everything that happens right now 🎵
🎵 Every warmth. Every embrace 🎵
🎵 How you say you love me dearly with all your heart 🎵
🎵 it matters not what kind of person I am 🎵
🎵 You always stand by my side 🎵
There there
Don’t cry
It’s your fault. You make me cry
Secret Crush On You, The Series
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Timing @breathejsmile @SaintChannel
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7
Directed by Thanamin Wongsakulpach