This is Year 2022. Stop calling me uncle and start calling me dad already!
- Call me mum, okay? Say it
- Yes, mum
Let’s take pictures together
- I went to Nuea parents’ anniversary yesterday
- Aha
And…I took pictures together with his family
Your hubby’s dad is soooo cool
Argh! Check this out
- What is it?
- Hey
- Let me see
Shit! So many people have commented
Nuea, look at this
Starring
Billy – Patchanon Aounsa-ard as “Nuea Nimman”
Seng – Wichai Saefant as “Toh Thima”
Heng – Asavarid Pinitkanchanapan as “Sky”
Surprise – Pitikorn Siripornsawan as “Kaojao”
Opp – Weerapong Aodherng as “Intouch”
Nut – Witsarut Khakum as “Daisy”
Freen – Sarocha Chankimha as “Khongkwan”
Becky – Rebecca Patricia Armstrong as “Fon”
Dew – Nitikorn Pankram as “Tor”
Looknam – Orntara Poolsak as “Som”
Ging – Areeya Ponfutrakul as “Prao”
Punch – Tipanan Nilsiam
Paper – Peerada Namwong
Anda – Anunta Teavirat
Guest-starring
Saint – Suppapong Udomkaewkanjana as “Thep”
Pete Thongchua
Chanokwanun Rakcheep
Inthira Charoenpura
Siwadol Janthasaewee
Adapted from novel – “Stalker: The Secret Crush” by Darin
Directed by Thanamin Wongsakulpach
Secret Crush On You, The Series
- Urgh. I’m starving
- Let’s eat, then
- What should we eat today?
Why are they giving us weird looks?
[Intense music plays]
Toh, let’s go
What the hell
Ah, hey Som!
Hey, give me back my phone
Can’t I just borrow it?
Yikes, so lame. Look
(t/n Som talks about the posts on IG where the account posted photos of Nuea with people he dated in the past)
Look at this
What? Let me have a look
Yuck. That’s too much
Let me see it!
Make sure you have everything deleted, Som
[Intense music continues]
Um
Hey, you 2, delete everything
Umm
Everyone who’s standing right here and walking past as well
Delete them all, you hear me!
Um
Let’s go
Yeah, delete them all
If I find out you haven’t deleted them
- I’ll certainly pull a punch or two on you
- Right
Make sure you delete them. Did you do it already!?
[Emotional music tunes play]
Toh
Toh, are you feeling okay?
Um, I’m okay
I’ve seen worse
- True. Let’s talk about it when there’s a video clip perhaps
- Som
- There’s no clip!
- My bad!
Are you not going to do anything about this, Toh?
If I find out who the culprits are, I’ll beat them up
- Are you gonna punch all those antis?
- Yeah. I’ll whack them all
Hmph, very manly, my dude Day
[Text from Nuea: I’m at the basketball court already]
- Let’s go
- Mm. Let’s go
[Uplifting music plays]
Toh
Come sit on the bench
let’s have a meal together after the match today
Sure. I’ll wait upstairs then
No. Don’t go. Sit right here, all right?
- Huh?
- Let’s eat together afterward, okay?
[Entertaining music plays]
Of course
- Ah, sorry we’re late, Toh
- We’re here
- Sorry sorry
Sorry we’re late. Are you all right?
- There you are
- Oh!
Sky
[Romantic music tunes play]
Um!
Are you here to give me support?
Erm…Nosey!
How’re things today? Better?
Um!
Argh. Don’t believe him, Sky. Those antis haven’t stopped at all
- Is that true, Daisy?
- Yes
No. It’s really all right. I don’t think too much of it
No, it’s not okay, Jao
I’m really worried about you.
Do you understand? Hm?
Mm!
My good kid. Give me a big cheer, okay?
- Hey, Sky!
- Huh?
- Warm up practice!
Got it! I’ll go first then. I’ll be back later
- Focus on the match and play well
- Got it
Hey
[Playful music tunes play]
I’m so confused. The player dropped by to send his encouragement to the spectator. So confusing…
Oh
Hi. Hello
[Crowd cheering]
Woah! Woah!
Yay...
[Crowd cheering]
Toh
- Wipe my sweat for me
- Huh?
Quick
Nuea
Quickly
Yes
My hair as well
Hey, stop taking your sweet moment, Nuea
Well, he’s my lover
Woohoo!
Quickly
[Romantic music tunes play]
It’s all dry now
You have to do this for me only. Understand?
Understood
[Phone cameras clicking sounds]
Are you not gonna say something, Toh?
Come on. Say something
[Phone cameras clicking sounds]
Ah! Give it your all, Nuea
Understood
- Damn…Toh, are you dead yet?
- Yeah
[Playful music tunes play]
- Hey
- Huh?
- Let me check the feedback [on IG] a little
- Right. Do it quick
Let me see
[Photo caption: “His real one is here”]
(t/n All the comments appear are positive ones saying how sweet of a couple NueaToh is)
- Ooh! Not bad
- Hey, not bad at all
- Yeah. Look look
(t/n All the comments appear are positive ones saying how sweet of a couple NueaToh is)
- Let’s check some more
- Check the comments
You’re going too far today, Nuea
What did I do?
Don’t you play pretend. I can tell what you’re trying to do here
[Romantic music tunes play]
Do you like it, then?
I do
It’s good that you do
I love you, Toh
I love you too, Nuea
Would you like to shower together with me?
Nuea! You’re crazy
- Then, I’ll go take a shower
- Yes
Nuea, your towel!
You can keep it. I have a few of them
Okay
Secret Crush On You, The Series
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
- This is the one that goes out with Sky
- For real? The one whose photos were circulated?
So fat
He was so plump back then. Check it out
I don’t wanna see it
Secret Crush On You, The Series
Colla-AC, 1 tablet a day to reduce facial and body acne
Shit!
What is it, Som?
It’s nothing. I’m good. Nothing happened
[Intense music plays]
Do you not realise how pitchy your voice is?
Give it to me
[Caption: So fat he’s bursting at the seams]
Huh!?
Oh
[Caption: So fat he’s bursting at the seams]
Hand it over
Toh!
Toh
Can I see it?
- Hm?
- Can I see it as well?
Jao, I don’t think you need to see this. It’s…it’s absolutely nonsense
- Yeah
- Right?
I wanna see it
Let me have a look
No
Please
[Intense rhythm plays]
Hey
I think this is far off the limit
Let’s report it
Aha
Give it to me
- I’ll report them all. Just you wait
- Yeah
I have 5 shadow accounts
I have 6
- Good
- Let’s do it
Hey, I’ve reported them all
Oh, wait. You’ll have to go meet Sky soon, right?
Jao
Do you want me to go with you?
That’s right. Let Toh tag along with you
- Right?
- Yeah, true
It’s all right
I can go there by myself
Jao, hi!
- Fon, hi
- Hello
Are you here for Sky?
He’s at the copy centre
Thank you
Then, I’ll go…
Oh
- Hello, Touch
- Hello there
Are you here to see Sky?
- Yes
- Hey. This is the one that goes out with Sky
- For real? The one whose photos were circulated?
- The one that has become the talk of the town
- Such an obese
- So fat
Jao
Are you all right?
Everyone has a belly
See, I have one
Touch also has it. Look
Yeah
Thank you so much
Then…I’ll look for Sky now
- Goodbye
- Yeah. Goodbye
Right. Have you seen Jao’s pic? The one that account posted this morning
Yeah. I saw it
It’s so mean. I think this is way too much
But…he was so plump back then. So cute I wish I could tease him
Take a look. Have a look if you don’t believe me
Enough already. Stop forcing me to look at it
Heh? How come!?
I don’t wanna see it
Hey
Be nice even if you don’t wanna look at it
Sky! Wait up!
Jao
I understand why you walked away
However
shouldn’t you have finished listening to their conversation first?
I agree with him
To be frank, things might not be what they appear to be
Correct
I don’t quite understand why
but
my feet moved on their own
Jao
But you’re not as chubby as you were before
But, does this mean Sky will no longer like me
if I become as fat as I used to be?
Jao
Easy
Don’t jump to a conclusion by yourself
It won’t do you any good
by overthinking things
How about you go to Sky and ask him directly
If he really does say he doesn’t like how you used to look
you can come back and consider if you wanna break up with him or look after yourself, so you won’t return to your old weight
True
I agree
This is the one that goes out with Sky
- For real?
- Yeah
- The one whose photos were circulated?
- The one that becomes the talk of the town
- Such an obese
- So fat
He was so plump back then. So cute I wish I could tease him. Have a look if you don’t believe me
- Enough already. Stop forcing me to look at it
- Heh? How come!?
I don’t wanna see it
Jao
Hm?
What’s wrong? Are you stressed out?
No
How can you still say no?
You can tell your friends anything
You don’t have to keep it to yourself
Um
You always have me beside you whenever you’re scared
And if you feel like you’re overwhelmed, I’m here to listen to your worries
Toh
Hm?
Thank you
Thank you so much
Don’t mention it!
What about you?
Are you all right?
You’re dealing with a lot of criticisms as well
I’m totally fine
because I have a special spell
Special spell?
Aha!
Do you want to know what it is?
Yeah
It’s such a simple way of thinking actually
Nobody can escape being gossiped about
We are no exceptions
Who knows
the people who are gossiping about us right now might be the same people whom we gossiped about in the past
So, I say this to myself… “We’re even”
Simple as that, Jao
Erm...
We’re even now
Like this?
Yup, exactly
Shall we go?
Yeah
Jao
Jao, are you okay?
You didn’t reply to my message. You didn’t pick up my calls. You didn’t come collect your worksheets
You scared me
Um
I’m okay really
It’s just…
there’s something I need to think about
Sky
Hm?
I want to ask you something
No!
No what?
I’m not breaking up with you
Breaking up?
What did I do wrong, Jao?
Was it because I took so much time photocopying the worksheets?
But there were so many people!
I didn’t know you would be so angry. I’ll take over the machine and do the service myself next time [instead of waiting for the staff]
Give me a chance, please
I’m not breaking up with you
It’s not about that
Oh
What would you like to talk about, then?
This
What do you think...
about this picture?
I think you’re cute
We should have met each other since the freshmen welcoming ceremony
Are you for real?
I overheard it…
your conversation with Khongkwan
You said you don’t want to see this picture
You went to the copy centre?
Yeah
Why didn’t you stay and listen till I finished what I had to say?
Because I heard what you said…
I couldn’t find the courage to stay any longer
It’s true I don’t like this picture
but it’s not because you don’t look cute
Look!
Your clothes are too revealing
I haven’t got a glimpse of [what’s underneath the clothes]
there…and there…
Shouldn’t I be the only one who gets to see…?
That’s absurd
You pervert!
Let me summarise for you
You look so cute in this pic that…
I wanna be in the room with just the 2 of us so I can kiss you on the cheek all day long
Stop!
What do you think you’re doing!?
- Just a little
- No!
Stop! Stopppp
- Mmmmm
- Oh, Sky
Hm, this person looks kind of familiar
Never mind
Can I sit with you?
Secret Crush On You, The Series
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
Promise me, then
You can always be cuter [in appearance], but don’t ever let your heart waver
Is your name Kaojao? Someone asked me to deliver these flowers to you
For me?
Hey!
Secret Crush On You, The Series
Stop!
What do you think you’re doing!?
- Giving you a kiss on the cheek, of course
- Hmph!
- Just a peck
- No!
Stop!
Oh! Sky
Hmmm
This person looks kind of familiar
Never mind
Can I sit with you?
Er…
up to you, Peach
Thank you
I’ll get my coffee first, then
[Peach’s phone vibrating]
Peach!
[Incoming call from Prao]
[New IG post photo caption: “True love or trying something different”]
Fuck
I think I know now, Jao…
Hm?
Oh
It all finally comes back to me
I know why his face looks familiar
You’re with the campus celebrity, Sky
Celebrity? What do you mean?
Ohhhh
It’s him of course
His pictures are everywhere on IG
especially the one shared this morning
Have you seen it?
I’ll show it to you
No, thanks
I don’t wanna see it
Oh, how come?
Well…
it doesn’t look good indeed
I think it’s funny though
The reason why I don’t wanna see it is…
I’m afraid I’ll look for the owner of this account
and crush the person once I do
[Intense music plays]
Is that so?
But
the person might be a girl, you know
Doesn’t matter who the person identifies themselves as. They have no rights to post pictures of my lover
And they have no rights to post malicious comments and bully others
I agree
I also think such people are bad
Right, Jao?
Um!
I also agree
I think
the people behind this know it’s a bad behaviour
That’s why they hide behind their fake ID
Yeah, it’s true
If they believe they’re doing the right thing
why would they use their shadow account, right?
I think deep down they’re ashamed of themselves
I’m kind of curious now
if I reveal their real account
how they will feel
I should find someone to do that right now
S…Sky! Are you really gonna do that?
Totally
They dare doing this to my lover
I won’t let them off the hook that easily
Erm…
Right. I see
I just remember I have an appointment with my advisor
I should take my leave first
- That was a close call
- Hmph
Ah…Nuea, hello
[Entertaining music tunes play]
Nuea
Do you know what the word “loh-pu” means?
(t/n “Loh-pu” is not a known term in Thai dictionaries. “Loh-pu” is an expression recently coined and better known/used among Thai LGBTQ+ community dubbed “Lu language”)
What does that mean, Toh?
It means…”get busted”
It refers to a person who’s not so slick or not very good at covering up their lies. That’s why they are “loh-pu” (get busted)
I see
I’ll take my leave now
Nuea
I feel a bit weary
Toh
Geez…what the heck
You’re a cheeky one, aren’t you
Hmph
[Uplifting music plays]
Just a little
Jao
Umm
How are you feeling now? Are you still concerned [about what’s happening]?
No, I’m fine now
What about you, Toh?
Are you still thinking about it?
Well
Me?
Not at all
The pictures they posted are the pictures of myself
Besides
I really am ugly
I have to accept it as fact
Toh
But, it doesn’t matter how ugly I look
I get to be Nuea’s lover
And Nuea is head over heels for me
despite me being an ugly duckling
So mischievous
Hee hee
Thank you so much
Sky
My lover is so cheeky
I’ll drop you off at your dorm, okay?
Let’s go
Study hard today, all right?
Yup
[Soft sinister tone tune as someone’s hand reaching out to Toh’s]
Hey
[Sound of fabric rustling as Toh’s hand being held]
Oh…Thep!
[SCOY music plays in the background]
Hey, don’t be so touchy feely
I’m just teasing you a little, Nuea
This one is off the limit. I’m quite protective of him
You too, Toh
Now that you have a lover, you’re showing off, hm?
Well…just a little, Thep
You can be a little less of a show-off maybe, Nuea?
No can do
I’m crazy in love
with this one
Fine. Let’s get into my business then
Seeing you now reminds me of something
Yes?
There’s a freshy in our club
who loves your work
Oh
So, I wonder if you have time
If you do have some spare time, I’d like you to help teach the kid some techniques
I think
you’ll like
the style of his
And, Toh must like his styles of photography as well
The style that I like
[“Oh my love” song starts to play]
🎵 Oh my love 🎵
Please teach me
Please teach me, Toh
🎵 Oh my love 🎵
Come on. Let’s go to class already
[Music interrupted by Thep]
- Yeah. See you later
- Yeah, see you at the faculty building
- Yes
- See you later, Toh
- Goodbye
Hey, look at Jao
He looks so serious
True
Very serious. He wanna score full marks perhaps
Right
So diligent, this one
I still have no idea what kind of photo I wanna take
What about Daisy here?
Not a chance ,The score will be a “zero”
(t/n This can also imply “he’s totally useless” - jokingly)
I don’t wanna be snapped by you either
Hello
[Guest starring: First - Piyangkul Saohin as “Kong”]
My name is Kong. I’m a Comm Arts freshman
I joined the photo club yesterday
because I really like the photos you take, Toh
Shit!
[Comedic tunes play]
Is he Toh’s twin brother!?
How can they look so much alike?
Well
I’m so glad
that you will teach me the techniques
I…like your photos a lot
I’d love to be half as good as you are
Woah
This one knows how to sweet talk
What’s the point of being half as good as I am
I’ll make you a better photographer than I am
Oh
I have some cool mise-en-scènes to show you
(t/n “Mise-en-scène” in photography refers to everything that appears in front of the camera lens and effects the shot taken, from lighting to props)
Let me show them to you next time
I’ll go for sure
But it has to be some other days
since…
I’ve made an appointment with my uncle already
and I’m already running late
the uncle will be mad at me
Could you take me to meet your uncle with you?
I’d love to meet your uncle
Oh
Sure
That’s fine
Then…
Hey
- Huh?
- Hm?
I’m leaving
- Yeah
- All right
Let’s talk some more in the chat group later on
- Yeah yeah. Go already
- Okay
Bye bye
Jao
Ah…you can go ahead. I’ll let him know
Okay
What
One shot. There we go
- Look
- Where?
Ohhh
Now, that’s one pic for Jao’s IG
Yeah…I think he looks quite cute in this angle
Yeah
- I agree. I think he’s so cute
- Aha
Why does he keep thinking he’s not?
Well…I think it’s time to launch a “PBS”
Huh? What’s that?
“A plan to boost self-esteem”
- Urgh…what plan again now dude?
- It’s “Day”, girl
Damn it. When will you stop acting like this!?
Yeah…tell me about the plan later
- I have to go now
- Yeah
- My uncle has been waiting for a long time already. He must have a backache by now
- Go
- Hm
- Bye bye
- Bye
- See ya
Let’s go
Look at them
Even the patches and keychains on their bags look similar
True
Right!
What about the plan you mentioned earlier?
What is it?
Hmmm
Ummm
Marvellous
Jao
My little cutie
Fine. I’ll go
Whose lover is this?
How come you’re so sulky?
[Romantic music tunes play]
Who teases me first here?
You’ve become more and more mischievous recently
Are you still taking photos?
Take one for me
Hurry. Just one
Nosey
I’m not doing it
Just one photo for me. Is it that hard, hmph!?
Give it back
No
Give my phone back
[Romantic music tunes fade]
What’s that, Jao?
Nothing
Can I see it?
[Fantasy music plays]
No way
May I see it please?
Mmmm
Nosey!
Here
Cut down carb intake
Exercise
No desserts allowed
Get enough sleep
Stop reading already
Are you serious about this?
What if you become even cuter and someone snatches you from me
I’ll break down and cry till I die
Hush! Silly
Sky!
Stop exaggerating
It’s just my scribble
Promise me, then
Hm?
You can always be cuter [in appearance]
but don’t ever let your heart waver
Understand?
Mmm
Um
Excuse me
[Intense and suspenseful music plays]
Is your name Kaojao?
Um
Well
Someone asked me to deliver these flowers to you
For me?
Hey!
Sky
Please calm down
Who the hell asked him to give you this!
Giving flowers to someone’s lover. What the hell are they thinking!
I have no idea either
Don’t be upset, Sky
Sky
- Hello, Sky
- Hello
[Message: “Flowers for the lovely one from T.”]
Who the hell is this “T.”!?
[Intense and suspenseful music continues]
I have no idea either
I’ve never met him
And I’ve never heard of the name before
Please don’t be upset
Secret Crush On You, The Series
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
Right…Daisy
Hey, the flower bouquet yesterday
how much was it?
Wasn’t it you who ordered it?
Not me
Wasn’t it you?
Not me either
Heh!?
Secret Crush On You, The Series
[Lively music plays]
Kong, wait here for a second
Sure
[“Oh my love” plays]
Got you
Ah
Hmm, Nuea!
Erm…
How long have you been waiting for me?
Just half an hour
Not that long
But
I’m starving…
Toh
[Music is cut abruptly]
Ah!
This’s Nuea. The one I told you about
Nuea, this is Kong. He’s the one Thep talked about the other day
I thought you were meeting your real uncle
Lover
Yes…that
Hello, Nuea
Aha
Let’s go
Huh? Wait just a minute. How do you go home, Kong?
Where do you live?
My place is in “Yim-gnam” alley near here
(t/n “Yim-gnam” means beautiful smile)
Oh, that happens to be the same way to your condo, Nuea
Then
should we drop him off first?
I’ll let you decide
Then, let’s leave together. We’ll drop you off
- Deal?
- Sure
Come
Nuea! Kong, come on
Let’s go
Argh! Hmph
Arrghhh
[“Like a star (My Stellar)” music plays]
Oh, wow!
Did you start to learn about photography since you were in secondary school?
Yeah
You’re so brilliant
What kind of photos [photography styles] do you like to take?
I like lifestyle photography
I see
Like “You are magic” that won the competition, right?
I like that photo a lot
Eh?
Is the person in the photo Uncle Nuea?
Oops, I mean Nuea
Yes, that’s right
I knew it! That’s why I thought his face looked familiar
I like that photo soooo much
During the showcase exhibition
I went to see that photo every day
I was hoping I could run into you
Oh, I see
Nuea
shall we find something to eat before we go to your condo?
Yeah, that’s a good idea
I’m starving as well
May I tag along?
Erm…
Sure
Then
let’s eat together
Thank you so much, Toh
Erm
- Okay
- Thank you so much. You’re the best
I see
[Lively music plays]
Toh
Huh?
- What’s going on? You seem exhausted
- True
It’s nothing
How about yesterday? What did you do?
Right. Hey, dude
- It’s Day
- Urgh. Fine. Day
The flower bouquet yesterday, how much was it?
Eh? Wasn’t it you who ordered it?
[Dramatic music tunes play]
Not me
Wasn’t it you?
Not me either
Huh?
Then, who ordered it?
That means
someone really sent him flowers
- Yeah
- That’s right
And, it’s not you two
- Na-uh
- Nope
So, this “T.” is a real person
- Um
- Yeah
And, the person is really pursuing Jao
- Right
- Um
Isn’t that good, then? Everything goes exactly like our plan
No no. It’s not good. Whatever you can’t control is never good
Eh? How come?
- Who in the world is it?
- No clue
- But Jao already accepted the flowers
This is not good. It won’t go well
I don’t know what to do now. I have no clue
- Toh
[Dramatic music tunes continues to play in the background]
Oh
Hello, everyone
- Hello there
- Hello
Move aside so they can stand a little closer
Excuse me. Someone asked me to deliver this to you, Jao
[Dramatic and tense music becomes louder]
For me?
It’s so cute, Jao
Sky
Is it cute?
[Sound of the doll’s bell tolling]
Cute?
Hm?
Such a childish gift
Hey, Sky
Didn’t you buy one for my sister on her birthday?
Well, your sister is still a kid
Er…Jao
- Hm?
- I think you should throw that plushie away
You know…in case it’s poisoned, right?
- Yeah, that’s right
- Right
- Throw it away. Throw it away
Som, are you mental? It’s a plushie. How can it be poisoned!
See? It’s so cute
[Bell-tolling sound as Jao continues to shake the doll]
I’m pretty sure
it’s all because of that stupid account
It keeps posting so many photos that someone starts going after my lover
Sky, calm down for a sec
The account was deleted ages ago. Why are you still holding a grudge?
Keep acting nonchalant, Nuea
Let’s see if you can still keep your cool if it’s Toh. I bet you’ll thrash anyone who’s going after him by now
Ooh. You’re so fiesty, Nuea
Som, he’s obviously exaggerating
Toh
Oh!
Hello
Let’s go take photos together
You told me you’d take me earlier
- Well…I…
- Please...
- Er...
- Please show me the place
- Please. I wanna take photos
Nuea
Would you like to come along?
No
[Dramatic and tense music continues]
It’ll be such a waste if we don’t go now
The light is perfect right now
Please
Well...
Ah...erm
Come on…
Okay. Fine
- I’ll text you in a bit
- Shall we go now?
- Let’s go quickly, Toh
- Hey, I’ll see you all later
- Toh
- See you
Bye
Well, then. Please excuse us. We need to go to class now
Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye
Come on, Jao. Let’s go
- Let’s go, Jao
- Come come
- I’m on my way
- Jao, hurry up
Quick
[Melodramatic tunes play]
Bye bye
- Come here now
- Argh
- Ouch ouch ouch! Khongkwan
- Be gentle!
Let’s go
Move your feet
Everything’s fine
Let’s go
Secret Crush On You, The Series
You put so much effort in fact. You even try to appear and act like him
Cuz it’s Nuea’s fucking taste apparently
I’m sure it won’t be long till Nuea can’t stand going out with that jerk Toh
MingErTeamSub
English translation: @procrast_stake
Edit & Proofread: @breathejsmile @procrast_stake
Subbing @ChenniiCharm
Thai Trans @morning_247 @PROMOTE_SAINT @Zorochi7 & Timing @SaintChannel
Directed by Thanamin Wongsakulpach