[Wyatt]
Previously On "Secrets of Sulphur Springs..."
My dad said it was all his fault.
That has to mean
he did something to Savannah.
(song playing on recorder)
[Zoey] Think it's Savannah?
♪ Here at dear Camp Tremont ♪
Your brother is missing,
and you're worried about a ghost?
This is serious!
So is this!
Not all my memories here were happy.
What happened to Savannah
is not something I've ever
talked about with anyone.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
(gasps)
(eerie music playing)
I‐‐ I dared her
to spend the night...
alone in the basement.
[Griffin]
Savannah must have
found the portal.
[Harper] Which means
she could still be alive somewhere in time.
[Harper]
1960?
Big storm's coming.
It's not safe here.
Wait. Someone's inside.
Boy, am I glad to see you.
Listen, we don't have a lot of time.
I really need you to come with us.
It could change everything.
[Griffin]
We need to get back to the hatch now.
Go!
[Harper]
Where is Savannah?She was right behind me.
(Savannah screams)
(hatch slams shut)
(eerie music playing)
(gasps)
Mom, what happened?
[Wyatt] You okay?
I just wasn't looking.
There was something‐‐
You look like you saw...
a ghost.
No.
It was right there...
in the mirror.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go. Now!
No more excuses, Ben.
No more finger pointing.
Just tell me.
What did you do to Savannah?
Jess...
I'm sorry I blamed you.
Minute I got to town,
it was the only thing I wanted to say‐‐
Save the apology.
I just want the truth.
(door closes)
I found this for the cops.
Harper wears it all the time.
It's got her scent all over it.
For the dogs?
Like in the movies?
That's great.
Thank you, baby.
(phone ringing)
It's Sarah.
Any news?
[Sarah] I'm at the house...
Something very strange
is going on here, Ben.
We're getting out now.
[Ben]
Sarah, what's wrong?
Sarah?
(Sarah screams)
(theme music playing)
♪
Edit & Cleaned By M_I_S
www.opensubtitles.org
Sorry, Ms. Campbell.
No one answered,so I let myself in.
Oh, it's fine.
You just scared me,that's all.
Do you have news?
Yes. We may have found something.
[Ben] (over phone) Sarah?
Sarah, what's wrong?
Dad, are you there?
Yeah, you've got to get here fast.
(grunting)
Savannah!
Hold on, we're coming!
Pull harder.
We have to get it open!
I'm pulling as hard as I can!
Savannah!
[Harper] Griffin...
(grunting)
Griffin, stop pushing
and listen. We have to go!
What? Why?
Because there's no point.
The hatch is stuck.
That tree must've fallen on it.
Come on.
No!
Savannah was right behind us.
She could be hurt.
Exactly. Which is why
we have to get out of here
and go back though
the portal again,then home.
Home? How's that going
to help her?
That was a huge storm.
The second we get back,
we'll check records from 1960.
Old newspapers,
anything that can tell us if a girl was found.
You mean,
if she was injured or...
There's no time
to think about it.Let's go.
Once we getpast the camp office,
it's a straight shot to the hatch.
(indistinct chatter)
Got here as fast as we could.
[Jess] What is it?
[Sarah] I couldn't tell.
But I thought maybe you can.
[officer]
Boot print. Fairly fresh.
Do you recognize the brand,
the tread?
[Jess]
Size looks close.
Maybe Harper's from last night?
What I was thinking.
You asked for something of Harper's.
Ah, that's perfect.
Go!
[officer]
He's got something.
(intense music playing)
(barking)
(phones chiming)
Wait, everyone‐‐
I know where they are.
Griffin?
Harper?
[Harper] Back here.
Oh!
You called the police?
Mom, I'm so sorry‐‐
Are you okay?
[Sarah] We were so worried.
Where were you?
[Harper]
Uh, we walked to Rayville,
to catch a bus.
Yeah.
So you were trying to run away?
Um...
Kind of, yeah.
(whispers)
Sorry.
It was mostly my idea.
I just wanted to get out of here.
We both did.
Because we were keeping you apart?
Or is it because of your dad?
A little of both,I guess.
Why did you come back?
Well, I, um...
Because Griffin talked me into it.
Yep.
You know what?
I'm gonna need another hug.
Can we go home now?
There's an important...
assignment I have to finish.
Fine, but we've got
a stop to make first.
Why are we here?
When we were looking for you,
Topher said you come here a lot...
to feel closer to your dad.
I thought maybe that's why you ran away...
because I kept you away from him...
and the memories.
That's not why we left.
Even so,I realize it was wrong,
what I was doing.
Not talking about it.
You want to lead the way?
I'll do it.
Toph, I know you don't really
remember your dad,
but you look and sound
more like him each day.
Figured that's where
I got my good looks.
(chuckles)
It's true, you did.
Very handsome.
I've always wondered...
what made you fall in love with Dad?
Well, a lot of things,
but mostly because...
he could make me laugh like no one else.
He also knew
exactly what to say to tick me off.
(chuckles)
He used to love pushing my buttons.
Kinda like someone else I know.
How did you meet?
(sighs)
When we were kids...
at Camp Tremont,believe it or not.
Guess you could say,
he was the one good thing to come out of that place.
Really?
That long ago?
It was the last day.
I was going home,and my duffel was huge.
He offered to help.
(chuckles)
Darn thing must've weighed more than he did.
He had this goofy grin
on his face,
and he stuck his hand out
and he said,
"Hi, I'm Chris."
His voice broke.
I remember it so clearly.
We just laughed.
I'm sorry I haven't talked
more about your father.
It's just‐‐
After the accident,
when we lost him,
I... didn't know what to say...
to anyone.
You guys became my rock.
And I love you both so much.
[Sarah]
I'm sorry, Ben.
It's just too much.
I can't do this anymore.
Ben: Do what?
What are you talking about?
[Sarah]
What do you think?
I've had enough.
I'm done.
The kids and I are moving back to Chicago.
[Ben]
Okay, wait.
I know it seems like
nothing's going right
since we moved here.
[Sarah] Seems like?
That's an understatement.
Look, Ben, I've tried,
but I'm starting to believe
this place really is haunted.
Fine, then we'll fix it.
We'll bring someone in or‐‐
No. This ends now.
The secrets,
the conversations with Jess.
I mean, you lied to me
about knowing Savannah.
What else are you hiding?
(sighs)
Wait, Dad told you he knew Savannah?
Griff, uh...
Just go to bed.
You are two hours early.
Yes! I thought I'd get a jump
on the day.
By breaking and entering?
So I could do some extra research
for a history project.
Mm‐hmm?
What's this project about?
The Great Storm of 1960.
Oh.
The internet has a zillion links
but not enough pictures.
But lucky for you,
before there was the internet,
before there were laptops,
there was this neat little thing
called microfilm.
Newspapers, periodicals,
all squeezed down into these little rolls.
The school has some?
Oh, going way, way back.
The Great Storm of 1960...
Uh, you may or may not know,
but I am an expert
on local history and lore.
So you remember it?
1960?
Honey, do I look that old?
I know of it and about it.
But I'll tell you this,
that storm changed a lot of lives in this town.
Is Dad back?
[Sarah]
Not yet.
Zoey? Wyatt?
Breakfast.
Have you tried calling him yet?
I'm sure your dad will be home soon.
Just sit. Eat.
He... He seemed pretty upset last night.
I mean, you both did.
Everything will be fine
once we're back in Chicago.
Wait, that's definite?
Yeah, I thought you'd be excited.
Well... Yeah, but...
things have changed now.Kinda like it here.
Because of Harper?
And you know...
all of it.
Well, it's what's best for this family.
It'll all work out.
Exactly what you said when we moved in.
And it almost did.
After you eat, you need
to start packing up your room.
Now?
What about school?
I already called and told 'em
you're not coming.
You'll start back
at your old school next week.
No, but I‐‐
Hey!
Just pack.
Wyatt? Zoey?
Still at it?
Uh‐huh.
Mrs. Douglas:
1962?
I thought you were researching the storm.
Yes, but I'm also interested
in how the community rebuilt.
Like what happened to people.
Some moved away.
Some stayed.
You've developed quite a passion
for Sulphur Springs history.
Yes, it's just fun
to imagine what it was like,
being a kid back then.
Well, finish up.
Classes are about to start.
Savannah.
(phone ringing)
Griffin, what's going on?
Why aren't you at school?
Trust me,it's not my choice.
What's up?
[Harper]
Amazing news.
You're not gonna believe this.
Look!
Whoa!
Is that Savannah?
At the grand re‐opening
of The Tremont in 1962.
That's two years
after the storm.
Exactly.
That's great.
I know, right?
Okay, give me a few minutes
and I'll be right over.
What?
Wait. No, no. I‐‐
Griffin, we have to go back. Now.
I know, and I would,
but I, uh‐‐ If you're grounded,
it's fine.
We'll just figure out‐‐Harper, my family's moving.
What?
We're going back to Chicago.
But that's crazy.
You literally just got here.
Oh, you thinkI don't know that?
Sorry, it's just‐‐
My dad told my mom that he lied,
that he did know Savannah as a kid.
Oh.
They had this huge fight last night,
and my dad left,
and he hasn't come back yet.
So as soon as he does,
we're moving.
Forever.
This is so messed up.
Yeah, tell me about it.
[Zoey] Griffin!
We need more boxes from the garage.
[Sarah]
Griffin.
I‐‐I gotta go.
Wait.
(sighs)
(phone ringing)
Sarah, hi.
Listen, I'm a little‐‐
Is Ben with you?
Excuse me?
Ben.
Is he there?
No. Why would he be?
You're friends.
Were friends.
And, uh...
you seem to know a lot about each other.
What's wrong, Sarah?
You can't find him?
Um... No.
Look, I'm‐‐ I'm sorry I bothered you.
Wait.
There is a place.
It's a long shot,
but it's somewhere he used to go.
Why aren't you guys packing?
We're on strike.
We don't want to move.
Chicago will seem boring now.
No ghosts.
Thought you guys were scared of ghosts.
We were, but now
we're kind of into hunting them.
You know Mom thinks she saw one.
And we heard the singing.
What‐‐
What singing?
The girl on the tape.
In the boarded‐up room?
That's impossible.Are you sure?
Yeah, freaked out Dad too.
Maybe that's why we're moving.
Hey.
(clears throat)
We should go.
The lovebirds probably
need some alone time.
To do what?
Oh.
(imitates kissing)
Wow.
So this is really happening.
(sighs)
Yup.
My mom wants us to leave
as soon as we're packed.
See, all this stuff with our parents
is just...
Last night,
I couldn't stop thinking,
if we could just find Savannah...
You could stay.
Yeah.
Okay, so we've got a few minutes.
Maybe there's something we're missing.
Like what?
Savannah's in 1962,
and the portal only takes us back
30 years at a time, so...
Unless you want to go back to 1960
and wait two years‐‐
Of course not, but...
maybe there's a way to control it.
And as long as she's alive,
there's hope, right?
What?
The thing is...
if Savannah was alive,
she wouldn't be a ghost.
She wouldn't still be
haunting The Tremont,
but... she is.
She is?
How do you know?
There's something I need to show you.
Come on.
[Sarah]
Get any sleep last night?
Not much.
Me neither.
I'm sorry I walked out like that.
I love you.
And you can tell me anything.
We were in camp here together.
Me, Jess, and Savannah.
Back then around the campfire,
the scariest ghost stories
were about the basement in the hotel.
So one night...
Jess dared Savannah to stay down there...
till morning.
I thought I'd convinced her...
not to do it.
We camped out...
up there.
The tree house.
But after I fell asleep...
she snuck out.
To go to the basement?
Yeah.
So I did too.
Ben.
[Ben]
It was dark and creepy,
but we told each other jokes
and tried to laugh
our way through it.
We were fine until we heard a noise.
It was all around us.
I took off.
I thought she followed,but she didn't.
She stayed.
And I didn't know...
till the next morning.
The police were there.
Search parties.
Kind of like today.
You were just a kid.
The only kid who could have
saved her life.
Griff was right.
(sniffles)
He said I came here
to make bad memories better.
But the truth is I can't...
and never will.
Savannah is gone
'cause I ran away.
So this is where the singing came from,
an unplugged tape machine.
Yesterday,which means...
She's still a ghost.
(buzzing)
Did you hear that?
It looks like the radio in the bunker.
[Griffin]
Whatever this is,
it doesn't look like it belongs.
No, won't budge.
Let me try.
A code?
Maybe.
Or a combination.
Let's find out.
(grunts)
There has to be a screwdriver here.
Here.
Thank you.
Bingo.
Go ahead. Dial it to the same numbers
from the one upstairs.
Me?
Yeah. It seems to respond to you.
(buzzing)
(button pops)
This is really weird.
Yeah, no kidding.
What do you think it wants us to do?
First of all,
I don't think it's an "it."
It's her.
It's Savannah.
And she's trying to help us find her.
(intense music playing)
[Griffin]
Next time on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
Maybe this little dial...
Choose any year.
[Harper]
Try 1962.
That picture I found of Savannah,
that's the year it was taken.
What if something goes wrong again?
I can be stuck there forever.
[Zoey]
This is crazy.
A wall of cold spots and now...
No. No frost.
You don't think Savannah's hiding, do you?
What if she finally got what she wanted?
Mr. Campbell,you have to come quick.
What's wrong?
It's Griffin.
He fell.