[Griffin]
Previously On "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
The twins told us
you were gone half the night.
Well‐‐ We just wanted
to be alone to‐‐
Play cards and talk‐‐
And have our first kiss.
[Harper]
Look, I need your help.
Again?
[Harper]
All I bought us
was 10 minutes,
and that's now officially run out.
You ready?
[Jess]
Is Harper here?
I think that
they've run off together.
What if they're never found?
Like Savannah?
[Harper]
We need to find out
what happened to Savannah after the campfire.
You were with her
last night, right?
Isn't she at her bunkhouse?
They were with Savannah
last night at the dance.
Now we run.
Not so fast.
Savannah!
[Jess]
The way you were
acting that day,
it's like you knew something
the rest of us didn't.
None of this would be
happening right now
if it hadn't been for you
and your stupid dare.
[Bennett, Sr.]
Unacceptable. I was with
an important client
when I heard that
a camper had disappeared.
Dad, you're not listening to me.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
Not...
another...
word.
[Harper]
You heard that, right?
[Griffin]
My dad...
He just confessed.
♪
Edit & Cleaned By M_I_S
www.opensubtitles.org
I don't get it.
My dad and Savannah
were friends.
Why would he hurt her?
Maybe they were
pulling another prank
and something went wrong.
Like an accident?
Better than the alternative.
But we heard him confess.
My dad said
it was all his fault.
That has to mean
he did something to Savannah.
Then why come back
to Sulphur Springs?
It doesn't make sense.
I thought you'd be glad
my dad confessed.
It means your mom
is off the hook.
My point is
we still don't know
what actually happened
to Savannah.
Yeah, we never will.
My grandpa
made sure of that
by getting my dad
out of town
before anybody
could find out the truth.
Well, we definitely
won't get any answers sitting here.
(people chattering)
Hey, hey.
Help us!
We need help over here!
Come on, help us!
Come on!
[Wyatt]
I can't believe
Griffin did all this for a girl.
So dumb.
Yeah, but it's also
kinda romantic
when you think
about it.
They're like
Romeo and Juliet.
Who?
Shakespeare?
You really need
to pick up a book now and then.
I read books!
Comics don't count.
Anyway, it's a story
about a teenage couple
whose families
keep them apart.
How'd it end?
Never mind. Bad example.
(song playing on recorder)
It's coming
from over there.
Think it's Savannah?
We did feel
a cold spot in that room.
Okay. Come on.
Wait!
Shh.
My hat.
It's upstairs.
Forget about it, Wyatt.
There's no time.
(grunts)
[(Savannah singing):]
♪ Any kid could ever want ♪
♪ Our hearts and minds
will always say ♪
♪ Here at dear Camp Tremont ♪
(theme music playing)
♪
[Harper]
Another cop was taking us
to find our parents,
but stopped here
to help search the lake.
It's been a while.
He probably forgot
we were in here.
If you'll just
let us go...
That's against protocol.
You have to wait
for the other officer to get back.
No, no.
We can't wait.
It's an emergency.
What kind of emergency?
I have to use the bathroom.
Really, really bad.
Girl stuff.
There's a bathroom
inside the hotel.
Come on.
I‐‐ I need to go too.
One at a time.
[Sarah]
I'll call Joey's mom
and see if they've
heard anything from Griffin.
What‐‐ You think
he's headed to Chicago?
All his friends are there.
My sister, your dad.
Makes sense he'd go
some place familiar.
[Wyatt and Zoey]
Mom!
Savannah is haunting
the hotel.
It's more than
just cold spots.
We caught this weird glare
on tape.
And now the creepy music.
Your brother is missing,
and you're worried about a ghost?
This is serious!
So is this!
I can't right now.
You deal with them.
[Zoey]
We aren't making this up.
There was definitely
music playing
in that room you found
behind the wall.
What kind of music?
(door closes)
[Wyatt]
Sounded like this...
(singing off‐key)
♪ There's a place in Louisiana... ♪
Only better.
Much better.
And a girl was singing.
It had to be Savannah.
There's no other
explanation!
Uh, Griffin was...
messing around
with an old recording
when we were in there
the other day.
Guess he must've left it on.
Mystery solved. No ghost.
What?
We'll be upstairs.
Let's go, Wyatt.
(tense music playing)
Harper would freak
if she found out
you were going through
her stuff.
Well, Harper
should've thought of that
before she took off
with Griffin.
Cold.
I like it.
You're just
gonna stand there?
What are we looking for?
Anything that can help
the police narrow the search.
Um, notes, receipts,
a journal.
Oh, she keeps that
under her mattress.
I'm guessing.
And you complain
about how I spend my allowance?
Keep looking.
Has Harper been going through
the boxes out in the garage?
How would I know?
Well, there's not much
that happens around here
without you knowing about it.
Or benefiting from it.
Valid point.
Toph.
Fine.
Harper wanted
a picture of Dad,
and I may have told her where‐‐
Grab your keys.
Why?
I think I know
where she is!
(grunts)
[officer]
Everything okay?
Answer me or I'm coming in.
Come on.
Where are you going?
Back to the hatch.
To do what?
Confront your dad?
Well, yeah, Harper.
He confessed.
I have to know why.
What makes you think
he'll tell the truth now?
Your dad's lied
over and over again.
I mean, so have we.
Even if we come clean
about everything,
the bunker,
the portal, the past,
no way our parents
will believe us,
especially
after last night.
So we just
go on with our lives?
Act like my dad doesn't know
what happened to Savannah?
I can't.
What if there was
another option?
We saw my mom
running out of the hotel
right before
your dad confessed.
You think Jess saw something?
Only one way to find out.
I know waiting
is hard,
especially when you're worried sick
about your friend.
Savannah wasn't my friend.
Police are asking us
to do another head count.
Make sure no one else
is missing from camp.
Sit tight.
I'll be back soon.
What are you doing here?
Um, we saw Ben's dad pick him up.
I think they went back to Chicago.
Figured you'd want to know
since he didn't get
a chance to say goodbye.
I don't care.
Ben was a jerk.
Because he spent more time
with Savannah than you?
(scoffs)
Wow.
Jump to conclusions much?
You're just like Ben.
I'm nothing like Ben.
You're accusing me
of being jealous.
He made accusations too.
Blamed me for what happened
to Savannah.
How come?
I‐‐ I dared her
to spend the night...
alone in the basement.
Hey, if Savannah
went through with it
and got grabbed by a ghost,
it's her own fault.
Wait.
So, Ben wasn't with her?
I'm done
talking about Ben.
Leave...
or I'll get Becky
back in here.
We should go, Harry.
Jess obviously wants
to be alone.
(door closes)
If Savannah was in
the basement all night long,
she would've had
plenty of time to look around.
Maybe even find the bunker.
She could be traveling
through time,
just like us.
Why would your sister be here?
'Cause Dad is.
Harper visits his grave a lot.
Makes her feel close
to him, I guess.
Do you visit?
I've been here
with Harper before.
It's not the same for me.
I don't really remember Dad.
Yeah, you were both
so little when he died.
How come
you never talk about him?
Well, it makes me sad
to think about the life
we could've had together,
the memories you and Harper
would have had with him.
She remembers things
about him.
Like what?
Trips to the zoo,
painting on the porch,
swimming in a lake.
That kind of stuff.
Why don't you go
look around for your sister?
Harper will be okay, Mom.
She's tough, like you.
Thank you, baby.
(tense music playing)
[Harper]
This has to be it.
[Griffin]
Savannah must have found the portal.
[Harper]
Look.
Savannah could easily fit through.
Which means she could still
be alive somewhere in time.
Explains why the police
never found her.
Yeah, well,
it doesn't explain why my dad confessed.
I mean, if she's okay,
why was he so upset?
We don't know
if Savannah came down here alone.
It's possible
your dad knows about the portal, too.
He does act weird
every time he's in the basement.
Let's say they found
the portal together,
but your dad decided
to stay behind.
Camp was ending.
He wouldn't see
Savannah again.
That's reason enough
to be upset.
I know, but think about
how my dad was as a kid.
I mean, no way
he'd pass up a chance to time travel.
He'd be up for the adventure.
Unless Ben thought
it'd make things harder for Savannah.
What do you mean?
Well, our parents
can be overprotective,
but your grandpa
is super intense.
If he found out Ben was sneaking off,
he'd want answers.
And he wouldn't stop
until he found the portal.
Exactly!
So, my dad
might've confessed
to keep the secret...
and make sure my grandpa
never came back to Sulphur Springs.
It's a good plan.
Yeah.
Was a good plan...
until my dad
bought the hotel.
Well, maybe he had
a pact with Savannah,
to come back one day.
Come on, Savannah.
What are you trying to tell me?
We should be
searching for Griffin.
Every minute counts.
The police told us
to stay put.
I can't just
wait around, Ben.
Our son is missing!
You think I like making calls
and checking social media?
I want to be out there
looking too, Sarah.
Instead, you're in here,
looking for ghosts.
Ben...
What's going on?
Talk to me.
Please.
There is something
you should see.
That was our chance to convince Mom and Dad
this place is haunted.
They didn't want to hear it.
Mom didn't,
but Dad was curious.
He even looked
a little freaked.
You gave up too soon.
Griffin ran away, Wyatt.
That has everyone freaked.
We shouldn't give Mom and Dad
more to worry about right now.
What if he didn't run away?
What if Griffin was taken?
By Savannah?
She has been trying
to communicate with us.
Maybe she got fed up
because we didn't understand.
Then we have to try harder.
Easy for you to say.
You're not walking around
with a bull's‐eye on your head.
Your hat?
That's what you're looking for?
Savannah doesn't care
about your red hair, Wyatt.
I was just
messing with you.
It has to be
here somewhere.
Wyatt, focus!
Griffin needs us.
You're right.
We could be his only hope.
Welcome to Camp Tremont.
Why are we here?
I need you
to see this place.
Maybe then
you'll understand
why I had to come back
to Sulphur Springs.
I loved spending summers here
as a kid.
Used to stay
in the bunkhouse right over there.
Swim in the springs,
pull pranks...
I already know
all about the happy memories you made at camp.
I lied.
Not all my memories here
were happy.
Some are pretty awful.
Looks the same.
Maybe the portal
didn't work.
I felt the jolt.
Okay, assuming we can bring Savannah back,
then what?
She'll need a cover story
about where she's been,
something that won't make
the police suspicious.
Let Savannah come up with that
on her own.
Your stories lead
to awkward talks and way too many questions.
Is thank you
too much to ask?
I did keep our parents
from finding out about the portal.
Our moms anyway.
Well, we can't be sure
exactly what my dad knows
until we find Savannah.
Let's check
the bunkhouse first.
Uh...
Yeah,
she's not there.
Why do you say that?
Well, 'cause
the bunkhouses aren't.
[Harper]
1960?
(tense music playing)
The summer
Savannah went missing...
I was here.
But you didn't know her.
It's not true.
We were friends.
Good friends.
Griffin was right.
I should have been honest when Griffin
first started asking
about Savannah's disappearance.
And instead,
you got mad at the kids.
Accused us of not giving
this place a chance.
And all this time,
you've been keeping secrets.
What happened to Savannah
is not something I've ever
talked about with anyone.
Not even Jess.
Why would you talk
to Harper's mom?
She went to camp here too.
Wait, what?
Sarah...
That's why she was telling me
to go back to Chicago.
Jess knew
you were lying to us.
(vehicle approaching)
Did she also know
about you buying the hotel
before I did?
All right,
it's not like that.
Jess and I lost touch
after that summer.
Never thought
she'd still be living in Sulphur Springs
or that one day
our kids would be close.
Mr. and Mrs. Campbell,
sorry to interrupt.
K‐9 unit just arrived.
The handler's asking for
some of Griffin's clothes
to help track his scent.
It's gonna be okay.
You don't know that.
There's nobody here.
The Tremont
hasn't opened yet either?
This doesn't make sense.
The sign back there said 1960, right?
Yeah.
Hotel's been in business
since 1944.
There's a map of The Tremont
on the wall downstairs.
The date's on it.
Maybe the portal took us
further back in time.
How? Whenever we went
through before,
we always ended up
30 years in the past.
And this time we came
from the hatch from 1990.
So... where is everyone?
Hey, what are y'all doing?
Um... we're looking
for a friend.
Uh, she's blonde,
about this tall.
You're not gonna
find anybody here.
Big storm's coming.
Everybody's gone.
I'm only staying
long enough
to board up the windows.
You two kids need
to get on home, okay?
It's not safe here.
Where else
would Savannah go?
We don't have time
to look.
I thought
you wanted answers.
I do, but...
What if we're wrong?
I mean, what if Savannah
never found the portal?
We can't risk
getting stuck here for nothing.
Wait. Someone's inside.
Savannah!
Oh, there you are!
Thank goodness.
Hermione! Harry!
Boy, am I glad
to see you.
I almost started
to think
I stepped into
"The Twilight Zone" or something.
All right, listen,
we don't have a lot of time.
This was Ben, right?
What?
Pulling one last prank
before camp ends?
Talk about epic!
He emptied out an entire hotel.
My dad doesn't know
about the portal.
What?
This isn't a prank,
Savannah.
It's the past.
1960, we think.
That's why
things seem different.
The past?
(chuckles)
Good one.
(wind howling)
(window rattling)
All right, we need to get back
to the hatch now.
You guys can drop the act.
Tell Ben to come out now.
Look around.
The phone, the calculator,
the guest book,
it's all from another time.
How could Ben have possibly
pulled this off?
His dad's rich.
You really think he'd ask his dad
for help with a prank?
Probably not,
but makes a lot more sense
than time travel.
Please, Savannah.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I really need you
to come with us.
It could change everything.
♪
What are you doing?
Oh, uh, just looking
for a picture of your sister.
Thought it might help
with the search.
(car door closes)
Mom...
[Jess]
Did the police find them?
They're asking
for clothes,
something with
the kids' scent.
I'll get it.
I told Sarah we knew Savannah.
She had a lot of questions.
(scoffs)
I'm sure.
I've been over and over
that day in my head.
And I keep coming back
to how weird you were acting,
how you blamed me.
I was upset.
It was more than that.
What really happened
that night, Ben?
I tried being supportive,
let Ben work through
his mid‐life crisis,
and now I find out
he's been lying.
About everything!
As soon as we find Griffin,
I'm packing up the kids
and moving back to Chicago.
(static over phone)
Jenny?
Hello?
Can you hear me?
(gasps)
(eerie music playing)
(wind howling)
Give me a hand with this.
(both grunting)
You first.
Okay.
(grunts)
Savannah, hurry!
I'm coming.
[Griffin]
Come on.
Go!
Where's Savannah?
She was right behind me.
(Savannah screams)
(hatch slams close)
[Griffin]
Next time on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
Savannah!
Hold on, we're coming.
Griffin, we have to go!
The hatch is stuck.
[Harper]
The second we get back,
we'll check records from 1960.
[Sarah]
I can't do this anymore.
I'm starting to believe
this place really is haunted.
Let's go. Now!
Griffin, what's going on?
Why aren't you at school?
We have to go back.
Now.
Harper, my family's moving.
What?
We're going back to Chicago.