Griffin:
Previously on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
Savannah:
The camp is opening today
and this time I'll be
the one creeping kids out
with the legend of Moss Man.
This place isn't haunted
by Savannah.
We know.
The mirror told us.
Wyatt: That's how
the ghost communicates.
Harper:
Elijah's ghost wants us to
go back to my family's farm.
We need to find out why.
(wailing)
It was never Elijah
leading us back here.
It was her. Grace.
My great‐great‐grandmother.
Ghost of The Tremont.
Zoey: No way
this came down by itself.
This is not normal.
How else do we explain it?
Zoey:
Except ghosts.
Mom and Dad
definitely won't want
to hear that.
Wait, is that mine?
Oh, this? Yeah.
I had to drink it.
It was melting.
There's always
the refrigerator.
So what's with all this?
Isn't it obvious?
Paranormal activity.
Zoey: You were home
the whole time.
Did you hear anything?
Like screams?
Clawing at the walls?
(mimics eerie scratching)
I actually haven't
heard anything.
House has been pretty quiet.
Sarah: Griffin,
that you down there?
Um, yeah, I‐‐
I was just out back.
Sarah: Okay, well,
all of you, time for bed.
We'll clean that mess up
in the morning.
Coming.
(mouths)
Tomorrow.
(light fizzling)
(eerie music playing)
Grace.
(theme music playing)
(yawns)
Wyatt,
it's too early.
I've been waiting
for the sun to come up
for about an hour.
Daylight. Safety.
Or not.
Zoey, get over here.
It's her.
The ghost. She's back.
‐Wyatt: Mom!
‐Zoey: Dad!
Hurry! The window!
You have to see this!
A ghost, right‐‐
There.
Plenty of mist
but no ghost.
She was there!
The silhouette of an old woman.
We both saw her.
We're thinking
maybe the same ghost
who tore down
the wallpaper.
We already talked
about the wallpaper.
A perfectly logical
explanation.
We're not buyin' it.
There is no explanation.
And there's
no old woman outside.
All we've got here
are two kids
with vivid imaginations.
They're referring to us.
Might I suggest
you two go downstairs
and pour yourself
some cereal?
We'll join you in a bit.
They're getting to you,
aren't they?
Yeah, a little.
You know, the mind
can play tricks on you.
Ghosts can play tricks too.
Look, I'm telling you,
it‐‐
It feels like
there is something
in this place.
Someone.
And it wants us out.
Wyatt: Mom! Dad!
Get down here!
Zoey:
More wallpaper fell.
(muffled explosions)
(metal creaking)
Griffin:
I have weird dreams
all the time.
They never mean anything.
Harper:
This was different,
real scary.
Griffin:
Like these pants.
It's like if I sneeze,
they're gonna split wide open.
Harper:
Then don't sneeze.
And remember the plan.
As soon as we realize
Daisy's not around,
I step in,
pretend I'm her,
and figure out
why Grace wants us back here.
And I... play the new kid
next door.
No, you want it more like...
that.
Just need a little 'tude.
How's that?
Close enough.
Griffin:
Harper, come on, let's go.
Coming.
♪
(leaves rustling)
(rustling continues)
Mom! Mom!
Oh, young lady,
what's this all about?
Something was following me
back in the woods.
A creature
all covered in moss.
I almost yelled,
but then it ran off.
Honey, that was Sam,
the maintenance man.
He's been out cleaning moss
from the trails.
You mean he's Moss Man?
No. I mean he's Sam.
And he's very busy,
so you best stay
out of his way.
(gears whirring)
♪
Darn‐ation!
Daisy!
You 'bout scared me
to death.
Wait. Who are you?
New neighbor
from down the road.
Name's Harry.
You're not the same kid
who was snooping around
yesterday?
That kid
with them two girls?
Asked him the same thing,
but he's not.
So... what is all this?
You know what it is.
My special project.
Harper: Oh, right.
Your special project.
If you don't mind...
You're trying to build
a time machine?
Did you tell him, Daisy?
Yeah, uh, sort of.
It's still in
the planning stages.
Some hiccups to work out.
Do you believe
in time travel, Harry?
I'm open to the idea. Yeah.
Sam:
Wait a second.
Aren't you supposed
to be out at the oak grove,
collecting pecans?
Where's your sack?
And why did you change
your clothes?
Oh, um,
I already filled the sack.
And I got dirty,
so I changed.
Did you say oak grove?
You mean, by the clearing?
Along the fence line...
where the pecans are.
Pecans...
Harry, we should go.
What do you mean?
We just got here.
Come on.
See you later,
Daisy's little brother.
Sam. Sam Tremont.
See you, Harry.
What're you doing?
Where're we going?
That kid wants
to build a time machine.
That can't be
a coincidence.
Earlier,
when we came through,
I had a feeling
someone was watching us.
Daisy?
Oh, no.
This is not good.
This is not good at all.
♪
She found it!
Daisy found the portal.
Oh, and if she's
a relative of yours,
she couldn't help
but go exploring.
Harper: Daisy!
Jess: Harper?
Oh, uh, there you are.
Kirstin's coming in late,
so I need your help
at the café.
There's no time to explain.
Who are you?
What is this place?
I‐‐ I don't‐‐
I'm your great‐granddaughter,
and you traveled through time.
Time?
You're way in the future.
Like way, way.
You need to be me,
and I'll go back and be you
just for a little while.
My name's‐‐
Jess: Harper!
Come on! No dawdling.
Please. There's no choice.
Go! Be me!
(car dings)
Seatbelt.
(phone ringing)
Kirstin: Hi, Jess.
Jess: Kirstin, hi.
What's the update?
Kirstin (over phone):
I'm running Justin home,
and then I'll head back
to the café.
‐Jess: Great.
‐Kirstin: Thanks.
(seatbelt clicks)
Um, excuse me,
but Daisy went that way.
Off to the café, sounded like.
You've got to get to her.
Explain all this somehow
and get her back here
by, say, five o'clock?
While you head back
to the 1930s.
Our original plan,
posing as Daisy.
I mean, what better way
to find out what
Grace wants us to see?
Offhand, I can
think of about six.
Five o'clock.
Don't be late.
(door creaks open)
♪
Where've you been?
I've been doing double‐time
on our chores.
I just‐‐
She was beautiful,
wasn't she?
Yes.
(rocking chair creaks)
The rocking chair?
Mother's rocking chair.
Papa's been up there all day.
Is everything all right?
Come over here. Sit.
Your mother was the one
who knew the numbers.
I can't figure this out
to save me...
and save the farm.
Nothing for you
to worry about.
You know, you look
more like your mother
every day.
Growin' up
so beautiful and smart.
And you love this place
as much as she did.
Especially those springs.
She was so convinced
they could save her,
she had us
believing it too.
Yeah. She did.
I feel closer to her here
than anywhere else
in the house.
So when does it do it?
Any particular
time of day?
It's random
and, so far,
for our eyes only.
And you're sure
it's not Savannah
who was writing in the mirror?
Positive. We asked
the ghost point blank
and it wrote, "Nooooo..."
Only not quite that dramatic.
I would love a peek
at that mirror.
Still no idea
where your dad hid it?
Not a clue.
But we do know
every nook and cranny
in this place.
I say we start
with the secret room.
Secret room.
I like the sound of that.
♪
(door creaks open)
And who might you be?
(indistinct chatter)
(phones chiming,
devices beeping)
Jess: Harper?
Harper?
Earth to Harper.
Folks on table three
need help. Go.
And smile.
Good afternoon.
May I be of some assistance?
Yes, please. Can I have
a double‐decaf, no‐foam latte?
And I'll do a skinny,
half‐caf, white mocha, no whip.
So that was a double scoop‐‐
Uh, I mean, a‐‐ a skinny?
No. No, no.
A double‐decaf, no‐foam latte.
Mine is the skinny.
Yeah, uh, she'll
get right on it.
Excuse us, guys.
Did you say anything?
To Mrs. Dunn? To anyone?
Did you tell them
who you really are?
‐No.
‐Okay. Okay, good.
That's good.
Everyone here
is so frantic and busy.
Yeah. It's 2020,
the age
of "frantic and busy."
Uh, sorry.
I'm just so confused.
Okay. It‐‐ It's like
in your little brother's book.
You traveled through time.
And that bunker
in the basement,
it's a portal,
a door to the past.
I mean, for you,
I guess it's a door
to the future, but...
You talk too fast too.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I do that
when I get excited.
‐The girl who looks like me‐‐
‐Harper.
She's my great‐granddaughter?
That's just impossible.
Trust me,
it's‐‐ it's possible.
Trust you? How can I?
I don't even know
your name‐‐
It's Griffin.
Griffin Campbell.
‐Oh, my...
‐Daisy, what is it?
I‐‐ I don't feel
so well.
Harper?
Oh, whoops!
You caught us.
We were just practicing
our dance moves.
Harper's studying the 1930s
and, uh, there's
a school dance coming up.
There is?
Yes.
Yup, it's right around
the corner.
Well, come on, girl.
Kirstin's here.
So I can get you back
to do your homework.
Yeah. About that.
Um...
‐About what?
‐Griffin: Her homework.
Uh, she has this test
to study for.
It's, uh... history.
Yes, history.
Griffin: It's all a part
of that 1930s thing.
You know, I said
I'd help with the,
uh, the dance moves
and the flashcards
and all that.
So, uh, can she
come over tonight?
You know,
she's always over there.
Griffin, why don't you
come home with us? Hm?
Last I heard,
flashcards work anywhere.
We'll call your mom
from the car.
Yeah, okay. Okay.
Don't worry, I got this.
Got what?
Of course, Dad hides it
in the scariest place
possible.
Should've
looked here first.
(lights fizzling)
It does that sometimes.
We think it might be
in the wiring.
Or the mirror.
So how are we gonna
find the ghost?
I don't see
anyone in there.
What if we try
talking to it again?
Good idea!
Do you want me to?
I'll do it.
What do you think
I should ask?
Try...
"If you're not Savannah,
who are you?"
Only like this...
"Whooo are yooooou?"
Okay, got it.
So if you're not Savannah,
whoooooo‐‐
Sarah:
Are you kids down there?
If you are,
you know you're
not supposed to be.
‐Busted.
‐Totally.
Be right up!
You stay, Topher.
See if you can get it
to write something.
Hi. I'm Topher, by the way.
And you are?
Maybe instead I should ask,
who were you?
Okay. You don't like "who."
Let's try "why."
Why are you haunting this place,
these kids, this family?
Give me a letter.
Two letters, initials.
I'll take anything.
Whoa!
(tense music playing)
(door creaking)
No way!
Jess: Topher!
He was told
to come straight home.
Topher! Get down here!
Uh, Harper,
can you run upstairs
and get your brother?
Ten to one, he's streaming
some horror opus
instead of doing
his homework.
Yes, ma'am.
Ma'am?
Uh, Mother?
Mom is fine.
Always has been.
Griffin, what is going on
around here?
Oh, like I said,
it's a part
of her history class.
Harper's taking
this full immersion thing
very seriously.
Jumping in with
both lace‐up boots.
(sighs)
Nothing for dinner.
You know,
if you wouldn't mind,
can you tell Harper and Topher
I had to run to the market?
Oh, uh,
tacos are good for you?
Great!
I love tacos.
Of course,
they probably didn't have
tacos in the 1930s,
but I'm sure Harper
will gobble 'em right up.
Yeah.
She's an artist too.
Is that supposed to be
her father?
Griffin:
I guess so.
He died
when she was younger.
Like my mother died.
‐Grace?
‐Yes.
Grace.
I suppose
Harper misses her father
as much as
I miss my mother.
Look, Harper's mom
just ran to the market.
This is the perfect
opportunity to get you
back to 1930.
But we have to leave
right now.
Come on.
Leave, okay.
♪
(clock chimes five o'clock)
(radio whirring)
♪
Harper:
Next time on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
I can't be stuck here.
There used to be
a crystal in here.
Looks like you're stuck here
being Harper.
Harper will cover for you.
What game
are you playing?
Trying to contact the ghost
who pulled down the wallpaper.
Grace, is that you?
No way!
My friend Savannah
just sent me a picture.
It's the maintenance man
in 1962.
Sam? My brother?
It's her!
The lady we saw
through the window.
Daisy:
Some women in our family
see things before they happen.
Bad things. Really bad.