Griffin:
Previously on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
I'm your great‐granddaughter
and you traveled through time.
You need to be me,
and I'll go back and be you
just for a little while.
Jess:
Harper! Come on!
Go! Be me!
I step in, pretend I'm her,
and figure out why
Grace wants us back here.
Savannah:
Something was following me
back in the woods.
Caroline:
Honey, that was Sam,
the maintenance man.
Sam:
Daisy! You 'bout
scared me to death.
Griffin:
You're trying to build
a time machine?
Do you believe
in time travel, Harry?
This is the perfect
opportunity
to get you back to 1930,
but we have
to leave right now.
♪ ♪
What the...
But it was just here!
Oh, no!
(light fizzling)
(screams)
(tense music playing)
Griffin:
It's almost 5:00.
Harper's waiting for us.
‐We have to hurry.
‐Daisy: I'm coming.
(shimmering)
(rumbling, clanking)
No, no, no, no,
this can't be happening.
‐What's wrong?
‐I don't know.
It's never done this before.
Oh, come on!
I don't understand.
My family's radio
is a time machine?
Yeah, I mean,
at least it was.
Usually, we would
just press this button
and then flip the dial,
but...
‐Oh, no!
‐Daisy: What?
There used to be
a crystal thing here.
‐A crystal thing?
‐It's like a glowing rock.
It's gone.
And until we find it...
looks like you're stuck here
being Harper.
Griffin, no! I can't!
Papa and Sam depend on me.
Do you think
someone took it?
Maybe.
Besides Harper and Savannah,
no one else even knows
this place is here.
Unless it was the ghost.
Come on.
Wait! The what?
(theme music playing)
Griffin:
It'll be fine.
Whatever you normally do,
Harper will cover for you
until you guys switch back.
Yes, but even
if she can be me,
I can't be her.
Of course, you can.
You pulled it off earlier.
Yes. With your help.
And what was that
you just said about‐‐
Here.
‐What's this?
‐It's Harper's clothes.
Once you put 'em on,
you'll look exactly like her.
And as far as being alone,
you won't be.
Now that you have this...
I'll be right there with you.
What is‐‐
Griffin, no!
This is all too much.
I can't‐‐
And what were you saying
about a ghost?
Oh! Right! About that...
My mother's mirror?
Yeah, but it's more than that.
It's how she communicates
with us.
Who? The ghost?
It's not just any ghost.
It's...
Well, it's y‐‐ your mother.
What? Griffin,
that‐‐ that's impossible.
No. No, it's crazy.
Crazier than time travel?
I think
she wants to help us.
Maybe if you ask her
something...
Mother, if that's really you,
please... I have to get back
to Papa and Sam.
Do you know
where the crystal is?
(squeaks)
Home? Yes, that's where
I'm trying to go.
It doesn't make any sense.
If she knows
the crystal's missing,
she has to know
I'm stuck here, right?
Yeah, but...
What if that's not
what she's saying?
I mean, she knows
you're staying at Harper's.
Maybe that's where
she wants us to go.
(indistinct chatter)
♪ ♪
♪ One‐way ticket
on a one‐way flight ♪
(music continues on radio)
(clears throat)
Didn't anyone ever tell you
it was bad manners
to spy on folks?
Greg! Hi.
I was just‐‐
Well, I saw
what you were doing.
And, frankly, I don't think
Sam would appreciate it.
You're right. Sorry.
Guess my curious nature
gets the best of me sometimes.
I should probably
work on that, huh?
Mmm. Might be a good idea.
And I think
your mom and dad would agree.
Excellent point. See ya.
(clears throat)
You forgettin' somethin'?
What do you think?
Third coat really brought out
the grain in that oak, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, really did.
I gotta say, I'm feeling
pretty handy these days.
Think I might even build
a new deck out back.
Hot tub, maybe a...
You know,
maybe a waterslide.
I'm kidding.
Sorry.
Guess I'm just feeling
a little, um...
Overwhelmed?
Scared.
I get it.
Money's a little tight
right now but‐‐
That's not what
I'm talking about, Ben.
I'm sorry, I‐‐
I tried to shake it but I‐‐
I can't get past
this feeling that
someone or something
is trying to‐‐
(door slams)
Griffin, what did we
tell you about the door?
Oh, sorry, I forgot.
Where have you been?
Harper's house. Why?
Well, you haven't been
down in the basement lately,
have you?
Not...
since Dad and I
moved the mirror
down there yesterday.
A decision
I'm starting to regret.
Yeah, we caught Wyatt and Zoey
down there earlier.
‐Really?
‐Ben: Yeah.
So if you wouldn't mind
setting a good example‐‐
No more basement!
Okay?
Of course.
Yeah, I‐‐ I get it.
Um, I'll just be upstairs
if you need me.
(running footsteps)
Zoey:
What is it, anyway?
Wyatt:
Guess it's some kind of rock.
Zoey: So that's it?
It doesn't light up
or move or anything?
Wyatt:
Try shaking it.
‐Put it down now!
‐(twins scream)
Oh, um...
Griffin! What the heck?
Sorry, I‐‐ I thought
you guys were...
Never mind.
So what game
are you playing?
It's not a game.
It's a spirit board.
We're trying
to contact the ghost
who pulled down
the wallpaper.
We might be
doing it wrong, though.
we couldn't find
the instructions.
Cool.
What did you think
we were doing?
Oh, uh, I, uh,
I thought you, uh...
You know what?
I forgot, actually.
It's kind of weird, huh?
Very weird.
Yeah, I know. Uh, sorry.
Well, good luck on you guys',
uh, board thingy.
He forgot?
Probably hormones.
Teenagers are totally bizarre.
Harper:
I can't be stuck here.
I've got to get home.
It's okay,
they're just running late,
that's all.
I just wish there was a way‐‐
(floorboard creaks)
(clattering)
Jess:
Harper, is that you?
Yes, it is I‐‐ Me.
Harper.
Glad I caught you.
Where's Griffin?
He had to go home,
I suppose.
Uh, it's probably
for the best.
Taco night's gonna
have to wait.
The walk‐in at the cafe
broke again.
So I'm meeting
the technician now,
and that means
you're gonna have
to make dinner.
Dinner? Are you sure
that's necessary?
Well, it's not like
I'm asking you to cook
a four‐course meal.
There's lasagna in the freezer.
Just zap it in the microwave
for 10 minutes.
Microwave for 10 minutes.
Got it!
Thanks.
Oh, and could you please
go up and tell Topher
to stop goofing around
on his laptop
and finish his
language arts homework, now?
Stop goofing around
on his lapftop.
Lapftop?
I'm sorry, I meant...
I mean, um...
Harper, are you feeling okay?
Yes. I think I'm just...
‐I'm...
‐Having a rough day?
Aw, baby.
We all have those.
Thank you.
That's what moms are for, right?
I'll be no more than an hour.
Stop goofing around
on your laptop.
Lap‐top.
(doorknob rattling)
Hey! What are you doing?
I'm supposed to be the one
who enters without knocking.
I'm sorry.
No one told me that.
‐What?
‐Never mind.
Um, Mother told me
to tell you
to stop goofing around
on your laptop.
Seriously?
Man, how does she do it?
What?
How does Mom always know
what I'm doing,
even when she's not here?
Gives me the creeps.
Well, some women in our family
do have the sight.
The sight?
They're seers.
They see things
before they happen.
What kind of things?
Bad things, usually.
Really bad.
♪ ♪
(distorting)
(light flashes)
♪ ♪
Best thing about
sending a letter to the future?
No stamp!
(hinges creak)
"Guys, help.
I'm stuck in 1930."
Oh, my gosh!
Harper!
(bottles clinking)
Grace?
(hinges creak)
"Get this, Moss Man is real.
"He's the maintenance man
here at the hotel,
"and I just saw him
coming out of the secret room
in the parlor.
"He's definitely
up to something.
"Hope to know more
next time I see you.
Savannah."
No way.
(phone vibrating)
Daisy, did you find
the crystal?
I've barely had any time
to look.
Mrs. Dunn asked me to cook
some strange food for supper,
and now I can't even remember
what it was.
So? I mean,
you live on a farm,
you must know
how to cook something.
Of course, I cook
for Papa and Sam every day,
but... I don't know
how to use anything in here.
Well, sure you do.
How about the oven?
Yes, I see it.
Great. Uh,
now open the fridge.
And that's the, uh,
big silver box over there.
And cook the first thing
you find.
Daisy:
Oh, my! Okay.
I think I can do that.
Then what?
The only thing that matters:
find the crystal.
You gonna keep staring
into that thing?
Or are you gonna start supper?
I'm working on it, okay?
This biscuit recipe
calls for milk,
but I guess we're out.
Maybe we can call Papa
and ask him‐‐
Call Papa?
How're you gonna do that?
Holler out the window?
(laughs)
Sorry, I meant, um,
where can I find milk?
Where do you think?
Okay, Sadie,
this is totally new for me.
So if I do anything wrong,
just... bleat.
And I'm sorry
if my hands are cold.
(milk squirting into bucket)
Sadie, you're a lifesaver.
Okay. A double.
A little late in the day,
isn't it?
Yeah. I just haven't been
sleeping that well lately.
Please tell me
it's not more creepy humming.
No. Thankfully not.
Well, what's going on?
Just a lot of little things,
I guess.
Every time I try
to tell myself,
it's nothing‐‐
(child screaming)
Sarah:
What's going on?
Ben: I have no idea.
They just‐‐
It's her!
‐Sarah: Who?
‐Zoey: The ghost.
The lady we saw
through the window.
We told you about her!
But you didn't believe us!
Okay, this is going
to end now.
You can't just
go around yelling‐‐
Her name is Mrs. Barker.
She's here
at least once a week.
She's definitely not a ghost.
Jess, we are so sorry.
Right, guys?
Sorry.
Yeah, sorry.
It's okay. I get it.
I've got my own little
paranormal hunter at home.
Delicious!
What is this called again?
Creamed chicken and toast.
Huh! When did you learn
how to cook?
Last week, I watched you
burn frozen egg rolls.
Twice!
It's not that hard.
I just used some things
I found in the kitchen.
Come on,
how'd you really do it?
Must have some new recipe app
on your phone, right?
My phone?
This has recipes?
Only like a billion of 'em.
Man!
And just when I thought
we were having
frozen lasagna again.
Huh. Lasagna.
Saw Hoyt Sanders
at the post office
this morning.
Told me Molly's about
to start the fourth grade.
Fourth grade, huh?
I always did like Molly.
That's good to hear,
'cause you might be
seeing her again soon.
How's that?
I believe it might be
time for you
to start back at school
in the fall.
‐Both of you.
‐School?
But who's gonna help
with the chores?
This place is a lot of work.
And Mother always said
you're not
a young man anymore.
(chuckles)
Your mother had a point.
But your education
was important to her.
Come on, now.
I haven't made
the decision yet.
Just thinking about it,
that's all.
Oh, no!
I'm so sorry.
I have no idea
how this happened.
It's all right, Daisy.
Just a little burned soup.
But I turned off
that burner.
I know I did.
Well, memory can be
a tricky thing sometimes.
Now the two of you
get started on these dishes.
That old pot needs
to soak for a while.
(distortion)
(light flashes)
(evil laughter)
man on video:
...state of matter.
(man cackling)
(buzzing)
(laughter on TV continues)
(shimmering)
♪ ♪
Why would Moss Man be
in the secret room?
Sam?
(line ringing)
Griffin, I tried to search
Topher's room, but I‐‐
No, it's okay. Listen.
My friend Savannah
just sent me a picture
and I need you
to take a look at it.
What is it a picture of?
It's the maintenance man
at the hotel in 1962.
I think his name's Sam.
‐Sam? Like my brother?
‐Griffin: Exactly!
And it may just be
a coincidence,
but...
It could be him.
But why is he working
as a maintenance man in 1962?
Griffin:
No idea.
But he's an inventor, right?
I mean, I saw him
on that crazy bike thing.
And he's into time travel,
H. G. Wells,
that kind of stuff.
Yes, that's my brother.
Why?
Well, what if somehow
he's the key to all of this?
(knocking)
Sam. Everything okay?
Yeah. Guess I'm just thinking
about what Papa said.
You know,
about selling this place?
He just said
he was thinking about it.
Are you worried?
Yeah.
But not for me.
For you.
What do you mean?
Our plan, remember?
I'm gonna travel the galaxy
like those fellas in my books
while you stay here
and tend the farm.
That's still your dream,
right?
Yeah! Yeah, of course!
I'm just‐‐
Um...
Sam,
something happened today.
I had this vision.
Vision?
I'm in a room,
but I can't tell where I am
because there's
so much smoke.
Smoke?
Like the burned soup earlier?
Maybe.
Oh, my gosh!
Daisy, you know
what this means.
‐What?
‐You've got the sight!
‐The sight?
‐You're a seer.
Just like Mother.
Of course, she always said
it skipped a generation.
So it wouldn't pass on to you,
only your daughter
if you ever had one.
Guess she was wrong.
So what do you think
it meant?
The vision, I mean.
Beats me.
But like Mother always said
when she had one...
it's never anything good.
And is usually a lot worse
than a burned pot.
Hang on, Harper. I'm coming.
Oh, come on!
Please work, please work.
Who said
you could touch that?
Sam.
Stupid rock!
Just like that movie.
Nooo!
Oh! (panting)
(screams)
Wyatt:
Next time on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
There might be a way
we could get the portal
working again.
A way that involves
your brother.
We just need to find out
how he did it.
Savannah:
I know what this
radio really is.
You're building a time machine.
You have to go to school
to maintain cover as Harper.
Couldn't have changed
that much in 90 years.
It has to be here somewhere.
You've been acting
so strange lately.
Sometimes, I don't know
who to trust.
If we want more information
on ectoplasm,
we need to find experts.
Hello.
To be continued.