Griffin: Previously on
Secrets of Sulphur Springs...
♪ ♪
- What are you doing here, Dad?
- You shouldn't be here, Bennett.
None of you should.
Griffin:
My grandpa being here,
my dad's acting even
weirder than usual.
I know that you asked Harper
to stay away from Griffin.
I think it makes sense
to keep them apart.
At least for now.
Zoey: This is where we
felt one of the cold spots.
We're gonna finally
catch that ghost in here.
Zoey: No one else believes
us about Savannah's ghost.
Topher:
That's what the camera's for?
Your funeral.
Young Ben: Savannah's
different, you know?
Of course,
not everyone appreciates that.
Young Jess:
I just think this place
would be a whole lot
nicer if she'd just...
- go away.
- Harper [on phone]: Griffin,
my mom didn't just
hate Savannah.
She acted on it
at the talent show.
And the winner is
Ben Campbell!
[light applause]
Harper [on phone]: I think she might've
actually done something to Savannah.
Harper Marie,
you skipped school today?
I just got off the phone with
your principal.
- You're grounded.
- Grounded.
Young Ben: Last big camp
event of the summer. Should be fun.
- I was thinking of skipping it.
- You have to be there. Trust me.
It'll be a night to... remember.
♪ ♪
Meteorologist [on TV]:
Highs around 90 degrees.
- Overnight lows in the
50s initially, - [banging]
Bumping up again towards
70 degrees. Looks like a chance
for spotty rain will
continue throughout the day
with a chance of thunderstorms
until around 9:00 tonight,
so don't forget your umbrella.
Thanks, Marla.
Today marks the anniversary
of one of Sulphur Springs'
most notorious
unsolved mysteries.
Savannah Dillon
disappeared
30 years ago tonight
following a camp dance
at the historic Tremont Hotel.
Dillon's disappearance
set off a parish-wide search
- involving multiple
law enforcement agencies. - [click]
♪ ♪
[thunder rumbling]
Man, I've never been in such
a hurry for school to be over.
Me either. I just kept
thinking about Savannah.
What time is it?
It's 3:15. The camp
dance starts at 8:00.
That gives us less than
five hours to go back
and try and save her
from...
♪ ♪
Just say it. My mom.
We don't know that
for sure.
Either way, you'll have
to keep an eye on her
- if I can't make it.
- Wait, what? You have to come.
I'll try,
but it's gonna be tough.
I mean,
I am super grounded.
So, now I have to keep
an eye out on your mom,
Savannah, and anyone else who
looks like they're gonna try
- and do something bad to her?
- Possibly.
That stinks. We're better
together, you know?
As a team, I mean.
I know what you mean.
[car honk]
- Harper!
- One second!
- Now!
- [honking]
Griffin!
Griffin:
Wow.
- It's like they're a team now.
- Harper: Remember,
if I can't make it,
you have to go back, okay?
We have to
save Savannah.
♪ ♪
Theme song playing...
*SECRETS OF SULPHUR SPRINGS*
Season 01  Episode 05
Episode Title: "Parsley, Sage,
Rosemary and Time"
Aired on: January 29, 2021
[footsteps approaching]
Why did I let Kirsten talk me
into hosting this open mic
- at the shop?
- She's a very persuasive woman.
Jess:
This is true.
I'm late.
Oh, before I forget.
♪ ♪
What's this?
Your sister is going through
a challenging time right now.
She's... rebelling a bit.
You're putting me in charge?
I'm asking you to keep
an eye on her, okay?
She leaves this house for
any reason, you call me.
Consider it... done.
And clean up this mess, huh?
[door opens, shuts]
Did I just hear Mom leave?
- You must have excellent hearing.
- Harper: Did she say
- when she'd be back?
- Topher: No.
Why? Going somewhere?
No.
Okay, let's say I do
have some place to be.
- What's it gonna cost me?
- What've you got?
Uh... 20 bucks,
and my Scream Stream password.
But you have to really
cover for me, okay?
Hm...
- That is enticing.
- Just think.
All those super scary zombie
flicks Mom won't let you watch.
- You'll be having nightmares for weeks.
- Sounds great.
♪ ♪
Nice doing business
with you.
[birds chirping]
There you are.
What took you so long?
I had to wait for Mom
to leave the kitchen.
Parsley?
Rosemary? I told you.
We need sage to cleanse
the hotel of Savannah's spirit.
I know, but we're out.
So I thought I'd substitute.
- Chipotle mayo?
- That's a spice!
It's a condiment!
Wyatt, this is important.
I saw it on the news!
Tonight's the anniversary
of Savannah's disappearance,
which means she'll probably be
haunting this place extra hard.
So, if we don't have sage,
why don't we try something else?
- Like what?
- Well,
I guess we could always
give her something.
Yes!
Like a peace offering!
But, what kind of things
did Savannah like?
I don't know,
but it better be cheap.
I only have
eight dollars and 74 cents.
That's okay.
We'll find some good stuff.
♪ ♪
[chains rattling]
[creaking]
- [clang]
- [chains rattle]
- [whooshing]
- Ah!
Dude, I don't think I'm ever
gonna get used to that.
[sighs] - Dude, did you
really just call yourself dude?
- Uh, yeah, I guess I did.
- [laughs]
Don't feel bad. You don't wanna
know what I said when I felt it.
- [Griffin grunts]
- [bangs]
Hurry up. We don't
have much time.
The dance is gonna start
soon.
[creaking]
♪ ♪
Griffin: All the reports say Savannah
went missing after the dance,
but they didn't
say how soon after.
Right, so all we have
to do is stay with her
until we're positive
she's safe in her bunk,
while keeping
an eye on Jess.
Or anyone else
suspicious.
Preferably before my mom gets
home from work and grounds me
- until I'm 28.
- You make it sound so easy.
[laughs]
Wait,
If they're both
going to the dance,
- we can't crash dressed like this.
- Don't worry, we're covered.
- I even brought you something.
- [opens bag]
A tie?
- With vampires on it?
- It's Topher's,
but we won't even need it
if we can somehow
- convince Savannah to skip the dance.
- Oh! Yeah.
- I had an idea on that.
- [unzips bag]
A tablet? There's no
Wi-Fi here, remember?
I know.
Before I left, I downloaded
a video of the local news
from the day
Savannah went missing.
- When she sees it...
- You think she'll believe it?
Of course. How can we
fake an entire news report?
Good point.
But in case she freaks out, be
gentle when you show it to her.
Me?
Why do I have to do it?
Because I'll be too
busy watching my mom.
♪ ♪
[birds chirping]
[Jess sighs]
If you're looking for
Savannah, she's not here.
Uh, no, actually.
I was passing by
and thought I'd say hey.
Why would you do that?
We're not friends.
I know. I just
wanted to say, uh...
That's a pretty dress.
Big dance tonight, huh?
- Highlight of the summer.
- You look great.
Although...
Although?
- Nothing. Just your makeup.
- What about it?
Tiny suggestion.
[opens bag]
It's called Berry Bliss.
Something tells me
it'll look amazing on you.
♪ ♪
- Never heard of it.
- It's new.
Like, really new. [laughs]
I just figured with your
complexion and that dress,
it would go amazing.
- [laughs] Wow!
- [caps lipstick]
Where'd you get this?
- My mom, actually.
- I love it.
Hey, Hermione, um...
do you wanna come to
the dance with me tonight?
Yeah! Sure! Uh,
I think I even have
something to wear.
But, why me?
Like you said,
we're not friends.
Well...
we're not friends yet.
Besides, I can always use
a partner in... crime.
♪ ♪
[clears throat]
Mom. You're home early.
Yeah. Kirsten
offered to close up.
Where's your sister?
In her room, asleep.
Guess all that misbehavior
kinda wore her out.
Hm, I see.
Well, maybe I'll just
pop in and say goodnight.
Oh. Okay.
- Good night.
[door creaks]
♪ ♪
[snoring]
- [door creaks, shuts]
- [snoring]
[snoring on speaker]
- Wyatt: So that's it?
- Zoey: I guess so.
I just wish we knew more
about what she liked.
Well, everybody likes
money and cheese.
And that '90s guy
is pretty cute.
Whatever.
So, what do we do now?
We wait.
♪ ♪
[birds, insects chirping]
- [thud, scrape]
- [grunts]
- [ladder rattling]
- Griffin: Hey.
Hey, Harry.
How'd you get here?
Nobody knows
about this place.
I, uh, I saw you a little
while ago by the springs,
and I followed you here.
- Okay...
- Listen,
there's something
you need to see.
- It's a...
- Cool! What is that?
Is it a video game?
Can you play Dragon Blaster?
- Or Laser Patrol!
- Savannah.
- [sighs]
- Hey!
Just watch it, okay?
[Savannah sighs]
Oh no.
No, no, no, no.
- What's wrong?
- I think the battery's dead.
That's okay. They sell
batteries at the gift shop.
What kind does it take?
Double A?
- D?
- It's not that kind of battery, okay?
Harry, relax.
It's just a toy.
It's not like someone just died.
Well, not yet, anyway.
♪ ♪
[footsteps approaching]
I see you finally decided
to fix that window.
Yep. Good as new.
Just as long as you don't
try to open it. Ever.
- [laughs]
- [guitar strumming]
Griff's getting pretty
good on that guitar, huh?
Yeah, he really is.
But I'm worried
about him, Ben.
We pulled him away from
all of his friends,
and now
that he has a new one...
We're telling him he
can't see her anymore.
- Think we should go talk to him?
- In a little while.
I'd hate to interrupt his jam.
[guitar continues]
He really is
getting pretty good.
[guitar strumming]
♪ ♪
I just don't get
what the big deal is.
[ladder rattling]
Savannah,
there you are.
Hey, Harry.
The dance is about to start.
You're coming, right?
No, I don't think so.
Exactly!
Camp dances
are pretty stupid.
Is this about that
thing that Jess said?
You know she was kidding, right?
- What'd she say?
- It was so dramatic.
She was talking about the dance.
"It'll be a night to...
remember." [laughs]
Young Ben:
Hey, that sounds just like her.
Please come.
Just for a little while.
♪ ♪
Fine. But only for a
little bit. Later, Harry.
- Take me with you!
- To the dance?
Yeah!
But you just said
it was stupid.
And it is.
But, the thing is, I'm...
kind of an awesome...
dancer.
And you're looking for some
place to show off your moves.
Uh-huh.
Uh, okay. Sure.
Come on.
Let's go.
I can't wait to see
these moves.
Yeah.
Me neither.
[heavy breathing]
♪ ♪
[breathing continues]
- [children chattering]
- [music playing]
[chatter continues]
Wow. Good thing you
decided to pack that dress.
Yeah.
Just lucky, I guess.
Um, this place
looks great.
Looked much
better last year
when I was on the
decorating committee.
[inaudible]
Harper:
What is she doing here?
And... [scoffs]
What is she wearing?
Listen, Jess,
you're not planning on
doing anything tonight,
are you?
- Like what?
- I don't know.
Anything weird?
You're the one
being weird, Hermione.
- Don't make me regret bringing you.
- Sorry.
- [inaudible] - So, um, you
gonna ask Ben to dance?
Please. I'd never ask a guy to
dance this early in the night.
Trust me.
When I'm ready for us
to dance, we'll dance.
Uh, okay.
[music continues]
Griffin, what is
Savannah doing here?
Didn't you show
her the report?
Yeah, I tried,
but the battery was dead.
You forgot to
charge the tablet?
No, I swear!
Something must've happened when
it went through the portal.
- The jolt.
- Yeah. There's more.
Jess made some creepy
comment to Savannah
about how tonight's gonna
be a night to remember.
Makes sense.
She practically told me
she was planning
to do something to her.
She's got something
in this bag.
- Like what?
- I don't know.
She didn't show me. Anyway,
I better get back to her.
Anything else I should know?
Young Ben:
Hey, Harry! There he is!
Let's see those moves.
Yeah. Apparently,
I'm an amazing dancer.
Come on!
Let's see it!
- I don't know, guys. Maybe later.
- Young Ben: No way, dude.
We even picked
a song just for you.
[dance music playing]
- Go Harry. Go Harry. Go Harry.
All:
Go Harry! Go Harry! Go Harry!
[trailing off]
♪ Do what I want,
who will say I can't ♪
♪ Feel so good,
I'ma do my dance ♪
Is he okay?
Give him a chance.
Maybe he'll get better.
♪ Let me share a little
something with you ♪
Or maybe not.
♪ I'm feeling like
y'all can't move ♪
y'all can't lose ♪
♪ I'm feeling like... ♪
Savannah:
[laughs] Nice try.
[song ends]
[laughs] Keep practicing,
Harry.
Hey, that's okay.
No time for
dancing anyway.
[sighs]
I'll keep an eye on Savannah.
You go find Jess.
♪ ♪
[burps]
Savannah?
You burped in your sleep.
I didn't know that
was even possible.
Oh.
Guess we shouldn't have
eaten all that cheese.
You shouldn't have
So, she didn't come?
Not yet anyway.
Too bad.
Oh well.
- I'm going to bed.
- You know, Wyatt.
- Yeah?
- I was thinking.
Maybe you should
sleep here tonight.
I mean, since it's
the anniversary
of Savannah's disappearance
and everything.
Okay. But, just for tonight.
[dance music playing]
Dance is practically
over, huh?
- [inaudible]
- [party chatter]
Guess it's almost time for you
guys to head back to the bunks.
What? No! Light's out isn't
for another hour.
Besides...
it's time.
♪ ♪
Side A, please.
[clicks]
[slow dance song playing]
♪ Everybody's asking ♪
♪ Who I will be ♪
I love this song.
Do you wanna dance?
Hey, why not?
♪ Making predictions on ♪
♪ Where I'll live ♪
♪ Ah... ♪
♪ And make it last ♪
♪ Drive it fast ♪
- Griffin.
- Yeah. I saw.
Your mom is not happy.
You really think she's gonna try
- and pull something?
- I don't know,
but we better stay close to
Savannah in case she does.
How? She's out
there dancing.
How do you think?
Come on.
♪ ♪
Still can't believe I pulled
off those dance moves.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure this
is more your speed.
♪ I don't know, I don't know
where I'm going to ♪
♪ All I know is I'm getting
on a train soon ♪
♪ I don't know, I don't know
where I'm going to ♪
♪ ♪
What are you smiling about?
- Jess, everything okay?
- [scoffs]
Please don't try
to act innocent.
You knew I was going
to ask him to dance,
and you had Savannah ask
him first to humiliate me.
No! I'd never!
This isn't over, Hermione.
♪ ♪
Whoa. What was that?
I have no idea, but we better
keep her away from Savannah.
[crickets chirping]
[heavy breathing]
- [muffled music, chatter]
- [heavy breathing]
♪ ♪
- [inaudible]
- [heavy breathing]
Sync corrections by srjanapala
Topher: Next time on
Secrets of Sulphur Springs...
Zoey: This is definitely the
right way to summon a spirit.
This is our best chance
to get proof she's real.
Whatever's gonna happen,
it's gonna be soon.
Griffin: We cannot let
Savannah out of our sight.
- Harper: Or my mom.
- Girl: Let's go talk to the manager.
You're not leaving this office
until you tell us how
to contact your parents.
Everything you do
is to get attention.
"I'm not afraid of anything."
- I'm not, including you.
- Jess: Yeah?
Everything would be
better if you were gone.
♪ ♪