Griffin:
My dad bought an old hotel.
Now I'm stuck here
while my parents fix up
The Tremont.
(loudly):
You live at The Tremont?
Zoey:
Who's Savannah?
The ghost of a kid
who's supposedly been
haunting the hotel
for 30 years.
I said supposedly.
We saw a ghost
in The Tremont
last night.
‐(ghost screams)
‐(Topher screams)
I saw a ghost.
Tremont has a bunker?
Griffin:
Let's check it out.
Griffin, look.
Griffin: It's like
we stepped back in time.
Harper:
She's alive, Griffin.
Time travel
is the only explanation.
Savannah?
Harper:
The Tremont
is completely safe.
Jess:
The Tremont is cursed!
Griffin:
Maybe we're messing
with things
that shouldn't be
messed with.
(gasps)
Harper: Savannah!
You said you were never
coming through the portal.
I know.
Then I found this.
Looks like you're not done
time traveling either.
Griffin: Finally,
an adventure that
doesn't involve saving you.
So a ghost
that's not me.
It could be anyone.
Griffin:
There's only one way
to find out.
Harper:
Let's go.
Griffin:
As long as we're home
before dinner.
(intense music playing)
(woman humming "Amazing Grace")
(humming continues)
(rocking chair creaking)
(humming stops)
(creaking stops)
(gasps)
Ben! You scared me.
Sorry. Uh, I was
looking for Griffin.
He in there?
No one is.
man:
Daisy, is that you?
‐He's coming.
‐Go!
Who‐‐
Woah.
What was that about?
It was all so strange...
like looking in a mirror.
How do you mean?
Didn't you see that girl?
We're nearly identical.
She could've been me.
How's that possible?
Sam, come back!
Where is he off to now?
Sam went tearing through
the field after some‐‐
Probably realized
his chores
are still waiting.
Pay him no mind.
That boy's head
is always somewhere else.
Let me give you a hand.
(tense music playing)
(theme music playing)
That man was
in the same chair
I saw rocking
by itself earlier.
That can't be
a coincidence.
Do you think we saw
a ghost back there?
I'm saying
he must be the ghost
haunting the hotel now,
the one who led us
into the past.
But why?
And what about the girl
on the porch?
She has to be
one of my relatives.
My family used to own
The Tremont,
back before it was
a hotel.
That explains
the resemblance.
But the man
in the rocking chair
was calling out
for somebody
named Daisy.
‐So that would make her your...
‐Harper: I'm not sure.
After my dad died,
my mom didn't talk
about it much.
All I really know
is that they met
on her last day of camp.
‐Oh, no!
‐What's wrong?
I have to get home.
The camp is opening today
and I'm supposed
to be helping everyone
get settled
into the bunkhouses.
Kind of wild you're gonna be
a camper there again.
Junior Counselor, actually.
This time I'll be the one
creeping kids out
with the legend of Moss Man.
And busting them
for pulling pranks.
I wouldn't go that far.
I mean, I am still me.
(lights crackling)
Well, guess this
is goodbye again.
Doesn't have to be.
There could be a clue
in 1962
about the man
in the rocking chair,
who he is and why he's
haunting the hotel.
If you come up with something,
send us a message.
Tree house again?
Like we did
with the coffee can?
We shouldn't chance it.
There's too many people
that know about that place.
What about the basement?
Under a floorboard or something?
Bottom of the stairs?
That works.
Sure you won't get in trouble
for snooping?
We don't wanna mess things up
for you back home.
Can't get in trouble
if you don't get caught.
I should get back too.
The twins probably think
a ghost grabbed me.
A ghost who wants
to melt off our faces?
‐I was kidding about that.
‐Uh‐huh. Sure you were.
(radio whirring)
Maybe it only
feels comfortable
rocking in front of kids.
It's a chair, Wyatt.
It doesn't have feelings.
He means the ghost.
And this one
definitely has feelings.
Big feelings.
Frustration mostly
because we can't figure out
what it's trying to tell us.
Tell me again
what you think you saw.
The chair started
to move...
Back and forth.
Real slow.
Wait. I thought
you two are done
with all this
supernatural stuff.
So did we!
But the ghost keeps
reaching out
to draw us back in.
It would be rude
not to listen.
Here's an idea.
Why don't you try
listening to your parents
for a change?
We mean it when we say
this place isn't haunted
by Savannah.
We know.
The mirror told us.
The mirror?
Wyatt: That's how
the ghost communicates.
Leaves messages
on the glass.
It wrote, "No,"
when we asked
if it was Savannah.
It was probably just Griffin
messing with you guys.
What about me?
Have you been pranking
Wyatt and Zoey again?
The mirror fogged up
and the message appeared.
No way Griffin could
pull that off.
Just get rid of it, Ben.
‐You can't!
‐We'll never know
what the ghost wants.
I think we'll all sleep better
with the mirror gone.
Besides,
all of this ghost hunting
has become
a huge distraction.
Your mom is right.
It's going to take
everyone pitching in
to get the hotel
finally reopened.
You two can start
by giving me a hand
downstairs.
‐But I‐‐
‐Sarah: That wasn't a request.
Maybe we shouldn't toss it.
Don't tell me you believe
all that ghost talk.
This old mirror might be
worth something.
Could put the money
toward the renovation.
Yeah,
every little bit helps.
But we can't leave it up here.
Too tempting for the twins.
Take it to the basement?
They're way too scared
to go down there.
Argh.
The screws are stripped.
We're gonna need
some serious tools.
Pliers, a drill.
I ever tell you
about the time
Grandpa tried
to teach me
how to use one?
Nope.
Went about as well
as you'd expect.
(ominous music)
Jess:
Is your brother
still on the couch?
Said something
about slime creatures
and an epic battle
for humanity.
Well, humanity
will have to wait.
It's his turn
to help fold.
‐I'll do it.
‐Help yourself.
So, was Dad into
all that stuff too?
You know,
monsters and ghosts.
Your dad? Please.
Couldn't pay him
to sit through a scary movie,
at least not without
squeezing the life
out of my hand.
Not sure where
Topher got it from.
Am I anything like Dad?
I'd say you're a good mix
of the both of us.
He had that same
quiet confidence,
but your stubborn streak?
Whew, that's all me.
I was named
after his mom, right?
Yup. Your Grandma Marie.
Wish you could've met her.
She had a big heart
just like your dad.
And her parents?
What were they like?
Why all the questions?
There's just a lot
I don't know
about our family.
Guess I never will.
You know, the thing
about Grandma Marie,
she saved everything.
Yeah, it took your dad
close to the three months
to clean out her house
after she passed.
This belonged to her.
‐No telling what's inside.
‐You've never opened it?
I think your dad
was saving it for you kids.
Guess now's
as good a time as any.
(phone chimes)
Ugh, sorry, baby,
Kirstin's not feeling well
and she needs me to close.
It's okay. You should go.
You know, I'm gonna take
your brother with me.
He can mop up the cafe
since he couldn't be
bothered to help fold.
‐Need anything?
‐I'll be fine.
You always are.
‐Strongest girl I know.
‐Learned from the best.
Okay.
Bunkhouses are
straight down this path
and the springs
are back there.
Can we swim any time?
No campers out here at night
without a counselor.
Well, I'm not afraid
of the dark.
Well, it's easy
to get turned around
when you don't know
these woods...
or what's in them.
In them?
Legend has it,
something lives out here.
Waiting...
‐watching.
‐(leaves rustling)
What was that?
Probably just the wind.
Stay here,
I'll go check it out.
(campers chattering)
(suspenseful music playing)
Up a little.
Down.
Lower.
That's too low.
You want it perfect,
right?
I'd settle for done.
Yup, uh,
that's gonna be
a problem
'cause these are
the last two rolls.
You checked the closet?
Yep. And we are
all out of paste.
‐Shocking.
‐I'll run to the store.
Oh, let me.
Could use a break.
When do we get a break?
You haven't exactly
been helping.
Uh, yes, I have!
All you've done
is stand there.
It's called supervising.
That's one word for it.
Have fun!
Well, I think
we've all earned a break.
‐Ice cream at Dunn's?
‐Dibs on the front!
Zoey:
You had it last time!
‐Wyatt: Called it first!
‐You comin', bud?
Um, I have a lot of homework
to finish.
Bring me back a shake?
Chocolate with
extra whipped cream?
It's a good guess.
That's what you order
every time.
Not exactly
a man of mystery, Griff.
(suspenseful music playing)
Hello?
Can you hear me?
(phone ringing)
Daisy's my great‐grandmother.
And the man
in the rocking chair,
that was her father,
Elijah Tremont.
So that's where
the hotel got its name.
Did your mom tell you
all this?
I found pictures...
in an old trunk
my dad kept in the garage.
You'll never believe
what else is inside.
Look.
A... bracelet?
My bracelet!
I was wearing it
when we went to 1930
this afternoon.
It must've fallen off.
Someone in my family found it
and kept it all this time.
Harper...
It's incredible to think
something of mine
was passed down
for generations
before I was even born.
Harper, how soon
can you get here?
Why?
Look.
Hey, Jess.
Hey! I was wondering
if I'd get a chance
to see you guys
before the big move
back to Chicago.
Change of plans.
We're staying
in Sulphur Springs!
‐You are?
‐We can't leave yet.
Things are
just getting good.
Well, I know two kids
who will be very excited
to hear that.
Topher's out back
bussing tables
if you wanna
tell him the news.
Wyatt:
Wait till we tell him
about the mirror.
Figured you'd finally
had enough of living
in a haunted hotel.
Ah, the only thing scary
about The Tremont
is how much work
it needs.
Once we fix one problem,
we find another.
Well, some might say
there's a reason for that.
Now you sound like
the twins.
People have been
telling stories
about seeing ghosts
around that place
for generations.
That's all they are.
Stories.
Urban legends
like Moss Man.
What if they're not?
I heard humming
coming from Griffin's room
earlier.
At least, I think I did.
Probably just left
some music playing.
No, it wasn't the radio.
It sounded like
"Amazing Grace."
A woman.
When I got to the door...
she stopped.
Nope. Uh‐uh. I would be looking
for a new place pronto.
We can't afford
somethin' else.
Opening the hotel
is our only option.
‐You ready?
‐Huh?
Oh! Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where'd you get
this stuff from, anyway?
In that trunk
with the photos.
My grandmother really did
save everything.
This was
her wedding dress.
Relax,
no one's getting married.
The goal
is to blend in, right?
This was
the best I could do
on short notice.
Right.
So what's the plan?
Well, Elijah's ghost wants us
to go back to my family's farm.
We need to find out why.
All right. All set.
Here you go.
(radio whirring)
(woman humming)
Do you hear that?
It's coming from
over there.
(woman humming "Amazing Grace")
Maybe she's the reason
we had to come back.
Or whatever
she's looking for.
(continues humming)
Flashlights have been
passed out,
clues for the scavenger hunt
have been hidden,
and the birdhouses
are ready to be assembled.
I wish all the councilors
were as responsible as you.
Kids?
Take it outside
before something gets‐‐
Broken.
Sorry.
We‐‐ We'll clean it up.
It's almost time
for lights out.
Head back to the bunkhouses.
I'll take care of this.
I need to sweep up this glass
before someone gets hurt.
I'll get the broom.
Thanks, honey.
There's one in the basement.
(door opens)
(footsteps receding)
(door closes)
♪
Moss Man!
Griff, we're back.
Ugh, look at that!
All that work.
Urban legend, huh?
Oh, man!
It's starting.
Just like Topher said.
‐The ghost?
‐Has to be.
You used like
a gallon of paste
on that paper.
There's
no other explanation.
Mom and Dad are
really gonna regret
moving that mirror.
Daisy: They were
in the house, Papa.
It's not the first time
we've found people
wandering around.
This wasn't like before.
These...
These people were different.
Only one reason
somebody be looking around here.
The Springs.
Elijah:
Probably had the same notion
your mother did.
But we know
there's nothing special
about that water.
I'm gonna turn in.
Sam, make sure to help
your sister with the dishes.
Sam: Yes, sir.
You're right.
Those people aren't
like the others.
And I know why.
They're from outer space.
‐Finish your supper, Sam.
‐I've got proof.
‐Found this in the field.
‐My bracelet.
See? A star.
People don't just disappear
into thin air, Daisy.
Except somehow they did.
(floorboard creaking)
Harper, wait.
There she is.
(tense music playing)
(wailing)
Come on.
You saw, right?
The woman in the springs,
she just‐‐
Vanished.
And if she's a ghost...
We had it all wrong.
It was never Elijah
leading us back here.
It was her.
Who is she
and why did she
scream like that?
I don't know.
Griffin, wait! Look.
There's our answer.
Grace.
Daisy's mother,
my great‐great grandmother.
The ghost
of The Tremont.
Griffin:
Next time on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
Wyatt:
This is not normal.
‐How else do we explain it?
‐Zoey: Ghosts.
It feels like
there is something
in this place
and it wants us out.
Savannah:
Something was following me,
back in the woods,
a creature
all covered in moss.
And remember the plan,
as soon as Daisy's not around,
I step in,
pretend I'm her.
‐Daisy!
‐What is all this?
Trying to build
a time machine?
Do you believe
in time travel, Harry?
She found it!
Daisy found the portal.
‐Harper: Daisy!
‐Harper?