Savannah:
Previously on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
Griffin: I thought
the springs dried up.
Ben:
The springs, they're back!
This means our luck
is changing.
Bennett, Sr.:
I want to help you bring
this place back to life.
With just a few phone calls,
I'll have a dozen workers
over here.
‐Zoey: That was
no electrical surge.
‐Wyatt: No way.
I think
our ghost is getting
really ticked off.
Hoping I could talk you
into reconsidering my offer,
Elijah.
One bad season.
Heck, one bad accident,
and all you'll leave
your children with
is a mountain of debt.
Harper:
Do you trust that man?
Sam:
Sometimes, I don't
know who to trust.
But I do know
one thing for sure.
You're not my sister.
So who are you
and where did you come from?
Savannah:
I've been trying to think
how I can prove to you
I've traveled through time,
but all I have is this.
"Guys, help.
I'm stuck in 1930.
I'm trying my best
pretending to be Daisy."
Daisy's my sister's name.
Griffin:
You have to go to school
to maintain cover as Harper.
Mrs. Roth:
You got every single question
on the quiz wrong.
It's not like you at all!
The truth is,
I'm not who you think I am.
I'm sorry, it's just‐‐
It's‐‐ It's‐‐ It's a lot
to process. So...
So‐‐ So you're saying
that you and your friend,
Harper‐‐
We've both used your machine.
And not just us,
Daisy too.
It says here she's stuck
in the future.
And if Harper's
trapped in 1930‐‐
That means
they're both in trouble.
Exactly.
Which is why
you really need
to get back to work
on that invention
of yours.
Whoa, whoa, hold on.
Now, even if all this is true,
it doesn't change the fact
that my... invention
isn't working now.
Yeah, but you're so close.
You must be.
Caroline: Savannah,
are you in there?
I need help with dinner.
Sure, I'll just
be a minute!
No, no, no. No, no.
You go help your mother.
Look, I'm just gonna
finish up here,
and then I'll,
uh, head down
to the basement
and I'll take a look
at that‐‐
‐Time machine.
‐Yeah.
I think I have an idea
to get it up and running.
Cool! I'll see you
in the basement after dinner.
Whoa. What's that?
Found it
in the springs.
Guess it's some kind
of weird rock.
Not like
any rock I've seen.
Maybe it's from space.
Definite alien vibes.
Could be.
Why don't you guys
do some research?
Oh, no! We broke it.
What do you mean,
you're not who I think
you are?
I just meant I'm...
not as smart
as you thought I was.
I get it.
There's a lot of pressure
on kids these days.
If you'd done the reading,
the quiz
should've been easy.
I know.
And I'll do better
next time, really.
You're one
of my best students,
Harper,
which is why
I'm gonna allow you
to take a makeup quiz
tomorrow.
This time,
come prepared.
‐Fair?
‐Yes, ma'am. Very fair.
Hey, nice save.
So listen,
I've been thinking‐‐
No, Griffin.
I can't do this anymore!
I'm a nervous wreck.
Every second I stay here
is just another chance
I'll get caught,
and then what?
But you've been doing
so great.
Great?
Until this morning,
I didn't even know
we had 50 states.
Alaska and Hawaii,
when did that happen?
I don't know.
A while ago.
Look, I was thinking about
what you said earlier.
Topher told you
he was sleepwalking?
Yes. He woke up this morning
covered in mud.
Said something
about eating worms.
‐Worms?
‐Yeah.
See, that's pretty weird,
even for him.
He's gotta be
hiding something.
The crystal?
Griffin, I told you.
I already searched
his room.
You said
you were interrupted.
Yes! And I was almost caught.
It's too risky.
Look, do you wanna
go home or not?
(theme music playing)
Look who it is.
Good afternoon, kids.
Afternoon.
Doing
a little shopping, I see.
Miss Landry's
famous beignets.
Must be
a special occasion.
Mother's favorite.
Papa treats us sometimes.
Your father's
a fine man.
I just wish
he'd let me help him
with your... situation.
We don't need your help.
We just want the farm
to stay in our family.
Well, of course,
you do.
But that's what
I want too.
If only someone
could get your father
to listen to reason
and sign these.
I'll talk to him.
Smart girl.
Let's work together.
Save your sweet mother's farm
before it's too late.
Why'd you take
those papers?
Because if I didn't‐‐
I have a reason, okay?
More of a feeling,
actually.
A feeling?
I wish I could explain.
So why can't you?
We tell each other
everything.
Or at least we used to
before you started acting
so strange.
Sam...
(distortion)
Oh, my gosh.
The judge...
He's really gonna do it.
foreman:
Nail it down good.
The deck is rotten through.
‐Nice.
‐You got it.
Uh, hi.
You in charge here?
I am.
Are you the owner?
Depends. You about
to hand me a bill?
Actually, someone's already
taken care of that.
That would be me.
Bennett Campbell.
Appreciate
the business, sir.
We never worked a job
in Sulphur Springs before.
Really?
Where are you from?
Waller City,
about 100 miles
north of here.
Heard you guys are having
some plumbing issues.
Mind if I take a peek?
Go right ahead.
Dad, this is generous,
but you should've
talked to us first.
Oh. Oh,
I'm sorry, Bennett.
I thought we covered that.
When? You just got here.
Come here.
There's something
I wanna show you.
What do you think
about a parking garage
right over there?
Once this place takes off,
all those guests are gonna have
to have some place
to park, right?
I guess so.
Yeah. And that's‐‐
that's only the beginning.
Once this hotel
is done, Bennett,
trust me,
everyone in town
will forget
all about
that ridiculous
ghost business.
Dad!
Oh. Ugh.
Dad, are you okay?
Better me than a guest.
Looks like I got here
just in time.
(objects rattling)
(rattling continues)
Hello?
Whoever's there,
I'm under legal obligation
to warn you
these hands
are lethal weapons.
(screams)
What're you doing
in there?
I could've
seriously hurt you!
What's going on in here?
Harper was snooping
through my stuff again.
No, I wasn't.
I was just, uh‐‐
Planning to do my laundry?
No, you don't understand.
Then maybe
you should explain.
First, I get a call
from Mrs. Roth
telling me
you failed a quiz.
And now this?
I'm sorry, Mother‐‐
Mom, I, uh‐‐
Harper, what is going on?
I know you haven't been
sleeping well.
Or is it something
at school?
Baby, just talk to me.
I wish I could.
I can't.
Dad, hey, have you seen
Topher around?
Not since yesterday.
Have you asked the twins?
They're not
in their rooms.
Yeah, maybe check
the springs.
‐The springs?
‐Yeah.
Yeah, I found
this crazy‐looking rock
in the water earlier
and gave it to 'em.
They're probably down there
looking for more.
Crazy‐looking rock, huh?
Yeah, I was
kind of hoping
it'd be a distraction
from ghost‐busting,
but I guess we'll...
see.
Just tell me
where it is, okay?
Haven't you ever
heard of "finders keepers"?
Come on,
you didn't find anything.
Dad gave it to you.
Exactly.
Which makes it mine.
Ours.
Zoey:
Why do you want it so bad?
I just...
I just do, okay?
Must be
really valuable.
Definitely alien.
And don't even think
about looking for it,
because I found
the ultimate hiding place.
If you want your own,
why don't you come in
and look for it?
Because I'm running
out of time, that's why!
Zoey: Whatever.
Let's keep looking.
(phone ringing)
Great news!
Wyatt and Zoey
have the crystal.
That's wonderful!
So they'll give it
to you, right?
Griffin:
Clearly, you don't know
my brother and sister.
No, they're hiding it
somewhere.
Oh, my!
Any idea where?
‐(door closes)
‐Griffin: Not yet.
But as soon as we find it,
we're heading straight
to the bunker.
‐Meet me at The Tremont.
‐I'll be right there.
Everything the judge said
is right here.
Man of his word.
‐You okay with this, Daisy?
‐Sam: No, I'm not!
Please don't sign, Papa.
This land
is all we have left
of Mother.
Sam, listen to me.
Your mother's
always gonna be with us
wherever we go.
You know that,
right?
Then why does this feel
so wrong?
I know this is hard but‐‐
Why should I believe
anything you say?
Because I'm telling
the truth.
If Papa doesn't sign
those papers...
‐Remember that vision
I was telling you about?
‐Yeah?
I've been having
more of them.
And each time,
it's been about a fire.
Someone's going to burn down
our home, Sam.
‐I can feel it.
‐Who?
Judge Walker?
Remember the other day
when he hinted
that something could
go wrong?
Some kind of accident.
‐You really think he'd‐‐
‐Yes!
That's why I need you
to trust me on this.
So what's
the big wire for?
Power.
Lots of it.
I'm just hoping
it doesn't overload
the capacitor bank.
It's been an issue
in the past.
Cool.
‐Hey, Sam.
‐Yeah.
Do you hate it here?
Now why would you ask me
a question like that?
I guess I just know
what it's like
to want to run away.
And you are building
this machine.
So you think I wanna
run away too?
Am I right?
I used to.
Studied hard,
got an engineering degree,
and a big job
lined up in Boston.
So why'd you come back?
The springs.
After my mother got sick,
she used to soak in them
for hours.
Believed they had
healing properties
that came from
these little guys
right here.
So it's true?
The crystal
has magical powers?
Energy.
It didn't save her life,
but it might have extended it.
Now I'm trying to use it
to power this contraption.
Dedicated the last
18 years to it.
Wow.
So where are you gonna go
when it finally works?
Far into the future,
to a time where they had
a cure for what took her.
And with any luck,
that crystal
might save her life yet.
So what do you say,
you wanna give it another try?
(radio whirring)
Oh, my gosh!
It's working!
How much longer
is this going to take?
I've got five cases
of melting Nutt‐O Bars
in the deep‐freeze.
Any minute,
Miss Caroline.
And you.
How many times
have I told you
to stay out
of this man's hair?
What? I'm helping!
The best assistant
I ever had.
Well, she's
the only assistant
I ever had.
Might be good for her
to learn the ins and outs
of this place,
you know, in case
I'm not around
one of these days.
Now, Sam,
why would she do that?
It's not like you're
leaving anytime soon.
I appreciate
the hospitality, Elijah.
Beignets were
as delicious as always.
Least we can do,
considering how much
you're helping us out
with the farm.
I like to assist when I can.
So what do you say
we get down to business?
Everything all right?
Everything's fine, Judge.
Just fine.
Come on, we have to hurry
if we're gonna find the crystal
before Wyatt and Zoey
get back from the springs.
Any idea
where it could be?
No, but... it can't be
that hard to find.
I mean, Wyatt's hiding spots
tend to be kind of lame.
Topher?
Oh. Hey, guys.
What's up?
What're you
doing here?
Me? What are you
I live here.
Okay. Valid point.
Th‐‐ This place
is a mess!
‐What're you looking for?
‐Uh, I...
Why were you
going through my closet?
Don't change the subject.
You told me you were
sleepwalking last night.
What were you really doing?
Could you rephrase
the question, please?
‐Topher...
‐Fine!
I took the crystal,
but it was a huge mistake.
That thing is cursed.
Cursed?
Weird things
kept happening.
We need to put it
back where it belongs.
That's what we want too.
Then we're all
out of luck.
I've been through
this whole room,
and it's not here.
So let's check
Wyatt's room.
Not in there either.
I have a lot
of cleaning up to do.
So what do we do now?
I don't know.
(sighs)
Oh, a long day, huh?
Would've been a lot longer
without that crew you hired.
You sure
you don't wanna
ice that ankle?
Oh, no,
it's just a scrape.
It's fine.
Hey, listen, Dad, uh...
Sorry, if I didn't seem
more... appreciative earlier.
It means a lot to me that
we're doing this together.
That's good to hear,
Bennett.
Now we just
have to figure out
a way to brighten up
this whole fire trap.
‐Yeah.
‐It's depressing.
(bulbs exploding)
What was that?
Probably another power surge.
Have to get that contractor
before he leaves.
This place
is a disaster.
(radio whirs)
(radio powers down)
Doesn't make any sense.
There should be
more than enough power.
Maybe try another cable.
There's more in the barn.
No, no, it just‐‐
It doesn't work, that's all.
I should've known better.
But you can't
give up!
Harper needs us!
Your sister needs‐‐
(shouts):
There's no point!
(softly): I'm sorry, okay?
It's not your fault.
You‐‐ You're a kid.
Guess I just wanted to believe
that crazy imagination of yours.
‐Sam, please...
‐No.
No, your mother's right.
From now on,
just stay out of my hair.
(shouts):
Why won't you work?
(radio whirring)
I'm on my way,
Harper.
‐Savannah!
‐Got your note.
Figured you could use
a lift home.
I can't believe it's you!
I can't believe
you got stuck here!
What have you been doing?
Pretending to be
my great‐grandmother.
It's been so crazy.
I cooked
this terrible dinner.
I milked a goat.
Then I kept having
these visions
of this horrible judge
burning down the house.
Whoa!
You milked a goat?
Yes, an actual goat.
Did you not hear
the part about the visions?
Oh, no.
‐What is it?
‐I don't know.
But go. Now!
(loudly):
Papa, something's happening.
I really think
you should come out here.
Good afternoon, Sheriff.
Something I can
help you with?
Elijah Tremont?
Yes.
According to your agreement
with Judge Emmet Walker,
you are hereby ordered
to vacate this property
within 48 hours.
Elijah:
Vacate?
No, no, Sheriff,
there must be some mistake.
The judge and I have
an agreement.
And that agreement's
in your hand.
If I was you,
I'd start packing...
now.
Think...
where else could it be?
I don't know,
but Zoey and Wyatt
are gonna be back
any minute.
(sighs)
Hey, uh, Topher,
I just had an idea.
Uh, do you think
you could go down
and stall the twins
for a bit?
You know, give us
more time to search?
I guess so. Sure.
I can't do this anymore,
Griffin.
Every time
I think we're close,
something happens.
I might as well accept it.
I am never going home.
Actually,
I... think you might.
What do you mean?
I mean, I...
think I'm sitting
on Wyatt's hiding place.
Oh, my goodness!
I've never been
so happy to see anything
in my whole life!
Me either. I‐‐
‐Is that a crack?
‐A crack?
This jagged line
right here.
That wasn't there before?
No, it wasn't.
Harper:
Next time on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
Your family can't let
that slimy judge win.
Harper:
We have to stop him.
Judge Emmet:
You got the document
for their farm?
associate:
If you mean the original.
I'm not sure I can leave.
What? No!
You have to switch back.
Zoey:
This is... new.
Topher: It's the ghost
sending a message
loud and clear.
(Bennett Sr. yelps)
Topher:
Put the rock back now...
(electronics going haywire)
‐Or else...
‐Fire!
Savannah!
Are you down there?