Harper:
Previously on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
For the first time in my life,
I have a mom and dad
who love me.
I can't leave here.
I just had an idea.
This was inside
an old coffee can
Savannah and I used
to pass messages.
She's out there
just living her life.
Change of plans, Griff.
We decided to stay.
Harper:
Don't you ever think about
what things would be like
if Dad hadn't died
in that crash?
Wouldn't it be amazing
if we could go back
and change things?
Of course it would.
Hey, what's up?
You need some help?
Before I know it,
I'm flying over the handlebars,
and I'm thinking,
"Where did that
dumb log come from?"
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down now.
So where's the bike?
Left it by the creek.
Bent frame.
Chain's in a knot.
I was wondering
if I could get
a ride back into town.
Didn't your daddy ever tell you
not to accept rides
from strangers?
Actually, you're
not really a stranger.
Uh, my mom knows your wife.
You're Mr. Dunn, right?
My dad's Mr. Dunn.
You can call me Chris.
- And you are?
- Marie... Granger.
Marie?
That's my mother's name.
How about that?
Hop on in, Marie Granger.
Oh, you really don't want
to take Bayou Road.
I don't?
It's closed up ahead.
You should take
Sugar Hill instead.
It's faster too.
If you insist.
I come out here every Sunday.
Drive around
the old Tremont property.
Don't tell anyone,
but I'm planning to buy it.
You are?
I mean, that old place?
Why... Why would you
want to buy The Tremont?
The land was owned
by my family for generations,
even before it was a hotel.
Just a farm back then.
Sugar cane mostly.
- Look out!
- (horn blaring)
(sighs in relief)
That was close.
Thanks.
Guess it's what I'm here for.
Oh, there's Sugar Hill.
(theme music playing)
♪
(rock music playing)
(both continue playing)
(Ben playing uptempo riff)
Ooh!
Ooh, hoo-hoo.
- Woo!
- Yay!
You're really good, Dad.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Yeah, it feels like forever.
Okay, check this out.
Prepare to be amazed.
(playing rock riff)
(playing off-key)
Gah! Dang!
I always mess up there.
'Course when you're on a stage
in front of a bunch of campers
and your father...
Is that the same song
you won the trophy for?
Yeah, with the same mistake
and all.
I still have no idea how I won.
You know, maybe
they stuffed the ballot box.
I remember thinking
the exact same thing.
Well, it's good old
Camp Tremont.
You know, I had a dream
about it last night.
I was 12.
Everything was
exactly the same except...
you were there.
Me? Uh... really?
Yeah. We were hanging out
in one of the bunkhouses,
and talking about...
I don't know, who-knows-what.
Then I woke up.
Hmm. That's...
It's weird.
Yeah, it kinda was.
I hope I'm not keeping you
from your family.
My dad said he'd be here soon.
No worries.
I've got some time
till we go out to the lake.
The... the lake?
My other Sunday tradition.
When the weather's nice,
I take the family
for a picnic.
Thought it'd be the perfect time
for me to tell them
about my plan
to buy the place.
- Your wife doesn't know?
- No.
I didn't want
to get her hopes all up
until I had the money
to get it started.
It's going to be
such a great place
for the kids.
So, how old are your kids?
Well, there's Harper.
She's four.
And Toph is three.
Harper's my little artist,
and Topher, he's turning
into the family comedian.
So the idea is to move
into The Tremont
when you buy it?
I used to work summers
at the hotel when I was a kid.
It's where I met my wife.
Jess.
She was a camper,
and I'd help out
the bellhops
or whoever else that needed me.
Heard The Tremont has a ghost.
Hoo-hoo-hoo, yeah.
Savannah Dillon?
(chuckles)
Hmm. Don't tell me
you believe that stuff.
Oh, well, I did.
I mean, I used to.
Listen, I've been
through that whole hotel.
I didn't find any ghost.
But that car of mine?
'67 GTO.
Restored it soup to nuts.
And when I sell it,
that'll be the money
I use for my down payment.
Sorry. Like you care
about any of this.
No. It's really cool.
I definitely care.
- What?
- It's... it's just funny.
You remind me
so much of my daughter.
Oh, no.
Not an artistic bone
in my body.
Hmm.
Well, I should get back
to the tribe.
I don't want to be late.
You sure your dad is on his way?
Be here any second.
It was really nice
meeting you, Marie.
Um...
Um, it was just a ride.
Uh, I know. Sorry.
I just get silly sometimes.
Well, Miss Silly Marie,
I'm guessing we'll be
running into each other again.
Counting on it.
Wyatt?
Where are you?
- What are you doing?
- Shh.
It started rocking...
all by itself.
Come here.
Sit down.
Watch.
- I really don't think...
- Shh.
You're gonna scare it.
(creaking)
Just like before.
Savannah...
is it you?
(eerie music playing)
I think I'm gonna need my hat.
- Hey!
- Oh!
There you are.
- How did you find me?
- I was looking for you.
To tell you that
we're not moving,
after all.
And then I noticed
that the tumblers
on the radio
were set to 2011.
The year that your dad died.
I saved him, Griffin.
I saved my father
from the car accident.
That...
That's... That's incredible.
How?
What happened?
I got in his car with him.
There was this truck
headed right for us.
I warned him,
and he avoided the wreck.
We took a short cut into town.
And then we had coffee
at my mom's place.
Only it wasn't Dunn's.
It was some other name.
But get this!
My dad's dream
was to buy The Tremont.
And why?
Because it was in his family
years and years ago.
But how could you not know this?
I mean, before now.
My mom never talked about it.
Maybe she didn't know.
He was planning
to surprise her
the day he died.
I know what you're thinking.
You're worried.
I messed with destiny,
changed things.
But I'm telling you, Griffin,
when we get back,
my dad will still be alive,
waiting at home for me.
And everything
will be all right.
You'll see.
We're going to find
a whole new world up there.
(door opens)
It's all the same.
Okay, then he didn't buy it.
Probably bought
the coffee shop instead.
He'll be at home.
Harper, come on.
I mean, what if he...
Why are you doubting this?
For once, why can't you
just be happy for me?
Dad?
(footsteps approach)
Did you just say, "Dad"?
Yes, I did.
Yeah. I've been thinking
about him too.
Today's the anniversary of...
the accident.
(door closes)
(knocking on door)
Topher:
Harper...
you okay?
Yeah, Toph, I'm fine.
I just need some time.
(melancholy music playing)
♪
(sniffling)
(music intensifies)
(music continues)
- Shh.
- You'll scare it.
Scare what?
And why
is this rocking chair
in my room?
We brought it in
to keep an eye on it.
This is a stake-out.
There's a ghost.
Guys, come on,
I thought we were done
with all this ghost stuff.
- We saw the chair rock.
- Twice.
In Mom and Dad's room.
By itself.
- Savannah?
- We thought that too.
But when we asked,
"Are you Savannah?"
It wrote on the mirror again.
Wrote what?
N-O.
Noooo.
So we think it's someone else.
Someone who likes
rocking chairs.
Sit with us.
Help us watch.
But just so you know,
it only comes out...
when you're really...
really quiet.
Topher:
Harper, wait!
What are you talking about?
I remembered.
It all came back.
What?
Our dad didn't die
on Bayou Road.
It wasn't a car accident.
Oh, my poor baby.
We were at the lake.
Our canoe went over.
I held on, but Dad didn't.
And I blocked it all out,
didn't I?
The whole day. All of it.
Yes, baby, you did.
The doctors...
They said not to tell you,
not to force things,
that it would all
come back on its own.
But you told me
it was a car accident.
Oh, sweetie,
you woke up one morning
and you said
it was a car accident.
And for the first time
in forever, you seemed so...
at peace.
I figured it was
the closure you needed.
That's why you always said
The Tremont was cursed.
Because that's where
we lost him.
In that lake,
on The Tremont property.
And after that,
I never wanted
either of you
anywhere near that place.
Because bad things happen there.
Did you know
it was Dad's dream
to buy it?
I knew it had been
in his family,
that he liked
to go out there, but...
buy The Tremont?
- No, he never told me that.
- He was gonna fix it up.
Move in.
Baby, how could you
possibly know that?
I don't know.
Maybe I made that up too.
Whatever happened
to his yellow convertible?
I sold it.
For a down payment
on the coffee shop.
It's where we had
our first date.
And a lot of dates after that.
You okay, baby?
Yeah, I am.
I am now.
Finally, it all makes sense.
(Wyatt sighs)
I'm hungry.
Can you watch it
while we go get
something to eat?
If you make me something too.
Peanut butter and jelly?
Yeah, that works.
Great. It's the only thing
we know how to make.
(rocking chair creaks)
(tense music playing)
(music continues)
Harper?
I... I tried reaching you...
Your dad's still gone.
He didn't die in a car accident.
My mother just told me.
After it happened,
I blocked it out.
Came up with the car accident.
But... what actually happened...
was he drowned.
The same day but later.
So even if I wanted
to go back, it's too late.
I'm sorry.
Griffin, I started
to think about it,
all you've said.
No, no. I...
I shouldn't have.
I should have just
kept my mouth shut.
But you were right.
We can't change things.
And we shouldn't try to,
ever again.
The truth is...
my father died so I could live.
He died saving me.
That's what was
supposed to happen.
Maybe we should close it up.
Yeah.
(whooshing)
It's cold.
Do you feel that?
Where did those come from?
Oh, the rocking chair upstairs.
It was rocking by itself
and then
whatever was rocking in it
came down here.
Wet footprints.
My father died in a lake.
(objects clattering)
- (Griffin exclaiming)
- Hey, guys.
- Miss me?
- Griffin: Savannah!
You said you were never
coming through the portal,
that you've found your family.
I know. I know.
But then I found this.
Looks like you're not done
time traveling either.
(intense music playing)
My folks had me
clearing out
this storage room.
It was sealed
in an envelope
in a crack in the wall,
I'm guessing, by you.
Griffin:
W-Wait, back up.
Savannah:
What are you not
understanding?
It's like what we did
with the coffee can.
You did the same thing.
Went back to 1930,
put on those clothes,
got your picture taken,
and then left it for us to find.
But why?
Why would I go back to 1930?
Maybe because The Tremont
is in your family.
It has to be connected somehow.
Well, there's only one way
to find out.
I mean... unless you have
somewhere else to go.
As long as we're home
before dinner.
We'll pick up clothes
on the other side
so we don't stick out.
This is really cool.
Yeah. Finally, an adventure
that doesn't involve
saving you.
So that's how you do it.
How did you
ever figure that out?
It was really weird.
We're still not
exactly sure
how it works.
We might've gotten
a little help
from the other side.
So a ghost that's not me.
- Who do you think it is?
- It could be anyone.
I followed
those wet footprints
down to the basement.
It's like it was reaching out,
like it was pointing the way.
This is really spooky,
but, like, good kind of spooky.
All set. 1930.
(radio whirring.
Electricity crackling)
Harper: Let's go.
Wow!
Griffin:
Savannah, wait!
Ow!
(birds chirping)
There's no rust.
Welcome to 1930, guys.
So cool.
Epic.
(horse neighing)
(rooster crowing)
Remember, guys,
we're just here
to check it out.
Stay together and out of sight.
You guys see anything?
(sighs) Nothing.
It's too dark.
Maybe the door's unlocked.
Well, shouldn't we knock first?
Not dressed like this.
Whoa!
Where's the lobby?
Guess it was added later
when they turned
this place into a hotel.
(jazz music playing)
Where's that music coming from?
Let's go.
(music continues)
That's the radio
from the bunker.
Well...
what do we do now?
(creaking overhead)
(footsteps)
Upstairs.
(tense music playing)
(floorboard creaks)
- Go, go, go, go!
- Griffin: Hurry up!
Go!
- (Harper gasps)
- (gasps)
♪ There's a place
in Louisiana ♪
♪ Under sugar maple shade ♪
♪ Full of fun and games
and laughter ♪
♪ Where our best
friendships are made ♪
♪ Our hearts and minds
will always stay ♪
♪ Here at dear Camp Tremont ♪
(girl screaming)