Harper:
Previously on Secrets
of Sulphur Springs...
Who are you guys?
I'd know it
if you were campers.
Uh, I'm Harry
and this is...
Um, Hermione.
Griffin:
My dad said
he didn't know Savannah.
He lied to me.
It's every place
we felt a cold spot.
In the kitchen,
in the dining room.
There's a room
behind this wall.
A secret room?
Ben:
Probably boarded-up
years ago.
(girl singing on recorder)
* Under sugar maple shade *
-(Ben exclaims)
-(music stops)
Griffin:
Dad's been lying.
He knew Savannah.
You got all this from Harper,
didn't you?
You and Harper
need to take a break.
Is that where you were today?
The Tremont?
Did you used to go
to camp there?
(scoffs)
Of course not.
You're wasting your time
on that freaky Savannah.
You must be new.
I'm Jessica,
but everyone calls me Jess.
Harper:
My mother flat-out said
she never went to camp.
She's covering something up.
Just like your dad.
(door creaking)
Griffin:
How are we gonna
save Savannah?
(door creaking)
Harper:
She's here.
Maybe we should
just throw it out?
No, no.
I can save it.
I just need...
Griffin. Perfect guy
for the job.
We'll put this thing
right in no time.
Won't we, bud?
All right.
I'll let you two guys
get to it.
(phone chimes)
Actually, now's not
a really good time.
Come on, Griff.
Let's show your mom
we can do this on our own.
It'll only take a minute.
What do you need?
Hold this straight
while I secure the base.
Looks good, huh?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Can I go?
Yeah, yeah.
(vehicle approaching)
Grandpa!
(chuckles)
Griffin.
What are you
doing here, Dad?
Better question, son.
What are you doing here?
Hey, go grab my bags
out of the car,
would you, Griffin?
I-- I would,
but I got to go.
Griffin,
help your grandfather,
though I can't imagine
he'll be staying long.
I'll stay as long as it takes
to talk some sense into you.
You shouldn't be here,
Bennett.
None of you should.
(theme music playing)
(objects clattering)
Wyatt:
It's not in here.
It has to be.
Look harder.
(clattering continues)
(door creaking)
-Wyatt.
-I'm looking!
(whooshing)
-Got it.
-(floorboard creaking)
(all scream)
You guys scared me.
We scared you?
Zoey:
Uh, what are
you doing here?
I thought you couldn't
come over anymore.
I snuck in to hang out
with Griffin.
What are
you doing down here?
No one else believes us
about Savannah's ghost.
So we're gonna catch her
on camera.
Just got to figure out
how it works.
Think it needs
a little cassette in there.
My brother's a geek
for that kind of stuff.
He can explain it better.
You should go find him.
You guys aren't supposed
to be down here.
Neither are you.
We won't tell Mom and Dad
if you don't.
Okay fine.
-(footsteps receding)
-(door closes)
You don't think
they found the bunker?
No, but it'll ruin everything
if they did.
We have
to be more careful.
-Are you ready?
-Definitely.
We have to go back
and find out exactly what
our parents are hiding.
And fast.
When we felt Savannah's ghost
in your room last night,
I think it was her way
of urging us on, you know?
-Like she
wanted us to hurry.
-I know what you mean.
We don't have
much time though.
My grandpa just
randomly showed up,
and now we have to have
family dinner tonight.
You can't get out of it?
No way.
With my grandpa
being here,
my dad is acting
even weirder than usual.
I just don't get it.
As a kid, he was so chill.
What happened to him?
Why do you have
to be so bratty?
How can you be
so selfish?
Savannah:
I'm not being selfish.
I'm having fun.
You should try it sometime.
Jess:
Well, sorry if
my idea of fun
doesn't involve
stealing punch
and throwing it
around springs.
I mean, what if
you attracted
grizzly bears here?
Grizzlies?
In Louisiana?
Whatever!
You're going to keep
getting in trouble,
and you're going
to get Ben kicked out.
Ben can do what he wants,
and so can I.
Just because you act like
you're in charge
of everyone here, Jess,
it doesn't mean
you actually are.
Whoa, was that your mom?
Yeah.
She's a lot different now.
Griffin:
I'll go find my dad.
See if I can get him
talking about Savannah.
And I'll ask Jess.
I mean... my mom.
(exhales)
Man, this is so strange.
Tell me about it.
Do you think
she'll talk to you?
Don't worry.
I have a strategy.
Yeah.
Remember,
keep it subtle.
Way ahead of you.
(playing rock guitar riff)
Harry, what's up?
Get kicked out
of the hotel yet?
Not yet.
Why? You and Savannah
need help on your next prank?
As soon as we plan one,
we'll let you know.
What about
the camp dance?
You're probably
going together, right?
Nah.
Sorry. I thought
you liked her.
I mean, sure I like her.
Savannah's different,
you know?
Of course,
not everyone appreciates that.
Hey, you doing okay, Jess?
Do I not look okay?
Oh, no. You do.
I just-- I, uh--
I saw you and Savannah
fighting outside.
It was hardly a fight.
It was Savannah being
her usual obnoxious self.
Yeah, she was
pretty awful to you.
I know, right?
She thinks she's so cool but
it's so fake.
I can't believe
Ben doesn't see it.
Are you, um...
Are you jealous
of her and Ben?
Jealous?
Of Little Orphan Annie?
Please.
I just think
this place would be
a whole lot nicer
if she'd just...
like... go away.
(continues guitar riff)
What song is that?
Uh, just something
I've been working on.
You wrote that?
Uh, yeah.
I'm supposed to be practicing
for the talent show tomorrow.
My dad's coming,
and he wants me to play
something boring
and "classical."
I don't know.
(sighs)
I'd rather play
my own thing, you know?
Then you totally should.
That song you were playing
was awesome.
Really?
-Yeah.
-Thanks.
Uh, well, of course,
I actually need
to finish it first.
Uh, want to help?
-Yeah.
-Awesome.
(playing riff)
My mom was
definitely jealous
of Savannah.
Did you get
anything out of Ben?
Um, not a lot.
He showed me a song
he was working on, though.
I got to help with it.
Like actually helped
write it.
It was so cool finally getting
to play guitar with my dad.
Griffin! We're not here
to make friends
with our parents.
We're supposed
to save Savannah.
Yeah, I know that.
But Ben doesn't really seem
to be hiding anything.
We know he is.
Why else would your dad
be lying to us back at home?
Your mom lied too.
Which is why
I'm taking it seriously
when I question her
and not just giggling
over music together.
Ben and I didn't giggle.
You're just mad
that my dad, as a kid, is fun
and your mom,
as a kid, is...
kind of the worst.
We better get back.
Wouldn't want you
to miss dinner
with your fun dad.
(sighs)
Sarah:
I would have
fixed up the guest room
had I known
you were coming, Bennett.
-I hope it's okay.
-Oh, I'll make do.
Griffin,
we've been waiting for you.
Where have you been?
Just, uh...
Just doing homework.
All afternoon?
Good man, Griffin.
Study hard, rise to the top,
and do important things.
It's the Campbell way.
At least it was
until recently.
I am doing something
important here, Dad.
Don't you remember
what this place
used to be like?
All too well.
I'm worried that you're the one
with the faulty memory, Bennett.
You know, it's not too late
for you to go back to Chicago.
I can always get you
reinstated at the firm.
-You were doing so well.
-Ben: Dad.
Enough.
Kids, what are you
hiding under there?
We found it.
Hey, Grandpa,
you're really old.
Do you know how
to find something
called a cassette?
Wyatt!
-I am so sorry.
-It's okay.
So what are you hoping
to record with that thing?
-A ghost.
-Ah.
Savannah's ghost.
Savannah?
How many times
do I have to tell you
we're done talking
about ghosts?
You didn't say much
at dinner.
-What's going on?
-It's just...
Why are boys
so frustrating?
You talking about
any frustrating boy
in particular?
I hope it's not one
who lives in a certain hotel
that I most definitely
asked you to stay away from.
No, it's not Griffin.
Just...
boys in general...
can be so...
immature.
(chuckles)
Yeah, I remember
what that's like.
Come here.
Boys can make
you feel like you're crazy,
especially when
you have a crush.
Did your first crush
make you crazy?
If you count filling up
two notebooks
of Mariah Carey lyrics...
-(Harper chuckles)
-...then yes.
Um... How did it end?
Was it bad?
It ended the way
all crushes do,
with someone
getting crushed.
(door opens)
-(footsteps approach)
-(door closes)
Hey, Grandpa,
can I ask you something?
Yeah, sure.
Why are you so mad
at Dad for coming back
to Sulphur Springs?
Well...
I've always wanted
what was best for your father,
and sometimes we disagree
on what that is.
You think this place
is bad for my dad?
How come?
Well, look at it.
It's nothing but
a pile of old wood
and bad memories
sitting in
a backwater swamp.
No place for a Campbell
to end up.
Bad memories?
What kind of bad memories?
The past
belongs in the past.
Best to leave it there.
(tense music playing)
♪*♪
Wyatt:
There he is!
(door bell jingles)
Topher, we heard
you were the guy to see
to get this thing to work.
-You heard right.
-Great.
The sooner we get
Savannah's ghost on camera,
the better.
That's what the camera's for?
Your funeral.
Okay, now,
here's what you gotta do.
Sarah!
I see
you didn't take my advice
to get your family
out of that deathtrap
of a hotel.
Well, with my husband's
fix-it skills,
we've officially upgraded
from deathtrap to money pit.
Look, I know that
you asked Harper
to stay away from Griffin.
It's nothing personal.
Just protecting my daughter.
I completely understand.
It seems those two
are a bad influence
on each other.
I think it makes sense
to keep them apart,
at least for now.
Hmm. Might me easier to do
if there are two of us
keeping an eye out.
I'm glad
we're on the same page.
-I'm sorry, I--
-I was thinking--
Uh, look, I think
we can both agree
-yesterday was
kind of a bust.
-Yeah.
No matter what happens,
it's better when
we work together.
-As a team.
-Exactly!
And we definitely
still have work to do
if we really wanna find out
what our parents are hiding.
I wish we could
go back now.
How are we gonna
sit around all day,
learning about mitochondria
and eating bologna sandwiches
-when Savannah's life
is on the line?
-We're not!
I just paid Topher 30 bucks
to drop off notes
to the front office
saying we're sick.
So, are you ready?
(indistinct chatter)
What is this?
Griffin:
It must be that talent show.
Man:
Nice job!
Wow, what a talent!
Uh, next up...
Let's welcome
guitarist Ben Campbell
up to the stage,
playing Greensleeves.
I know I'm supposed to play
Greensleeves,
but instead,
here's something
I just finished writing.
(playing rock music)
(audience cheering)
(stops playing)
(playing discordant notes)
Let's give it up again
for Ben Campbell!
(light applause)
Hey, hey, hey-hey.
You think I got off work
and came all the way down here
to listen to you
play that... garbage?
Clearly, sending you
to this camp
was a mistake.
You embarrassed me today,
Bennett.
You embarrassed yourself.
Wow! Has your grandpa
always been that mean?
Not to me.
Guess I've never seen him
alone with my dad.
And our last performer
of the day will be...
Savannah Dillon.
♪ There's a place
in Louisiana ♪
This is the song I heard
in the secret room.
♪ Under sugar maple... ♪
It was Savannah singing.
♪ ...shade ♪
(upbeat music playing)
♪ There's songs
around the campfire ♪
♪ There's kites
around the lake ♪
♪ We're smiling busy campers ♪
This part's new!
♪ It's the greatest
summer getaway ♪
♪ Any kid could ever want ♪
♪ Our hearts and minds
will always say ♪
♪ You're a dear, Camp Tremont ♪
(audience cheering, applauding)
Well, that was unique.
Now it's time for everyone
to cast their ballots
for the winner.
I'm glad
Savannah's gonna win.
She deserves it.
But...
she's not gonna win,
my dad is.
I saw a picture of him
holding the trophy.
Maybe we changed things.
I did tell him
to play his own song.
Hiding from your dad?
Nope, just fixing a draft.
Why? He's not around,
is he?
(laughs) He's upstairs.
Uh, I didn't want
to get into this
in front of him,
but I think Griffin
might be hanging around
Harper again.
I spoke with Jess.
I wanted to let her know
that we're on the same page.
Did she say
anything else?
Not really. Why?
No reason.
You know, I don't think
this screwdriver
is the right size.
I'm gonna go
find another one.
(thudding)
What are you two up to?
This is where we felt
one of the cold spots.
We're gonna finally
catch that ghost in here.
I know it.
The only thing
there is to catch
in here is tetanus.
This area
is officially off limits.
Clear out.
(tense music playing)
(music intensifies)
All of your ballots
have been counted,
and the winner of
the camp talent show is...
Ben Campbell!
(hesitant applause)
Maybe it was destiny
for him to win,
no matter what.
Or maybe someone
rigged the results.
You really think
your mom cheated?
Man, she must really
like my dad!
Or really hate Savannah.
(tense music playing)
♪*♪
Ben:
Leaving already?
Well, it's clear
you won't be talked
out of this, uh, project.
I know
you may not believe this,
but everything I've done
is for your benefit.
I'm a grown man now.
I can make my own choices.
Yes, so I see.
Just remember, Bennett...
one of these days,
when your choices
land you in hot water,
I won't be there
to bail you out.
Thanks for dropping by, Dad.
Drive safe.
Hey, Griffin.
You stay
out of trouble now.
How much of that
did you hear?
-(door closes)
-Some.
My relationship
with your grandfather is...
(car engine starting)
is complicated.
You're probably too young
to understand.
I understand.
At least,
better than I used to.
Think I get it now.
Get what?
Why Grandpa
bothers you so much.
It's like...
he wants to be
in charge of what you do.
And maybe that's why
you brought us here.
'Cause you have
all these bad memories
you wish could be better.
Better get going
on your homework
before dinner.
You're quiet tonight.
Still upset
about the boys at school?
No. Now it's another girl
who's the problem.
Ah, yes.
Middle school boys
can be frustrating
but the girls?
(scoffs) They could be
downright cruel.
Don't I know it.
Topher,
why don't you go
set the table?
Last night, you were telling me
about how your first crush
drove you crazy.
Did you ever take it out
on anyone else?
Like another girl?
Harper, what is going on?
Is some girl bothering you?
No, not me.
Um, someone else I know.
I'm probably overreacting
anyway.
Most mean girls
are actually harmless, right?
Deep down?
I think you should
stay away from
girls like that.
It starts off as a game,
can become very real.
Griffin, my mom
might be worse than a liar.
I think she might've actually
done something to Savannah.
I don't know.
Rigging a talent show
is a long way from
disappearing somebody.
I didn't want
to believe it either
but think about it.
My mom
didn't just hate Savannah,
she acted on it
at the talent show.
And I think
she'll do it again.
(door opens)
Harper Marie,
do you have something
you need to tell me?
You skipped school today?
(door opens)
Griffin,
I just got off the phone
with your principal.
-You're grounded.
Get used to this bedroom,
Harper.
Because you're not
going anywhere.
(tense music playing)
♪*♪
Ben:
The last big camp event
of the summer.
Should be fun.
I don't know.
I was thinking
of skipping it.
Camp dances
are pretty lame, right?
Oh, yeah.
I guess they are.
This dance
isn't going to be lame.
You have to be there.
Trust me,
it'll be a night to...
remember.
(tense music playing)
Next time on Secrets
of Sulphur Springs...
Tonight's the anniversary
of Savannah's disappearance.
she'll be haunting this place
extra hard.
The camp dance starts at 8:00.
That gives us
less than five hours
to save her from...
Just say it, my mom.
-Going somewhere?
-I do have someplace to be.
-But you have to
really cover for me, okay?
-Done.
Jess: Hey, Hermione,
do you wanna come
to the dance with me tonight?
I can always use
a partner in... crime.
♪*♪