Harper:
Previously on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
Our names aren't
really Harry and Hermione.
‐I'm Griffin.
‐Harper.
For real?
What if I put the money
into the hotel?
50‐50 partner?
Harper:
You can rest easy now.
It's over.
The Tremonts are back
on the land.
You see it, right?
Griffin:
It came from the mirror.
Harper:
Her spirit's freed,
and there aren't
any more ghosts.
(door slams)
(whispering):
Sam, your time machine,
it works.
nurse: He disappeared
during the middle
of the night.
You wouldn't happen to know
where he is, would you?
Sam?
"I've gone on a journey
through time.
If I'm not back in three weeks,
destroy the radio."
The future.
I missed you
while you were gone.
Like... a lot.
I missed you too.
So, um...
Our parents are going all‐out
for this opening tonight.
Gift bags.
Theme party.
Heard there's
even a band.
Yeah, should, uh...
Should be fun.
Yeah.
I hate this.
We haven't
really hung out
in weeks.
It's not that
I don't want to,
it's just...
Things have just felt
kind of weird.
Maybe they wouldn't be
if we talked about
what happened that night.
You mean about
how‐‐ how we, uh...
‐you know, how, uh‐‐
‐Just say it.
We almost kissed.
Unfortunately,
we're all booked.
But if you want to leave
your contact information,
I can add you
to the wait‐list.
Great!
Hope to see you soon.
I hear that right?
There's a wait‐list?
Two pages long.
People are lining up
to stay here,
and the doors
aren't even open.
Guess the price
those contractors charged
‐to finish was worth it.
‐We are about to make
someone on that list
very happy.
Finally found the key
to 205.
Kids are
cleaning it out now.
Uh, but it has that draft.
We still haven't figured out
where that's coming from.
Eh, nothing an...
extra blanket can't fix
in the meantime, right?
Hi, this is Ben Campbell
from The Tremont.
As a matter of fact,
a room just became available.
Did you see this website?
It's about the opening.
Have you looked
at the comments?
"Always wanted to stay
in a haunted hotel."
"I can't wait
to see a ghost tonight."
The ghost left weeks ago.
We saw it happen.
Which means the opening
is probably gonna be
a bust.
Unless...
‐Where are you going?
‐To give the people
what they want.
(ominous music playing)
All I'm saying is
it's common for people
in stressful situations
to do things
they normally wouldn't.
Having to pretend
to be someone else
definitely qualifies
as stressful.
Daisy did her best,
but wearing your clothes
didn't make her you.
‐I mean, I could always tell.
‐Always?
‐Except for that one time
in the bunker.
‐Yeah, okay.
But that's only because
I was focused on
switching you back
before people got
too suspicious.
Sam knew
something was off
right away.
Would've had
to tell him the truth
if I was stuck
in the past much longer.
We can't risk
messing with time
like that again.
Too many things
could've changed.
And that's not
what we want.
Is it?
To change things?
We should, um...
We should get
these bags finished.
Right.
(theme music playing)
Mrs. Barker. Hi.
Harper...
from the cafe.
Is there something
we can help you with?
It might be a good idea
to let someone know
you're here.
You live at Shady Acres,
right?
Oh, uh, looks like
your ride just pulled up.
Don't do it.
‐Sorry, what?
‐Don't go forward.
It's time
to head back now,
Mrs. Barker.
Don't go forward?
She's just
a confused old woman.
Probably doesn't know
what she's saying.
Uh, what if she was talking
about the future?
Like, don't go forward
in time?
‐That would mean...
‐Mrs. Barker knows
about the portal.
‐(knock on door)
‐Come in.
‐Hey, Mom.
‐Lunch is almost ready.
Planning on
coming down soon?
I'm not really hungry.
Wherever Sam is,
I'm sure he's just fine.
We don't know that.
What if he needs help?
Honey, you have
such a big heart.
I know you're worried,
but it might be time
to accept Sam isn't
coming back.
He left weeks ago.
Three weeks ago.
Anything could've happened.
Or it's possible
Sam may not want
to be found.
We need to respect that.
I'll see you downstairs.
Don't do this to me, Sam.
Please come back.
(water bubbling)
Sure this is gonna
work?
This is my area
of expertise, remember?
Go ahead, try it.
Like I said,
instant ghost.
We've seen
what a real ghost
can do.
It's way creepier.
Patience, people.
I'm just getting started.
Something has been
drawing Mrs. Barker
to the hotel.
Now she warns us
about going into the future?
It can't be
a coincidence.
She never
actually said future,
you did.
What else could she have meant?
Any number of things.
For all we know,
Mrs. Barker was talking
to the driver of the van,
telling him
not to go forward.
She grabbed my arm,
Harper.
Stared me
right in the eye.
‐That warning was for us.
‐Okay.
Um, excuse me.
We're looking
for Mrs. Barker's room.
Visiting hours are over.
Oh, uh,
we won't stay long.
We just wanted
to bring this by for her.
It's souvenirs
from The Tremont's
grand opening party tonight.
We know how much
Mrs. Barker likes the hotel.
You can leave it
at the front desk.
Down the hall
to your right.
Thank you.
Well, that was a bust.
Harper:
Maybe not.
Mrs. Barker?
Remember us?
We saw you
at the Tremont earlier.
You gave us a warning.
What'll happen
if we do go forward?
Sounded like
you've seen it.
Griffin,
we need to leave.
Griffin: Mrs. Barker,
if you've been
to the future,
you can tell us,
we'll believe you.
You're not supposed
to be in here.
We were headed
to the desk
and saw Mrs. Barker.
Just figured
we'd drop this off
with her.
Mrs. Barker needs her rest.
I'll show you out.
Harry, Hermione,
it was good to see you again.
Savannah?
Harper: Mrs. Barker comes
into the cafe all the time.
I can't believe
I never recognized her.
Why would you?
I mean, Savannah's
like 70 now.
She's still
the same person, Griffin.
Something should've seemed,
you know, familiar.
Well, Savannah grew up.
She got married,
and she lived this whole life.
I mean, it'd be crazy
if she wasn't any different.
I mean, think about
how much our parents changed
from when they were kids.
That's true.
Hey.
What do you think
we'll be like
at their age?
Hmm...
Taller.
‐At least I better be.
‐(laughs)
Would we still
recognize each other if
we passed on the street?
Come on.
You know,
you're pretty unforgettable.
Locker ninja.
We have a problem.
Oh, if it's about the napkins,
I've already called‐‐
We have to close
the springs.
I was just down there
and‐‐
Knock, knock!
Allison!
Hi, uh,
good to see you again.
Allison is writing an article
for the local paper.
I hope you don't mind
the early check‐in.
Just wanted to get
a little preview
of the springs
before it gets too crowded.
Well, we, uh, have
just been so focused
on getting the hotel ready
that our landscaping plan
fell a little behind schedule.
‐Oh.
‐Which is why
we will be having
you back
for a second
complimentary stay
as soon as
the springs are open.
Here, let me grab
that bag for you.
Oh, don't forget
this one.
Just a little something
to help you settle in.
Thank you.
Ben: We have
a great room for you.
‐What happened?
‐The springs are a mess.
I mean, it smells like
the end of a week‐long
music festival.
Of course, they do.
Every new business
has its little hiccups,
especially during
the first week.
Probably won't be
the only thing
to go wrong tonight.
It has to be subtle.
You're talking
to the king of subtle.
Hey, guys.
The king, huh?
Mmm‐kay.
‐Done with 205?
‐Yep. All clean.
Except for the floor.
You know, I can't figure out
what this is.
Wouldn't have anything
to do with
whatever's hiding
behind your back, would it?
We were making slime
to scare the guests.
You really need to learn
when to stop talking.
Ben: We have a lot
riding on tonight.
It needs to go off
without a hitch,
‐which means no‐‐
‐(Allison screams)
Pranks.
That was set up
way before the slime.
Downstairs. Now!
When I was a little girl,
The Tremont meant summer camp
and brunch on Sundays.
Back then,
I never would've guessed
that one day I would have
my own restaurant here.
Or that my children
would be so deeply connected
to the history of this hotel
and this land.
The Tremont now represents
a rebirth for me,
for the next generation
of the Tremont family,
and for our dear friends,
the Campbells, as well.
Sarah:
Restoring the hotel
started as
my husband's project,
his passion,
but soon became
our family's lifeline.
Uh, this process nearly
broke us at times,
but, uh, it also built us
back up again.
We made so many
special memories here.
We hope you will too,
for generations to come.
It's our pleasure
to finally say...
all:
Welcome to The Tremont!
(all cheering)
(indistinct chatter)
(loudly):
Did you hear that strange
scraping noise last night?
It was coming from
across the hall.
Room 205, I think.
Strange scraping noise?
(quietly):
That's good. Keep it up.
(loudly): It sounded like
someone or something
was trying to get out.
Keep what up?
And why are you shouting?
I'm standing right here.
What part of
"we need to convince people
that this place is haunted"
do you not understand?
Dad said no more pranks.
Rumors weren't
taken off the table.
Is that...
Savannah?
(loudly):
Oh, my gosh!
It is her!
‐Look!
‐Over there.
(quietly):
Oh, my gosh.
It is her.
I take back
everything I said.
That was incredible.
How'd you
pull it off?
You'll have to be
more specific.
Savannah walking
through the lobby.
Wyatt:
Had to be a look‐alike.
Or maybe a hologram.
I'm good but not that good.
So you didn't
set anything up?
My mom already
grounded me for a week.
Not looking
to do hard time.
It really was a ghost.
Come on.
Why would Savannah risk
coming up here?
She wouldn't
unless something happened.
Split up.
The sooner we find her,
the better.
(distortion)
Griffin: (in distorted voice)
Help!
Is anyone there?
Please, don't leave me!
Savannah's not down here.
Let's check upstairs.
Harper, do you see her?
I saw you...
trapped in a fire.
I'm still not sure
how it actually works.
I mean, maybe the vision
doesn't mean anything.
I've been wrong before.
I'm not waiting around
to find out.
There must be a reason
Savannah warned us
not to go into the future.
I'm not asking you
to go with me.
Don't you know me
better than that by now?
If you go, I go.
‐Griffin: Savannah!
‐Thank goodness.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing
up here?
Sam went into the future
and hasn't come back yet.
The future?
2024.
He left me a note telling me
to destroy the radio
if he wasn't back
in three weeks.
‐That's tonight.
‐What's in 2024?
Sam was hoping to find
a cure for his mom.
But if I break the radio,
he won't be able to save her.
‐So what do I do?
‐Go home.
‐But Sam‐‐
‐The crystal's cracking,
Savannah.
It gets worse each time
we go through.
If you don't go home now,
you might not get
another chance.
Harper:
You've already risked
too much.
I just can't believe
I won't see you guys again.
I have a feeling
someday you will.
Here, take this.
No one else can know
you're here.
Jess:
Oh, uh, Harper?
This is Allison Carter.
She's doing a story
on the hotel's history,
and she had
some questions for you.
Okay.
Your mother
was just telling me
about the document you found
in the city's archives.
I'd love to hear
more about it.
‐Would now be an okay time?
‐Of course.
Allison: So, first,
just a little bit about...
Wyatt:
So what would you do
if you came face‐to‐face
with Savannah?
Well, I'd ask her
to dance.
Stay out of sight.
I'll distract them.
Hey! So, uh, you guys‐‐
you guys enjoying the party?
Whoa! You all right?
You may wanna slow down.
It's pretty crowded tonight.
No kidding!
Never know who
you'll run into.
Okay, last question.
What does it mean to you,
as a Tremont,
to have this property
back in the family?
In a word...
everything.
All right.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Uh, hey. Hey.
‐What's going on?
‐Huh? What do you mean?
Well, you look worried.
Wouldn't have anything
to do with Griffin
and that girl, would it?
That is not
a little hiccup.
Where's Griffin?
He's keeping
Topher and the twins busy
so I could get down here.
I just saw them.
Griffin wasn't up there.
Maybe he's already
in the bunker?
Let's find out.
(electricity crackling)
(crystal cracks)
Sarah:
Look at all this water!
Where is Zoey
with that key?
We need more towels!
‐Here you go.
‐Are those my sheets?
It's all
we could find.
Water just keeps
coming.
A‐‐ A pipe
must've burst.
More like
the sewer line. Ugh.
Smells like the springs
up here.
Well, we can't
close the hotel.
That would be
a disaster.
What is this
considered?
Got the key!
Dad's looking
for a wrench
to turn off
the water main.
It's like something's...
wedged against the door.
Make room for the muscle.
And change of plans.
‐Did that just...
‐Move!
(wood cracking)
(intense music playing)
2024? That's where Sam is.
You think Griffin
went to warn him
about the crystal?
And bring Sam back?
They aren't coming back.
Dad! Mom!
Whoa.
No! My‐‐ My family
could be in there.
Let go!
‐Wyatt! Zoey!
‐It's empty.
Has been for a while.
‐A while?
‐Yeah.
You're sure?
Except room 205.
Something evil
took hold up there
and wouldn't leave.
It has no choice now.
Sam got the crystal
from the springs.
We'll find another one,
and then I can go home.
‐Savannah‐‐
‐No!
We have to find a way
to fix this.
I can't stay here!
I have a family now.
I have a family.
Ben:
Harper?
Mr. Campbell.
(door closes)
What is this place?
(intense music playing)
♪ ♪