Wyatt:
Previously on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
‐Have you seen Savannah?
‐No. Not all day.
Caroline:
I thought she might be
helping you out again.
Sam: Savannah!
Are you down there?
(grunting)
Topher: It's the ghost
sending a message
loud and clear.
You don't have
to leave tonight.
Haunted or just cursed,
that place wants us out.
‐firefighter:
Anyone living in room 205?
‐Sarah: Why?
firefighter:
When I was checking it out,
I noticed it seemed very cold.
Wyatt:
There's a ghost in that hotel.
Griffin:
There's no telling
how this is gonna end.
Your family can't let
that slimy judge win.
You got the document
for their farm?
If you mean the original,
it can go out
with tonight's trash.
I'll take care of it
tomorrow.
You need to switch
with Harper
and make sure
she gets back here.
There's something
you need to know
about the farm.
The judge tricked
your dad with a switch
of the documents.
Take this inside,
and the land stays
yours forever.
Only it's not
what you're going to do.
In fact,
that's the last thing
you're going to do.
If what you're saying
is true,
that document will allow us
to stay on our property.
Harper, come on,
give it to Daisy.
‐Wasn't that the plan?
‐I'm changing the plan.
I can't give you
the document.
But I don't
understand.
It's too big a risk.
If we change things
in 1930,
the future will be altered.
Yes, the farm would stay
in the Tremont family,
but you'd grow up
a completely different person.
Maybe you'd
never get married.
never have children.
The entire Tremont lineage
would be interrupted.
And you and your brother
would never be born.
Griffin said the same thing.
Harper, you're just
thinking about this now?
Why did we swipe it
in the first place?
You have to go back.
Live your life.
It will all work out.
Your father only wants
what's best for you and Sam.
But my mother will be trapped
in that hotel forever.
Not forever.
I promise.
Strange saying goodbye
to someone who hasn't
even been born yet.
I so want
more time with you,
my great‐granddaughter.
I want the same thing.
Okay, you two,
don't be bashful.
Hug it out.
Wyatt: Pretty obvious
Dad believes in ghosts now.
All that yelling
proves it.
That was so cool
when he took on the ghost.
You believe now too,
right, Mom?
Pretty much.
I'll loan you my hat,
if you want.
Uh, I'll let you know.
Meanwhile, I think
our ghost is on notice,
thanks to your dad.
Or he made her mad.
Her?
W‐‐ Why do you think
it's a woman?
We don't, really.
It goes back and forth.
One day she's a "she,"
the next he's a "he,"
or our favorite,
"it."
Covers all the bases.
If there was just some way
to free her from that mirror...
That‐‐ that's where
Topher says she's trapped.
You wouldn't have any ideas,
would you, Mom?
I mean, like
how to un‐trap her,
or de‐trap her,
or whatever the word is.
I'll give it some thought.
Meantime, you two need
to get to sleep.
It's been a long day.
‐On or off?
‐What do you think?
Sleep tight, you two.
As if any of us will sleep.
(ominous music)
Ben: Hey.
Twins in bed?
Uh, half of them.
Wyatt's on the floor.
You know, it actually feels
calm around here,
like... kinda peaceful.
Do you trust it?
Not for a second.
Daisy! What are you
still doing here?
You're supposed
to switch back
with Harper.
‐I know, and‐‐
‐This is crazy!
I mean, you know
what Harper means to me
and how much
I need her back here.
I know now.
Wait a second.
You're... Harper?
(laughs) Yeah.
‐You're home.
‐I'm home.
(theme music playing)
(siren wailing)
(indistinct chatter)
There you are!
Is everything all right?
I'm fine.
What happened?
Sam took a fall
down the basement stairs.
He's unconscious.
Nasty bump on the head.
After all the times
he's been down those stairs,
it seems crazy he fell.
He'll be all right.
Mom, I really need
to see him.
In time.
No, you don't understand.
I have to. Right away.
Wait. So Savannah
was in 1930?
She'd intercepted a note
in the floorboard
I'd put there for you,
that I was stuck
in 1930.
Then grown‐up Sam
finished the radio,
and Savannah was able
to open the portal
and come through.
I guess her idea
was to rescue me.
Everyone's idea.
You'll never believe
what I found out in 1930.
The land, the house,
and the springs were stolen
from my relatives,
the Tremonts.
This judge was behind it.
And probably the one
who turned it into a hotel.
Okay, I wanna hear all this
but we've got to get up there
before someone else
finds this place.
Wait. Someone else?
Who else?
‐Your brother.
‐Topher?
He was in the bunker?
And he swiped
the crystal.
‐Which is how I got stuck.
‐Right.
Anyway, you've got
your long story
and I've got mine,
and both will have to wait.
After you.
(portal opening)
You're not finished,
are you?
Please, leave my family alone.
I know you're hiding in there.
You talked to me before,
just talk to me again.
Tell me what we can do
to help you.
Harper:
Your mom was talking
to the mirror.
She knows?
My dad too.
Do they know its history?
That it's Grace?
No, but we almost
had a fire today.
Fire trucks,
lots of smoke.
What?
Remember when I told you
about my dream,
that nightmare
about smoke and a fire?
Sure. The day
you switched places
and got stuck.
In 1930, I learned
it wasn't a dream,
it was a vision.
I had more too.
Glimpses of the future,
of things to come.
I have this gift,
the same gift Grace had,
of seeing
into the future.
Bad things mostly,
like the smoke
and fire
that I thought
was gonna be in 1930,
but it must've been
in the present.
The Tremont now.
No one found any fire.
They couldn't explain it.
Wow. You've been to the past
and you can see into the future.
It's pretty impressive,
Harper.
Well, thank you.
Excuse me.
We're looking
for Sam Townsend.
He was admitted
earlier.
Colored ward is that way.
doctor: Still waiting
on those test results.
Can you check
with the lab?
Doctor,
you've just been in
with Sam Townsend?
‐Yes.
‐How is he?
His vitals are strong,
but he remains
unconscious.
Time will tell.
Uh, do you know
where I can get
his medical record?
Sorry, I don't.
(whispering):
Sam. Sam!
Your time machine,
it works.
I used it, Sam.
I went back to 1930
when you were a kid.
I saw the hotel
when it was the farm.
I saw your father.
I saw you.
Caroline:
Honey, we have to go.
The doctor said
no visitors just yet.
(whispering):
Get better, Sam.
You have to see it working.
It's a beautiful thing
you created.
Harper:
It's all here.
The sale of the farm.
The judge's plans
to build the hotel.
The healing springs.
Delay after delay,
problems with
construction...
The judge went through
like six architects,
had to go to Baton Rouge
to find the right one.
The first grand opening.
1944.
Fourteen years later.
Harper:
When you take a look
at the false starts
and the construction delays,
it becomes so obvious.
The ghost of Grace
was behind it.
Ninety years
of blinking lights,
cold spots, and water leaks.
You said you had a way
to free her?
Harper:
With this‐‐
the document
that'll change everything.
This is the original,
which would have allowed
Elijah to stay on his land.
The forged second document
was used against him.
This is proof
the land was stolen.
Which means the land
still belongs to the Tremonts,
to my family.
Explaining why Grace
won't leave the hotel.
Anyone other than a Tremont
is an intruder
and must be dealt with.
Plus, I've always been
drawn to it.
My father too.
Even Topher.
And I'm thinking
it's because
it's still ours.
You realize my father's put
his whole life in that place?
This is huge.
One hotel, two owners.
What're we gonna do?
What we always do.
Figure it out.
And we're very close
to finishing.
Spackle, paint,
uh, a tricky furnace,
but the place
has good bones.
I don't know
if you've ever been
out there...
Sure. As a kid.
We'd throw rocks
through the windows and run.
I'm sure you know, the place
has quite a reputation.
Mr. and Mrs. Campbell,
you seem like nice people
and certainly very competent.
But there's
obvious risk here.
I noticed
you didn't mention
the recent fire.
Oh, that?
Mostly just smoke.
Right, Ben?
No damage,
aired it right out.
banker:
And lost a few contractors
along the way.
Some back pay is owed,
I understand.
‐Any refills?
‐banker: No, not for me.
Your passion
for this project
is undeniable.
But bottom line,
I can't recommend this
for a loan.
Thank you for your time.
You guys okay?
How could we be anything but
after your incredible pastries?
What Ben is trying to say
is that we may have
just lost our last chance
to finish the hotel.
Ben: Why don't you
join us, Jess?
As someone once said,
"Misery loves company."
(rooster crowing)
‐Hey, Sam.
‐I don't get it.
I packed this whole crate
two hours ago.
You didn't pull
all this stuff out,
did you?
Can't say I did.
Maybe it was Papa.
Now, why would he
do that?
I can't believe
we're actually leaving
this place.
Well, one chapter ends,
another one begins.
Unless you're at the end
of the book.
Sam, I'm saying
you're destined
to do great things.
You have to continue work
on your special project.
See it through.
Never give up on your dream.
Having visions again?
Looking into the future?
Something like that.
Something just as cool.
Cool? What does that mean?
Like chilly? Cold?
Like... magical.
Knock it off!
Every day a new Daisy.
Is he...
Is he gone?
nurse: Not in the way
you're thinking.
He disappeared
during the middle
of the night.
You wouldn't happen to know
where he is, would you?
Actually, I just might.
Harper:
It's the best way
to help Grace move on.
In fact, it may be
the only way.
I'm not disagreeing.
You're not agreeing
either.
It's just‐‐ (sighs)
My parents have
so many other problems
right now.
Piling more on them
just seems crazy.
I don't see this
as a problem.
Like you said,
we just need to get it
all out in the open.
My mom's car...
She's here.
We'll have everyone together.
Come on.
Now's the perfect time.
Harper:
It's a document that shows
this land, the springs,
all of it still belongs
to our family,
to the Tremonts.
Those signatures,
back in 1930,
they guaranteed
we'd never be evicted.
‐Where did you find this?
‐Harper: Archives downtown.
When I learned
we'd owned the land,
I was curious, so...
I did some research.
‐Griffin helped.
‐Sarah: So you're saying
this land was stolen
from the Tremonts
by this judge?
Technically, yes.
Jess: Exactly.
Technically.
This is an old document.
I mean, any lawyer
could easily argue
it's no longer valid...
no matter
what our kids uncovered.
Doesn't change things.
I, we, everyone knows
how you invested in this place.
It's your dream.
It was your husband,
my father's dream too.
That paper,
that lie has lasted
generations,
and we have to make it right.
Ben, you don't owe us anything.
Ben:
Harper's right.
If it's true,
if any of it is true, we...
we have an obligation,
a moral obligation
to return the land.
What happens to us?
Griffin:
Guys, it's‐‐ it's okay.
I mean, they're just
figuring things out.
Nothing has to change.
Right?
Jess:
Wait. Everyone...
I have an idea.
Now, hear me out.
You need money,
and I've been saving
to buy a better
and more upscale restaurant.
What if I put
the money in here?
Into the hotel?
50‐50 partner.
You'll have the money
you need to finish.
I can have my restaurant.
And we can restore
The Tremont back
to its greatness.
I mean,
it is your legacy, kids.
You okay with this?
Yeah. Yes, of course!
And yes from me too.
Ben?
Th‐‐ Th‐‐ This is...
It's‐‐ It's incredible.
Wyatt:
I vote...
‐Take the deal, Dad.
‐I'll second that.
‐Third.
‐Fourth.
‐It's unanimous.
‐Hm. Looks like a quorum, Ben.
Jess, I‐‐
‐We...
‐Jess: I know.
Enough said.
So, what do you say
we break out
some sparkling cider
to celebrate?
Sarah:
I'm on it.
Wyatt, Zoey,
I'll need help
with the glasses.
I hate sparkling cider.
Makes me sneeze.
Zoey:
No one cares, Wyatt.
Hey, which room is mine?
Jess:
So what do you think?
How soon can you get
the contractors back?
Oh, now that there's
a paycheck in their futures,
I'd say sooner
than later.
Well, Tremonts back
in The Tremont.
What Grace wanted
all along.
I hope you're listening,
great‐great grandmother.
(light flickering)
Sam?
"I've gone on a journey
through time.
"Don't come after me.
"If I'm not back
in three weeks...
destroy the radio."
2024. The future.
You can rest easy now,
great‐great grandmother.
It's over.
You're free.
The Tremonts are back
on the land
just like
you always wanted.
(voice humming "Amazing Grace")
(thudding)
(mirror cracks)
(humming continues)
I sneezed, like, five times.
Now I have to pee.
Really more information
than we need.
Is it just me,
or does this place
feel different?
Different, how?
Like, peaceful?
Yeah, I'm getting
the same vibe.
Maybe because
we all want it
to feel that way.
Don't turn around,
Zoey.
No, turn around.
Don't‐‐ Do‐‐
Don't‐‐ Do, do.
Don't‐‐
You see it, right?
It came from the mirror.
We freed her.
(dramatic music)
(singing "Amazing Grace")
Oh, my gosh!
Topher:
We did it.
We freed her, guys.
(singing continues)
‐I don't think
we tell our parents.
‐Agreed.
They wouldn't
believe us, anyway.
Is it over?
Well, her spirit's freed,
and there aren't
any more ghosts.
Yeah. It's over.
Zoey:
Which means you can
finally go back
to snoring
in your own room.
She is so going to miss me!
‐Heading home, Harper?
‐Go ahead, Toph,
I'll catch up.
‐So‐‐
‐I, uh‐‐
(chuckles)
You can go first.
If it's not obvious,
I missed you
while you were gone.
Like... a lot.
I missed you too.
I, uh...
I better get inside.
Right. And I have
to catch up to Topher.
Yeah.
‐Good night, Griffin.
‐Good night, Harper.
(ominous music playing)
(door slams)
♪ ♪
Harper:
Next time on "Secrets
of Sulphur Springs"...
Sarah:
It's our pleasure
to finally say...
all:
Welcome to The Tremont!
(all cheering)
Finally found the key
to 205.
Sarah:
But it has that draft.
We still haven't figured out
where that's coming from.
That is not
a little hiccup.
Well, we can't close the hotel.
That would be a disaster.
Sam went into the future
and hasn't come back yet.
Crystal's cracking,
Savannah.
If you don't go home now,
you might not get
another chance.