[thunder rumbling]
[narrator] Bhannawadee Mansion
was originally the residence of
Princess Bhannawadee Rasmee.
She was murdered by her gardener,
53 years ago.
The building was inherited
by her descendants
and later sold to a series of owners.
Finally, it was turned into
St. Maria Convent.
It remains so to this day...
[man crying hysterically]
[crying hysterically]
[gasps]
No! I didn't do it!
No! [groaning]
[breathing heavily]
-Help... me...
-[whimpering]
[screaming]
[thumping]
HELP
-[man] Help me! Help me!
-[screaming]
[screaming]
Stop screaming!
You'll get us into trouble!
I won't tell you another story again!
Shit. It's Ma Soeur.
[Ma Soeur Audrey] Who was that?
Piangfah?
Oh, the new girl, Ma Soeur.
Her name's Mon.
Mademoiselle Adhiti! Anything to say?
It wasn't me.
It's you!
The whole room heard it was you, right?
[all] Yes, it's her! Mon was screaming.
[all clamoring]
I didn't do it.
[screaming]
[church bell dinging]
[organ music playing]
[Ma Mere Hannah singing]
Hey, Mon, why are you mopping the floor?
[sniffing]
[door slams]
Come in.
[Ma Mere Hannah] She doesn't get better?
Meningitis? That's too bad.
I pray every day for a miracle,
but there's no miracle.
You have to understand.
I wouldn't have been so strict
in trivial matters,
if your aunt hadn't left you in my care
when she got sick.
So don't disappoint her.
Now go.
[door opens]
It wasn't me.
-[door creaking]
-[door closes]
[Adhiti] No...
I said no...
Why keep bothering me?
No...
Damn it. I said no!
Um...
I don't want fish.
Piangfah, here she comes.
Don't be pushy! Beat it!
Watch the crazy bitch catching a frog.
-[winces]
-[all] Oh!
[all laughing]
-A frog indeed, it's big and green!
-[all laughing]
Bitch!
[Ant] Mon.
Can I sit with you?
Yuck! What're you eating?
Mashed potatoes? So gross!
Oh. Shit, I have mashed potatoes too.
Bummer!
When I was a child,
my mother made this for me every morning.
I think my head has more mashed potatoes
than brains. [chuckles]
[laughing]
She thinks she's so pretty, huh.
Looking for dicks everywhere.
[Ant continues talking]
I heard gossips from her old school mates.
They confirmed she's a real slut.
Her dad's super-rich, the bitch's spoiled.
She slept around with a lot of boys.
[all] Eeh!
When school's out,
I usually go to Disneyland.
Have you been?
Hollywood too.
No wonder she has no friends
and has to hang out with that freak.
The old guy with long white hair...
The one in "Harry Potter".
What's his name?
Oh! I remember now. Gandalf!
Yes, Gandalf!
Gandalf your ass!
That's "Lord of the Rings"!
[all laughing]
Is it that good?
You eat like a starving pig!
[loud clatter]
[tray crashes]
Shut up and get lost!
-[girl talks indistinctly]
-[laughter]
[rain pattering]
Come with me?
[car engine starts]
[car door closes]
My name's Adhiti,
but everyone calls me Mon.
From the day my parents died,
12 years ago,
I'd began to feel that
death always hovered around me.
Silence has been my best friend since.
I knew it better than anyone else.
Silence has many levels.
The silence that lets
you hear leaves ruffle,
or insects flutter their wings...
The ticking of the clock,
the beating of your heart.
-[steady breathing]
-[monitor beeps]
And...
the silence of your own thought.
[door opens]
Hi, Mon, you're here.
[sighs]
No, I'm not.
I've got this for you, almond cookies.
I saw it freshly-baked this morning
after I finished my shift.
I remember you like almonds, so--
Excuse me, Doctor No.
I gotta pee.
[stutters]
[Adhiti] But the deepest silence...
is the silence so complete that
you can hear the spirit talking to you.
[sniffing]
You're here?
Keep following me, huh?
[Senior] I've come for your answer.
What answer?
I already said no.
[Senior] Please. Only you can help me.
You're such a pest!
[Senior] If you don't help me,
I'll keep following you.
Just go away!
Watch the crazy bitch catching a frog.
[Senior] Watch out! Step over! Back-heel!
[grunting]
Is it that good?
You eat like a starving pig!
[Senior] Please, only you can help me.
Shut up and get lost!
THE NIGHT BEFORE
[keyboard keys clicking]
[sniffs]
Who're you? How did you get in here?
[Senior] I was a student here
a long time ago.
Bullshit! This is a convent school.
[Senior] Thirty years ago,
it was a male-only business college.
Yep! I see.
What's your name?
[Senior] Just call me "Senior".
[Adhiti] Senior?
Fine.
What do you want, Senior?
I need your help.
[Adhiti] That was the first time
I met the mysterious Senior.
I didn't know why he told me
about the murder
in Bhannawadee Building 50 years ago.
[Senior] The gardener was sentenced to
death for the crime he didn't commit.
His ghost keeps coming back
to demand justice.
If the real murderer is still out there,
he will keep haunting the place forever.
Even the dead want justice.
Why are the dead asking
the living to help?
I think ghosts know everything.
[Senior] No, only what's left of
their memories when they're alive.
Some of the memories are lost,
and sometimes we don't even remember
how we died.
[girls talking indistinctly]
[mockingly laugh]
"GRADE WHORE!"
[Ant sobbing]
[crying tearfully]
[sniffling]
Leave me alone, Mon.
I'm a slut.
I'm a bitch, a spoiled child.
I'd sleep with any men!
I'm a whore, a skank, a shameless hooker.
When you finish punishing yourself,
tell me.
Wait!
I've just finished.
[Adhiti] Here.
Keep it. I don't need it.
[blowing nose]
They call me a slut...
because I get close to Master Rati,
the new chemistry teacher.
You know him, right?
Yeah.
When I got good marks,
they spread a rumor
that I slept with the teacher.
What should I do?
I'm going crazy!
Ant, your mom's dead, right?
How do you know?
Five years ago, she hung herself
to get back at my father
for having a mistress.
Then my dad married his lover
and they moved to the US.
[sighs]
Hey, can I ask you something?
Why's your nickname "Mon"?
When you were a baby,
you were round and cute like Doraemon?
I don't know.
My guess is Mon is from "Salmon".
You like salmon?
No, I don't eat fish.
Duh!
What about your "Ant"?
A short for "Giant"?
Yes, when I was a kid I was so big,
my mom called me Giant.
Growing up, I was so embarrassed
by the name.
So I shortened it to "Ant". Cute?
As hell.
[both laugh]
[music playing]
Honestly,
I have a huge crush on Master Rati.
I think he likes me too.
Let me show you something.
Ta-da!
He gave it to me on Valentine's Day.
Lovely, isn't it?
To be frank,
I have a bad feeling about him.
How can you say that about my boyfriend!
You're jealous, aren't you?
[dog howling]
Dumb dogs!
Why do they make that stupid noise?
Mon, they say dogs howl
because they see ghosts, true?
Ant, do you know
dogs have such shitty eyesight?
But they have a very good nose.
So dogs can't see ghosts.
They smell them.
How come you know so much about dogs?
Were you one in your past life? [laughs]
No. But I can smell ghosts too.
Don't kid me, I'm scared!
I don't. It's a secret
I've never told anyone before.
[brakes screeching]
When I was four, I survived the car crash
that killed my parents.
Since then, I can smell dead people.
Just by sniffing at the things
they touched.
Right now,
I can smell your mother.
You're bullshitting me.
Lavender... cool but sad.
That's my mom's favorite perfume.
How do you know?
Don't fool around with that man.
Your mom asked me to tell you.
[speaking in French]
PRINCESS MURDERED IN THE POOL
[Senior in Thai] So you've agreed to help?
You just had to play hard to get.
"No! No! No!"
Crazy!
Who was that?
You always wanted to help me, admit it.
You know it so why did you ask?
Adhiti, you want to test me?
[chuckles]
So hot-headed!
If you were my sister,
I'd smack your head.
Go on! I dare you!
Mademoiselle Adhiti!
"I'M A NUTCASE.
DON'T COME WITHIN 100 METRES."
[Senior chuckles]
[Senior] So we're partners now, right?
Partners in what?
Detective partners.
To investigate the case,
I need an assistant.
So I'm your hands and feet?
Come on, I mean,
I'm from a different period.
I don't know
what's going on in this world.
Like that flip-flop TV you have,
I never saw it before.
Flip-flop TV? Duh!
It's a notebook computer!
Anyway,
aren't you afraid someone will see you
walking around like this?
You're talking to me now
and you don't see me.
Don't be paranoid.
Why are you so sure?
The people who can see me
are only those who're about to die.
[Adhiti] Once I'd decided to help Senior,
I started digging for information.
The murder took place at night.
Princess Bhannawadee was hit
by a hard object at the back of her head.
The impact broke
the back part of her skull.
Her body fell into the pool.
The police found a blood-stained shovel,
which led to the arrest of the suspect,
Jit, the long-serving gardener.
They searched his house
and found a stash of jewelry,
which belonged to the princess.
The court ruled that
the defendant's argument didn't add up.
Jit was sentenced to death
by firing squad.
-[gun firing]
-[Jit screaming]
I found out that there were three people
involved with the case.
First is the princess's doctor, Dr. Saner.
He was the one who
found her body in the pool.
He's still alive today.
The second is Mr. Praphan,
the lawyer who was in charge of her will.
He died five years ago.
The third one is Miss Woranart,
the princess's former secretary.
She was fired for embezzlement
and disappeared shortly before the murder.
Anyway, how did you get in here?
You just walked right through the wall,
like in ghost movies?
When I was a student,
there was no washroom here.
Just a balcony.
I don't get it. Tell me.
People believe spirits can
walk through walls, but that's not true.
We can touch only the things or places
that existed when we were still alive.
When you see a spirit walk through a wall,
that's because in the past,
there was no wall there.
So the spirit could simply walk through.
But if there was a wall there
and now it becomes a door,
the spirit can't go through it.
[thuds]
This is why I need your help,
get it now?
Now you're right here, aren't you?
You can smell me?
Yes.
Don't you want to know how I look?
I do. I have a mental image of you.
What's it like?
Well... you're good-looking, tall,
and slightly pretentious.
Whoa, you can tell that much
from the smell?
Senior, do you think we can touch?
In theory, no.
Because when I was alive,
you didn't exist.
Is that so?
Follow me.
Where are we going?
[Senior] The pool where
the princess's body was found.
When I was a student here 30 years ago,
the pool was still there.
But it was a forbidden area to all.
When the place was turned into
a convent school,
they filled up the pool
and turned it into a cemetery.
Where you're standing now
is the edge of the pool.
It's about ten metres wide.
Where? Left or right?
[Senior] Left.
Now keep going.
-[wind howling]
-[growling]
[child laughing]
Stop right there!
That's where the body was found.
Tell me, what do you feel now?
[sniffing]
I smell blood.
Mixed with the smell of...
[sniffs]
...hatred.
Wait... there's something else.
[sniffing]
The smell of gunpowder...
swirling in the air from the past.
Unlikely.
In the case file,
there's no mention of any gun.
The murder weapon was a shovel,
hidden near the pool.
With blood on it.
Proved to match
the blood type of the victim.
There was no DNA test back then.
DNA?
[Dr. No] Hi, Mon!
Mon.
[pants]
Here, what you asked me to look for.
I had to dig into old hospital
registrations. My eyes almost popped out.
The filing was a mess,
everything was manually done back then.
Thank you, Dr. No.
Instead of a thank-you,
let me take you to dinner.
[gurney rattling]
Do you believe in ghosts?
[mumbles]
Baloney! There's no such thing!
[gurney rattling louder]
What the heck? Why did you push me?
[Senior] You have to go in by yourself.
In my time, this place was a swamp.
[door creaking]
Excuse me, are you Dr. Saner?
I'd like to ask you about
the murder of Princess Bhannawadee.
[breathing heavily]
[screaming]
Damn it! How did you get in here?
What do you want?
I want to ask you about "Baby Daeng".
What?
[Dr. Saner] Baby Daeng was an orphan
whose mother died in the hospital
where I worked.
The princess...
took pity on her
and adopted her as a niece.
When she was 12,
Baby Daeng ran away and disappeared.
[coughs]
You know Mr. Praphan, right?
That vile lawyer? Of course I know him!
I know him more than anyone else,
and I'll never forget him
till my last day.
[chuckling]
I heard he died from
alcoholic liver disease.
[laughing]
Serves him right.
[chuckles]
-[sniffing]
-[Dr. Saner] Karma caught up with him!
[laughing]
Where did you learn about Baby Daeng?
In the case file.
When the murder happened,
she was just six.
Eyewitnesses testified that
she was sleeping in her room.
The name sounds familiar to me.
I must've heard it before.
Anyway, how did you get into his house?
Just walked right through walls,
like in ghost movies?
[sighs]
He left the back door open
like an invitation.
A buffalo could've waltzed in.
[wind howling]
[sniffing]
Shit, she's sniffing the wall.
Frigging insane!
So your mother is a dog!
[laughter]
[girl] She is really a dog.
[indistinct scream]
[Adhiti] I smelled rage and vengeance.
I could tell
it was a female spirit that's related to
someone in the mansion.
[elevator creaking]
A lot has changed here,
nothing is the same as it used to be.
See that abandoned room,
it used to be a delivery room.
[babies crying]
[squelching]
You've been here a long time.
Ever seen something unusual?
So often that it stopped being unusual.
See that room?
I used to see the ghost
of a pregnant nurse
walking in there every night. [laughs]
Dr. Saner worked as an obstetrician here.
The ghost of a pregnant nurse could be
another piece in the puzzle.
Or maybe she's the mysterious
spirit that appears on the school wall.
But from our research,
no one fits the description.
The only possibility is Miss Woranart.
Right, I found that Mr. Praphan had a wife
called Wipa.
She's still alive.
Maybe we should go talk to her.
Why is a born-yesterday asking
about something that happened ages ago?
What for? Go away!
Not working.
A born-yesterday, so what?
[melancholic music playing]
[teacher speaking]
SENIOR
[cell phone buzzes]
MON, SEE ME AFTER SCHOOL. SAME PLACE.
Are you certain?
He knew?
[Ant] I showed him the test result.
He doesn't believe me
and said I was lying.
[Adhiti] Master,
can we talk?
[Rati] HCG is a hormone that can be
found in some types of drugs.
Mix it with urine and put a drop
in the home pregnancy test,
and you get the positive result.
Cheap trick. I'm a chemistry teacher,
she can't fool me.
Will you take her to a hospital
for another test then?
Why would I do that?
I have nothing to do with this!
Everyone knows that Ant is...
Is what?
[mutters]
Well, she sleeps around with lots of men.
Including you.
So?
She came on to me!
You're a jerk!
I'll go to the police. She's a minor!
Uh-uh-uh.
Well, that's not very smart,
if you still love your friend.
I'll show you something.
What if these photos
get into the social media?
What would happen to your friend?
Master, delete these pictures. Please!
Sure,
but that depends on
what I'll get in return.
Hmm?
What do you say?
[grunts]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[Ant] Where're you taking me?
The hospital. You must have another test.
No, I'm embarrassed!
Ant, did you lie to me?
I... No! I didn't!
That's it... Don't talk to me ever again.
You're no longer my friend.
Come back! Mon! Don't leave me!
Mon!
-[thunder rumbles]
-[rains heavily]
Mon... I need to talk to you...
[sniffles] Please talk to me...
[sobbing] Mon.
Mon.
[music playing]
[Ant continues sobbing]
-[music stops]
-[knocking at door]
It's me again. May I ask you...
[door closes]
[knocking at door]
I'd like to...
I...
uh...
Dr. Saner already told me everything.
He said he'll tell the truth
and expose what you did.
That son of a bitch is still alive?
What has he told you?
You want me to say it right here?
Come in.
Let me tell you.
My husband had nothing to do
with the princess's death.
Even though he was named
the executor of the will,
that asshole died penniless.
He left me nothing.
I actually had to pay off
the mortgage for this house.
I'll go upstairs to look around.
You keep talking to her.
[Wipa] What happened, happened a long
time ago. I don't want to dig it up.
[sniffing]
[Wipa grunts]
Now tell me,
what fiction did that quack tell you?
Wipa already told me everything.
[scoffs]
Don't listen to that drunken bitch.
She's no different from
her deceitful husband.
Dumb woman, she didn't know
that he had been cheating on her.
Cheating on her?
Yes, with that secretary.
Actually, I suspected that
Praphan killed his lover, Woranart.
On the day Woranart disappeared...
I found her bracelet
on the floor in the library.
Praphan looked so nervous that day.
I also noticed cement powder
on his elbows and shirt sleeves.
[Wipa] Back then, everyone knew that
the princess took fancy of her doctor.
There was an issue of age and class,
so they couldn't get married.
She was a princess,
and that quack was a lowborn commoner.
The royals would never allow that.
So they secretly had an affair.
They were lovers...
Whatever you call it,
but it was "adultery" in my time.
One day, he took a baby girl
from the hospital.
Told the princess, she was an orphan
whose mother died in childbirth.
[wind howling]
-[growling]
-[gasps]
[thudding]
[whimpering]
[yelps]
-[objects crashing]
-Senior!
Who are you? What're you doing here?
[yells]
[sniffing]
-[indistinct chattering]
-[child shrieking]
[baby crying]
[growling]
[wind howling]
Let her go!
[Senior grunts]
[Adhiti breathing heavily]
[paper rustling]
-[growls]
-[Senior yells]
Senior!
[growling]
[Senior grunting]
[Wipa] Stop!
Stop it!
That's enough! I can't stand it anymore.
Get out!
Get out of here!
Both of you!
Get out!
[Senior] I found another will. It names
Dr. Saner the executor of the estate.
But it doesn't have
the princess's signature.
In the real will,
Praphan was the executor.
Now Praphan has become my prime suspect.
Why?
If Dr. Saner has told us the truth,
then Praphan must have been
such an evil man.
He killed his own lover.
What would stop him from
killing his boss to steal her wealth?
Senior... I have to go now.
Where're you going?
I have a date.
[indistinct]
[Ant screaming]
So you're gonna stare at me
'til we get the check?
What about that thing I asked you?
"That thing"?
Yes, I did some research.
Sodium thiopental is a type of barbiturate
that can cause
sudden loss of consciousness.
If used in modest amount,
it will make you feel heady,
and do whatever you're told.
Like being hypnotized.
Thank you so much for
having dinner with me.
Come to think of it,
we have a lot in common.
Your nickname, Mon,
must've come from the cartoon "Doraemon".
My name's Mano.
I used to wear thick glasses
so my friends called me "Nobita".
Doraemon and Nobita [claps]
are from the same cartoon!
It's fate! Don't you think?
[electricity buzzing]
Thank you for your help. I have to go.
Actually, my nickname
is a short for "Demon".
You're following me again.
You want to know whom I just met?
No. I'm just wandering the streets
I used to walk.
This photo studio has been here
since my time.
You like old photographs?
Hmm.
Yes, I always stop to take a look.
Me too.
I've always thought that a photo studio...
is where the good moments of
the past generations are kept.
Some in these pictures no longer
have the smile they once had.
Some became nothing but ashes.
But here, they're frozen in time,
in eternity.
That's my parents' wedding picture.
Really? What a coincidence!
Senior.
How did you do that? It was cool.
What did I do?
Making the light go on and off
at the restaurant.
Uh...
I don't know. It's energy, sort of.
Wow, you are the real X-men.
[music playing]
[inaudible]
[Adhiti] Thanks for walking me back.
You came back by yourself.
I just followed you.
We had a pleasant evening...
If I could see you when I talked to you,
that would be great.
[closes window]
[Ant crying]
[screaming]
Ant.
Mon.
[Ant] Mon,
let's take a selfie.
Your face is a friggin' mess
and you want a selfie?
[camera clicks]
[chuckles]
[Ant] Why do you always make a dead face?
Need to take a shit?
Better die than do
your stupid girlie pose.
Mon.
I'm sorry.
We're still friends, right?
[sighs]
You're a real piece of work.
I really love him.
True love... you can call it that.
Don't throw up.
I dream of spending my life with him,
like husband and wife--
Ant.
I warn you to stay away from him.
That man is very dangerous.
How do you know?
I... I smelled something bad.
You really hate him, don't you?
What about your guy?
Hmm?
What guy? I don't have any.
Don't play dumb!
That day when Ma Soeur Audrey
punished you,
I saw a guy sitting next to you.
Real cute.
Who's he?
Ant,
what did you just say?
You saw him?
[groggily] Boyfriend you never
told me about.
[exhales]
[thunder rumbling]
[Wipa] When you were alive,
you treated me like dirt.
You never cared about me!
But when you were sick and dying,
you came crawling back.
Asshole husband!
-[gunshot]
-[body thuds]
Doctor!
Wake up! Doctor! Don't die!
What the hell should I do?
Wake up! Don't die!
-[coughing]
-[ball rolls away]
[Dr. Saner] Heart disease.
I could drop dead any day.
Thank you for visiting me.
Actually, I have a question.
But let's wait until you get better.
Just ask. I'll tell you
what you want to know.
The princess originally named you
the executor of her will.
But after she died, Mr. Praphan's name
was in the will instead.
Yes, Praphan switched the wills.
[panting] He wanted to have everything
for himself.
[breathing heavily]
You know, I never believed that
Baby Daeng just disappeared.
I'm sure it's Praphan.
He's the one who got rid of her.
What?
Baby Daeng was murdered!
Yes.
It's getting more complicated.
Let's weigh the possibilities here.
The will specifies clearly that
Bhannawadee Palace was not to be sold.
So Praphan managed to lease it
to a private business college
for many years.
That means he didn't get anything
from Baby Daeng's death, did he?
Correct. Had Baby Daeng been alive,
Praphan would've benefited more.
-[door opens]
-Happy Birthday, Mon!
Have a good one!
[exclaims]
Here, you like it?
I spent hours picking it.
It's Dora-Demon!
[Adhiti] You over-do it.
But well,
thanks.
Like I said before, instead of a thank-you
have dinner with me please!
I won't hear a "No".
I've already booked a table.
I bet you'll like it.
The mashed potatoes there are damn good!
And it won the Iron Chef Award
three years in a row.
Must be the wind...
But how come there's a wind
in a closed room?
[Senior] How did you find me?
I followed your smell.
You're not going to your birthday dinner?
If I went, I wouldn't be here.
You're mocking me.
Can I ask you something?
When you were alive,
did you have a girlfriend?
[Senior] I don't remember,
it was a long time ago.
Let me guess,
you were good-looking
and tons of girls queued up for you.
But you're so sensitive. No girls would be
able to stand you, right?
Cheeky girl! A smack on the head
would do you good!
How did you hit on a girl in those days?
No cell phones, no internet.
You called her house number
or wrote her letters.
Sometimes, it took months to get a reply.
Your girlfriend must've married
someone else already.
It was exciting.
You wrote a letter and wait
in anticipation whether she'd write back.
Some women sprinkled her favorite perfume
into the letter.
When the guy opened it,
he would smell her.
So romantic!
Did you do it?
Do what?
Wrote letters to your girlfriend.
I told you I don't remember,
it was such a long time ago.
[girls whimpering]
[Adhiti] After that,
the spirit of the mysterious woman
made spooky noise from behind the wall,
as if she was trying to tell us something.
-[thump on wall]
-[breath trembling]
[girl inhales sharply]
-[thumping]
-[all screaming]
We're trying to find the real killer.
Please... help us.
LIBRARY
This used to be the library
of Bhannawadee Palace.
When I was a student, it was still in use.
But it was closed along with the college.
In my time, there was a wall
separating the two sides of the room,
now they're connected.
At the far end,
was the librarian's office,
and... over there
was a shelf full of antique books.
Let's split up.
I'll cover the present-day library.
You do the old library of your time.
Call me if you find anything.
Okay.
[door creaking]
[blows and grunts]
HANSEL AND GRETEL
HISTORY OF BHANNAWADEE PALACE
[Senior] Partner! I've found something.
What is it?
[wind howling]
[sniffing]
[Adhiti] Senior!
Help!
Senior!
[Senior] Wait! I'm coming!
-[Adhiti] Help me!
-[Senior] Damn it!
[grunting]
[door creaking]
[gasping]
Mademoiselle Adhiti,
what're you doing in here?
[coughing]
You've broken the rules many times.
But this is the most serious.
If your parents were still around,
I would have to call them here.
[sighs]
I'm sorry I have to punish you
by grounding you
in the Room of Repentance
for one day and one night.
[key rattles]
[footsteps walking away]
HANSEL AND GRETEL
SARANRAS RASMEE (BABY DAENG)
[sniffing]
Partner!
Are you in there?
Come in. I want to talk to you.
I can't. There used to be a wall here.
I found something in this book.
You should take a look.
I'll toss it over the wall,
make sure you catch it.
[grunts]
HISTORY OF BHANNAWADEE PALACE
DIARY
I'm Woranart Petai. I'm writing
this diary to serve as evidence...
[Adhiti] The diary was a record of
the affair between her and Mr. Praphan.
It also described how Praphan forced her
to steal the princess's money
to pay off his gambling debts.
[Woranart] I will talk it over
with him tonight.
If he refuses to own up,
I will hand this diary to the princess,
and the whole truth will come out.
[sniffing]
I get it!
[knocking at door]
Ma Soeur,
open the door. It's time. Let me out!
[key rattling]
[exhales]
Sorry, I forgot all about you.
Something terrible happened.
[breathing heavily]
[all chattering indistinctly]
[engine starts]
[siren wailing]
[indistinct conversation]
[Ant screaming on video]
GRADE WHORE
[Ant] Mon, where are you?
I called you a dozen times.
I'm depressed. No one loves me.
I want to talk to you.
I'll wait at the same place.
[crying]
[Adhiti] Ant.
Why did you do it?
Why?
Why did you do it? Why? Why?
Why did you do it?
[crying hysterically]
[car starting]
[Adhiti] Stop! You did this.
Don't you run away!
-Where're you going?
-[tires squealing]
Murderer!
Senior! Where are you? I've helped you.
Now it's your turn.
What do you want me to do?
-[commentator on tv]
-[Rati grunting]
[Rati] Kick it! Kick!
[whining]
[clicks tongue] What the hell did you do?
[beeping]
[corn popping]
[Ant] It's hot! It's hot!
It's hot! It's hot!
It's hot!
-[screaming]
-It's so hot!
Honey, what've you done to me?
It's so hot!
-[gasping]
-I can't stand this! Help!
[groans]
[screaming]
[Rati screams]
-[microwave dings]
-[screaming]
[gasping]
[panting]
[grunts]
[woman] What's wrong?
You screamed like
someone's squeezing your balls.
[Rati] I just saw...
[panting]
...a popcorn ghost!
A popcorn ghost? Are you high or what?
This pallid face in the microwave oven.
And then...
its pus just pops like popcorn.
Like this?
[breathing raspily]
[screaming]
Honey, where're you going?
Come back! I love you!
Love you! Love you!
[screaming]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
[screaming]
-[Ant chanting] I love you! I love you!
-[whimpering]
[chanting continues]
[Ant] Honey!
Where're you going?
[whimpering]
You said you loved me!
I love you! I love you!
Love you! Love you! [laughing maniacally]
[Adhiti] The next morning
Master Rati, half-crazed,
confessed everything to the police.
He said he preferred prison
to the most horrifying thing
that visited him last night.
[door opens]
[gasps]
Mon!
Are you happy now? Witch hunter!
[sobbingly] Mon, I'm sorry!
About what?
About Ant... I know I was wrong.
I never thought what I did
would blow up into this.
After she died,
I began to hallucinate.
I kept seeing Ant hang herself
over and over.
Day and night...
[screams]
I'm losing my mind!
Mon, you don't have to forgive me.
But I should say sorry to you.
Ant would want me to do that.
She loved you so much.
[Adhiti] Ant was not born
to know happiness.
But for a brief period in her life,
she believed that she'd found true love
before it turned into a nightmare.
During that period,
Ant found real happiness
in her own private world,
the world that everyone condemned
as nave and promiscuous.
But she didn't care.
[sniffing]
Ant.
[Ant] Thank you, Mon.
You're the only friend I ever had
in my life.
Goodbye.
[sobbing]
[Adhiti] At that moment,
I smelled Ant's favorite perfume.
The smell of clear-eyed despair.
I felt her presence,
coming to say goodbye...
for the last time.
[Adhiti] Where do we go after death?
[Senior] Nowhere.
The spirits remain where they're familiar
with until the time comes.
Like us?
Yes...
like us.
Let's see what we have
at this point. First,
the demon that tried to stop us
was Mr. Praphan.
He didn't want us to find out
about something.
The night Woranart confronted Praphan
and threatened to tell the princess
about the embezzlement...
[choking]
...she was strangled to death.
Praphan covered up his crime
by hiding her body in the wall
and put cement over it.
The building was being renovated,
so no one took notice.
That's the reason
Woranart disappeared without a trace.
Wait!
Something's not right.
You mean Praphan didn't strangle Woranart?
Yes, she was strangled,
but Praphan didn't do it!
[gasping]
[thuds]
Wipa! What did you do?
This slut... she deserved this!
[gasping]
[snarling]
Praphan's spirit tried to stop us,
because he didn't want us to expose
the murder committed by his wife.
In this regards,
he wasn't such an asshole of a husband.
Now let's consider the next point.
Dr. Saner and Praphan conspired
to steal the princess's wealth.
Dr. Saner gave her thiopental.
Then they tricked her to sign a will
that gave everything to Baby Daeng,
with Dr. Saner as
the caretaker of the benefits.
After the princess's death,
the will was opened.
And Dr. Saner knew he was double-crossed.
Praphan had given the princess
another will to sign.
That will name Praphan as
the executor of the estate.
[Dr. Saner] We agreed to split it up!
You're a thief!
[Praphan] Back off, Doc. I have evidence
that could ruin your life.
If the police sees these prescriptions,
you're done for.
Get the hell out of this place
and don't ever come back!
Senior, I think I know
who the real murderer was.
Do you?
Who was it?
But first I need to ask you something.
Remember I told you once that
I smelled gunpowder at the pool.
I thought it had something to do
with the princess's murder.
But it was another murder
that happened 20 years later.
A MALE STUDENT OF RASMEE BUSINESS COLLEGE
WAS SHOT TO DEATH.
HIS BODY WAS FOUND IN THE SAME POOL
AS PRINCESS BHANNAWADEE'S BODY
[Adhiti] The murder victim was...
you.
[Senior] Spirits lost some parts
of their memories...
they can't remember how they died.
Now...
I remember...
Actually, I was a distant relative
to Jit, the accused gardener.
This case always troubled me.
I sneaked in here one night
to look at the crime scene.
[Senior grunts]
I died not knowing who killed me,
so my spirit has wandered the building
for 30 years trying to find the killer.
So that's it!
Senior.
Senior!
[church bell dinging]
[chorus singing]
Ma Mere Hannah?
Ma Mere Hannah.
Baby Daeng!
My time has come then.
Where did you find it?
This book was my birthday present
when I turned six.
It was the only happiness
in my forgettable childhood.
Princess Bhannawadee was a cruel person.
In public, she treated me with mercy.
-In private, she beat me and tortured me.
-[Princess scolding]
[Ma Mere Hannah]
She locked me up in a closet.
[Baby Daeng crying]
[Ma Mere Hannah] I only had this book
to keep me company.
I read it over and over.
The more I read it, the more
I saw her as the witch in the book.
[witchy cackle]
My hatred for her grew,
fueled by my childish imagination.
One night, the princess
was about to lock me up again.
I ran away to the pool.
[Princess] You brat!
You can't hide from me!
I'll beat you up when I find you!
Baby Daeng!
[yells]
[groaning]
[snarling]
[cackling]
SHE PUSHED THE WITCH INTO THE OVEN
AND CLOSED IT.
[snarls and cackles]
[screaming]
Baby Daeng! Help me! [coughs]
Baby Daeng! Help me!
[groaning]
[Ma Mere Hannah]
I remained in shock for years.
When I turned 12, I decided to run away.
I wandered about, until...
I found a new life through
the mercy of God.
I took my vows and
changed my name to Sister Hannah.
I took possession of
Bhannawadee Building
as stated in the will,
and donated the building to
the Catholic Council to redeem my sins.
Twenty years later,
I was chosen as Mother Superior.
Here at my old home.
God is merciful.
I don't have to run away anymore.
Ma Mere!
[man] Don't be alarmed.
It's just a tranquilizer.
[tranquilizer clatters]
Dr. Saner.
I just don't want her to hear
what we're going to discuss.
You don't have heart disease?
[chuckling]
I'm healthy.
I like you a lot,
you remind me of my daughter.
Is Baby Daeng your daughter?
Yes,
but I don't want her to know
that I'm her real father.
She's a beautiful thing,
the last beautiful thing
in my sordid life.
[glass breaks]
Asshole!
[Dr. Saner] The princess
was a very possessive woman.
When she found out
that I already had a wife,
a nurse who was pregnant at that time,
the princess gave me an ultimatum.
Choose one,
either that bitch or your child.
Or I'll destroy your career
and your family.
[Dr. Saner] I was so scared,
she was powerful and could do
what she threatened to.
I chose my daughter.
I injected a drug that
made my wife's heart stop
after she gave birth to the baby.
That night when I arrived,
I saw Baby Daeng with
a blood-stained shovel in her hand,
frozen in a state of shock.
Stay here and don't go anywhere.
If they ask you, say you were sleeping.
You don't know anything.
Remember! I'll take care of it.
After I left the palace, I tried to
find out what happened to Baby Daeng.
When I learnt that she became
a nun in a convent,
I was relieved.
The secret of the case would
remain hidden I thought.
But one day,
a college student came to see me
and asked about the case.
He was getting close to
know the existence of Baby Daeng.
I decided to protect my girl
by following him back to the pool.
I thought it was all over.
I never thought that 30 years later,
I'd have to come out to save my girl again
from a born-yesterday like you!
-Come here!
-[Adhiti] Let me go!
[Dr. Saner] Come here!
[Adhiti] What... What're you doing?
[Dr. Saner] An accident, of course.
A curious girl
sneaks up to the church's bell tower
and falls to her death.
[laughing]
[church bell dinging]
[Adhiti] Let me go!
Let me go!
-[Dr. Saner] Jump!
-[Adhiti] Help me!
-[Adhiti] Help!
[Dr. Saner] You jump now.
-[Dr. Saner] Jump!
-[Adhiti] No!
[Adhiti] Help!
Will you just fall on your own,
or should I pull the trigger?
A born-yesterday!
[Senior] Back-heel him, quick!
Jump!
[grunts]
[groaning]
I hate it when people call me
a born-yesterday!
Son of a bitch!
-[Dr. Saner screaming]
-[gunshots]
[church bell dinging]
-[whimpers]
[screaming]
Senior!
We can touch each other!
[Senior] Every rule has an exception.
[church bell dinging]
Don't you just die!
[woman screaming]
[gasps]
[both screaming]
[screaming]
[baby crying]
[Dr. Saner screaming]
[exclaims]
Doctor!
[Adhiti] I smelled the spirit
of the nurse, the doctor's wife.
She'd been patiently waiting for 50 years.
Now the wait was over.
Senior,
why is your scent getting weaker?
[sniffing]
[Senior] Everyone has a fixed time.
Spirits as well.
When I know the truth about myself,
it's time... I'll be gone... forever.
Senior!
Senior! Don't go!
[sniffles]
We're in different worlds.
Sooner or later I have to go.
All I want you to know is...
you're the best memory
in my life after death.
Don't cry.
Take good care of yourself
after I've gone.
No! Senior... don't go.
[sobbing]
Good bye, partner.
Senior... don't go. Senior!
Senior...
[music playing]
Senior.
Don't go.
[wind howls]
Senior.
Come back...
[sobbing]
[Adhiti] After 53 years,
the murder case of
Princess Bhannawadee Rasmee
was reopened
based on the confession
of Mother Superior Hannah.
Jit was declared innocent.
All the blames wrongly put on the gardener
were cleared.
From then on,
his spirit never came back again.
As for Hannah, her crime was ruled
as unintentional wrongdoing.
and the case's statute of limitations
had expired.
Still, she vowed to devote herself
to the Carmelite convent,
turning her back to the world
for the rest of her life.
The mysterious skeleton inside the wall
matched the DNA of Miss Woranart.
After that, no one ever heard any sound
coming out of the wall again.
[Ma Soeur Audrey] Mademoiselle Adhiti.
Good luck. May God bless you.
Goodbye, Ma Soeur Audrey.
[Adhiti] Senior never returned since.
He disappeared just as mysteriously
as when he came.
As if...
he never existed.
[sniffing]
Senior...
where are you?
[Adhiti] Dear Senior,
you told me that writing letters
is very romantic.
I've never written one before,
I don't know what to write.
Well,
I miss you.
When will you come back to hang out
with me again?
I'll let you smack my head, all right?
Your Partner.
[sniffing]
[reporter on tv] An old photo studio that
has been here since the revolution time
is going to be demolished to build a new
condominium in the heart of the city.
The conservationist groups
have come out to oppose it
because the building has already been
registered with the Fine Arts Department.
We will update you
on the progress of this...
[electricity buzzing]
THE OLD PHOTO STUDIO...
BOTTOM ROW, THE LAST PICTURE ON THE RIGHT
[Adhiti] Since we were partners
in the investigation,
it was the first time I saw Senior.
The photo seemed to be smiling at me
from the distant past...
[sniffing]
[Senior] A photo studio is where the good
moments of the past generations are kept.
Some in these pictures no longer
have the smile they once had.
Some became nothing but ashes.
But here,
they're frozen in time, in eternity.
See you around,
partner.