Sairoong, have you seen
the Uranus clip on YouTube?
What clip?
The clip about Uranus. It's gone viral.
It's got over one million views now.
I haven't seen it yet. What is it about?
You probably think it's about aliens
but actually, it's not.
-I see.
-It has something to do with astrology.
This certain clip illustrates
how Uranus completes a revolution
around the sun
-once every seven years,
-I see.
and this has an effect on our lives.
To put it simply,
-All right.
-the 7th year,
-then 14th year, 21st year,
-Okay.
and 28th year...
-Think along with me.
-Okay.
-The first seven years of our lives,
-Yes.
we stay at home.
We are children.
But when we reach seven years of age,
we go to school and enter first grade.
-Oh, I see.
-Life begins to change.
-Yes.
-Then from 7, you turn 14 years old.
-I see.
-What was being 14 years old like for you?
-Me?
-Did anything special happen?
When I was 14 years old...
I had my first crush.
Wow. When people turn 14,
-most of us hit puberty, right?
-Yes.
They start falling in love.
What about when you were 21?
When I was 21...
I had my fourth love.
Wow. You must have been quite hot.
URANUS' IMPACT ON EARTH
I DON'T KNOW ANY PLANET
THAT HAS AN IMPACT ON EARTH
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
I AM AT A TURNING POINT IN LIFE
WHY? DO YOU LIKE GUYS NOW?
THE SUSPENSE IS KILLING US,
SO IT SHOULD BE WORTH IT
SINGLE
IN A RELATIONSHIP
AND ONE OTHER PERSON LIKES THIS
AND TWO OTHER PEOPLE LIKE THIS
AND THREE OTHER PEOPLE LIKE THIS
AND FOUR OTHER PEOPLE...
DAMN
WHO'S THE GIRL?
GOODNESS GRACIOUS
WHO'S THE BITCH? TELL ME NOW
I THINK IT'S MAY FROM CLASS TWO
MAY IS RUNNING FOR SCHOOL PRESIDENT
I'm running for school president.
Candidate number two.
I am Maythawee Suwichakornkul.
-Do I have to say it again?
-Yes.
Okay.
I am Maythawee Suwichakornkul.
-Again?
-Yes.
I am Maythawee--
MAYBE IT'S PAT, THE CHEERLEADER?
OBSERVE CLOSELY, PUAN SERVED PAT FIRST
You're all clueless.
Just ask him.
IT'S DEFINITELY FOUR
FROM THE JAPANESE CLASS
I'M SURE IT'S MILK
IN TENTH GRADE CLASS ONE
PUAN IS IN A RELATIONSHIP
MILK IS IN A RELATIONSHIP
THEY CHANGED STATUS AT THE SAME TIME
Shit!
PLEASE CHECK OUT THE END OF THIS CLIP
SOONTORNPHU'S DAY
Please enjoy the show.
POETRY DAY 2012
-There are two microphones.
-Oh, my goodness.
DID YOU THINK
I WOULDN'T NOTICE THAT, PUAN?
WHAT ARE YOU REFERRING TO, MR. DETECTIVE?
TOPTAP HAS TAGGED YOU IN HIS PHOTO
HAVE YOU BEEN HAVING A CRUSH
ON HER SINCE GRADE NINE?
WHAT'S GOING ON? TELL ME NOW
Hey, Puan changed his status
to "In a Relationship."
I heard it's Milk from tenth grade.
Milk the MC? She got to him first.
Do you remember Poetry Day?
Puan was rolling up the mic cord...
and his hand touched hers.
She didn't even say anything.
She gave him a big smile too.
He had a crush on her since ninth grade.
He always put away her mic.
Was that how he flirted with her?
But he rolled up the mic cord for me too!
Ngor, if I can't get him,
don't you even think about it.
Fine. I will just be one
of his Facebook fans.
Let's beat Milk up then.
No.
No one can have him.
Only I can have him.
Do you want to beat me up too?
This has gone too far.
I better sneak a peek at Puan's Facebook.
She's Puan's girl, not My Girl anymore.
Do you need any help
with your mic today, sweetie?
Stop it.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Posting a clip
is better than typing.
How do you know people want to see it?
Look.
Here.
There are 2,000 students in this school.
So?
What? Look.
Don't you see?
There are over 800 views.
That's a lot, almost half of the school.
Okay, you nerd.
You don't need to tell them that
our hands touched and we smiled.
People might think I am easy.
I love you because...
-you are easy.
-You're crazy.
-Bitch.
-Let me clean your ear.
Is it itchy?
-I'll scratch for you.
-It hurts. Why did you kick me?
Milk.
Puan!
What the hell?
It's a shark.
Puan, take a photo.
Puan.
I like it.
To be honest,
you can't find it anywhere else.
The clothes are amazing. It really is.
I just went to Japan
-and it wasn't this pretty there.
-Miss...
Excuse me. I need to take a photo.
Yes?
Koy.
Pe.
Could you two please take a photo
with my girlfriend?
Don't you want a photo anymore?
Oh, you two broke up.
-Milk, come out now. Milk.
-Goodbye.
Hello.
Hello. I'm on my way.
How was I supposed to know
they broke up already?
They broke up ages ago.
Wait.
Milk, wait.
Milk, put it down. Hang on.
Wait a second.
It's awesome. Give it a try.
Wait.
CAN WE EAT IT YET? IT'S MELTING
Just a second.
I want a picture before it melts.
You'll get to eat it soon.
It's perfect.
This will make
the popular page for sure. See?
Puan.
The drink.
What now?
-Hey, Milk.
-What?
Must you film this too?
Milk.
Do I look like myself?
This is even uglier than the clip.
Ouch!
That really hurts.
-Do I look like myself?
-Wow.
Are you an alien?
Puan.
Anyone view it
if you set it as public, right?
Yes.
Exactly!
So what?
I don't want others to see it.
Can you set it to private?
Hang on.
14 VIEWS
There are only 14 views.
Nobody is interested.
I watched it five times.
You watched it five times.
The other four were probably accidental.
Look.
Someone left a comment.
TWO COMMENTS
SHE'S SO CUTE
WHAT SCHOOL DOES SHE GO TO?
THAT WAS GREAT
Wow.
You're popular now.
Set it to private now.
Okay, sure.
PRIVATE
Done.
WHERE SHOULD I GO ON VALENTINE'S DAY?
It's soccer time. Come on.
WHERE IS THE MOST ROMANTIC PLACE
FOR COUPLES ON VALENTINE'S DAY?
PHU CHI FAH IS ROMANTIC
ESPECIALLY AT NIGHT
A bracelet for your girlfriend?
How many types do you have?
All types. Which would you like?
A good quality or a normal quality one?
IT'S CROWDED THERE
YOU BETTER TO GO DOI ANG KHANG
A ten-baht lighter?
You again?
ARE THERE OTHER PLACES NEARBY?
SANTORINI PARK IS A HONEYMOONER'S DREAM
SANTORINI PARK
IS THERE A THEME PARK TOO? WHERE IS IT?
CHA-AM CITY, IT'S ONLY
A TWO-HOUR DRIVE FROM BANGKOK
I'M ONLY IN ELEVENTH GRADE
DO YOU HAVE ANYWHERE IN BANGKOK?
WHAT ABOUT ROD FAI PARK?
IT'S ROMANTIC AND CLOSE TO THE SKY TRAIN
Milk, give me a smile. One, two, three.
Good.
-Milk--
-Puan.
A lizard!
Oh, my.
-Come here.
-Are you petting it?
It's kind of cute.
Okay, that's cool.
Pretty...
ugly.
Pretty ugly.
Puan, stop filming. Hurry up.
-Hey, Milk.
-What?
Why did you turn around?
The scene was so beautiful.
Can we start all over?
-Can we start here?
-The scenery over there is better.
I have to change the lens too.
Do you have to?
It was a bit narrow.
Please, start there.
Where?
Over there.
Fine.
PRETTY UGLY.MOV
That's so cool, Puan.
You're so in love. How cute.
Your MV is cool too.
If you're free, you can direct my MV.
This kid is so talented.
Talented...
PRETTY UGLY
LANGUAGE PLAZA
Please give a round of applause
for Puan.
I've seen your MV already
and I want to say that...
it's dope!
Super cute!
Awesome!
Yes.
Yes, speaking. Okay.
GMM Grammy just called.
They want me to direct an MV for them.
I did not direct Joke So Cool.
Joke So Cool directed me.
Today, we've got a new MV.
It's very special
because the director is only 17 years old
and is currently in eleventh grade.
Let me ask you.
Did you do all this for fame?
Or are you jealous
of other Internet stars?
Like Put-Dejudom, Kome-Pakarang, Chef Mee?
Listen, Woody.
If I wasn't famous,
you wouldn't have invited me here, right?
I'm kidding.
Ma'am, what is that noise?
Ask Puan!
Puan.
-Puan.
PUAN, WHY AREN'T YOU AT SCHOOL?
DID YOU GET DIARRHEA?
PRETTY UGLY.MOV
Pretty...
ugly.
BUT I...
I worked all night for this.
Don't you have anything to say?
It's good.
Just good?
It's better than
you filming me pick my nose.
But it's just "good" for you though.
IF FACEBOOK HAD A "LOVE" BUTTON,
I'D CLICK IT A MILLION TIMES
What's up?
I was just thinking of you.
Puan.
I showed my mom the clip.
-She scolded me.
-What?
Why?
She asked
why I didn't tell her
and if I got paid for it.
Geez.
I almost had a heart attack.
-You scared me.
-She thought it was a real music video.
You should quit school
and do this for a living.
I'm not that good.
-I still have a lot to learn.
-It's so cool.
Believe me, everyone will love it.
THIS VIDEO IS PRIVATE
Thank you for making this for me.
I'll head to bed.
Tomorrow, we won't see each other.
Don't miss me too much.
See you on Sunday.
Okay, bye.
Goodnight.
15 VIEWS
PRIVATE, ONLY PEOPLE YOU CHOOSE CAN VIEW
PUBLIC, VIEWABLE FOR EVERYONE
CHANGES SAVED
CAN I SHARE THIS ON MY PAGE?
What do you think about my clip?
It's awesome!
1,367 LIKES
Ten thousand views!
1,367 LIKES 1 DISLIKE
Puan, walk faster.
Milk.
There are 11,000 views now.
People on Twitter like it too.
My followers are going up by 300 now.
There's just one problem.
There is one dislike on YouTube.
What the hell is wrong with that person?
You can just turn it off
if you don't like it, right?
Why would you click "dislike"?
These people probably sit at home
staring at their shit.
I clicked it.
Why?
Didn't you say you made it just for me?
Yes, I did it for you, Milk.
I didn't make it for anyone else.
-Why did you post it?
-What?
Everyone else liked it. Except you.
Do you care more about those 10,000 views?
Wait, Milk.
What's wrong with you?
Of course, I care about you more.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have made it.
Take it down then.
You can't, right?
Why do I have to take it down?
EDIT PROFILE PHOTO
UPLOAD NEW PHOTO
"Your degree of bliss while in love
in retrospect will be the degree of sorrow
you feel but multiplied many times."
Sathu.
Did you break up with Puan?
No.
All his Facebook posts
sound like he's dying.
What a wimp.
He even posted Buddha quotes.
Just click "like" and he will feel better.
Why are you so mad at him anyway?
It was good.
Pretty Ugly music video, you know?
I wish I had one.
If he didn't love you,
he wouldn't have made it.
Actually, I am not that mad.
I'm just annoyed that he's so cocky.
You are just jealous
of the 10,000 likes he got.
No, I'm not.
You know, I clicked "like" too.
Don't be jealous of me.
Oh, god. Can you do it again?
Grab mine too.
Your name is Milk but you've got no milk.
What about you? Have you got any?
THE WATER THAT RUNS THROUGH
SHOWER IS JUST LIKE RAIN...
HOW ARE YOU? ARE YOU DEAD YET?
Puan, why aren't you wearing a shirt?
-Oh, no.
-Puan, why are you naked?
How's this shirt? Do you like it?
I heard you are a devout Buddhist now.
Yes.
1,872 LIKES 0 DISLIKE
Are you happy now?
Not really.
Why not?
I am sad
that you are mad at me.
You're being too extra.
Stop being sad.
I will
sing you a song.
Can you play it now?
Yes.
Goodnight, Puan.
Why did you do that?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about this stupid clip.
I played it for you only.
Why did you upload it?
I was happy that you played it for me.
I posted it as a thank you present.
Did I do something wrong?
Come in person if you want to thank me.
You can call me.
We can talk via Skype.
Look how inappropriate my clothes are.
Take it down right now.
But all the comments are positive.
BEAUTIFUL VOICE
SHE'S ADORABLE AND HER VOICE IS GREAT
OFFBEAT BUT WHO CARES?
HER FACE IS PRETTY
PLAY A SEXY SONG NEXT TIME
SO SLUTTY
SHE IS CUTE
AT 1:45 TIME MARK, I GOT TURNED ON
Take it down right now.
I'M OUT OF JUICE BECAUSE OF HER
I said, take it down.
2,711 LIKES 22 DISLIKES
Puan.
Are you listening to me?
We can talk after you take it down.
Puan!
All right, Milk.
I took it down.
DELETED
I'm hungry.
Milk, wait.
Milk.
Wait.
I already took it down.
What else do you want?
The damage has already been done, Puan.
Then
what do you want me to do?
Ask the people on the internet.
What if I stop using Facebook,
and YouTube?
Will you stop being mad at me?
Please?
Milk.
You're so cute.
Fuck you.
THE OLD CLIP WAS DELETED
SO I REPOSTED THE CLIP I SAVED
TO SHARE HER CUTENESS WITH THE WORLD
THIS WILL BE MY LAST STATUS UPDATE
GOODBYE
Hello.
I'm Puan.
I'm the one who posted the clip
of my girlfriend playing the song
"You are the Gift"
on ukelele a few days ago.
After I posted the clip,
there were some comments
that I didn't expect,
and my girlfriend didn't like them.
So she told me to take it down.
And I did.
But there were some people
who downloaded the clip
and reposted it.
That's why the clip is still on YouTube.
I tried to contact
the person who posted it
but couldn't reach him.
I tried to call Milk,
but I couldn't reach her either.
She probably
doesn't want to talk to me anymore.
I made this clip
because I want to apologize
to my girlfriend.
And I think this is
the only way to do it.
This clip is not meant to be shared
because I only want
one person to see it.
I WISH HIS GIRLFRIEND COULD SEE IT
That one person is
Milk, my girlfriend.
Milk.
IS THIS AN ADVERTISEMENT?
I'm sorry.
Everything was my fault.
You don't have to stop being mad at me.
Please give me
another chance.
WHY ARE YOU APOLOGIZING TO A COMPUTER?
WHY SAY ALL THIS TO THE INTERNET?
IF I WERE YOU, I WOULD BE APOLOGIZING
IN FRONT OF HER HOUSE
I'M IN FRONT OF HER HOUSE NOW
THANK YOU, EVERYONE
Milk.
I'm sorry.
About the clip,
I will track down
and delete those remaining ones.
My friend is an expert on programming.
If I post anything again,
I will ask you first, all right?
PUAN, THAT'S ENOUGH
I WISH HIS GIRLFRIEND COULD SEE IT
I ALREADY APOLOGIZED,
BUT SHE WOULDN'T COME OUT
SHE SENT ME A TEXT SAYING "THAT'S ENOUGH"
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
NO MESSAGES
You asked people on the internet
what you should do next.
I don't think
you need to do anything anymore.
Feel free to do whatever you want.
Post whatever you want.
You'll be fine without me.
You have tons of people
who love you out there.
YOU ARE THE GIFT
This looks good.
I want to eat a watermelon.
Stop spinning so hard.
-You can stop filming.
-Why?
This is
our first date after Valentine's Day.
I want the world to know
that I love Milk.
I love Milk!
Milk!
I love you.
If that wasn't enough,
you can replay it yourself.
Did you take my phone?
I just want to say
the only person who can make me smile
is you, Milk.
He's here.
CAN I TALK TO YOU?
Jon, come out and talk to me.
Jon.
Jon, come out.
Everyone, welcome to
the Back of House Tour.
In a minute,
you will get to closely observe
how marine creatures are taken care of
here in Siam Ocean World.
Jon!
How are you?
Please return to your group?
We must go as a group.
Follow everyone else.
It's me, Mam.
Who?
Do you really not recognize me?
I'm a superstar.
Bamrung, it's all right.
She's my friend. I'll take care of her.
All right?
Jon.
What time will you be off?
Let's go eat.
It's been a while.
We've got so much to catch up on.
If you're here to talk about the movie,
I've already talked to the director.
I'm not taking the role.
You should go.
Jon.
Don't be like this.
Do you have any idea how hard it was
to get a hold of you?
You wouldn't come out to see me.
I called so many times
but you wouldn't pick up.
I don't pick up calls from strangers.
Am I a stranger to you now?
Why are you here again?
To get my stuff.
SEA YOU SCRIPT
JON
MAM
Have you decided?
Is it going to be the rich playboy
or that lame singer?
SUPERSTAR GOSSIP
NO CLOSURE, LOVE TRIANGLE
If the old one was good,
I wouldn't have to find a new guy.
No.
Oh, no.
Shit.
Excuse me. It's nine o'clock.
We are already closed.
Oh, my friend is in the restroom.
Jon.
You, again?
Doesn't your boyfriend mind
when you stalk men like this?
Me?
No one would dare to.
Jon.
Jon, you haven't answered whether
you will be in the movie Sea You.
Nobody's going to watch this movie.
The first one was seven years ago.
-No one even remembers it.
-Are you crazy?
It made 100 million baht.
No one would forget that.
I think everyone's waiting for the
sequel. Please?
Please?
Can you take a good look at me first?
I don't think you've changed that much.
I know now
why you can't be with anyone.
It's because
you only think about yourself.
KAJON SUWANNAMED FROM SEA YOU
And those are the nominees for
"Best Rising Actor" of the year.
And now, please welcome
last year's winner, Mr. Jack Chalermpol.
He will announce
this year's Best Rising Actor.
It's an honor to have him here tonight.
And the award
for Best Rising Actor goes to...
my beloved brother,
Jon, Kajon Suwannamed.
Congratulations to Jon.
Please give a small speech for us tonight.
Thank you for this award.
This movie
helped me to get to know a lot of people.
I met this woman while filming.
I loved her very much.
But now,
she has become a slut.
I don't get it.
The more famous, the sluttier she got.
Since you want to break up,
let's just announce it here.
That bitch and I
are over.
Now that
everyone knows about our real score,
you are free to do whatever you want.
Go.
Go with him.
I've cleared the path for you.
Jon, come on. Don't do this. Calm down.
-Are you happy now?
-Jon, many people are here.
It's not your business!
All right. The Dive Communication Show
has come to an end.
Please give a round of applause to Jon.
Thank you.
Does anyone have any questions?
Do you want to ask him something?
Ask him something.
Why me? I don't want to.
-You ask.
-Why?
I'll do it.
Jon.
We need to talk to Director Ton.
Everyone's waiting for your answer.
They'll have a press conference soon.
Go home, Mam. We'll talk later.
Kids.
Did you know that I and Jon
used to be in a movie together?
It was very popular.
Raise your hand if you have seen it.
If not, it's okay.
Because there will be a sequel soon.
But you won't get to see it
if he doesn't come out
of the tank to talk to me.
So let's call out
his name
and clap all together, okay?
One, two, three.
-Jon!
-Louder!
-That's great. Louder!
-Jon!
In the previous one, it ended
with the couple falling in love, right?
This sequel starts with us being a couple
fighting and breaking up.
"Will they get back together again?
Stick around to find out in...
Sea You Again
part two."
I remember the synopsis that Ton sent me.
Oh, no.
I like it.
I think the story has matured.
In this sequel,
there will be no senseless fighting.
No revenge.
No unpleasantness.
It will be all about love
and forgiveness.
BITCH
We can't be in this movie together.
What is your reason
for not taking the role?
Is it because you're fat?
Jon, you can lose weight
and look good again in no-time.
Oh, I know.
Your girlfriend won't let you
work with your ex, right?
Is she afraid an old flame might reignite?
Tell her not to worry.
I won't steal you from her.
Don't tell me you are still single.
Single or not, it doesn't matter.
I won't star in it.
Jon.
Didn't you say
you loved this film so much?
Jon.
You're still cute.
Tomorrow, let's go to Ton's office.
See you at ten o'clock, okay?
Are you here for the casting?
I'm here to see Director Ton.
He isn't available.
He's casting actresses.
What movie is the casting for?
Sea You Again.
For which part?
We're casting for the lead actress.
For the lead actress, why?
Because we still have not casted
the lead actress, that's why.
That's not possible!
Are you here to audition or not?
If so,
then fill out the application form.
Here's the script.
I will call you
when it's your turn.
SEA YOU AGAIN
Jon.
The press will ask you about
being nominated for Best Rising Actor.
Do you remember your answers?
Just stick to the script.
-Okay.
-Great.
Babe.
The script is very good, right?
No, I won't let you take it.
Why not?
What kind of a movie
has a kissing scene on every page?
Can you be reasonable?
I am being reasonable.
You're being childish.
Why? I want to star in it.
The director is very talented.
He received so many awards.
Let him be.
Deaw Patcharawit is the actor.
Don't you know that he's a prick?
His nickname is Tongue-zilla.
So what?
You know about it and so that's why
you wanted that role, right?
That's sick.
Is that all you can think about?
Mam, we heard that you will be starring
with Deaw Patcharawit, is it true?
Yes, it's true.
Jon, why are you letting Mam work
with the actor known as "Tongue-zilla"?
It's her career,
her lips, her tongue.
It has nothing to do with me.
Excuse me.
One more question, please.
He has to get ready. We are sorry.
What's wrong? Why did Jon just walk out?
-What's going on?
-Is something wrong?
SEA YOU
Sorry, the number you have dialed
isn't in service.
Hello. I'm here to audition
for Sea You Again.
-Please read the script.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Peak!
-Noona!
-Peak!
Oh, my god! How are you? Long time no see.
You're still slim as always.
You, too.
I miss you so much. How are you?
Are you here to audition for the role too?
Yes, I really want this role.
I'm sure whoever gets this role
will be famous.
How come the previous couple
won't star in this sequel?
It's been seven years.
Nobody knows where the lead actor is.
But I think
their time has passed.
The girl is not famous anymore.
Now she's just a supporting actress.
If she didn't spread her legs so often,
she wouldn't even make the news.
I've never watched this movie before.
What is it about?
I was only in fifth grade then.
Well...
If I remember correctly,
it's about two strangers
who went on a trip together
and agreed not to tell
each other what their name is.
-Really?
-Yes.
What a cool plot!
-She sounds easy.
-If you really don't know it,
it would best to just shut up.
It's about two people who hate each other
but are forced to be together.
CAN TWO PEOPLE WHO HATE
EACH OTHER, FALL IN LOVE?
-Mam, it's the trailer. Come here.
-Is it here?
The highlight
of the Music Festival this year
is Zea from the band, To Die For
featuring with the boys from F14.
ZEA
THE ROCK STAR
We are
To Die For!
RANG
THE BOY BAND DANCER
THE LEAST FAMOUS ONE AMONGST ALL
TWO DIFFERENT PEOPLE
WHO MISSED THE FLIGHT TOGETHER
-How much is it to go to that island?
-Hey, Panda Eyes!
Are you sure you want to go there?
It's dangerous. You shouldn't.
It's easy for you to say.
You are just one of the F14 gay boys.
If you go missing,
nobody will even notice.
"It's dangerous. You shouldn't."
"It's easy for you to say.
You are just one of the F14 gay boys.
If you go missing,
nobody will even notice."
Did you just call me gay?
-I'll show you my manhood.
-No.
Miss.
I thought you were dead.
It seems like
we are the only ones here.
Why am I trapped on an island
with a pathetic guy like you?
How can you love me?
You hate my guts.
You don't even know
my band's songs.
I just know that
when I am with you,
I am so damn happy.
Is this what they call love?
When we get to the shore,
will we hate each other again?
TWO PEOPLE WHO HATE EACH OTHER...
ARE ABOUT TO FALL IN LOVE
SEA YOU
CASTING FOR SEA YOU AGAIN
-This way.
-Okay.
-Your audition went very well.
-Really?
-Thank you so much, Ice.
-Thank you, Director Ton.
-I will--
-Director Ton.
Why are you holding castings?
What about me and Jon?
If Jon isn't the lead,
then you can't be the lead either.
But I found Jon already.
He is on his way here.
Mam, if Jon was interested,
he would have been here already.
-I'll leave now--
-Director Ton.
Let's do this then.
Well...
Give me
the lead actress role.
You can cast the lead actor.
All right?
You don't need to cast the lead actress.
Listen, Mam.
You don't get it,
do you?
You and Jon are meant to star together.
Either you star together
or you don't at all.
Do you understand?
Have you watched Full House?
They're about to have a sequel.
Without Rain...
Without Rain,
who would Song Hye-kyo star with?
Will she star with Jang Geun-suk?
Jang Geun-suk and Song Hye-kyo?
That won't work. Do you understand?
You are watching
the Ocean Walker show.
If anybody is interested
in an underwater walk,
please contact our staff.
The next story is about the movie
we've all have been waiting for
Sea You Again.
That's right. After an exhausting search
for a lead couple,
everyone's been guessing
who would they be.
Finally, the next 100 million baht
box office film
has got its new leading stars.
Peach Pachara and Ice Preechaya
will be the new starring couple.
The director said that
he changed the main cast
to keep the story fresh.
The script was also updated
to make the main cast appeal younger.
Cut!
Get ready for the next scene.
Hurry up. The sun will set soon.
Cut. I said cut!
I thought I was going to die down there.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Really?
Here.
Thank you.
After we finish filming, what will you do?
I will go back
to get my marine biology degree.
What about you?
-I'll probably audition for a movie.
-Again?
Do you like being an actress?
It's my life and soul.
It makes me very happy.
Especially,
when people love and admire me,
it feels really great.
Don't you like being an actor?
I don't like acting.
Why did you accept this movie then?
Because of you.
After filming is done,
will we still see each other every day?
Of course.
Couples are supposed to
see each other every day.
How could he do that?
Is he crazy?
How can Sea You not be starred by us, Jon?
But I think we still have time.
It's not too late.
Director Ton will give us a chance, Jon.
Let me be straightforward.
This movie is my last chance.
I want to be a star again.
Your line starts here.
The highlighted ones are mine.
In this scene, the couple
already broke up
and they happened to meet again.
Let's pretend
that we are stuck on an island,
surrounded by fish
swimming all around us.
Are you ready?
Yes.
"How long has it been
since we last saw each other?"
"Since the concert last year,
when you wrote that song to curse me
and sang it on stage."
"You only remember
the bad memories, right?"
"Were there any good ones?"
"I'm sorry.
I am sorry for acting like a fool
and making you sad."
"But you were like that...
because of me too."
"So how have you been?"
"I've been good.
You were not there to nag me
for waking up late,
for leaving my clothes on the floor,
for not eating on time,
and for not putting lotion on before bed.
It was great."
"Do you think about those things?"
"Don't you?"
"No.
Because I never felt...
like you were gone."
"Rang.
Do you think
we can love each other again?"
ZEA: DO YOU THINK WE CAN LOVE
EACH OTHER AGAIN?
According to the script,
Rang has to kiss Zea.
RANG BENDS DOWN TO KISS ZEA
Gosh, can you kiss
like two people who are actually in love?
If you guys still can't kiss,
I will show you how to do it.
Jon.
I'm begging you.
Please focus.
Let's do it in one take.
Hey, try looking at each other.
Stare into each other's eyes.
Yes, like that.
Now, try to imagine what Zea and Rang
have gone through together
and their relationship.
They won't see each other again.
Jon.
Think about Rang and Zea.
Think about when they loved each other.
Think about when they fought so much...
that they had to break up.
Think about when they were alone.
It must have been lonely.
But now,
they ran into each other again.
"How long has it been
since we last saw each other?"
Well.
"Since the concert last year,
when you wrote that song to curse me
and sang it on stage."
"You only remember
the bad memories, right?"
"Were there any good ones?"
I'm sorry.
I am sorry for making you sad.
I was stupid.
Why did I have to be so damn jealous?
That was bad for us.
I've blamed myself every day.
Why did I have to be such an asshole?
I am sorry.
"But you were like that...
because of me too."
I'm sorry.
"So how have you been?"
"I've been good.
You were not there to nag me
for waking up late,
for leaving my clothes on the floor,
for not eating on time,
and for not putting lotion on before bed.
It was great."
"Do you think about those things?"
"Don't you?"
"No.
Because I never felt like you were gone."
"Do you think
we can love each other again?"
Do you think we can love each other again?
That was amazing.
You've made Rang and Zea
come back to life again.
But...
you haven't been
watching the news, have you?
That was the end
of the Dive Communication Show.
Please give a round of applause to Jon.
Does anyone
have any questions for our diver?
Jon.
You already knew they changed
the leading cast, right?
You knew I wouldn't get
the role anyway, right?
Then why did you rehearse
the script with me?
Answer me.
Is something wrong with the mic?
Excuse me, Jim.
I'm Jon.
Jon.
Do I make you nervous?
No.
Have you ever had a girlfriend?
Then, you've never hugged a girl before.
I met you.
I got to know you.
I loved you.
She has become a slut.
I fought with you.
Ouch!
I broke up with you.
I hated you
because of this movie.
The reason I didn't want
to be in this movie
was because I didn't want
to love you again.
I understand.
I'm glad
I got to share that moment with you again.
Thank you, Jon.
Mam.
"Do you think
we can love each other again?"
"Do you think...
-we can love each other again?"
-Jon.
Isn't that supposed to be my line?
One, two.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One early morning,
a gun
was about to take
a woman's life.
Meanwhile, she tried to figure out
how to start her life over again
after the gun went off.
Bang.
Raise your hands in the air
and let me hear some noise!
This is the Bangkok Giant Marathon
for everyone who loves to run.
Please make some noise
and let me see a show of hands.
We are here to welcome
all the Bangkok Giant Marathon runners.
Please make some noise
when they reach the goal.
Up until now,
this woman still can't find a reason
for running in a 42.195km
marathon at 3 a.m.
She can't make sense of it.
If wasn't for that fateful day
four months ago...
What's the matter with you?
Didn't you see me?
What were you looking at?
Hey.
Look at your arm.
Hey! Who do you think you are?
Do you have another pair of glasses?
How about this?
Let's go to my car.
Do you have glasses in your car?
I got Betadine.
-Where do you think you're going?
-Easy!
SEA YOU AGAIN
If there wasn't any raining sound
that evening inside his car,
it would have been totally silent.
Why do you go there to run?
-The traffic is bad.
-Why?
If I run on the road,
people will think I am a boxer.
Excuse me.
Is this the reason why
you're running a marathon?
She is thinking
there must be a problem
that caused anyone to run a marathon.
How far is a marathon?
It's like from Bangkok
to Pathum Thani.
Is it the west side or the east side
of Pathum Thani?
What do you think about when you run?
Is it fun to run alone
without talking to anyone?
By the way,
about your glasses,
I'll buy a new pair for you.
There's no need.
How would you know my prescription?
And how will we meet again?
At that second,
no one knows what set her heart in motion.
Whether it's
the Betadine,
the rain,
the smell of his sweat in the car
or maybe it's the blurry image of him
caused by her bad eyesight.
Do you run here every day?
If I were a dog,
I would have peed on every light pole.
How will I recognize you?
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Well...
I don't know your name yet.
-Did I not tell you?
-What?
I never asked.
Keep the glasses.
-What?
-I don't need them anymore.
Thanks a lot.
Wait.
She thought
he was the type of person
she'd like to spend time with
even when she wanted to be alone.
Hello.
It's you.
This is for the sandal I broke.
It costs more than your glasses.
How would you know?
It's nice.
And how would you know it is nice?
I just think so.
You don't have to say that
to make me feel good.
Here.
If you can make me run 5km,
it will improve my golfing skills.
Do you
have a lot of free time?
I've got heaps.
It means I have a lot of time.
I see.
What year were you born in?
What year...
What year was it?
-Hey.
-What?
Even though we are not
competing with anyone,
we shouldn't let a grandpa overtake us.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Can we not run the opposite way?
Why not?
There is no rule that says we can't.
But still...
YEAR OF DOG, PIG, RAT, OX, TIGER, RABBIT,
DRAGON, SNAKE, HORSE, GOAT, MONKEY
Gosh, 24?
Shall we try walking?
Like fast walking?
Let me ask you something.
The day you ran into me,
did you really not see me?
What were you looking at?
Runners only focus
on what is seven feet ahead.
Our job is to keep running.
Do you see what happens
if you only look at the ground?
So asthma motivated you to run?
Yes.
The thing is,
when I was born,
the doctor told my parents
to not let me do sports
and let me take it easy.
So I always thought to myself,
"Is this
how my life is going to be?
Will I be sitting around like this?"
You know,
I run
because it's the only sport
that I can do in private.
Who are you hiding from?
Don't laugh at me.
The truth is
I didn't mean to run
the opposite way on that day.
But I saw my grandma's friend
doing Tai Chi here.
Your grandma's friend?
She's a trouble maker.
She reports things back to my family.
Think about it.
I even have to wash
my running clothes outside of the house.
Wow, that's bad.
You know,
I really like Pid,
the bass player of Bodyslam.
He's very strong.
While he is holding a big bass guitar,
he can lift his leg over an amplifier
as tall as my head.
-Really?
-Watch me.
Wasn't that cool?
He told her that
a marathon
is a world that
nobody around him understands.
It's like a secret garden
where only he can enter.
At least,
I have a goal for myself every year.
I see.
That's interesting.
Do you think
I can run a marathon?
Well...
Why don't you give it a try?
While they were walking and talking,
his touch
was like
a tender peel covering an orange
in her hand.
Hold on.
Let me ask you about the roses again.
It...
It has nothing to do with
you being broken-hearted, right?
Well...
If I send you an email,
will you reply to me?
Then, they both walked away
with a new feeling
that grew into their hearts.
That night,
he emailed her
the marathon running schedule
of Jeff Galloway.
Inside, it listed
the running distance
that keeps increasing every week
until the day of the marathon.
It meant
the marathon
she had no confidence in
or ever dreamed of being in
was about to become a reality.
ENJOY YOUR FIRST MARATHON
I don't know if she will enjoy it or not.
But the fact that
she came out to run with him for months
probably meant
she wanted to do something with her life.
It's something
that she was not sure
would be possible.
Hey.
Hurry.
Faster.
Come on.
-You must try harder.
-I can't anymore.
On the day of the marathon,
you must run for four to five hours.
You go first. I can't.
You are already three weeks
behind schedule.
-I can't. I'm so tired.
-Here.
Just a little further.
Endure it. Come on.
Just go. I really can't.
-Come on. Quick.
-You go.
I can't. I'm tired.
I really can't.
There's no way I'll make it.
Seriously,
I better quit.
I think you should stop
thinking negatively.
No matter how tired you are.
Tomorrow is a new day.
That's for sure.
Everybody will have a new day.
But a marathon is not for everybody.
I wasn't born with eight nostrils.
Listen.
No matter how difficult it is,
our body will adjust.
If you don't push yourself a bit more
or try a bit harder,
you will never
move forward with your life.
Let's go.
No.
Why do I have to run this stupid marathon
and make myself suffer
just to overcome asthma like you?
Did you think
running was going to be easy?
You don't have to pressure yourself
to do something you don't want to.
I want to run,
but I don't want to be tired.
That's up to you.
If you want to run, 1km is enough.
But if you want a new life,
then run a marathon.
The moment happened very fast.
She thought he must be mad
because he said
"Up to you."
She was in shock
staring at his back
while he was walking away.
She wanted to say sorry to him.
But she was afraid that
he might turn around and say,
"Sorry for what?
I am not your boyfriend."
Then it would make her so sad
and she would say,
"Forget about being your girlfriend.
I can't even be your friend."
Luckily, the thing she was afraid of
didn't actually happen.
The thing is,
I had a bad experience at the 35-km mark
and that had to do
with the dried roses in my car.
In the morning of the race,
I bought those roses
and kept them in my car.
I wanted to see them when I drove home.
I wanted to celebrate
because I proved my doctor wrong.
He told her
that he ran
on his first marathon last year.
I went without preparing myself
or doing any research.
I only trained for a week.
I didn't drink water or eat
before the race.
I only thought about
keeping my pace,
so I could finish it fast.
At around 30km, I passed out.
I was running but at a walking pace.
I ran even though I felt
there was a knife in my back.
Then there was a voice
of a devil from afar saying
"Who told you to run anyway?"
He could only run for another 3km.
At the 35-km mark,
the sound of the devil in his head
which everyone told him to ignore
started up again like clockwork.
"Hey, what the hell are you doing here?"
His knee led his leg one after the other
in slow motion.
Then suddenly his legs got weak
as if there was a chain
attached to his leg.
And then I answered the devil.
"Yes.
You're right."
What happened next?
Sir.
Then I...
DNF.
What?
I did not finish.
Well.
They put me on a stretcher.
Really?
So I put those roses
inside the glove compartment
and planned not to open it
until I finish 42km.
Until I carelessly opened it.
I am sorry.
You know,
On the day of the race, at the 28-km mark,
we will see the sunrise
beyond the Rama VIII Bridge.
It's so cool.
At this moment,
anyone who is watching this
will probably expect an inspirational song
playing in the background.
MARATHON RUNNING SCHEDULE
In Buddhism,
everything in this world
moves in a constant flux
until it encounters a turning point
or an outside force.
And this story of hers
was no exception.
PONGSAKORN THIPTHINNAKORN
1854 RATCHADAMRI ROAD, LUMPINI,
PATHUMWAN, BANGKOK
Once you run for a few months,
you will feel like
you aren't the same person anymore.
Did she hear that phrase?
"You aren't the same person."
It's the same phrase that her husband
whispered in her ear
while giving her the wedding ring.
"You aren't the same person anymore."
During these past few months,
she's never spoken of her husband's death,
not even once.
Even though
she still remembers everything
on the day he passed away.
Breaking news,
a plane broke apart into two pieces.
The front of the plane hit the sand wall.
The tail of the plane
is stuck on the runway.
The time,
the place,
the hands of her friend on her shoulder,
and even the lights
seemed to focus on her
more intensely that evening.
Hey.
This is Sairoong,
her young colleague
who became her best friend.
You got darker.
All the stuff on your desk is with me.
Are you coming back to work?
You? Run a marathon?
Do you live in the same condo?
Don't you pick up your phone?
And how come you didn't join
the dinner last time?
I was busy. I wanted to go, though. But...
something came up. I don't remember.
-It's okay.
-Next time.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine. I really am.
Sairoong knows her very well.
Are you afraid of someone coming that way?
You look that way every 15 seconds.
So the rumor of you running
with a young guy everyday...
is true?
The rumor that Sairoong heard about
was missing one detail.
-Besides being young,
-Hello.
he's good looking too.
Since when?
What?
When did you decide
to start seeing that boy?
I knew that you would say this
because if I were you,
I would say the same thing.
So what was all the drama five months ago
about loving only one man in your life?
I never forgot my late husband.
It's true
that there is a new man in my life.
She told Sairoong about him
and the stories he told her
about the running schedule,
Milo's principle,
and the devil at the 35-km mark.
Before Lumpini park was closed that night,
Sairoong asked her...
Hey.
Are you sure you're not going crazy?
I understand you must be lonely, but...
I am lonely
but I don't want to be sad.
She wasn't sure
if Sairoong would accept her or not
if she told her the real reason
in her mind.
I can't accept this.
That night,
she laid on the sofa
and stared at the faint light
shining through the curtains
like in those Kazakhstan films
with a heavy heart.
Hello, this is Pongsakorn speaking.
Please leave a message
after the beeping sound.
Thank you.
Hello, honey. Have you already decided?
I am done with work.
See? I told you it would only take a day.
You always exaggerate things.
-I told you so and you didn't believe me.
-The beach here is beautiful.
Why don't you show me
how to dive in the pool here?
I've shown you many times.
You must be bored of it by now.
This week is really busy.
I've been working non-stop. I'm tired.
I'm lazy too.
You should change your flight
and come back now.
Hello, this is Pongsakorn speaking.
Please leave a message
after the beeping sound.
Thank you.
Don't come back.
Sorry, the number you've dialed...
ARE YOU SICK?
I'M DOWNSTAIRS, I'M GOING UP TO SEE YOU
Hey.
Did you receive my messages?
I told you not to do that.
I told you that's not how it is, Pat.
What about those things?
I didn't do it.
Then what did you do?
Be reasonable, Pat.
She spoke to him
trying to keep it down
so that it would not echo.
But at that moment,
she couldn't
keep her voice calm.
If I want to keep seeing you,
I will go running with you.
But honestly,
this has gone too far.
You shouldn't waste your time on me.
Do you know
that you're the most pitiful one?
Why?
Hey.
You know Milo's principle.
You planned a 40km running schedule.
How come you don't know
the answer to this?
These last couple of months,
I've been trying to tell you
that I like you.
Your family won't be okay with me.
No family would be okay with me.
My family isn't okay
with the marathon either.
In 20 years,
do you want to feed me the food
that old people eat before going to bed?
If you want to have dinner,
go eat with your mom at home.
You don't want to regret it later, right?
Do you regret
anything now?
The devil at the 35-km and 36-km mark,
did it not warn you
about your actions now?
My husband just died earlier this year.
I know.
It was in the newspapers.
-I just--
-Why did you ask for my name
on the day you ran into me then?
I wanted you to think
I didn't know anything about you.
What if
I was a normal guy
and you were
a normal girl,
without your husband...
could we be together?
What makes you think we could?
My instinct tells me so.
Either you watch too many movies,
or you are too young.
I am young,
but not that young.
I'm sorry.
I am not amused by your teenage quip.
Right before
you came to see me,
I was looking at myself in the mirror.
It was the first time in a few months
that I took a good look at myself.
I never felt
like I betrayed my husband
until today.
Do you know
what promise I have given him
at his grave?
I promised
that I would not love another man.
Thank you for introducing me to marathons.
But I don't want to see your face anymore.
That was an amazing story.
A group of teenagers fought
and the bullet
killed an unlucky crocodile...
After that day,
she thought about starting her life over.
But she could only turn on the TV
and pretend to watch Sairoong's show.
Or sometimes
she would turn her back towards the park
while the Skytrain approached
the park's station.
On a sunny day,
she thought of retiring her shoes,
just like those
retired football players do
when they stop using their studs.
It was a Saturday morning in October.
Her mom came to visit
with souvenirs from China.
Her mom asked her about work.
When are you going back to work?
In a while.
And then her mom made breakfast for her.
Even though her mom
didn't make it obvious,
a lot of little things made her feel
like her mom wanted to talk
about something.
Mom.
Did Sairoong tell you?
Yes, yesterday.
I met her and she told me.
Oh, no.
She couldn't think of anything
to say to her mom.
She told me
you're going to run a marathon.
Be careful not to break your legs.
On my way up,
someone asked me to give this to you.
I guess he tried to call
but your phone must be off.
YOU'RE INVITED TO BANGKOK GIANT MARATHON
ENJOY YOUR FIRST MARATHON TOMORROW MORNING
This time,
he really made her heart skip a beat.
Taste it.
-It's good.
-Okay.
And who was that guy?
Kids these days are so good looking.
Was he your trainer?
That's good. He can look after you.
While her mom was cooking that morning,
food was the last thing on her mind.
These past few months,
practicing for the marathon
gave her peace.
Living life seemed to get easier.
But right now she is afraid that
if she stays in this room,
she will keep staring into the mirror
over and over again.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
I want my new life to begin
with the sound of the gun going off.
I don't want to just run.
I want to start a new life.
I'm sure.
I want my car to smell like sweat, too.
I see the sunrise
at the Rama VIII Bridge now.
If I didn't run,
I wouldn't have seen the sunrise.
Come on. You're almost there.
I want to confront my devil
at the 35-km mark.
We have reached
the point of the race
where we all feel alone
and must make a decision.
We must ask ourselves
"How badly do we want to finish?"
Miss.
Do you need a ride?
And we must find the answer on our own.
What kilometer is this?
I don't know.
She never thought
she would end up on this road
at the age of 42.
Thank you.
Miss, just a bit further.
You haven't stopped running
in the opposite direction.
What took you so long?
I was waiting for you at the finish line.
Yesterday, did you tell my mom
that you would look after me?
Well...
It wasn't exactly like that.
What did my mom tell you?
Well.
-She said--
-I'm kidding.
Let's go!
She was thinking that in reality,
her past and memories did not exist.
Right now,
it was just a matter
of moving her legs
to keep moving forward.
You go first.
Come with me.
Come on. Just a bit more.
You go first.
I can't go on anymore.
Stop being pessimistic.
How hard can 2km be?
Tomorrow is a new day.
Don't you remember?
Give me your hand.
I already bought the roses.
Let's go.
Come on.
If there was no pain to endure,
why would anyone want to run a marathon?
They both ran for six hours,
slower than the fastest runner
by three and a half hours.
The finish line is there for all runners,
whether you're the first
or the 1,500th runner.
Everyone who crosses the finish line
will be treated as a winner.
By the way,
what did you say
to the devil at the 35-km mark?
She knew now that
despite what she told the devil,
she was not the same person anymore.
And this
is the only purpose humans live for.
Move forward
to cover the seven feet in front of you,
and look forward to the changes coming
in the next seven feet ahead.
Subtitle translation by Joey Vajrabukka