[Bright speaking Thai]
[Bright] Why do all we modern girls
have to rely on ourselves more?
Good men are not easy to find.
The female population is three times
higher than the male one.
Besides, some of them
tend to like each other.
But we don't really care
if nobody hits on us.
These days, women are smarter
and become more successful.
Many of us must be sick and tired
of letting men take the lead.
LET'S BREAK UP
Those who have had enough of being in love
set many rules for a new relationship,
become choosy,
or set their expectations too high.
If that's you, prepare yourself
to join the single ladies club.
Well, whether you're single
intentionally or not,
kind of single, forced to be single,
completely single, single but waiting,
single and daydreaming,
single and feisty, or whatever,
the fact is, we are on our own.
How many times have we wrestled
with this depressing label?
Stop caring about this word.
If having a boyfriend is bad,
then why bother?
We rather invest our time in making money
and stop being obsessed
and wasting time with this nonsense.
[inaudible conversation]
BRIGHT ON SINGLEHOOD
Let's change the way we look at it.
Actually,
being single is good in many ways.
There are always moments
we can find happiness
because our life is ours.
Why would we live it in depression?
When we are single,
we have lots of time to do many things.
It's a reward in our life.
BE SINGLE AND FABULOUS
[message notifications beeping]
All single girls have to be determined
to be independent.
If we haven't found the right one yet,
just stay fabulous.
Better we spend our precious time
in finding ourselves some happiness.
[audience applauding]
And what's the key factor
that makes you the idol of single ladies?
The answer is in this book.
We can still be happy,
even when we are all by ourselves.
[applauding]
Thank you very much, Bright.
Thank you.
[woman] Excuse me.
Sorry, sorry.
Can you sign a book for me?
Oops! Wrong one.
Sign this for me, please.
Have you figured out your life?
What do you choose?
I use your book to recharge my batteries
during singlehood
and have energy to search for my soulmate.
[announcer]
Please give Nida a round of applause.
Thank you. See you.
[Nida] Hello to all the fans.
Finding Mr. Right.
Mmm. She is looking
for her soulmate over there.
You are preaching
about being single over here.
Looks like we have a rivalry.
Come on, what rivalry?
We are just different.
She is living in a world full of rainbows.
The greatest gift in a woman's life is
the love that God has given us
to get rid of loneliness
on a lonely night.
I do believe
that we weren't created to be alone
because we all have
a soulmate waiting for us.
You have to find him,
so you can truly fulfill your life
with the happiness that love brings you.
I hope my book holds
a special place in your heart.
Thank you.
That sounds so delusional.
What's with all that looking
for a soulmate? [scoffs]
You should look for romance.
Come on. I've seen it all.
I can be romantic on my own.
Goodbye.
I'll see you to the door.
[elevator dings]
Thank you.
Oh, Bright, don't forget
the interview
for the Women Magazine award.
Yes.
Bye.
#SINGLE LADY
[man] As I have explained,
with the changes happening,
we may let go of some employees.
I'd like all of us
to be prepared for these changes
and cooperate with our partner in the USA.
[woman] I think we're gonna get fired.
Calm down. It might not be you.
A poster child like you
doesn't have to worry.
[women exclaim]
Hey, it's my birthday.
Oh, I forgot.
Let me make a wish.
Mmm, mmm!
I know what you are wishing for.
Come on. Give me some support.
Are you leaving me?
I love you the most.
Let's blow the candles.
-[upbeat dance music playing]
-[people cheering]
-[glasses clinking]
-[women cheering]
[cheering]
Give me a double. Make it strong.
Excuse me.
Yes.
What's your name?
Oil.
Pardon me?
Yes.
I'm Win.
[notification chimes]
OIL
THANK YOU, MY LOVELY SIS.
YOU HAVE MADE MY WISH COME TRUE.
MISS YOU.
I WISH FOR YOU TO FIND TRUE LOVE.
-[keys clacking]
-[mouse clicks]
[Bright] Eventually,
the last thing a woman wants is...
love.
IS...LOVE
[light switch clicks]
[Oil] Bright, let's take photos.
[both cheering]
You are so beautiful!
Take some photos with me.
[photographer] Okay, good.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I wouldn't be here without you.
That has nothing to do with me.
It's up to both of you.
Well, divorce him
if he's not the right one
and come back
to join my single ladies club.
-[Win laughs]
-Sure.
Don't forget to get spousal support.
So cruel.
More photos.
[camera shutter clicks]
[children] Aunty, can I get some cake?
[child] Aunty, give me cake, please.
Here it is.
Aunty, can I have some cake?
[girl] Let me have pink.
[boy 1] Aunty, I want the blue one.
[Bright] Okay, blue, it is.
-[boy 2] I want the blue one too.
-[snickers]
What are you laughing at?
No, I'm not laughing at you.
You're looking in my direction.
What should I think?
I was just thinking.
Can I not laugh at my own thought?
Then you should keep laughing
in your mind too.
[boy 1] Aunty, can I have some more?
[boy 2] Aunty, me too.
Aunty, one more.
Aunty, give me one.
Aunty, can you give me some cake?
I'm going.
It's hard to talk to an old lady.
Hey, kids!
Please don't.
Don't call a lady "Aunty," okay?
It's not polite.
You should call her "Granny."
May, is it you?
No, I don't know.
Go. Take these kids with you.
Go, fatty. Go.
Wait. Call me "Sis" now!
-[women cheering]
-Get closer, ladies.
Get closer. Come on.
Hey. No need to push, okay?
It's more fun to fight for it.
-[women assenting]
-Come on. The bride asked for this.
She wants you to get it.
The strongest wins, okay?
Come on.
How about, if anyone gets the flower,
my grandpa will read your future for free?
[exclaims]
Fortuneteller!
May, you're married.
Why would you want this?
I don't care.
For the fortuneteller, I'll fight for it!
-Come on. Are you ready?
-[women cheering]
I'm throwing it now.
Ready? Ready?
Have your fortune read for free!
Will you just keep looking?
She's difficult, this one.
But maybe this is your soulmate.
Things like that are fairy tales.
[speaking Hindi]
[Win in Thai]
My grandfather can't speak Thai.
I'll translate for you.
My grandfather
specializes in love and relationships.
-Yes, that's spot on.
-[women exclaim]
It's something I...
Something I really want to know.
You girls want to know
my story more than I do.
We wouldn't be here
if we didn't want to know.
[women laughing]
He will read the future
based on the marks on your body
because it's like a trace
of how we live our lives.
[grandfather speaking Hindi]
[in Thai] You have five moles.
Five moles?
[speaking Hindi]
[in Thai] On your hand.
[woman] Hey, there.
[women exclaim]
You really do.
[speaking Hindi]
[Win in Thai] Shoulder.
Right here.
[speaking Hindi]
[Win in Thai] On the back of your ear.
Oh, that's a big one. Look!
[speaking Hindi]
[Win in Thai] On your leg.
Here, spot on.
[speaking Hindi]
[in Thai] And the last one
is underneath your clothes.
[May] Let me see!
Come on!
No, I mean on your breast.
[women exclaim]
[woman] You nearly get to strip.
[May] Accurate.
Spooky.
[speaking Hindi]
[grandfather continues speaking Hindi]
[in Thai] My grandfather said
you have a soulmate
waiting for you to marry him.
[women exclaim]
I told you, you won't be single forever.
[Win] But it is because
you have upset someone a long time ago.
And his resentment has become a curse.
That's why you haven't found your soulmate
and have never had a solid relationship.
What should she do? [inhales sharply]
And is he one of her exes?
I think so.
[women exclaim]
Win, ask him how to fix it.
[Win] He said
you have to help that person
get back on the right track.
If you can, the door will open,
and you will find him
and be happy with love.
[women exclaim]
That's not too difficult.
Win, please ask him,
who is that guy?
-[sighs]
-[Win] He said
you have to find out yourself.
[May] Okay, goodbye world.
I can't help with that.
[speaking Hindi]
[in Thai] He also said
you have to do it soon.
The longer you wait,
the less time you have.
And you won't be happy again.
[woman] Geez! Bright!
[May] Looks like you're in trouble again.
No boyfriend is okay,
but no happiness even at work?
[overlapping conversation]
It might not be true.
[man] The board
hasn't decided yet what to do
with highly paid staff like you.
So they decided to suspend you
from the office.
If there are any decisions
made after the restructure,
I'll be in touch.
[woman] I can't believe
it turns out to be you.
You are so competent,
yet they kick you out.
[woman] Bright.
Bright.
[Bright] Yes?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Can you repeat the question?
I can't quite follow.
Is everything okay, Bright?
You don't seem focused,
unlike your blog.
You are an idol for single ladies.
You look worried.
What's wrong?
[woman] Bright!
Bright, hello.
I'm so happy. It's such an honor
to have been nominated
in the same award as my idol.
Can I shake your hand?
If you quit your job and only write books,
I'm sure you'll be successful.
Hey!
If you want to rub it in
that I've lost my job, just say it.
Stop being pretentious.
Excuse me?
Pretentious?
I don't understand.
Enough, you angel wannabe!
And stop giving people hope
with your romantic shit.
It can never happen in real life.
Nonsense!
[gasps]
I didn't mean it that way.
I might have misunderstood.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
Nida, the judges are waiting
for the interview.
[camera shutter clicks]
[child] Hey, please get my kite for me.
Here.
-Thank you.
-All right.
It's a small world.
What are you doing here?
Waiting for you, maybe?
This is a public place.
Why can't I come?
I get a headache talking to you.
Why are you so frustrated?
Are you worried about
fixing your fortune with you ex?
How do you know?
I was there when
Win's grandfather talked to you.
I don't care about fixing my fortune.
And I don't think I'll do it.
Isn't it a risk?
Not having a boyfriend is fine,
but the part
about never being happy again,
doesn't that scare you?
What's your nickname?
Oh, the single ladies' idol.
So are you afraid
of going back to your ex?
Come on.
Just think of it
as revisiting the good old days.
[plane landing]
[Bright] Mom, I'm here.
What's the name
of that place where we used to live?
Come on. It's been a while.
[camera shutter clicking]
[child] Bright!
Bright!
Aunt Nong! Aunt Nong!
[Bright] Aunt Nong.
Aunt Nong.
Bright, is it you?
[Bright] Things don't change much here.
I don't know
what my old friends will be like.
Aunty.
My friend, the tan, chubby one.
What's his name? I can't remember.
Your boyfriend, Jack?
He is not my boyfriend.
If you want to meet him,
just wait in front of the school
in the evening.
Jackass.
Jack.
Take your pick.
Five baht.
[school bell ringing]
[woman] Are you looking for Jack?
Not that meatballs guy.
You want Stingy Jack. He'll come around.
There he is, speak of the devil.
Hello! You're busy today.
Aunty.
You can get your underling to collect it.
This small amount isn't worth your petrol.
Oh, with money stuff, I trust no one.
One black coffee. I'll be back.
Okay.
Oi...
It's mine.
-What the hell are you looking at?
-[woman] Jack.
Jack.
What?
That lady is looking for you.
-Who is it?
-Back there.
[kids] Guys, attack!
[boy exclaiming]
You are thirsty, aren't you?
[bullies exclaiming]
I'll make you pay for this.
[boy 1] I'll see you next time.
I'll return.
[young Bright] Stop giving up.
You should fight.
Come here.
If you want to join the gang,
you have to accompany me home.
Very good.
It takes patience to be my sidekick.
Hurry!
I have something to tell you.
I'm very rich now.
I received an inheritance
from my grandmother.
Money, gold, properties...
You see those buildings?
They pay the rent to me.
They can't see rich people.
They're jealous.
You're wealthy.
You must be married then?
What a pity for me.
Not yet.
Oh...
It's difficult to find real people.
Girls only look for money.
Who could love us
like we loved each other
when we were kids?
I've never forgotten you.
Really?
I better go collect the rent.
I'll come back to pick you up for dinner.
I'll show you around.
Sure.
Your room number?
It's six... No. It's nine.
Number six... Nine.
Nok, bring some drinks for your customer!
-[Nok] All right.
-Can't you see? Bad service.
They don't hate that you're rich.
They just hate your guts.
Keep raising the rent every month,
try to make us leave...
You look forward
to selling to that capitalist.
Asshole!
Bri, Bry, Brai...
Bright.
Plus... Jack.
A... Seven
Bright plus Jack.
Now that she knows I've become rich,
she rushes back to me.
At least she's pretty,
even though she's a bit too old.
But it's okay.
I'll do you good tonight.
LOVE AT FIRST SIGHT CAFÉ
[singing in Thai]
You haven't had your drink.
[Bright] It's enough.
Come on, just a little.
Is it flat? Let me mix it.
[Bright] Jack, it's too strong.
Come on, here.
[Jack laughs]
Darling, you didn't give me
garlands tonight.
You normally tip us every time.
Not now. Don't you see I have a guest?
Go. Get lost.
Just a little bit.
Go!
[hostess 1] Does he even look at himself?
[hostess 2] If he weren't rich,
I wouldn't even look at him.
He is so ugly,
and what's with that haircut?
Don't you have friends here?
People here are divided,
the rich and the poor.
But it's okay.
I'm rich anyway.
Come on. Bottoms up.
Yeah, like that.
[dogs howling]
[softly] Hey, Jack.
[bike stand rattles]
[dogs continue howling]
Do you remember this tree?
We used to come and play around here.
You and I carved our names on it too. See?
Bright plus Jack.
And we played "Mommy and Daddy" here too.
Hmm. You played Mommy.
I played Daddy.
Hey, Jack.
Let's get back to the good old days.
Jack, are you crazy?
Are you out of your mind?
How could you do this, Jack?
This, too.
What you carved here.
Look, the resin is still running.
What?
You flirted with me back there.
Well, well, well...
You want a higher price because I'm rich?
You want more money?
Jack, don't.
[Jack groans]
I felt sorry for you and wanted to help.
But if you've become an asshole like this,
you can go to hell.
[Jack groans]
Do you think you can get away?
I will warn you just once.
Stop bullying people with your wealth.
It's not nice.
You've changed so much.
The Jack I knew was not like this.
I've become like this because of you!
You didn't keep your promise.
[May laughs]
You've kept your virginity for so long.
Almost got laid?
What did you promise him
for him to do that to you?
There's always something like that
with kids.
[May] Ah.
Let's not talk about this now.
God, couldn't it be someone else?
There's one coming your way.
Here, class of '98.
Have a look. I sorted it out for you.
You've just met
the grade school boyfriend.
Now you rush to
the high school sweetheart, huh?
[girls cheering]
[boy] What are you doing?
What do you want?
I'm sorry.
[inaudible]
[girls exclaiming]
I SUPPORT YOU
THANK YOU
BRIGHT
[Paul] Sure! I miss you too.
Let's meet at this pub.
I'll send you directions.
[dance music playing]
Bright.
It's me, Paul.
Can't you remember?
[thunder crashes]
Paul.
[giggles]
Or Pauly!
So pretty.
After graduation, I came out right away.
I was kind of a star for a while.
I had it all with them boys.
But I can't believe,
when we were together,
I didn't figure it out.
Well,
I guess it must be
because of our first kiss.
It made me realize what I really am.
Geez, I'm kidding.
Actually, I realized a long time ago.
[both laughing]
Bright, let's revisit
some good old memories.
[Bright] I miss that time
when we were kids.
[Pauly] Yeah.
When I met you,
it was the best opportunity
to learn about the ladies' world.
But I didn't use you.
[girls cheering]
Men's scent is so sexy.
I can feel testosterone
running through my body.
[sniffs] Once I smell it,
it's so fulfilling.
It was the only reason I played sports.
[boy 1] What did you do?
What do you want?
I was confused back then,
whether to come out or not.
[sniffs, sighs]
When we kissed,
it was a confirmation
that I am gay.
Mmm!
But you started it all. Remember?
And I knew right away
that I like being the bottom.
That was it.
My high school romance.
[exhales] Oh!
Oh...
And when we broke up?
So, May,
Paul is now mine,
and I get to kiss him too.
The diary trick, that's low.
Who would be as deceiving as you?
Shut up, bitch!
Bring it on!
[children clamoring]
Don't be overconfident.
You don't need to write anything for me.
We're over.
No, I wasn't upset or anything.
It's good that we broke up.
That was smooth.
And the important thing is,
I almost couldn't hide it at that point.
Then it's all good.
I feel relieved now.
[cell phone ringing]
It's my boyfriend.
Hello.
Yeah, come by and get it.
Get the money and get laid with me too.
I miss you.
[shouting] Bastard!
Do you think I'm stupid?
You always spend my money on girls!
Are you okay?
I'm all right.
I can handle it.
For a mama like me, this is nothing.
I just go to the toilet,
and I'll forget it.
If you need anything, please let me know.
I'm sure you'll be there for me.
Just like what you wrote on your page.
I'm your fan, you know?
-Really?
-Yeah.
See you later.
[inaudible]
I'd like to dedicate the next song
to the woman who means everything to me.
Bright.
Will you be my girlfriend?
[women cheering]
♪ Do you know how good that is? ♪
♪ Do you know how happy I am? ♪
♪ Do you know
How my old life has changed? ♪
♪ Do you know, before I met you ♪
[inaudible]
Ellie! Ellie!
Why can't you tell me where you are going?
I can always leave you alone.
Can you do the same for me?
It's so difficult to be a father.
It's so difficult to be a daughter.
So when will you be back?
Ellie!
When will you come back?
Hi, Tune.
Is that your bar here?
Take a seat.
I stopped playing guitar
after I graduated.
All my friends went their separate ways.
And I eventually got to run the place.
As you see.
Back then,
you really wanted to be a musician.
-You always wanted to write songs.
-[chuckles]
Is that your daughter?
She looks a bit feisty.
Her name is Ellie.
We always fight.
It's difficult.
I don't know what to do now.
And her mother?
We broke up long time ago.
You know,
I'm divorced.
It must be because she's my daughter.
That's why I can't understand her.
It's like we talk in different keys.
Tune, a delivery.
Will you please pay the bill?
That's right.
[in English] I'm going to the beach.
Will be back soon.
[in Thai] I guess I should leave.
I have to get back to work.
Don't you want to have dinner together?
It's okay.
I have to fly back tonight.
You don't understand your daughter,
but thing seems to go well with girls.
Bright.
Goodbye.
[inaudible]
[Tune] Bright. I'm sorry.
Can you please come see me?
♪ Do you know how good that is? ♪
♪ Do you know how happy I am? ♪
♪ Do you know
How my old life has changed? ♪
♪ Do you know, before I met you ♪
♪ How I used to be? ♪
♪ Do you know
How great it is to meet you? ♪
♪ It's you, all because of you ♪
You have a girlfriend and a daughter.
Your life should be great.
Okay, sure. See you then.
[exclaims]
I'm sorry.
Are you really his friend?
Not one of his girlfriends?
I'm really his friend.
We became friends in college.
You must be very protective of him.
That's why you are mean towards your dad.
Not at all.
I really want him
to have a real girlfriend.
But I'm not sure
if he can really love someone.
Sometimes,
I also feel
like he doesn't love me.
Why do you say that?
Who wouldn't love their own kid?
He might just be...
not so good at expressing it.
No way.
My mom left when I was born.
He was forced to raise me.
Every time I think about this,
it makes me not want
to live with him anymore.
I'm getting there.
If he pressures me too much,
I'll run away from home.
[man] Tune asked me not to tell you.
When that girl got pregnant,
he had to be responsible.
And when you saw him singing for her,
he wanted you to forget him,
even though he was still in love with you.
[Bright] I'm stressed out.
They're all in trouble.
I don't know who I should help first.
[Khem] Just help them all.
Who asked you for your opinion?
If it's that easy,
why don't you do it yourself?
Sure, if it was my problem,
it would have been done.
That's quick.
When did you get so close?
-Close?
-Who?
[Oil] What Khem said is right.
Help them all
before it gets worse.
[Win] That's true.
[Oil] Why don't we do this?
Since it must not be safe to go alone,
we'll keep you company.
Whenever you want to see your horny ex,
tell us.
Khem, come along.
You haven't been back to Thailand much.
You like traveling to find
the meaning of life anyway.
Maybe you'll find it this time.
The more, the merrier.
[chuckles] I'm afraid
I'll run into trouble.
If you're afraid, then don't go.
You weren't meant to be invited anyway.
Okay, I'm coming with you guys.
When are you going?
Bright, you don't need to help this one.
Not only do I not need to help him,
I even want to kick his ass.
[people cheering]
How's it going? Been here long?
That table?
Excuse me.
Well, excuse me.
Hey, what is that?
Something on your cheek.
It's Ken, the one Bright hates to bits.
When she left to study abroad,
she dated Ken while she was there.
Ken graduated first, so he came back.
And there he went.
He was flirtatious.
That lame trick, the face touching,
still works?
Well, that lame trick
did get someone to fall for me.
And when she returned to Thailand,
he wouldn't stop.
Bright told him,
if he could do it,
she could too.
[exclaims]
Sorry.
Forget it. Cheers!
[Oil] Almost broke the glass.
Whose phone is it?
[cell phone chimes]
WANT TO BRING UP SOME OLD MEMORIES?
OR ARE YOU GETTING TOO OLD NOW?
[cell phone chimes]
HAHA
What are they doing?
It's like a game. One has to win
so the other suffers.
The loser has to follow
the rules of the winner.
Like competing on who has the most lovers?
Mmm! Bright doesn't get in too deep.
She only wants to give Ken a lesson.
I see. She gets his deceiving tricks.
[cell phone chimes]
Ken. [exclaims]
[sighs]
What are you doing?
I don't want to get involved.
Come on. Play along.
Is that needed?
Well, I'm just playing along.
The knee will do.
[crying]
[laughing]
-Go away now.
-[laughs]
Bright, let's go home.
[cell phone ringing]
Hello, Mild.
Hi, how are you?
What's up?
Hey?
-Have you just got here?
-I'm leaving. Been here a while.
[Bright] Oil.
That's why it looked tricky.
Acting like
he's above the rules, arrogant.
"Everyone has to keep up with me
and stay under my rules."
Asshole!
Let's go.
I'll drive.
Hey.
It looks like he loves her.
But I don't think he could change.
He needs a lesson,
or else this girl will go through hell.
Don't you think?
Are you in?
[gasps]
-How did you get here?
-You dragged me along.
No, I didn't.
You really did.
And all so you can talk to yourself.
You know, messing with other people's
lives doesn't fix problems.
It creates more trouble.
I'm not asking for your advice,
so shut up.
You want me to go after him and help?
I'd rather ruin his life.
Let's go!
Oil, what did Ken do to Bright?
Why is she so furious?
Ken proposed to her.
She was very glad.
But everything turned out
to be a prank by Ken
so he could win the game.
Bright was furious and depressed.
It seems she'll hold that rage
for the rest of her life.
Let's go.
That's why.
[man] Let's eat.
[indistinct conversation]
Are you two getting back together?
No, Grandma.
Not at all.
I just came by to visit.
[woman] That's good.
I just want Tee to have
a real Chinese wife.
This room was almost our home.
Why don't you sell it?
I keep it as a safe house
to escape from my family.
Don't worry.
I'll sell it when I get a good offer.
I don't know if it was right
to break up with you.
You are so good, reasonable, and real.
You always listened to all my problems.
You were perfect.
How can I find someone like you again?
But you were bored eventually.
You lost all intimacy.
Living with me is boring.
And with my family on top of that...
That's why I decided to live alone.
Do you think
about what would happen between us?
We won't make it.
I really tried.
We can still be friends.
Right?
I'm sorry.
Hey!
Tee, got you!
[Tee] I met her on Facebook.
Then we chatted.
Just like that.
She is more than 20 years younger.
That's why you're much smoother now.
Really?
Yes.
I only date him
for movies and dinners.
It's nothing serious. He's too old.
[Tee exclaims]
[Tee] Are you using me?
Now you're being used by an old man,
and you like it?
You say it yourself.
You don't realize you're being used.
I'm just using you.
[laughing]
Have you brought Mint to your family?
When I was with you,
Grandma messed with me everyday, remember?
It would be the same with Mint.
What are you going to do?
[sighs]
I don't know.
Just keep it the way it is, I guess.
I haven't thought about it.
[both sigh] Boring.
[cell phones chiming]
KHEM, HAVE A SAFE TRIP.
[exclaims]
WE ARE ON OUR HONEYMOON.
HOPE YOU HAVE A FUN TRIP IN THE NORTH.
I've become like this because of you!
You didn't keep your promise.
You always spend my money on girls!
I'm sure you'll be there for me.
[Tune] It must be
because she's my daughter.
That's why I can't understand her.
What do you think about us?
Just keep it the way it is, I guess.
I haven't thought about it.
Oh.
Are you finished? I was having fun.
You talk in your sleep like a radio show.
[Bright] I have
a lot of good memories here.
It's peaceful,
and people have an easy-going lifestyle.
They are kind and welcoming.
[people shouting]
You did this to me! Just remember that!
[man] Go get him!
[woman] Where are you running to?
Stop it!
You know I can fight.
You are a cruel, stingy bastard.
I do what I want.
Are you sure we're at the right place?
Stop! Stop! Guys, stop!
Calm down. Let's talk about it.
I can't be calm.
He raised the rent so high.
How can we pay that much?
And you never really help us.
[people clamoring]
Remember, bitch.
I'll raise it even more
-until you can't stay.
-Selfish bastard!
-[man] Stop, stop.
-You were nice as a kid.
How come you turned into a bastard?
Have a problem?
What happened to you?
Why do you hate this place so much?
None of your business.
I'm a bastard. So what? This is my land.
I will get rid of you all.
You can't live here!
[all clamoring]
Please! Please stop.
I beg you, please don't hurt him.
I'm begging you, please.
[overlapping chatter]
Where are we going to live then?
Please calm down, I beg you.
[clamoring stops]
Please calm down. Please.
Piss off!
Go away.
It's none of your business.
You all remember this.
I won't raise the rent.
[engine starts]
But I will sell it out!
And that is your first love?
You get him from the ballot box or what?
[motorcycle engine revving]
This land is mine,
and I have just sold it!
[dog barking]
[sighs]
What's that?
[Bright] It's the toy you want to have.
I will come back to play with you again,
I promise.
But I never come back here
as I promised Jack.
Mmm...
It looks like this Jack guy
must have got a brain injury.
Who would take
a childhood promise seriously?
Nutcase, right?
Who would even remember?
[coughs] Wait.
You kept that?
You deserve each other.
Same nutcase.
What?
You'll break it if you throw it at me.
It's your childhood memory, isn't it?
How do you do it?
Get them connected like this?
And then blow the bubble.
So you play with bubbles?
Didn't you have one?
No, I grew up in the city.
Lame.
[inaudible]
NO PARKING
[shouting]
Take care of your house, will you?
They're getting old and decayed.
Take good care of it.
What the hell are you looking at, fatty?
What's up, brother? Any problem?
Don't you look at me.
I will mess with you.
Everyday.
Until you leave!
Sorry I'm late.
Come on. Hop on.
I'll take you around.
You are a grown woman
still playing like a kid, huh?
What's the trick today?
As you wish.
Wait. I'm coming.
Jack.
I think...
You got to be patient to be my sidekick.
Move it! Hurry!
Get on!
Go!
[inaudible]
[woman] Jack, you haven't come by.
Come on. Get your favorite snack.
Bring it to him.
Here.
Jack, I'd like you to keep this place.
It's not just for our memories.
But for all of the people that live here.
They have been living here
since we were kids.
Bright, I'll make this place prosperous
so you can stay and get a job here.
No need to go away.
And why haven't you come back here at all?
If not to see her first love,
she wouldn't be back.
Keep building it up.
[laughs awkwardly]
Do you really think I'm your first love?
Of course. [laughs nervously]
-Jack.
-Yes?
Please don't sell this place.
Please.
Let me think about it.
Jack, the good memories...
I hadn't thought of them,
but I never forgot.
[sighs]
Let's go. Four more of your exes to see.
Jack.
Bright knocked on every door this morning
and apologized on your behalf.
She also said that
everything that happened is her fault.
She begged everyone
to understand and forgive you.
[inaudible]
And Paul...ie,
your second boyfriend,
how will you help him?
I'm thinking about it.
What's your idea?
I kind of have an idea, but...
Why should I tell you?
You have to tell me first.
[Pauly] Why did you bring me here?
You should have told me.
Hey.
Hello.
-Please come in.
-Take a seat.
Being gay is not a disease.
You can't cure it.
Don't tell me you want
this bitch to cure me!
Shouldn't she cure herself first?
She looks more confused than me.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
Bitch.
[mouthing] Look, she is mean to me.
I bring you here to reboot,
upgrade yourself to become
the happiest gay man on Earth.
Trance.
What we are doing today is called
a trance.
Trance?
What's a trance?
Opening the door
back to your childhood complex
that causes you unhappiness.
Hey, my door is already opened.
And it's wide opened already, Bright.
Pauly, your door is rusty now.
You should open it again.
Try to open it.
Re-open?
Don't worry. I'll do it for you.
Do it with you?
Yes, I'm really good at it.
Lie down.
Be calm and relax.
Close your eyes.
Pauly,
relax your body.
Relax. Take it easy.
Now look into the dark.
In the dark,
you won't see anything.
Try to look at the end of the tunnel.
There is a bright light.
Do you see that, Pauly?
-Yes.
-Do you see it?
-I see it.
-That's great.
Now you look inside.
Let's get back to find something together.
Take a step.
Focus on the light.
Easy, easy.
Your lesbian lover is quite pretty.
I just hope this works.
[therapist] All right,
let's get back to the situation
that makes you unhappy.
The perpetual unhappiness in your life.
What is it?
[screams]
I know you used me.
But I have money. Do you want it?
Please, don't leave me.
I won't be bitchy. I'll be nice.
I am bitchy because...
I haven't taken the hormone pills.
[laughs] Bitches, you are jealous of me.
I'm pretty and fabulous!
All the guys that you fancy,
I do them all. [laughs]
Although I'm gay, I'm a queen.
But I can do all of your boys.
[laughs]
[moans]
Ouch!
The first time, it hurts.
Don't stop. Don't.
Harder!
Harder.
Is this a hypnosis therapist
or a shaman?
I'm coming. I'm coming.
[Khem] Yeah, I agree.
So haunting, isn't it?
[crying]
He left me again.
Men are all deceiving.
Why?
We are almost there.
[school bell dinging]
It was because of that bitch.
When I was in high school,
she used me.
No way.
That can't be.
That day, in the evening,
after school,
she kissed me.
My first kiss, it should be meaningful.
I realized later that she used me.
She never loved me, not one bit.
Busted.
After that,
I have always met deceiving people.
I'm afraid to love anyone
because I'm afraid I'll be used again.
And it's true.
I have only met deceiving people
since that day.
If not for that kiss,
my life wouldn't be like this.
Come on. At least
we know what the problem is.
The therapist can find the solution.
You should stay away.
Let's see how it goes.
Afraid I'll find out
more secrets about you?
[whispers] Okay, I'm going.
All the problems have been solved, Pauly.
All the bad experiences and memories
will fade away.
You have to tell yourself
that you will change
your life and move on.
You won't let those memories
bring you more sorrow again, ever.
Say it.
[cell phone ringing]
What do you want?
You ran out of money?
Is that why you call?
Oh.
I'm kidding.
Where are you now? I'll bring you money.
Okay, wait for me.
It's all done, Pauly.
[laughs]
It was really good.
-I'm glad you've come.
-I came?
-Yes, you did.
-Thank you so much.
Thank you, Pauly. I'm so happy for you.
Thank you, Bright.
I can't quite explain how good I feel.
But now, can you keep me company?
Let's go!
[cell phone ringing]
One moment.
Hello, are you here?
Okay. I'll get there.
Yes, I'm here.
Come here.
You have been using me all along.
[man grunts]
Don't tell me that you take my money
to give it to this ugly bitch?
Bitch, did he tell you
that he is of royal blood?
Actually, his name is Somchai,
and he works at the BBQ restaurant,
you dumbass.
[woman whimpers]
Why did you do this to me?
Bright.
Nida.
Thank you so much.
You made me realize...
It's true what you said.
Romance is not real.
It's all deception.
[crying]
Wait, Nida.
[Pauly exclaiming]
That feels good!
Pauly.
Is that a gay guy or a boxer?
You look more like yourself
since you've met Mint.
[Tee] Really?
Isn't that like when we were dating?
How could that be?
Mint is much younger than me.
[whispers] Old lady.
Bright, anything you'd like to talk about?
Since the other day.
You can just tell me.
Hello.
What a coincidence.
Tee, that guy over there is
my friend with benefits I told you about.
We met last week.
Is he cute?
[Tee] He looks dumb.
But not as cool as those last two guys.
You do as you please. Don't worry.
But not too often, okay?
Tee, I'm not mad at you
that you go out with Bright.
But you can't forget
my birthday next week.
See you later.
Bye.
See you.
Tee, you are a saint.
Aren't you jealous?
Why would I be?
She can hang out with anyone she wants.
Life is full of uncertainties.
Look at us.
I bought the wedding ring,
but yet haven't used it.
[sighs] What is ours
will always be ours.
Right?
Sounds like you let it all go.
Let me tell you something.
I have an arrangement
to meet the bride next week.
The elders have set it up.
Grandma expects me to get married.
I'm growing old.
Here, the daughter
of a canned fish factory owner.
The arranged date is Mint's birthday.
Does she know?
I'm breaking up with Mint
after we celebrate her birthday.
Then I'll go meet the bride
and talk about marriage that evening.
Break up?
She should meet someone real.
So she doesn't have
to waste her time with me.
Don't you love her at all?
I do.
But what can I do?
So I guess I'll see you later.
Sure, see you later.
[Mint] Bright.
I just want him to be jealous.
[sighs] But it doesn't seem to work.
You want him to be jealous,
so you love him.
[Mint sighs]
If this relationship is going nowhere,
I can't do it.
He'll see.
Someday, I'll really leave him.
This looks like a complicated case.
Well, we know now they are both in love.
But how will
we make his family accept this?
I think the most important is,
he has to stand up and fight for this.
That's right.
Okay.
Let's go to Pauly.
Wait.
What's the secret plan?
You look suspicious.
No.
-Huh?
-Hmm?
What are you going to do?
There will be little touches
here and there.
No way.
Why do I have to do this?
You will.
You really like me?
Don't fool me.
Don't pretend that you like me, okay?
Things like this,
you have to prove yourself.
[Khem] Hey! Hey!
I think we should take it slow.
Why should we?
It wouldn't hurt to go fast.
Right?
Are you shy because Bright is here?
Don't be shy.
Don't you worry about her.
Let's drink.
Oops! It's empty.
I'm gonna get more drinks.
Let me go get some more
so we have more energy, build a good vibe.
I'll get a lot more
so you can be in the mood.
Are you hot?
I don't really want to go, but I have to.
[chuckles nervously] Just go.
[chuckling]
Hey, I won't help you that much,
becoming his gay partner!
He went through trance
and got all assertive!
Come on. We went through that to help him.
Now you might want
to help him strip off too.
You are really making me his bitch.
Don't you want to try?
Maybe you'll find your true self.
I'm not sure how long I can play along.
Just play along.
What is it?
It felt like there was something here.
I can't walk.
All right, all right.
Okay.
Come in.
We're here.
Come on, Pauly.
Khem, you are so buff.
[Khem and Bright exclaim]
What are you doing?
Hey, Pauly.
What's going on?
I'll make your wish come true.
Liar!
What are you doing?
I'll make your wish come true.
Let me go. Come on!
What are you doing?
Pauly, open the door.
Khem!
Pauly, what's going on?
You freak! You fooled me back then
and now again with your boyfriend?
It's not like that. Listen.
I'm gay, but I'm not a fool.
Damn it!
It's not like that.
[both grunting]
Are you going to kick me?
Pauly.
Khem...
Pauly, open the door!
Bright.
Bright, Bright.
[cracking]
Khem.
Don't move!
Let go, Pauly. Let go.
Let go!
You'll be ruined.
[Khem] Bright!
You like fooling gay people, huh?
Now you will become one yourself.
-Khem.
-Hey, let go.
You kicked me?
I can also be your husband.
Bright, help me. Bright.
Bright!
Keep shouting. Shout it out!
Bright.
Pauly.
Bright, Bright.
Khem.
What are you doing?
[Khem whimpers]
Like it? Crawling spider.
Pauly, let go.
Have you ever been with a top?
You'll get served, Khem!
[Khem] No, no, Bright, help!
Pauly.
Stop fighting it.
Have you ever been with a top?
Pauly, get off.
Khem.
You liars.
You lied to me too.
My whole life, there have only been liars.
Why do I only meet liars?
I don't want to live anymore!
I don't want to live.
[Pauly whimpers]
What do you want? Why did you get in?
Pauly, calm down.
No, I won't.
If I hadn't been kissed by you,
my life wouldn't be messed up like this.
Don't you understand?
[Khem] Bright.
Are you okay, Bright?
Get out!
Get out now!
I'm sorry that I lied to you.
I just want you to be positive
and love yourself.
Otherwise, who could love you?
No one.
In my life, no one is sincere,
and nobody loves me for real.
I don't know if you can believe it,
but when we dated, I never lied to you.
A girl's first kiss is very important.
I won't mess with it.
Get out!
Get out, all of you!
[cries]
[Bright] You must have thought
I never loved you.
But I'd fallen for you a long time ago.
When I was challenged, I had an excuse.
So far, I have been very happy.
I'm glad
that my first kiss was
with the one I really love.
[sobbing]
You're bleeding.
Come here.
Does it hurt?
Don't press it hard.
[Pauly] Bright.
I have to thank you.
You made me realize
that I've had true love like others.
It doesn't matter
what kind of love it was.
At the time, it was real.
And it will be our good memory forever.
Don't worry about me. From now on,
I will happily take care of myself.
[Pauly chuckles]
Khem...
Yes?
I'm sorry that I was tough on you.
[exhales] It's all right.
If you ever want it some days,
you tell me first, okay?
I'll do it for you.
No, it's okay.
It won't hurt.
I don't believe you.
Take care of yourself.
Good luck.
Be happy.
That's not funny.
I was almost raped in there.
Don't you sneak out to come back for him.
Things like this, you never know.
Don't you regret it if I come back.
[indistinct conversation]
I know, Dad.
Yes, I will be there.
Yes.
[sighs]
[cell phone chimes]
Tee,
we had to break up
because we didn't get along.
It was not a match,
no matter how hard we tried.
But today, Mint really makes you happy.
You should really keep this relationship.
What made me love you
when we dated
is your determination.
Now I ask you to do that again
for your happiness and the one you love.
This ring
is the one you bought for the wedding.
You should give it
to the one you really love.
Mint.
It's so beautiful.
Mint, I have something to tell you.
Mmm?
Tee is not usually late.
Maybe he's busy getting ready.
Let's eat.
I don't want to eat.
[sighs]
[man] There he comes. Tee.
Tee is here.
Take a seat.
I'm sorry.
I can't marry someone I don't love.
[speaking Mandarin] You're a bastard!
Who do you think you are? Go to hell!
Getting married with someone like you?
Fuck your marriage!
-How did you teach him?
-[gasps]
Mom, let's go!
Marriage? Fuck your marriage! Go to hell!
Oh dear, calm down.
You are bullshit! Go to hell!
Wait, wait, wait.
They're gone.
Why won't you get married, Tee?
Are you gay?
Just tell me. I can try to understand.
Mint.
Who is that?
Uh...
This is Mint, my girlfriend.
[women] What?
Girlfriend?
Look at her makeup and dress.
I can't take this. No way.
Look, Grandma. She's not Chinese.
She looks so Thai.
Grandma won't let her marry him.
Anyway, I insist
that I will only marry the one I love.
Even though you don't like it,
I will continue living with her
and will never marry anybody.
Grandma, she must have used black magic.
[women clamoring]
It's up to you.
[women] What?
Grandma, are you out of your mind?
How come? I don't understand.
[sighs]
[Bright] Grandma.
This is the one Tee loves.
Tee is very happy when he is with her.
I think it would be great
if Tee were happy like this every day.
[grandma] I've never seen Tee
smile so happily like this before.
Good posture. She'll have many children.
Now I can hold some babies.
[women cheering]
[woman] That's great.
Thank you, Bright.
You thought about proposing,
don't you want to ask me at all?
Will you marry me?
You can make me wait,
but I will marry you for sure.
[all] Yeah!
Let's go celebrate.
[exhales]
-Bright.
-Yes?
Thank you.
When will you two get married?
Grandma, no, it's not like that.
He is not my boyfriend.
I haven't thought
about marriage for a long time.
Even though it's destiny.
But if we don't fight for it,
there is no way we get what we want.
[dance music playing]
[Bright] First thing first.
Stop making that silly face.
If you help me, we are even.
If you call it even,
I'll do anything you want.
Let's discuss the plan.
So you just walk your sexy self in,
lure him into the trap.
Flirt with him!
Seduce him so he shows his true colors.
And do I have to get laid?
I'm scared.
Not a big deal.
You'll remain intact.
I'll use my connection in marketing
to get Mild here to discuss work.
Wait.
What's happening?
Someone you know?
Should we go say hello? I'll go with you.
Where is your friend?
Where has he gone?
Do you see him anywhere?
Is it him over there?
You're doing much more
than you were paid to do.
Isn't that your fiancé?
This is too much. Don't let him.
Take a video for evidence.
Here.
Hold it. Press the button.
[Bright] Oh!
Mild.
Well, when you make an evil plan,
you seem to enjoy it so much.
[Bright] Then I will turn
her good-girl attitude
into a feisty one
so she never gets used by a bad guy.
Double shot.
I think that's enough.
If it was you, what would you do?
First of all,
I wouldn't go home to cry alone, ever.
We have to go through this,
or we will always lose.
But it's not me at all.
Then change.
Everybody can change.
Then you can, Mild.
It's men's nature.
What's difficult to get is,
they want even more.
What's easy to get is,
they think it's worthless.
The advantage bitches have
over a good girl like you,
you know what it is?
They are never submissive to men.
This is what men like
because it's exciting.
But the most important thing is,
no matter what kind of victim they are,
girls have to wait for men to choose.
Why is that?
Why don't we start
hunting them down ourselves?
You have build it up this way.
Don't you think you can fix your fortune?
You'll get more bad karma this way.
Mild, take a look over there.
I think he's been looking at you a while.
Take a chance.
And you will find excitement.
I got it now.
I'll call off the engagement tomorrow.
Thank you.
Now I'm all pumped.
I'm more ready for excitement than ever.
Good.
Hello.
You come with your older sister?
Mild, I will see you later.
Excuse me.
Do you want my number?
Really?
Hey, Bright.
Get away!
Why?
Get away now!
It's Mild, isn't it?
Bright, can't we just talk like normal?
No, go back to wherever you crawled from!
[screams] Get away!
What's happening?
Get away!
Get away from what?
What?
Don't.
Yes, thank you.
I'll call you later. Bye.
[Ken] Mild.
Mild.
You got what you deserve.
I don't agree with what you did.
Hmm?
What did you say?
I can't hear you!
Where is Gee?
Well, well, dreamy, isn't it?
You're shimmering.
Just almost.
He stopped all of a sudden,
said he couldn't, and then he left.
No way! Someone like him? No.
Gee, one moment.
Hey, seriously,
do you resent him this much
because he was bad to you
or because he didn't choose you?
[cell phone ringing]
Hey,
Ken is calling.
Did I get busted?
If you want to know, answer it.
[Bright] Why do you
bring back old history?
[Ken] I'm not bringing it back.
But if we've ever done anything wrong,
we don't want to repeat it, do we?
Have you ever thought,
when we were dating,
what were we doing?
Of course, you never even said
the word "love."
Isn't it better than someone
who says it all the time?
If that day,
I hadn't pushed you too much,
you might have heard it from me.
Oh, the prank when you proposed to me?
I really wanted to propose you.
Ken. [exclaims]
It's time.
I love you, Ken.
[laughs]
You love me?
You lost.
Go to hell!
Bright.
Bright, wait.
I truly loved you.
But I didn't know
how to tell you that I loved you,
that I was sorry.
I love you, Bright.
But if I had been calmer
and stayed a bit longer,
we could have got married.
[chuckles]
After that,
I never got serious with anyone.
It's not that Mild can control me.
[laughs]
But who would want
to win over someone
who always lets you win?
And now, I realize
that I will never wrong anyone
like I did you.
Will you forgive me?
All right.
I forgive you.
Thank you so much.
Well, I'll propose to Mild tomorrow.
I'm sorry that I got you wrong.
Ken will propose.
She will break up with him!
What should we do?
[indistinct conversation]
How do we fix this?
Do you want to tell him the truth?
Everybody.
Mild and I, we have both been engaged
for a while now.
I think this is the right time
for us both--
No!
I can't marry this selfish man.
Mild.
Here, Ken.
What should we do?
Dad.
Mild, Mild.
I can explain it.
It's not what it looks like.
I don't want to listen.
-Mild.
-No!
I don't want to listen.
I've had enough with selfish guys.
So I can take him now.
Ken, we can finally make it.
What do you mean?
Do you really want to know?
Actually, I can't forget him.
So I came up with a plan
to take him back from you.
-[exclaims]
-[insistently] Mmm.
You!
You guys are in this together?
Was it all your plan?
You manipulated me to be bad like you?
Mild.
Mild, calm down.
Ken, back off.
I will take care of the one who'd ruin us.
Bright.
Wow, you are doing great with this.
Great what? I didn't mean it.
-Mild, don't.
-Look out!
Let go, Ken.
[Bright grunts]
[softly] Do something.
I can't feel my face now.
[crying] Ken.
Stop now, Bright.
More.
I never want to get back with you.
I only love Mild.
No way.
It's not true.
[wailing]
Have I lost?
This is not true.
Go away. Get out.
Look out.
Bright.
Mild.
Mild, careful.
Khem.
Ken.
-Khem.
-Ken.
[all clamoring]
Ken.
Hurry. Do what you need to do.
Mild.
I love you, Mild.
[laughs]
Will you marry me?
[exclaims]
I will, Ken.
[all cheering]
You have gone from a bitch to an angel.
And you,
from a villain to a hero?
So why did you go to work abroad?
I guess I...
I don't want to live a predictable life.
You know, since I was a kid,
I've tried so hard
to get to study what I like.
But I got a job
that had nothing to do with my studies.
And the company was looking good,
but it went bankrupt all of a sudden.
There is no certainty in my life,
so I don't want to hold onto anything.
But it's funny.
One day, I decided
to take a chance abroad.
It went well.
And you living your life like this,
will there be any girl who accepts this?
I haven't met anyone to date.
Maybe I have to talk
to a fortuneteller with you.
So I can have someone.
And what about you?
Do you know who suffers
the most because of you?
Yeah, I really want to know.
[inaudible conversation]
[indistinct announcements on PA]
Hey.
[Khem] Your first love is pretty good.
He is great.
He didn't sell off the land,
but built a market road for the village.
See?
Yeah.
You didn't care about looks as a kid
but got handsome guys as you grow up.
As a teenager, you liked a musician,
then a guy from an elite family.
After your heart was broken, a handy man.
Bright, you have had it all.
All kinds.
But, ultimately, why are you still single?
[panting]
I can't find her anywhere.
-All over the beach?
-Yes.
Hi, Tune.
What happened?
Ellie, I don't know where she's gone.
And she doesn't answer her phone.
I asked her friends. Nobody knows.
You weren't mean to her again, were you?
I just talked to her
about boarding school.
But she didn't say anything.
She just left.
I think I know where to find her.
Let's go.
Ellie!
Hi.
Tune.
She said Ellie is at
a Russian friend's party.
[kids talking indistinctly]
[Bright] Tune! Tune!
Tune.
Leave some for me. Yummy!
Ellie, let's go home!
What?
This is ridiculous.
This is why I'm sending you
to boarding school.
Tune.
You should listen to her.
This is your daughter.
You want to send me away,
so you can spend
more time with your girls.
I'm unwanted.
You never want me.
That's why you never love me.
You've got me wrong, Ellie.
-You've got me wrong, Ellie.
-Let go.
You're not unwanted.
I love you so much.
Then you should want to live with me.
Why do you send me away?
I just...
I am just scared
that I can't raise you well.
But now,
I know that we have to stick together.
[sobs]
I won't let you go away.
I'm sorry.
[sighs heavily]
Ellie.
Just turn it over.
All right.
Happy family, Mommy.
I kind of enjoy that.
[inaudible]
[camera shutter clicks]
This one is pretty big.
[Tune] Is it too late to say sorry?
It's in the past.
Don't worry about it.
We don't always get what we want.
Both of us today are different
from who we were the other day.
Life has changed.
Our dreams are different.
I understand.
In the past,
I thought of being a musician,
but now it's all about Ellie.
I haven't played guitar at all.
I broke up the band.
I don't have the courage
to go back to see them.
I don't know what happened to them.
Jealous?
Jealous of who? No.
We're not a couple. No jealousy.
You sure?
I'm sure you're jealous. I know it.
Now I realize
you're the one my dad loves so much.
Yes.
But the woman your dad chose is you.
The one he loves the most.
He chose me,
and who will you choose?
[indistinct conversation]
Look.
It's Dad.
[inaudible]
What are you doing here?
Waiting for you maybe?
This is a public place.
Why can't I come here?
You're something.
What are you looking at?
[inaudible]
We can say goodbye here.
This song is for you, Bright.
[playing guitar]
♪ Do you know how good that is? ♪
♪ Do you know how happy I am? ♪
♪ Do you know
How my old life has changed? ♪
♪ Do you know, before I met you ♪
♪ How I used to be? ♪
♪ Do you know
How great it is to meet you? ♪
♪ It's you, all because of you ♪
♪ That my life is memorable ♪
♪ It's because I've met you ♪
♪ Thank the heavens
For crossing our paths ♪
♪ Thank that person who had us meet ♪
♪ Thank all the stories ♪
♪ And all the reasons ♪
[whoops]
♪ You, my love ♪
♪ Thank the heavens
For crossing our paths ♪
♪ Thank that person who had us meet ♪
♪ Thanks all the stories ♪
♪ And all the reasons ♪
♪ That made me meet ♪
♪ You, my love ♪
♪ Oh, heavens ♪
♪ Thank you ♪
♪ Thank the heavens
For crossing our paths ♪
♪ Thank that person who had us meet ♪
Both sing badly.
Hurry. Do what you need to do.
But I choose the latter one.
He looks determined.
♪ Thanks all the stories ♪
♪ And all the reasons ♪
♪ That made me meet ♪
♪ You, my love ♪
[people cheering]
[man] After we've restructured
the company board,
this very chair I'm sitting on
will be yours.
I'll be promoted to member of the board.
For you, there is only one condition.
You will work at the US headquarters
for two years
before you come back
to take this position.
So now...
Congratulations in advance
to the new CEO.
[Bright] On top of being promoted,
I won the Woman of the Year award.
It would be nice
if I was lucky with other things too.
The city I'll live in
is only a few hours away from LA.
When will you get back?
We can catch up there.
I don't think I'll go back
to the United States.
Why not?
I'm back home because
I was put on suspension just like you.
But now, it turns out
that I have to relocate to work
in China.
I have to pack up and leave next week.
Eventually,
we will live on different sides
of the world.
I don't know if we'll still want to meet.
Are you kidding?
That's exaggerating.
You didn't tell me.
If I'd told you,
would you have wanted to hear it?
When we met here by accident,
what were you doing here?
It might not be by accident.
Then what?
Is it fate that had us meet?
Had us meet for a while
only to tear us apart?
Bright, there is something
I want to tell you.
What is it? I'm listening.
It's about me and this girl.
I met her a long time ago. Many times too.
But it's strange.
No matter how often I met her,
I never got to know her at all.
I wanted to say hello many times.
Will you be my girlfriend?
I only got the opportunity
to just keep looking at her from afar.
I got to see her when she was sad.
[inaudible]
DON'T WAIT FOR ME.
TOEY
I saw her when she was happy.
Even though I had many chances,
I never took them.
I don't want to be played by fate again.
[inaudible]
It's funny. The more I try to run away,
the more I have feelings for her.
There might be many people
in your memories,
but, in mine,
there is only her.
And this person is you, Bright.
Actually, we have met many times,
but we never had a chance to talk.
We did? Really?
How could that be?
I don't know if you remember.
I was the one who told you
that you look better with the smile.
I thought it was over.
But since the first day
I came back to Thailand,
I've known there is no escape.
[inaudible]
What are you laughing at?
I was just thinking.
Can I not laugh at my own thought?
I never want to believe in fate.
But I want to give myself another try
and see what it brings.
Okay, I'm coming with you guys.
Come on.
Just think of it
as revisiting the good old days.
And all the time we've spent together,
it made me realize
how my fate plays out.
Even when we meet the right person,
if we don't fight for it,
there is no way we get what we want.
I told you all my stories.
Are you crazy?
Nonsense! How could that be possible?
[women] Bright?
-Bright.
-Bright!
You are my idol.
Can I get your autograph?
Here.
[women] Thank you.
May I take a picture?
It's too close.
Could you take a photo for us?
-Is everybody ready? One, two...
-[camera shutter clicks]
Thank you.
You are so beautiful.
Thank you. I love you so much.
Being single brings good things.
Thank you for your help so far
and all the unexpected.
But I'd rather stay the same.
Love is not really for me.
Bright.
You know,
we can't choose to be in love.
We can't choose not to be in love either.
I should go now.
[Win] Already gave up?
Look on the bright side, man.
[humming]
Naughty.
BRIGHT - THE BEST FORM OF LOVE IS...
TO LOVE YOURSELF.
YOU LOOK BETTER WITH THE SMILE.
[Khem] I was the one who told you
that you look better with the smile.
[cheering]
No, it can't be now.
Things are looking great now.
I can't let you in.
[sighs]
[cell phone chimes]
[inaudible]
[chime]
[Khem] And what about you?
Do you know who suffers
the most because of you?
[female announcer] Please welcome
the winner of the Woman of the Year award
for best writer.
[audience applauds]
[whooping]
[cheering dies down]
Thank you for your votes.
And thank you to all the judges.
The most important thing is,
I want to thank singlehood
for giving me this level of success.
[applauding]
[applause dies down]
But I have to apologize.
It just happens that, recently,
I've come to look at everything
in a different way.
I have found something.
The most important thing for women
is love.
[indistinct murmuring]
But a perfect love is
one where you have your loved one
right next to you.
I'm sorry.
I have something to do.
I'm so sorry.
[gasps]
[mic feedback]
So let me wrap this up.
Men are not important.
But love, you can't live without.
If you want love,
men are part of the package.
[clamoring rises]
Come on. Why are you sitting there?
Go out
and find your Mr. Right.
Let's go.
Oh, she changed.
[cheering]
[women] Bright, Bright.
Bright, stop. Here.
I totally forgot.
In such a hurry you forgot your bag.
He has everything you are looking for.
Come on. Go ahead.
You go, girl.
Thank you.
Go!
Come on!
Good luck.
Catch up with him.
Thanks, girls!
Can I check the flight schedule
to Shanghai?
Today, first flight.
Excuse me, Bright.
Can you sign this for me?
How could you get here?
Because of you.
I went that far,
but you still haunt me.
I can't really run away from you.
Because this book
was like a sign for me to come back.
What about your work?
I quit already.
I think I'll look for another job
in the United States.
Really?
Well, fate only gives opportunity.
If we want to be happy,
we must keep trying.
Oh, shit!
Why? What happened?
I rejected the job in the United States.
I thought I was going to find you
in China.
Oh, you want to go to China?
Do you have feelings for me?
Oi!
Silly.
So what now?
We're both unemployed.
It's all right.
I still have some writing jobs.
Don't forget.
You are not
a single lady anymore.
That's not a problem.
I'll just change the topic.
I'll write about
how to be fabulously in love.
So you agree to be in love now?
What do you think?
[upbeat music playing]