You know.
I think this world is so small.
Prince’s boyfriend is the older brother of Kluen’s boyfriend.
And Kluen’s boyfriend is the little brother of Prince’s boyfriend.
So the one you always talked about when we studied together was Daonuea?
The one and only in my life.
What about you?
When did you guys like each other?
At first,
I even despised him.
But after a while,
my feelings just changed.
I think your stories are exactly like novels.
Two stories in the same universe.
I gotta go.
Fah is here to pick me up.
Yeah.
I have to pick Daonuea up too.
Should we go?
Hold on.
What about me?
Me?
Go back to your place.
Go back?
What?
And who’s paying?
Guys, who’s paying?
We’ve arrived, Prince.
This isn’t my place.
This is a lesson.
You get in a car and fall asleep, always.
What if someone kidnaps and traffics you?
Like what you’re doing now?
I will never sell you.
I will keep you all to myself.
No one can have you.
Why did you take me to your place?
Well.
Daonuea is spending the night at Kluen’s.
And I feel lonely.
So I took my boyfriend here to sleep with me.
But...
I don’t have pajamas.
You can wear Daonuea’s.
I don’t have my bolster.
You like to hug a pillow while sleeping?
You usually hug me.
What are you saying?
Did you…
ask your boyfriend if he wanted to spend the night with you?
Of course, he does.
Sleep here with me, please.
Please. Please.
Please.
Alright.
Fine.
Just to keep you company.
You really think that’s it?
You should sit down.
Or you can go straight to the shower first.
You look tired today.
Oh, Fah asked if you wanted to come over for a meal the day after tomorrow.
Prince is coming too.
Wanna come?
What’s wrong?
Just want to be clingy.
Should we go to Hua Hin this weekend?
So you can take a break.
You want me to take a break or you just want to go to the beach?
Let’s go.
Go to my beach.
Ask Fah and Prince to come along.
Your beach?
You said it yourself.
Is this the place you asked me to come along?
Does it mean this beach belongs to your family?
Yeah.
It belongs to you too.
Hello,
Fah.
I’ve arrived.
So you heard me, didn’t you?
Um.
Why did you pretend not to hear?
I was a little blushing.
You, wicked.
I will take you there.
To the real beach of yours.
What do you mean?
It’s a secret.
You’ll see.
Without you by my side,
I’ll be so dishearted.
Hang in there.
You’ll be graduating in a few years.
You’ll be a dentist soon.
You remember when I said The North Star always stays at the same spot?
It always stays with you, Kluen.
Do you get that?
Can you not get any lovelier than this?
I’m a lovely person.
I can’t quit being lovely, can I?
Don’t quit then.
Continue being lovely.
And I’ll continue loving you.
Love you with all my heart.
Kluen.
I’m not even afraid.
You’re challenging me.
You should be afraid.
Go take a shower.
Shower. Shower.
Fine.
You get away this time.
Here.
[Don’t forget to eat. I prepared them for you. - Dao]
Daonuea is so cute.
How was your class?
Tired?
Not as tired as you.
So…
How was today at the hospital?
If you’re asking about the patients,
they’re fine.
But if you’re asking about the doctor,
he suffered so much
because he was thinking about his boyfriend all the time.
We’ve been together for so long.
When are you going to stop hitting on me, sir?
Well, I think…
I’m just gonna keep hitting on you like this.
I like it when you blush.
Cute.
Blush, my foot.
By the way,
Daonuea...
...is going to Hua Hin.
He asked if you wanted to come.
Interested? Will you be free?
Ask yourself if you will.
I can be.
If you say yes, I’ll clear my schedule for you.
So we can go together.
Go take a shower.
I’ll bring you Dao’s clothes.
Hey.
I changed my mind.
I don’t just want your company in bed.
I want my boyfriend in bed.
Got it?
In this world,
if not you, no one will be able to put up with Fah.
For someone like Khabkluen, no one will get him either.
You have a point.
He’s so tight-lipped.
Hi, Prince.
Here. Let me help.
We arrived at the same time.
It’s your favorite, right?
Right.
Fried chicken.
By the way, did Fah tell you about the Hua Hin trip?
He did.
Coming?
Sure.
Yeah!
Let’s go.
Fah hasn’t come yet?
He’ll be here soon.
Don’t make that face.
Smile for me.
Fah is always like this.
He said it was an urgent case.
Please don’t be mad at him, Daonuea.
In this world,
if not you, no one will be able to put up with Fah.
For someone like Khabkluen,
if not you, no one will get him either.
Didn’t see that coming.
You have a point.
It’s so hard to know what’s on his mind.
He’s so tight-lipped.
So close-mouthed.
What are you doing, Kluen?
Prince is right here.
So?
I wanted you to prove if my lips were really tight.
I used to be like that.
But now I can say I love you every day.
I love Daonuea.
I love Daonuea so much.
Prince.
I love Daonuea.
Did you hear that?
Hey.
Sorry, I’m late.
Urgent medical case.
There weren’t enough doctors so I--
Abracadabra. I wish for your tiredness to disappear.
I was so worried you’d get mad.
It’s your job. How can I be mad?
Besides,
I’m a grownup.
But I’m mad.
Kluen.
I think…
we should eat.
Fah.
You don't tell me things now.
You only told Prince you’d be late.
I guess I’m not on your priority list anymore.
It’s not that, Dao.
Well…
But you left me and spent the night at Kluen’s for a week.
You left me alone here.
Should I be mad at you?
No. You can’t get mad at me.
Then you can’t get mad at me either.
Be fair.
Ah. Let’s eat, guys.
Let me feed you.
Yum.
Is it good?
This is your favorite, isn’t it?
Dao.
Are my clothes still in your room?
Yes.
If so,
can I spend the night?
No.
Don’t you even think I have no clue.
I know when I was on the mountain,
you made my brother sleep at your place.
You should keep your distance sometimes.
Fah.
Hey.
Daonuea and Khabkluen have been together for so long.
Don’t be overprotective.
I don’t know.
I just despise him.
Come on.
Be reasonable.
If you don’t let Kluen crash here,
I will…
You will what?
I’ll make Prince sleep in my room tonight.
Are you crazy? No way.
Why not?
I’m scared of ghosts. I don’t want to sleep alone.
Dao,
you’ve been sleeping by yourself since young.
Why scared now?
I didn’t have Kluen in my life then.
And don’t you want to hug Prince to sleep tonight?
Fine.
Everyone sleeps wherever they want.
Eat and go separate ways.
Hey!
You don’t dry your hair again.
You can get sick.
Because I knew you’d do it for me.
Am I spoiling you here?
If you keep doing this for me,
I’m willing to be a spoiled brat for the rest of my life.
I just love this one so much.
Don’t have to say that often.
I’m afraid you’ll get tired of it.
It’s not gonna happen.
Got it?
Kluen, stop.
Don’t do this.
Then I’ll just continue studying.
Study again?
You should take a break.
All right.
That’s it for today then.
Kluen!
Kluen, don't play like this.
You said you would take a break.
I’m taking a break.
Not like this.
This kind of break keeps my tiredness away.
Kluen.
What?
No.
I miss the mountain vibes.
I miss the children.
You?
No.
Well.
What I miss the most about the mountain
is right here.
I still remember the first day we met.
In front of the school.
Actually,
we met before that.
I’ve just arrived.
Taking the stairs.
Yeah. Okay.
I’m sorry.
Thank you.
Sure.
Don’t know if you remember.
I do.
But I didn’t realize it was you.
If I’d known I would love you this much,
I would’ve hit on you then.
So we would be boyfriends months sooner.
My Prince.
Are you blushing?
Listen to what you’re saying.
Are you challenging me?
I am.
when will you stop picking on Khabkluen?
I’m not picking on him.
Don’t you dare.
Here.
Prince.
Do you have any problem dating Fah?
Fah and I already had all problems on the mountain.
We understand each other well now.
You know?
I missed this version of Fah so much.
How come?
The one who smiles.
The one who is happy.
Not just Fah who can smile because of me.
I used to think I wouldn’t love anyone again.
Until Fah.
Then I should congratulate both of you
for having each other in life.
Come on, Prince.
Are you ready?
Do your best, Daonuea.
Oh!
Whoa!
Prince, get closer.
No!
I think only toasts and sausages should do.
Here.
You made a very good toast.
Crispy and tender.
The color is also nice.
The sausage is very well cooked.
Good job.
The sausages, Prince fried them.
As for the toasts, Daonuea made them.
Oh.
Both of them look great, right?
Right.
It’s the toast my little brother made.
Of course, it’s great.
Let’s just eat.
Then we can head out.
It isn’t Kluen’s House.
I told you I’d take you to Dao’s beach.
Dao’s Beach?
What do you mean, Kluen?
[DAO’S BEACH]
My family built another resort.
My mom asked me to name it.
And I named it Dao’s Beach.
Kluen!
You don’t have to do that for me.
Is your mom okay with the name?
She loves it.
Two resorts named after two of her children.
Thank you, sir.
They are so cute.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Finding info.
On what?
How to buy a mountain.
Huh?
Dao, do you want an island?
A couple of islands should be nice.
I’m buying you a mountain.
Are you nuts?
A mountain isn’t something you can buy.
You don’t have to do anything for me.
Just stay with me forever.
I love you.
I love you too.
About the mountain purchase,
don’t you ever tell anyone.
It’s embarrassing.
It’s been so long since my last beach trip.
It’s beautiful here.
The weather is nice.
By the way,
when will you stop picking on Khabkluen?
Who is? I’m not picking on him.
Come on.
I’m joking.
He deserves it.
He used to make Dao cry a lot.
Fah and Prince are cute together.
I just want to thank Prince a million times for bringing back the old Fah.
I want to thank Prince too.
For what?
Because Prince came into Fah’s life,
Fah is now less protective of you.
Fah, Prince,
get in the water.
Hold on.
I don’t want to get wet.
You don’t?
Fah.
Prince.
Come on.
Quickly.
Let’s go.
Hey!
I hadn't been in the water in a long time.
I’m exhausted.
You must admit.
Age matters.
Are you saying I’m old?
I’m not.
But if I’m old and still get to be clingy around you,
it’s okay.
You.
Dao,
you have an inhaler?
Fah left it with me.
Look at Fah.
He seems younger when he’s with Prince.
Prince!
Fah,
take the inhaler.
It’s refreshing.
Hey!
Smells nice and refreshing indeed.
Well. Well.
You guys are so sweet.
We read each other’s minds.
We’re at the beach.
It’s a must to bring this tee.
It’s the cutest tee in the world.
I worked hard to paint it for you.
Say it isn’t cute, and you’ll be punished.
The tee is cute.
But I think the painter is cuter.
Dao, are you finished?
Grilled shrimps will become dried shrimps if you let them wait any longer.
Can we go eat now?
I’m done. Coming.
Hey.
Should we go out to see the sunrise tomorrow?
Wake me up, Kluen.
Roger that, sir.
Fah, Prince,
come with us.
Please.
Sure.
Yeah.
Just eat.
Did you just give my brother an order?
Hey.
I’m sorry.
Come on. Let’s eat.
Yum.
Yum. Yum.
Don’t you dare.
Here.
Fah,
want some crab?
Yum. Yum.
Give it here.
It eats you in the face.
Here.
dao
After graduation,
will you live here with me?
What’s with this bracelet that keeps you staring so much?
When I bought it,
I didn’t even have the courage to give it to you.
Look now.
It’s so beyond my expectation.
Come on.
The bracelet is already beyond your expectation?
What about us being together now?
Isn’t it something even greater?
It’s like a dream.
If this was really a dream,
I wouldn’t want to wake up.
Why did you pick a sunflower bracelet for me?
Because you’re my sunflower.
You shine so bright when I look at you.
People stare at you when you smile.
You are so cute.
You know that?
Well.
I kinda know that.
You, little wicked thing!
I don’t want to leave yet.
Then…
After graduation,
will you live here with me?
You know
waking up to see the beach is my dream?
But
it’s okay.
Just take me here often. It’s enough to make me happy.
Dao.
I never had a dream.
But now I do.
What?
My dream
is to see you every morning.
To see your smile every day.
So living here isn’t a big deal at all
if it’s your happiness.
You see over there?
It’s where you can see the best view of the sea.
You’ll see the sunrise every morning.
So I’m thinking of building a house there.
Build a painting studio where there’s every shade of watercolor for you.
There will be a small sunflower garden.
Right there.
There might be a living corner with a big tree.
When you want to paint outside,
you can do it under that tree.
So it won’t be too hot for you.
Thank you.
Thank you for doing so much for me.
Thank you for always loving me.
And thank you for not giving up on loving me.
Dao.
I told you before.
No matter what happens,
it’s your call.
Kluen.
I don’t get to visit beaches very often.
Now that I’m here,
it feels so special.
Then I will take you here again and again.
Only when you’re free is okay.
Prince,
I’m thinking of making a new plan.
I will keep you separate from work.
I promise I will make it work.
But
I might need some time.
It’s totally okay.
I’m never mad about these little things.
I want you to rest
because I really am worried about you.
Thank you.
Between the mountain and the beach like this,
which one do you prefer?
Actually,
I like every place.
Whether it’s the beach or the mountain.
It can be anywhere as long as I have you.
Well then.
Should our wedding be held on the beach?
We will only invite those whom we’re close to.
Invite people on the mountain down here.
But if they can’t make it,
we can get married again on the mountain.
Fah.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
I will.
I love you.
I love it when the four of us are together.
I’m so happy.
Right now
I’m happy too
because everyone I love is here with me.
Prince,
please take care of Fah.
With pleasure.
Kluen.
Thank you so much
for loving my brother almost as much as I do.
I love Dao more than you see.
Don’t be sulky, my Kuafah.
You’ll pay for that later.
From now on every beach trip I have
will remind me so much of this moment.
After this,
it won't be only Daonuea who loves the beach.
It will be a special place for us all.
Look.
It’s beautiful.
Isn’t it?
How about we take a look closer?
Again, Kluen?
Seriously?
What?
Come on.
When an eclipse is near,
a curse falls on Suppalo students who violate the rules.
I know you’ve come to mess with my school.
You’ve been following me everywhere.
Are you into me, student prefect?
Ever since you joined, this school has been full of chaos.