Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Come on. We’re almost there.
Have you ever wished to climb the Himalayas
only to share the breathtaking view with someone?
Are we close, Uncle?
We’re nearly there.
Sorry, my car broke down. So we need to walk.
We’re almost there.
You said that 20 minutes ago.
(That was what I wanted to do.)
(But without knowing it, the one next to me was gone.)
Where are my friends?
Right here.
Why are they crowing?
This hill is freaking steep.
Why is your dad doing this to us?
I think we should head back.
You still want to walk?
You out of your mind?
It’d be dark until we get down there.
What if there’s a bear?
There’s no bear on this mountain.
There’s no bear here. There’re only pigs.
What kind of pig?
Those that give us Kurobuta?
Wild boars.
They attacked the villagers the other day, spilling out their guts.
Shit!
Fah, call your dad.
Tell him to send someone to take us home.
If I could really do that, we wouldn’t be here, would we?
Come on. Let’s go.
Help me up.
Come on.
Hey! Slowly.
After that, any mountains were the same to me.
Without someone walking alongside me,
I didn’t see the point of climbing mountains anymore.
Big bro, where are you from?
You are so handsome.
Come here. Look!
Mister, are you an actor?
Children, don’t bother him.
Back off a little.
But then I realized that maybe…
we climb a mountain just to meet someone waiting for us up there.
Come on, children.
Let’s get back inside.
Fah.
What are you dreaming about?
Keep walking.
People from Bangkok might find it hard to live here.
We don’t have electricity.
We only have solar power that barely works.
The phone reception is very poor as well.
Poor phone reception?
Yes.
That’s another necessity of life.
Then what do you have up here?
This.
Do you want some?
Very tempting but
no thanks.
Uncle,
we traveled all the way to Chiang Mai's hilltop
in the hopes of finding a nice BBQ and a great view.
What do you even have here?
Karaoke?
And Bingsoo?
Bingsoo, seriously?
Let’s just go.
He’s done with you two.
Uncle.
What are we doing here?
This is Dr. Fah’s accommodation.
You two share a house.
What?
Why does he get a private house?
Right.
Tell me how much he paid you.
I’ll give you more.
Uncle, can we have another private house?
You guys
stop bothering him.
I happen to be so handsome.
That’s why I get a VIP house.
Wait a minute.
That’s your reason? Handsome?
Being handsome gets you a house?
I’m a doctor. That’s why.
That’s all.
So?
What about us?
No.
I meant I’m a doctor. I need to work and rest.
What?
And I don’t need to rest?
I don’t need to work?
You two can share a house.
I don’t want to share a house with him. He snores.
- You snore too.
- You’re louder.
Let’s go, Uncle.
No one has lived in this house for a long time.
You need to clean it a bit.
Wow! VIP indeed.
The house that comes with cobwebs.
Awesome!
A luxurious house in the heart of the mountains.
You wake up to a sea of mist and the unpaved road.
Wow!
A great location you can’t find anywhere.
Good luck. You’ll love it here.
I didn’t think it’d be this bad.
Uncle, where is our house?
That way.
Please give us a nice one.
Sure.
Hold on.
Keep me company.
Wasn’t it you who wanted to be alone?
The VIP man.
Help me clean up, at least.
I won’t dare step into a doctor’s house.
We don’t want to bother.
You have it all to yourself. It’s a house for one.
See you.
Hang in there, man.
Clean up nicely, VIP man.
So many yantra amulets.
Why are there so many yantra amulets?
Children.
Guys, I’m here.
Wanna play games?
Let’s go.
Wee-ah, it’s my turn. You sweep the floor.
Two more games.
Teacher Prince is coming.
Shh!
Where are the children?
So you speak the central dialect too?
I asked you where the children were.
Children?
What children?
It’s just me here.
Tell me why you’re skipping class.
This man threatened to hit us if we didn’t help him clean up.
What?
Who threatened you?
We will talk again in school.
I’ll see you guys there in one minute.
Go.
As for you,
did you really threaten them?
I didn’t.
I just asked them to help me clean up in exchange for some mobile games.
Didn’t you know they had class?
How would I know that?
I just got here.
Next time, stay clear of my students.
You’re a volunteer doctor, you should know…
Hey!
It’s rude not to give eye contact during a conversation.
But on your head,
there’s a spider.
Come on.
If you’re scared, why didn’t you say anything?
Why acted cool?
None of your business.
Don't mess with my students again.
I’m warning you.
Time for me to go.
You got all the essential medicines?
I do.
And the food in the fridge,
do you have enough?
I do.
Hold on.
I should be the one checking on you.
Make sure you have everything. You’re about to hit the road.
Well, I’m worried about you.
Don’t worry about me.
I have Khabkluen to take care of me here.
I’m worried because you’re with him.
While I’m away,
take good care of my brother.
Don’t do anything bad to him.
What do you consider bad?
You know what I mean.
Is holding hands allowed?
It is.
And kissing on the cheek?
Twice a day is fine.
I’ve reached my quota.
Kissing on the lips?
Kiss my foot!
I’m being nice to you and now you want to cross me?
I’m kidding.
I promise to take very good care of Dao.
I will do anything bad.
I will not do anything bad.
Okay.
Don’t worry about me. Worry about yourself.
Take good care of yourself while you’re there.
Consider it your personal time.
Yeah.
Take care.
Have a safe trip, Fah.
Dao,
can I go beyond my quota?
No.
Why not?
You’ve met all your quota for today.
But…
I haven’t.
Come on.
There’s still some quota left.
Hey.
What are you daydreaming about?
Thinking of girls in Bangkok?
Like I have any.
I haven’t yelled at you for ditching me yet.
We didn’t ditch you.
We just went with the flow.
Yeah. Whatever.
I’m done with your excuses.
I’m hungry. Let’s find something to eat.
Perfect timing.
The village chief invited us for dinner at his house.
Let’s go.
I told you to wash your face.
You’re just 25 and already a doctor?
[VILLAGE CHIEF OFFICE]
He’s a genius.
He got a high school equivalency certificate at 16.
Took a test for med school after that.
And he got accepted.
You’re great.
I bet many hospitals fight over you.
Fight over him?
All he does is drink in a bar.
Stop talking already.
You may call him a bad doctor.
Hello.
Hi.
Have a seat.
Sit here.
Your son?
No, he’s not.
This is Teacher Prince, the other volunteer teacher here.
I invited him over since you all need to work together.
So you’re a volunteer teacher?
I’m a volunteer teacher too.
My name is Mesa. Nice to meet you.
Of course. I’m Prince.
Mesa, a person’s name, not a month (April).
I’m JJ.
A Maintenance Officer.
What a nice title.
All you will do is fix houses and paint.
Asshole.
Sorry.
And this foul-mouthed man is Kuafah.
He’s a …
A burden, isn’t he?
You two have met?
We met while I was cleaning up the house.
Never mind.
Long story.
Let’s eat.
All right. We should eat now.
Make yourself at home.
Can you please pass me those plates?
Let me help.
I’m helping.
Please enjoy. Eat as much as you want.
Mom made extra food for the guests.
Put them right here.
This is Yayah, my daughter.
Wow.
How pretty.
Are all northern girls this pretty?
I’m flattered.
Doctor,
you don’t like the food?
I do but…
The food here is quite spicy.
Spicy food isn’t my thing.
My friend is a picky eater.
One thing he isn’t picky about is girls.
Shut up.
Make yourself at home.
I’m going to use the restroom.
She’s so pretty.
Tell her, not me.
Is it true that you’re not picky about girls?
True or not…
depends on who is asking.
What if Yayah is asking?
Will I get the chance?
Yayah.
Come on. I’m kidding.
Don’t tell my dad, Teacher Prince.
Would you excuse me?
What’s so funny?
She’s faster than wifi.
You again!
As always.
Get home safe.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
Village Chief,
this batch of volunteers is weird somehow.
How weird?
They don’t seem voluntary.
As if they’re forced to be here.
I don’t want to say much but
since you’ve mentioned it, I’ll tell you the truth.
Those three are sent to do their community service.
Community service?
Yes.
I heard they’re high society people.
They must have driven when drunk.
That’s why they’re doing the community service here.
Can they be trusted then?
That’s my concern too.
But I couldn't do anything.
The order was quite hard to turn down.
I’ll keep an eye on them for you.
If they do anything distrustful, I’ll chase them away.
Of course.
Is Dr. Fah here?
Shit! We’re late.
- Wait.
- Hey!
This is it.
This is a shelf for generic drugs.
Watch out!
Hey, Fah.
We just departed.
You miss us already?
Mesa,
can I borrow your phone?
Phone?
Why borrowing me? You have one.
I have no reception.
I saw you got reception at some places.
Yes, some places.
But not here.
I walked around the village.
No reception anywhere.
What?
They don’t even get phone reception here.
Is there any decent thing here at all?
Exactly.
The weather is freezing.
The food is spicy.
And lots of mosquitoes at night.
Mesa.
Yeah?
Don’t you have anything to complain about?
No.
I adjust easily.
Adjust easily?
Yeah?
What are you chewing?
Don’t tell me…
- Give it here.
- Mesa!
Whoa!
Mesa!
I knew it.
I saw you got your backpack full.
Easily adjust, my ass!
Hey. Don’t.
Now that we saw them.
You’ve got snacks.
Good.
Because I’ve brought…
some alcohol too.
What?
Let’s drink and enjoy the snacks.
Let’s do it.
Let’s start.
Hi. I’m Prince.
Is Dr. Fah here?
I need to take him to the health center.
Is anybody here?
Shit! It’s late.
Hey! Teacher Prince is here.
Hey, wake up.
Dang!
He can’t see us like this.
Let’s move. What are you hanging around for?
Wait.
Hey.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
What time do you think it is?
I have no idea.
You tell me.
There’s no clock here.
Hey, why are you in such a hurry?
Can you wait till I get changed first?
Next time, get up earlier.
I was nice enough to let you stop by your house.
Hurry up. I have a class to get to.
Wait.
Hold this.
Come on.
This too.
It smells like alcohol.
I’m sorry.
My friends spilled the drink on me.
Please hold on to that for now.
Don’t you have anything better to do than being my navigator?
As someone who lived here first,
I should guide a noob like you around.
Walk faster.
I must get to class on time.
How old does he think he is?
Acting like he’s been here for 10 years.
I heard that.
Hurry!
Yes, sir.
HEALTH CENTER
It’s here.
That’s the check-up spot.
Anything else you need,
you can find them inside.
This is a shelf for generic drugs.
These cupboards are miscellaneous storage.
Hey, watch out!
That was close.
Who on earth stored things like that?
I guess…
the previous volunteer doctors.
They weren’t careful enough.
You do better then.
MEDICAL STORAGE ROOM
So that’s it.
Most of the supplies you need are here.
If you need anything else,
inform the village chief.
Why are you staring at me?
You said I didn’t give eye contact yesterday.
I am now.
If we’re all set here, I’ll head to the school now.
Thank you.
These medicines have expired.
This is no good.
Nothing here can be used.
Is this a health center or a haunted house?
Doctor, I need help!
Doctor!
I carried heavy items.
My arms are sore.
I have a stomachache.
Stomachache!
Here.
I think I have food poisoning.
Let’s get you checked up.
Are you mad?
What is this? What are you playing at?
Why?
Wasn’t it smooth?
Our acting was great.
I told you your plan wouldn’t work.
Honestly,
we’re slacking off.
Slacking off?
Yeah.
They made us work so hard.
I was told to dig a water well, fix the roof, and mow the lawn.
And me, I was a tiger back in Bangkok.
Now I feel like I’m a puppy.
Those children picked on me.
They’re monkeys.
I have no idea how Teacher Prince can get them to behave.
It’s good you got work to do.
Look at me.
No one has come here.
It’s been eight hours now.
Ever since we started working up until now,
it’s only been three hours, man.
Three hours?
I felt like it was forever.
That’s right.
Time goes by slowly when we are tortured.
I miss Facebook
Instagram.
I miss my bed.
I miss everything.
- Dr. Fah.
- Yes.
I’m going down to the city.
Do you need anything?
Sure.
May I go with you? I will go buy some food.
Hey!
Who is going to take charge here?
The thing is Dr. Fah is in charge here.
And he has two dear friends.
That’s you two!
Clean it up nicely for me.
Beloved friends.
He loves us all of a sudden.
All of a sudden!
Doctor,
she fell and got a scratch on her knee.
So I…
Sompor, can you wait here?
Yes.
Mister.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Where is Dr. Kuafah?
Kuafah?
He…
went…
Went where?
He had an errand to run nearby.
He’ll be back soon.
Just wait for a little more.
Sure.
Why is Kuafah taking so long to get food?
Will he bring us snacks too?
So an errand he’s running
is buying food?
Maybe something else too.
Everyone, I’m back.
We have both rubbing alcohol and alcoholic beverages.
If you came up here just to change a place to drink,
you better go back.
My friend isn’t here just to change a place to drink as you said.
He had other reasons.
Does it hurt, good girl?
Everyone, I’m back.
We have both rubbing alcohol and alcoholic beverages.
Wow!
Don’t get so excited.
Hey.
She’s got a scratch?
Let me see.
Don’t.
I took care of it.
Hey,
I can explain.
I went down there to…
If you came up here just to change a place to drink,
you better go back.
You should at least respect the uniform you’re wearing.
I get it.
I’m leaving.
Should we go too?
Are you waiting for him to splash the alcohol in your face?
Leave now.
Get home safe, everyone.
Thank you, Teacher.
Teacher Prince.
How is the girl with the scratched knee doing?
She’s a lot better now.
Actually,
you’re older than me.
Don’t need to address me so politely.
What should I call you then?
Teacher…
I see that you don’t call Kuafah Phi either.
So I wasn’t sure how to talk to you.
‘Phi’ is only for those I respect.
I’m sorry about him.
I know this might not help
but he’s being like that because he’s heartbroken.
That’s why he acts like a jerk sometimes.
He wasn’t like this before.
How was he then?
He used to be a workaholic.
So hard-working.
But because all he did was work,
he got dumped without warning by his girlfriend of 7 years.
After his heartbreak recovery, he was back again.
He pretended to forget his past.
He became a drinker, a player who wasn’t serious with anyone just to torture himself.
At one point, I thought he had moved on.
He even insisted on going to his ex’s wedding.
You know how it turned out?
Bad.
JJ and I drank with him a lot.
Without knowing it, we were in a car he was driving.
We would have got to the condo safely
if that car hadn’t cut him off.
Kuafah’s car hit the side of the road.
Luckily, no one was injured.
The police had him tested for alcohol.
As punishment, the court ordered that we all do community service.
Actually, his dad could help soften the sentence.
But he wanted to teach him a lesson.
And that’s why we are here.
It’s true we’re here because we did something bad.
But my friend isn’t here just to change a place to drink as you said.
He went out because he had other reasons.
Does it hurt, good girl?
- No. It doesn’t hurt at all.
- Actually, he didn’t go out to buy drinks.
He went to buy more medicines and supplies for the health center.
I’m going to apply a plaster now.
I got you a piggy plaster here. You like it?
Really?
Supplies at the health center are too old.
Some medicines have expired.
Dr. Fah is sorry for coming back so late.
Will you forgive me?
I will.
But he also came back with liquor.
That’s why it looked quite bad.
Hi,
Teacher.
Can I borrow your phone?
I will try to call home.
In case they can find me a new volunteer location.
Your dad said if you couldn’t handle it,
you could come back to Bangkok.
So…
When are you leaving?
Tomorrow morning.
Did you talk to Prince last night?
Why?
Follow us and you’ll see.
What is happening here?
So…
Do you
have anything to say?
Your bag.
A prince crown bag.
Did you make it yourself?
The children made it for me in art class.
I taught them what Prince meant.
And they made me this.
Cute.
Right?
I fell for it the moment I saw it.
I meant you.
You must be very cute in their eyes. That’s why they made it for you.
What are you saying?
Here. Take it.
A dinner box.
I made it.
It might not be as good as the food in Bangkok.
But it’s not spicy. I think you can handle it.
Thank you.
Such a nice farewell dinner.
So…
When are you leaving?
Tomorrow morning.
Don’t need to shoo me away now.
I won’t bother you for long.
Well then.
May I get inside?
Thank you.
Mesa, can I borrow your phone?
When will you leave my phone alone?
I told you there’s no phone reception.
Why do you still want it?
Whatever.
I will try to call home.
In case they can find me a new volunteer location.
What?
I told Teacher Prince you went to the city to buy medicines.
He hasn’t forgiven you?
I guess he has.
But what am I supposed to do?
You want me to tell him, “Oh! I changed my mind.”
“I’m not leaving anymore.”
Like that?
That isn’t cool.
Cool?
When did you say you’re leaving?
Tomorrow morning.
Wait a minute.
Tomorrow morning?
Yeah.
We haven’t even done unpacking yet,
Mr. cool guy!
What? You want to leave right after you just came?
Stop complaining.
Don’t you want to get out of here asap?
Give me your phone.
I’ll try to call home.
Here.
Take it.
Good luck with the reception.
Is this one yours?
Yes. I just told you to grab it.
Come on, reception.
Give me something here.
Hello, Dao.
It’s me, Fah.
I borrowed Mesa’s phone.
I thought you forgot about your brother.
(Sorry.)
There’s no phone signal up here.
I had to walk all over the mountain to get a signal.
How are you doing anyway?
(Not so good.)
That’s why I called.
I’ve got a favor to ask.
Can you find me a new volunteer location?
Somewhere not here.
I knew you’d call asking for this.
Actually,
your dad said if you couldn’t handle it,
you could come back for the community service in Bangkok.
Seriously?
What service?
Cleaning the city intersections. Want that?
No.
Is there anything medical-related?
No?
Dao, I gotta go.
I guess I’m being too loud.
People might come yelling at me.
I’ll call you again when I go to Chiang Mai downtown.
Talk to you later.
What?
You two haven’t packed?
Fah.
Did you talk to Prince last night?
No. Why?
Follow us and you’ll see.
Move. Why just standing there?
What is happening here?
Teacher Prince and the kids have been cleaning since dawn.
Did you tell him we’re not leaving?
It’s dusty here.
So I wanted to help you clean it up.
Right. We’re doing our best.
Do you like it, Dr. Fah?
Uh…
The kids are helping here.
Don't you like that?
I do.
Of course.
Thank you.
Dr. Fah, my plaster is about to come off.
Because you’re helping me clean?
Yes.
Then I'll apply you a new one.
Okay.
Do you like a kitty plaster?
I do.
From what I see,
we don’t need to hurry home anymore.
I see something too.
Okay.
Let me apply a new plaster for you.
See what?
I see we’ll be here for a long time.
Okay.
And we’re done.
Thank you, Dr. Fah.
I won’t tell the village chief about the other day.
But if you do something terrible again,
you won’t get away with it.
Keep a close eye on my then, Teacher.
Please take care of me.
Everything about love, in my viewpoint, is chaotic.
Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul
Hey!
How did you get in here?
Don’t you have to conduct medical check-ups today?
I’m feeling hot.
If you don’t believe me, feel it.
I like Teacher Prince.
Can you spy on him and see if he’s dating someone?
Shit!
I just stepped on pigshit.
Are you nuts? Why does it have to be me?
Wait.
What are you doing?
Other people get generic check-ups.
But you get a special checkup.