Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Tomorrow will be the last day we’re here.
I just want to have a date with you where we first met.
Up here on this mount.
Your hand is burning hot.
This is not okay.
Why don’t you tell me you’re sick?
Prince, are you okay?
His body is so cold.
He’s shivering.
No.
Hey, why are you back here?
If you’re looking for antibiotics, I moved them outside.
I’m looking for medicines for malaria.
If he doesn't get cured now, he can be dead.
Look at Prince now.
Let me take care of him.
We can clearly see here you can’t take care of him.
Teacher Prince.
I bought you and the kids some snacks.
Wow!
Thank you so much, Uncle Phang.
No problem.
Did you just get back from somewhere?
I went down to pick up the three new volunteers.
Guys,
a new volunteer doctor said if we help him clean his house,
we will get to play new mobile games.
Oh, Teacher Prince.
Did you threaten them?
I just asked them to help me clean up in exchange for some mobile games.
If you came up here just to change a place to drink,
you better go back.
It’s true we’re here because we did something bad.
But my friend isn’t here just to change a place to drink as you said.
I made it.
It might not be as good as the food in Bangkok.
But it’s not spicy.
I think you can handle it.
Thank you.
Hello, Dao.
It’s me, Fah.
I borrowed Mesa’s phone.
There’s no phone signal up here.
I had to walk all over the mountain to get the signal.
Dao,
I gotta go.
I guess I’m being too loud.
People might come yelling at me.
Okay. Talk to you later.
Prince.
Finally, you’re awake.
I was so worried.
Did I…
Prince,
you had malaria.
It nearly killed you.
If it wasn’t for Sincere who drove you to this hospital,
it could be bad.
Drink some water.
You know, Prince?
You slept the whole day.
But you’re fine now.
Thank you so much and…
I’m sorry if I worried you.
And don’t worry about the villagers.
Everyone is doing well now.
You can head home with no concerns.
I heard your new semester is about to start.
What about Dr. Fah?
He already left the mountain.
Probably on his way back to Bangkok now.
I think you should take some rest in order to recover quickly.
Thank you so much, Uncle Phang, for driving us all the way here.
No. I should thank you.
If it wasn’t for you, my life would be a disaster.
I made you guys grilled pork and sticky rice.
Here. Enjoy.
Thank you.
Yes, chief.
Ah!
Teacher Prince is conscious now?
Doctor, Teacher Prince has awoken.
Can I please talk to the village chief?
Chief, Doctor Fah would like to talk to you.
Thank you.
Hi, village chief.
Can I please have the name of the hospital Teacher Prince is in?
To be honest, Doctor.
I’d like to tell you that.
But Sincere asked me not to tell where Teacher Prince is.
I must apologize.
Okay.
I understand.
So?
Which hospital?
Don’t think we can go.
They aren’t okay if we go visit.
Seriously?
Yeah.
And I have work tomorrow.
I can’t hang around.
Then I wish you all a safe journey.
Come visit us again.
Sure.
When you’re home, don’t drink too much.
All right.
- Goodbye, everyone.
- Goodbye, Uncle.
Thank you so much.
- Bye.
- Bye now.
To celebrate your return.
Cheers.
The grilled pork is yummy.
I like it.
Right?
I told you his pork is superb.
The weather is nice. The food is nice.
I guess you lived comfortably up there.
Not even close.
No electricity.
The internet barely worked.
It wasn’t just cold. It was freakin’ cold.
To keep me warm, I almost set myself on fire.
But every time you talk about it, you seem so happy.
Well,
it’s positive thinking.
I lived up there for so long.
If I wasn’t being optimistic, my life would be miserable.
Fah,
I talked to Dao and decided to go to Germany with friends next week.
Wanna join us?
It’s a long weekend next week.
And you still got your visa left.
Slow down, guys.
I just got home.
You want me out again?
I also need to check if I’ll be available.
Come on, Fah. It isn’t like we get to travel together very often.
You can take the one on the mountain with you.
Are you okay, Fah?
I am.
It’s just that we don’t talk anymore.
Sorry. I didn’t know.
Why did you two stop talking?
Things just didn’t really work out.
Forget it.
Let’s not talk about it.
Let’s drink.
Here. Let me pour it for you.
You poured it for yourself too.
Actually,
it’s for you but...
many things happened.
Well then.
Can I just give it to you now?
Get well soon.
After your recovery,
I have something for you as well.
Of course.
They've invited me to the medical supplies handover ceremony.
I think you should go.
At least you will get to say a proper goodbye.
I just want Prince to be with someone good.
Someone who can take care of him.
I don’t have to take care of patients.
I have time for Prince.
Unlike when he was with you.
ONE MONTH LATER
How are you?
I’m good.
Fah.
I’d like to trade shifts with you this Saturday.
Ah!
You sent someone to talk to me earlier, right?
You got it.
Alright. Thanks so much.
Sure. My pleasure.
Hey.
Seriously, what’s your boost, man?
You work like a horse.
I finally got back to work. I want to do my best.
Don’t just work.
Find someone to share things with.
Our profession doesn’t really afford that opportunity.
Maybe I’m better off alone.
Will you excuse me?
Of course.
Wow!
You all did so well today.
I’m sure the real event will be just spectacular.
You’re so great.
Everyone can go home and rest now.
Prince.
It shouldn’t be just me who gets a medical checkup.
You should get one too.
That’s all right.
I’ll get it some other time.
I don’t think there’s a problem.
Of course.
Being in a hospital just reminds me of Doctor Fah.
Have you two been in touch?
We have not.
Why not?
I got his number from the village chief but it’s not reachable.
He probably changed it.
You want me to help find Dr. Fah’s phone number?
I’m sure he wants to reach out to you as well.
If he really does, he should have called long ago.
Maybe he doesn’t have your number either.
If he called the village chief, he would get it right away.
Never mind him.
He might work so hard and forget all about me by now.
Fah.
There’s a letter for you.
The credit card company?
I think I just paid them.
No.
Look. It says here it was sent from the mountain.
Really?
They've invited me to the medical supplies handover ceremony.
Wait.
Why you, Fah?
Because I was the one filing the request to station these supplies on the mountain.
You know what?
It was so hard to request anything.
What a good heart you have.
Are you going?
Don’t think I can.
I got work here.
Yeah?
Not because you don’t have the guts to see the teacher up there?
Hold on.
How did you know about this?
Mesa and JJ told me everything.
I think you should go.
At least you will get to say a proper goodbye.
Don’t leave it hanging.
Hello, Uncle Phang.
Hello.
Didn’t think I’d get to see you again this soon.
It’s my day off so I thought I should visit.
Sure.
These are vitamin C for the chil…
Oh.
Teacher Prince went to the restroom.
Ah!
And what are you guys drawing?
Teacher Prince told us to draw whatever we like.
Wee-ah,
do you have paper and colors for me?
I do.
May I borrow them?
Have you guys finished?
We have.
If you’re finished, hand it to me.
This is my assignment, Teacher.
What are you doing?
The assignment you gave.
Draw whatever I like.
[By Prince]
Hey.
How come you’re here alone?
Isn’t Teacher Prince with you?
I was going to return him the tote bag he forgot.
After we both went home, we never contacted each other.
Why?
Did you have a fight?
Not exactly.
I think there is someone who can take better care of him than I can.
Come on.
What now?
Are you giving up already?
I’ve thought it through, Yayah.
Know what?
I was gonna make a more beautiful and bigger bag for Teacher Prince.
But he didn’t want it.
Do you know why?
His reason was simple.
He said he just liked this embroidery.
Life is that simple.
Sometimes,
you don’t need reasons to like something.
But…
I think it’s too late, Yayah.
He probably has a new tote bag now.
Just got back from the mountain?
Yes.
You look disappointed somehow.
Guess you didn’t see who you wanted to see.
I went to Chiang Mai
hoping to see Teacher Prince. That’s all.
I wanted to know if he’s happy under your care.
You don’t need to ask.
I don’t have to take care of patients.
I have time for Prince
when he needs it.
Even so,
he doesn’t seem happy.
Unlike when he was with you.
I know I don’t have the right to say this.
I just want Prince to be with someone good.
Someone who can take care of him.
From now on,
please take care of him.
Hello.
I don’t think I can take your shift tonight.
I’m going to Chiang Mai.
Teacher Prince.
Are you home?
Prince.
Hi, Mr. Kuafah.
Hello.
Is Teacher Prince home?
Sorry, sir.
Nobody is home.
This family is traveling to Germany.
Germany?
Fell in love with the teacher on the mountain.
And going to Germany to look for him.
- More romantic than a movie.
It’s Germany, not Siam.
I’ve kept him waiting for so long.
I don’t want him to wait any longer.
Seriously, Fah?
Yes.
I’ve made up my mind.
It’s Germany, not Siam.
I’ve kept him waiting for so long.
I don’t want him to wait any longer.
Let’s go then.
Prince?
I’m already at the airport.
That’s okay.
I should be the one who feels bad for missing your event as a drum major.
But I know you’re great. You will definitely nail it.
Keep fighting.
Don’t forget to record the video for me to watch later.
Sure.
I’ll see you.
Bye-bye.
Wow!
And that was our opening parade.
It was just gorgeous.Right, everyone?
Let’s give it up for them.
Here.
What are you doing?
I’m taking you traveling but you’re messing with me.
Just giving you a drink.
As a thank-you for taking me out.
Excuse me.
Guys.
Is anyone there named Prince?
There’s someone asking for you.
Prince?
Hey! Prince.
Someone is looking for you.
Over there.
Prince!
You wait right there.
Okay.
There he is.
Aw!
Go.
I’ll walk you.
Come on.
You…
How did you know I’m here?
We got an hour before we can check-in.
So that’s the story.
Whoa!
That is so cool.
Fell in love with the teacher on the mountain.
And going to Germany to look for him.
- More romantic than a movie.
Don’t support him on that.
Trust me.
You can never find him.
Your story sounds familiar by the way.
It’s like my friend’s story.
He said when he was a teacher up on the mountain, he git his heart broken by the doctor there.
Really?
Yeah.
So many coincidences in this world.
Your friend doesn’t happen to be named Prince, does he?
How did you know that?
Wait a minute.
Does your friend Prince have the last name of the northern monarch?
Damn right.
How did you know that?
For real?
Is this world really that small?
Smaller than you think.
Prince is also my and Kluen’s friend.
Huh?
Let’s leave the small world aside.
Prince isn’t in Germany right now.
He’s a drum major right now at his university.
That’s right, Fah.
Then.
I should go.
What?
Such a small world.
Keep going, Fah.
Find him!
Fighting!
And here I am.
So…
Why do you want to see me?
I got something for you.
I chose the pink stone that brings good luck in love.
So our love will grow beautifully.
Aw!
May I?
Will you be my boyfriend?
Say yes.
What are you even saying?
What do you say?
Say yes.
Um.
Don’t leave me again.
No one can make me leave because I will never leave you.
What are you doing?
Why?
Because we’re in public?
Do you think I care?
Let’s go.
Teacher Prince.
I used to be so afraid to climb the Himalayas.
Now I’m not anymore.
Why?
I have you to climb it with me.
Are you sure you will be my Prince?
Hello.
Didn’t think we would meet again so soon.
And now you got more friends with you.
Teacher Prince.
Teacher Prince, I made this for you.
Tell me.
How much is 1+1?
2.
And 2+2?
4.
And Kluen+Dao?
Boyfriends.
- I…
- have something for you.
You made it for me too?
Yes.
May I wear it for you?
It’s chilly up here.
You’ve been warned to wear warmer clothes.
You are just stubborn.
Stubborn but still cute, right?
Is it better?
Thank you.
You know?
I used to be so afraid to climb the Himalayas.
The Himalayas?
It’s a metaphor.
I compare the Himalayas to life achievement.
I used to dream of climbing the Himalayas with someone.
After I and my ex broke up,
I’ve been so afraid to climb it.
But now,
I’m not anymore.
Why?
Well.
I have you to climb it with me.
Please stay with me and climb the mountain together.
Teacher Prince.
Are you sure
you will be my Prince?
No.
It’s you who will be mine.
Are you ready,
my Kuafah?
You’re on.
Nevertheless…there is only one Himalayas in the world.
Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul
Fah asked you to come over for a meal.
Hey!
You two should keep your distance sometimes.
Hey.
Daonuea and Khabkluen have been together so long.
Don’t be overprotective.
I don’t know.
I despise him.
Should we go to Hua Hin this weekend?
Prince, I want to thank you a million times for bringing back the old Fah.
I love you.
Dao,
after graduation,
will you live here with me?