Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
When are you coming back?
I’ll be away for just two days. Will be back in no time.
I promise
I will be a good boy.
Teacher Prince is sick.
Aou is nursing him.
Don’t let him be alone with Aou. Got it?
(Are you the one Kuafah met on the mountain?)
(I’m Kitty, his girlfriend.)
A girl called this number.
Teacher Prince took the call.
I will be so happy if you can climb the Himalayas again.
If that person can inspire you to climb again,
don’t let that person go.
I’m back.
You.
Don’t you have a birthday party to get to?
Ah!
My little brother has got something urgent to do.
So he postponed the party.
That’s why I hurried back.
Right.
Hey.
About last night…
Teacher Prince, we have a situation.
Wee-ah and Sompor are fighting.
What?
Sompor,
do you have anything to say to Wee-ah?
I’m sorry, Wee-ah.
Wee-ah,
do you have anything to say?
I’m not wrong. Why should I say sorry?
Wee-ah,
I heard the story from Sompor.
She said you broke your word.
You said you would buy her a birthday gift.
But you bought gifts for other girls too. Is that right?
But I don’t think Wee-ah did anything wrong.
What?
He promised to buy her a present.
And he did.
Buying things for other people at the same time isn’t breaking the promise.
That’s right.
Why are you mad?
Wee-ah,
this is about feeling.
Though you didn’t mean to, you let her down.
Aren’t you going to say sorry?
If you let someone down and don’t apologize,
you will grow up to be a bad adult.
Are you talking about me?
No.
I’m talking to Wee-ah here.
You talked to him but looked at me.
If you did nothing wrong, you have nothing to worry about.
See?
You were talking about me.
I said I was talking about the kids.
Why is it so hard for you to understand?
Talking about the kids? Then why did you say he would grow up to be a bad adult?
You’re referring to me.
Calm down.
Happy birthday, Dao.
Thank you.
I wish you a very good year.
It’s already good because you’re with me.
But let me sleep 10 more minutes, please.
Of course.
If the kids didn’t stop me,
I’d definitely fight him.
Do you guys get me?
I do.
But I think you’re still at fault this time.
You even had a guilty conscience.
What?
You promised him before you left you would behave.
But you got wasted
and that girl called and bothered him.
Do you think that a good adult should be?
It wasn’t a big deal.
Besides,
He and I aren’t a thing.
You get me, don’t you, Mesa?
I do.
But if he’s nothing to you, why the heck did you give him the promise?
What?
You guys are my friends.
How about you take my side?
No.
Someone like you will never change no matter how much time passes.
You’re never regretful.
Make it up to him.
How would I do that?
All I got today was anger radiation from him
Like this.
Do what you do best, manipulate.
Pretend to get sick.
He will have a pity for you.
Interesting.
Did you just say I’m manipulative?
Just realized that?
Come on.
Tomorrow, pretend to be sick.
I will tell the children you’re sick.
And they will spread the news.
It’s more reliable that way.
He will believe you’re really sick.
Gosh! Dr. Fah has a serious stomach ache?
Keep it between us.
Don’t make people panic.
Trust me on that.
Hot news!
What? Dr. Fah is pregnant?
What?
Teacher Prince.
Is it true that Dr. Fah is sick and you are pregnant?
Sompor.
I think there’re some misunderstandings here.
Doctor.
Hey.
Did you spread a weird rumor to the kids?
Hey!
JJ.
Why are you here?
Teacher Prince.
I’m in charge here for Kuafah.
And…
where is he?
He has a stomach ache.
He’s resting at his house alone.
Poor him.
He’s a doctor.
But when a doctor gets sick, no one takes care of him.
It’s me.
Are you in?
Ouch!
I am.
I brought you congee and antacid.
I heard you have acid reflux.
Thank you.
Argh!
Ouch!
Are you okay?
I am.
Oh!
Ouch!
You don’t look okay at all.
Here.
Let me help.
Is it all right?
Of course.
It’s good.
Take the medicine and get some rest.
I’ll just leave now.
Hold on.
I’ve got something to say to you.
What is it?
I…
I want to explain about the other night.
You don’t have to.
Just get some rest.
I can’t.
If I don’t get this out, I won’t be able to sleep.
That night, I didn’t mean to go out and get drunk.
My brother’s boyfriend took me there.
And how old are you now?
Don’t you know how to say no?
I went out just to drink.
I just didn’t think I’d be that drunk.
And the girl who called you took my phone when I was using the restroom.
What she said was all nonsense.
She isn’t my girlfriend.
What she is to you doesn’t concern me.
It does.
You’re mad at me.
I’m not.
You are.
I can tell from your voice you’re mad.
If I didn’t pretend I was sick to get you here,
I wouldn’t know you’re this mad.
Oops!
It’s not that.
I mean…
Do you think I’m that silly?
I didn’t mean it that way.
I just don’t want you to be jealous over nothing.
Damn!
You’re a jerk and a narcissist.
What a waste of time.
Hey.
I heard there was a fight.
Pretty bad.
You should help him with the sports day thing.
That way you can be close to him.
Let’s make it fun then.
I will help you with that.
Thank you.
Hey.
Mesa.
Did you forget something?
No.
I came to talk to you.
I heard there was a fight.
Yes.
Pretty bad.
That’s what I heard.
If you want my help, feel free to ask.
Are you sure?
Of course.
I know both parties.
I don’t want the fight to keep going.
I’d like to ask you one thing then.
Can you hand this to the village chief for me?
You wrote a letter to my friend…
Wait.
The village chief?
Yes.
This is a permission letter to organize a sports day in the village.
A sports day?
Because of the fight between Wee-ah and Sompor.
This idea is to amend their relationship.
So the fight you mentioned…
It’s Wee-ah and Sompor.
Wee-ah and Sompor.
Yes.
So this is for the village chief.
Got it.
So he’s only concerned with the kids fighting.
He doesn’t even care about you at all.
Hell yes.
I’m so pissed.
How do I patch things up with him?
I already faked my sickness.
How about you fake your death this time?
Maybe he’ll forgive you.
What a smart idea.
Fah!
How on earth did you come up with that?
One more scoop, please.
I think you should help him with the sports day thing.
That way you can be close to him.
That’s right.
Good idea.
Show him your hard work. He might come around.
Fine.
I will try.
Thank you guys so much.
Here is your reward.
Argh!
The kids should be so proud to have such a caring teacher.
No.
You’re the one who cares about them.
You’ve brought them lots of snacks.
They should be so happy.
I’m happy too
to see you smile.
I mean I’m happy to see the kids smile.
Excuse me.
You’ve got the paint there.
Okay.
Hey, Dr. Fah.
Are you here to help?
Yes.
But I see there’s nothing for me to do.
I’m not needed.
You are.
There’s a lot left to do.
Please.
Here.
Yes.
Where should I paint?
That’s not for painting.
Please clean it for me.
I will change the colors.
Let’s not bother him.
He’s a doctor.
He has to take care of many people.
I can do it.
Unless someone doesn’t want me to.
Everyone wants your help.
There’s a lot left to do.
Please help.
Sure.
Thanks for having me.
Everyone has the paper with the team name on it.
According to the lucky draw,
there will be the blue and the white team.
Open it and see.
You can now go to your team and practice for the competitions.
Wait up.
The children said they wanted you to compete too.
Are we sure about that?
We are.
I will join too.
The more the merrier.
Is that right?
Right.
See?
That’s good.
JJ and I will compete too then.
You didn’t even ask me.
Come on. Just help me.
All right then.
We have some lottery left.
Draw one.
Which color are you?
Blue. You?
I got blue too.
We’re on the same team.
Can I call it destiny?
This is not a very good start at all.
The sports day will be held next week?
It sounds fun.
That’s right.
The children were so excited today.
But we’re not on the same team.
What was it?
I mean…
Wee-ah and Sompor.
We want them to make up
but they are on different teams.
Who knows?
When two people compete,
they might understand each other better.
I heard you guys are competing too.
Dr. Fah’s team will win for sure.
Is that right?
Your body is fit and firm.
But Teacher Prince won the football match against Dr. Fah.
So?
There is no football game on the children’s sports day.
Dr. Fah’s team is going to win.
No.
My team is.
Let’s say the losing team must buy the winning team snacks.
Deal?
Deal.
I will even buy you BBQ pork.
I think…
this has gone a little too far.
That’s okay.
This is fun.
Can I join the BBQ pork party?
Now let’s eat before the food gets cold.
Eat first.
How is Fah doing?
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, happy birthday ♪
Happy birthday,
my sunflower.
Thank you.
Make a wish.
It smells so nice.
Did you make it?
Vanilla scent.
You like it?
Get home safe.
Well…
How about I walk you home?
That’s fine.
I can manage.
I knew this would happen.
Come on.
Let me walk you home.
Thank you.
What?
Why such a big sigh?
You hate to walk with me that much?
No.
I’m worried about the sports day.
Why?
Actually, I never want the competition to get this serious.
But look what Aou and Yayah are doing.
I get you.
You just want it to be fun.
Then
let’s make it fun.
Don’t make the event very competitive.
I will help you with that.
Thank you for understanding.
Do you think they will finally talk?
He refuses to apologize.
He refuses to say he likes her.
It's not always simple to speak up.
It's not always simple to wait either.
Have you competed in a running race before?
I haven’t.
That's okay. I’ll guide you.
There are four steps.
First, on your mark. Stand behind this line.
Okay. Next is get set.
You will bend your knee in a sitting position.
That’s right.
Your hand can’t go beyond this line.
Put it right here.
Left hand as well. That’s right.
In the third step, raise your body up.
Look ahead.
Do it like this.
Teacher Prince, what are you doing?
Making cheerleading pom-poms with the children.
Can I help?
Of course.
This team does the same.
Go!
Am I doing it right?
Yes. Keep making it into small pieces.
Teacher Prince.
Time to eat.
Thank you.
Grilled pork.
Did you do that?
Hey.
The village chief asked me to bring you these sports jerseys.
Are you home?
Hey,
what are you doing in the dark?
Nature calls?
Are you nuts?
I’m searching for something.
Searching?
At night?
Why didn’t you look in the daytime?
I know you’re afraid of the dark.
I’m not.
You remember it wrong.
- Boo!
- Hey!
What the heck are you playing?
What am I playing?
I just wanted to see the reaction of someone so tight-lipped.
So what are you looking for?
The hair clip Wee-ah gave to Sompor.
Ah!
The one Sompor threw away.
Why?
You want Wee-ah to give it to her again?
Yes.
I’ve been looking since the evening.
Still can’t find it.
Okay then.
I will help.
It’s okay.
I can do it myself.
Hey.
When people offer their help,
you should learn to take it.
There’s no need to handle everything yourself.
Here.
I’ll help you find it.
Do you think they will finally talk?
You might not know this but I do.
Those two like each other very much.
Yeah?
That’s why Sompor is so mad.
Right.
And Wee-ah is a tight-lipped one.
He refuses to apologize.
He refuses to say he likes her.
He does things halfway.
That’s why Sompor gets angry.
Come on.
It's not always simple to speak up.
It's not always simple to wait either.
Are you saying you used to wait…
It’s late.
We should go home.
We need to get up early tomorrow.
The village chief has an urgent business to get to.
[BAN KHUN OM HAET NOK SCHOOL SPORTS DAY]
So I’m here to commence the event on his behalf.
The event wouldn’t happen without Teacher Prince’s creativity.
It’s because we teamed up.
Ever since the first day we met…
Does he think this is the wedding of him and Teacher Prince?
Nice speech.
The opening ceremony has ended.
Give him a big hand, guys.
Thank you.
We’re about to start the first game of the day.
You’re with me, the hottest MC.
January, no!
February, no!
March, no!
April (Mesa), yes!
And me, an MC who is hotter than mountain chillis.
Yayah.
Dr.Fah.
Let’s make today a fun day.
The only fun thing I expect
is to see you buy everyone BBQ pork.
Let’s go, everyone.
We’re starting our first game here.
This game is easy.
Two people will be carrying the one on top.
The one on top has a paper hat on
and must steal the hat from the opponents.
Fah, why don’t you concentrate?
Let’s steal more hats.
Did we lose?
Yes.
Dr. Fah, why are you absent-minded?
Wow! They’re going all in. No one wants to lose here.
Go. Go. Go.
Wee-ah, if we win, I’ll buy you snacks for a whole month.
Really?
Hey.
When we fall, we get back up.
Or you want to keep sitting on me?
No!
Aw!!
This game is called balloon stomp.
You sat on me in the last game.
It’s time for me to step on your ballon now.
No way.
Are you sure?
Ouch!
I’m sorry.
So this is how you want it?
Fine.
Here.
Get this.
Now what?
Here’s your food box.
Thank you.
I have a question.
What is the fight between you and Teacher Prince all about?
Nothing.
I can tell even from the distance.
Don’t tell me you’re fighting over me.
I don’t think so, Yayah.
It’s a long story.
Go ahead and tell.
I have time.
So that’s what happened?
I get you, Dr. Fah.
Really?
But I understand Teacher Prince as well.
I feel sorry for him.
He’s going through the same thing again.
No wonder why he's so down.
What do you mean, Yayah?
Thank you
for taking me to the finish line with you
and for finding the hair clip for Wee-ah.
I’m sorry for being unreasonable.
What if I say I get you?
From this moment on,
can I flirt on you?
We’ve come to the last sport of the day
which is a triathlon.
That’s right.
It’s consisted of three different sports.
The first one is an eating challenge.
The second sport is cycling.
And the last one is a three-legged race.
Teacher Prince, are you okay?
I am.
Just warming up.
We will be competing in three sports.
The team that gets to the finish line first wins.
If you’re ready, 3 2 1, go!
The game has started.
They are eating as fast as they can.
Go. Go. Go. Do your best, everyone!
The blue team is in the lead.
The white team is tailing them so closely. So so so close.
Come on.
Faster.
Tag my hand.
Let’s go.
We’ve just started the second competition.
What a close game.
No way.
The blue team is so much ahead.
Can the white team catch up?
Keep going. Keep cycling, my friend.
It’s your turn now, Teacher Prince.
- We’ve come to a three-legged race now.
- Let’s go, Sompor.
The blue team has just started.
I wonder if they can level it up at all.
Teacher Prince has gone so far now.
Teacher Prince, are you all right?
Fah, come on.
- Blue!
- White!
Oops! What is going on over there?
Teacher Prince just fell all of a sudden.
Fah, it’s your chance now. Surpass him.
Dr. Fah, why are you stopping?
The blue team, keep going!
Let’s help Teacher Prince up.
Come on.
Let’s go to the finish line together.
Wow! Dr. Fah comes back and helps Teacher Prince up.
What a lovely ship. No! I mean what an impressive race.
And they finally get to the finish line together.
The blue and white teams finished at the same time as a result of today's competition.
We have a tie game.
No matter who wins or loses, every contestant will get a medal.
Teacher Prince, is this the real gold?
It’s a chocolate medal.
So delicious.
That’s only a consolation prize.
What you best deserve is this one.
Hey.
How did you get it?
Before the competition started,
I went looking for it.
Besides,
I know everything, Wee-ah.
Know what?
You gave plain hair clips to other girls.
But the one you gave Sompor was custom-made.
That’s right.
I chose a pink hair clip because Sompor likes pink.
Why didn’t you tell Sompor from the beginning?
Because it’s not cool.
But I think it’s much cooler telling the truth.
It’s not too late to tell her.
The sooner you tell, the sooner you’ll look cool.
Come on.
Yes, sir.
How is your ankle?
It’s all right.
Thank you.
Let’s get you bandaged.
Come on.
HEALTH CENTER
You got a sprained ankle. You should be fine.
Next time, don’t force it.
That’s why you looked painful when you ran.
Thank you.
Your welcome.
It’s a duty of a doctor to take care of his patients.
I mean thank you for taking me to the finish line with you.
And for finding the hair clip for Wee-ah.
- I’m sorry.
You first.
I’m sorry for being unreasonable.
There’s no reason for me to be angry at you about that night.
What if I say I get you?
What do you mean?
Yayah told me what you’ve been through.
What do you mean, Yayah?
Teacher Prince told me he had a terrible ex.
That person couldn’t provide him with clarity.
He came when he wanted to.
He went with someone else when he felt like it.
Teacher Prince couldn’t even get jealous.
Because there was no established relationship.
What did Teacher Prince do?
They were together for a brief amount of time.
Teacher Prince couldn’t endure it at last.
He broke up with that person.
And what you’re doing is a repeat of what his ex did to him.
No wonder why he’s mad.
He doesn’t want to get hurt again.
Just because I’m not being clear doesn’t mean I’m not serious with you.
But I’m so serious that I’m afraid it’s too soon.
I’d been with my ex for seven years yet we couldn’t make it.
That’s why I don’t want to rush things.
But if my actions get you the wrong idea,
from this moment on,
can I flirt on you?
Prince,
I’m returning the cap gun I borrowed.
Oops!
Am I interrupting?
No.
Will you please excuse me?
Thank you.
What were you two talking about?
What was it?
Nothing.
I was just giving him first aid.
Where are you going?
That gunshot was a signal to start.
This game isn’t going to be as easy as the one we competed in today.
We’ll see about that.
Because I never lose.
I just want to try hard.
I want to stop everything…just to be with him.
Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul
Hey!
What are you doing?
You allowed me to flirt on you.
From now on, I’ll just flirt on you non-stop.
Prepare yourself for that.
Can I put my hand right here until it gets warmer?
Prince, this way.
Teacher Prince already has someone he’s talking to.
Don’t worry.
I’m not trying to steal him.
I just want him to meet someone who can take care of him better than me.
What are you doing?
Your friend should know you have a doctor to take care of you up on the mountain.