Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
This batch of volunteers is weird somehow.
If you came up here just to change a place to drink,
you better go back.
It’s true we’re here because we did something bad.
But my friend isn’t here just to change a place to drink as you said.
I won’t tell the village chief about the other day.
But if you do something terrible again, you won’t get away with it.
Keep a close eye on my then, Teacher.
Please take care of me.
Fah.
Fah, are you up?
Don’t you have work to get to?
I need a few more minutes.
Why don’t you take care of yourself?
All you do is drink. That’s bad for your health.
Have you ever got a health check-up?
Why would I?
I am a doctor.
Just get up. I’m leaving for class now.
Don’t be late for work, alright?
Off you go, Dao.
Hi, there.
Are you leaving?
The little brother is.
But the big brother isn’t.
Wow! This is good.
You are so good, baby.
You’re breathing heavily.
Baby.
Babe.
Hey!!
How did you get in here?
Hi, Gong.
You’re here.
Been looking for you.
Come on. Let’s go home.
Bye.
Goodbye.
No!
Wait!
How did that pig get into my room?
It’s the children’s pig.
They took him out for a walk.
He must have wandered here.
Take him back then.
I’ll continue my sleep.
Please deal with him.
Wait a minute.
Don’t you have to do health check-ups for the villagers?
That’s on the 9th.
And what’s the date today?
6th.
Today is the 9th.
The 6th.
Just check the calendar there.
The first patient, please come in.
Have a seat.
Open your mouth, please.
Should I take it off?
No! Not that.
I mean…
Hey, Wee-ah.
Let’s get on the weighing scale.
I’m 30 kilograms.
30…
What?
I’m feeling hot.
I might have a fever.
No, Wee-ah.
You need to stand on both feet to weigh.
It’s okay. I’ll just go with 30 kilograms.
I like it that way.
Come on, Wee-ah.
No, I won’t.
I don’t want to weigh.
That’s normal body temperature.
No. I’m feeling so hot.
If you don’t believe me, feel it.
Yeah, you’re sweating.
Did you just expose yourself to the sun?
- I don’t want to weigh.
- Get up there.
Don’t resist.
Wee-ah.
Don’t be stubborn.
Teacher Prince.
We talked, didn’t we?
Outside school, you must behave.
Yes.
I knew this would happen.
The village chief sent me to help.
Uncle Phang, please step on the weighing scale first.
This thing keeps moving.
It’s making me dizzy.
The problem isn’t with the scale.
It’s with you, Uncle.
How about this?
We do that later.
Let’s just sit him down.
Hey!
Hello, Doctor.
I’m this way.
Why didn’t you tell me?
Hello.
Okay then.
Open your mouth, please.
You smell like alcohol.
It’s daytime and you’re drunk already?
A drink party with friends once in a while.
Once in a while?
You drink every day.
You know me so well, Teacher.
I’m right here, Uncle.
Who moved you here?
All right.
Please let the next patient in.
Hold on.
Aren’t you going to have lunch?
There’s a lunch box from the village chief for you.
You go ahead.
I will continue the check-ups.
I will help then.
You should eat now.
A kid like you should eat like a horse, you know?
If you don’t eat, you won’t have the energy to work.
What about you?
You haven’t even had breakfast yet.
Where’s the source of energy to work?
Okay.
If I eat, we’re good?
This is my lunch, right?
Don’t I get an omelet too?
The village chief made it.
Of course, no omelet.
Seriously,
his food is good
but it’s just a bit too spicy.
To be honest,
your omelet and rice
was really good for my soul.
What an overstatement.
Let’s eat already.
We need to work, don’t we?
Okay.
Come on.
Hurry up. I don’t want to be here.
The other room is available. You can use it.
I’m done!
Okay. Just a sec.
I’m done here.
What’s the hurry?
Hey. Where have you been?
Don’t you have medical check-ups to do?
I’m here to use the restroom.
Dang! Very smelly here.
Sorry.
Fah,
I have a question.
Do you like Teacher Prince?
You’re crazy?
Teacher Prince? Who would like him?
Mesa said everyone who sees him will fall for him.
Even you.
Mesa,
what is that supposed to mean?
Don’t tell me you…
Yes.
I think I like Teacher Prince.
They teach together.
After spending time together, he’s fallen for him.
Well. He’s cute.
Cute
?He’s so cranky.
Not just with the kids, but with me too.
Someone like you deserves all condemnation.
You’re working with him today.
Try to find out of he’s dating someone, will you?
Are you nuts? Why me?
No.
Well then.
No more borrowing phone for you.
Relax.
Think about it.
You can choose to be lonely at night
or call your beloved brother sometimes.
No more patients so…
Will you excuse me?
Hold on for a sec.
Actually,
I still have one patient left.
Who?
The one in the mirror.
No need to speak in riddles. Could’ve just said it.
Bring that chair and sit over here.
Open your mouth.
Everything seems fine.
I’ll check your heart now.
Stop! What are you doing?
Listen to your heart.
I won’t hear it clearly through the shirt.
But other people got their hearts listened through clothes.
Well.
Other people got general check-ups.
But this is a special check-up.
Why?
Are you shy?
I’m not.
Just curious.
Do it quickly.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
(You’re crazy?)
(Teacher Prince? Who would like him?)
(Everyone who sees him will fall for him.)
(Even you.)
You have a strong heart.
I guess it’s well taken care of.
Are you dating someone?
What?
What does that have to do with anything?
The doctor asked you a question.
You should just answer.
Why?
Are you hitting on me?
Well.
I just want to know my patient’s heart condition.
You’ve been here for a while now.
Must be lonely living far from your lover.
I’m not dating anyone.
In case that’s what you want to hear.
And I’m not lonely.
Are we done checking?
I’ll leave now.
He is just so damn cute.
I’m gonna find out what Teacher Prince's weakness is.
I have no clue what you want.
But if you have that much free time,
you should spend it on taking care of the villagers.
Argh!
Tag!
Look.
He is just so damn cute.
I really want to be those kids.
I want to play tag with him.
What an adorable human being.
You’re exaggerating.
Let me tell you.
They used to have only him here.
But now, they have Dr. Fah up here too.
Teacher Prince will surely be forgotten.
You’re so confident.
Let me prove it to you.
Girls.
Stop. Stop.
Stand here.
I have a question for you.
Yes.
Between…
Teacher Prince and
Dr. Kuafah
who is hotter?
Teacher Prince, of course.
Oh! I got you, man.
That’s right.
Teacher Prince is hot, cute, and nice.
Dr. Kuafah has nothing on him.
Let’s go.
“Dr. Kuafah has nothing on him,” she said.
“Has nothing on him.”
Kids don’t lie.
Kuafah's throne is under threat.
From Bangkok's it boy to the mountain's loser.
No way!
I haven’t lost yet.
You’ll see.
I’m gonna find out what Teacher Prince's weakness is.
BAN KHUN OM HAET NOK SCHOOL
Teacher, I have a question.
Yes, Wee-ah.
If 2 + 2 isn’t 4, then what is it?
2 + 2 equals a rabbit.
You never fall for my joke.
What?
He can be entertaining and academic too.
Aw!
He’s smart and doesn’t care about his image.
That’s easy. Anyone can do that.
Watch me.
Shit!
I just stepped on pigshit.
Help me wash it up.
Thank you, Teacher Prince.
You’re such a great help.
You’re welcome. I’m willing to help.
I’m feeling faint.
Hey!
Let’s get you inside.
Gorgeous, smart, generous, and strong.
Nobody is perfect.
You sound envious.
Me? Envious?
No way.
I’ll show you
I’m a lot better than he is.
Playing football?
Can I join?
How about we make this game more fun?
How?
If I goal, Teacher Prince must take off one piece of clothes.
But if your Teacher Prince can goal,
I’ll take off one of my clothes.
You sure about that?
I am.
Right?
Right!
Teacher Prince, go go!
Teacher Prince, keep fighting!
Dr. Fah, boo!!
Teacher Prince, go go!
Tired?
I play football often.
This game will not tire me out.
I meant are you tired of stalking me?
Stalking you?
You think you’re a TV star?
I have no clue what you want.
But if you have that much time,
you should spend it on taking care of the villagers.
Uncle Phang, for example,
who drinks every day.
I know.
We already have an appointment.
Yeah?
When?
This evening.
I’ll go see him after this.
I’m taking off then.
Wait.
What?
Uncle Phang’s house is this way.
I know.
I just forgot.
Dr. Fah, you’re naked.
Why are you following me?
Are you trying to pick on me?
What?
I’m bringing something for Uncle Phang.
Argh!!
Why are you so shocked?
Look closely.
Oh!
That’s Uncle Phang.
I thought it was a body.
So…
Your hands, when will you let go?
Sorry.
Uncle.
He’s always like this.
Drunk every day.
Sometimes he sleeps in water pottery when drunk.
Wow!
That’s terrible.
What if something happens to him?
Everyone tries to make him quit.
He just won’t listen.
Then it is hard.
Hm?
I’ve met a lot of patients like him.
Stubborn type.
When I give them advice or warning, they even talk back.
I can’t do anything more than give him treatment when he’s ill.
Come with me.
I will show you something.
Who is this?
Uncle Phang’s wife.
Wife?
Where is she now?
She passed.
The village chief told me
Uncle Phang and his wife made the best roasted pork around here.
They sold it down the hill.
Why did he stop?
After his wife died three months ago,
he’s just lost it.
All he does is drink.
What’s up with my patients these days?
When they get hurt, they get drunk.
So bad.
Right?
Just like someone around here.
Oops!
Did I just call myself out?
I know it’s hard.
But from now on,
please take care of Uncle Phang for us.
A doctor is the only one he will listen to.
Good evening, Chief.
Are you visiting Uncle Phang?
I am.
It’s good you’re here. I have news for you.
What news?
There will be a ritual slaughter tomorrow.
It’s Gong, the children’s pig.
So please inform the children for me.
Wow!
That’s a tough job too.
Good luck.
Children.
I’ve got news for you.
What? Slaughter?
Hey!
How did you get here?
We overheard Teacher Prince say Gong is about to be slaughtered.
We brought him here as we know people don’t like to come here.
Where is Gong?
This is a health center.
How can any pig be here?
Enough with the nonsense.
Children.
I’ve got news for you.
Teacher.
My dad is ready for the slaughter.
What? Slaughter?
Ah!
She said scissors.
The village chief needs scissors to work on something.
Let’s talk outside.
Why did you lie to the kids?
Because I haven’t told them yet.
You must tell them now.
I need to take the pig to shower first.
My dad is ready to kill it.
Can you give me more time?
I’m afraid the kids will be shocked if I’m not careful.
Sure. I understand.
But please don’t take too long.
Or my dad will yell at me.
Hey!
How did you get here?
What is happening?
We overheard Teacher Prince say Gong is about to be slaughtered.
Yeah?
It’s time?
You’re making me hungry…
I mean thirsty.
Why is there no water here?
Why did you bring him here?
We brought him here as we know people don’t like to come here.
Teacher Prince said he wouldn’t come here if not necessary
because Dr. Fah is not a good man.
What?
Teacher Prince said that?
Why did he say that?
Children.
Where are you guys?
Teacher Prince is here. Let’s get Gong hidden.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Where is Gong?
Gong?
You mean the pig?
This is a health center.
How can any pig be here?
Yeah?
Then what is it under the tablecloth?
Hey, Gong!
When did you get here?
He must have flown here.
Enough with the nonsense.
HEALTH CENTER
Teacher, can we spare Gong’s life?
Please. He is so lovely.
Children,
let me ask you something.
What do you study for?
It’s our duty.
When we grow up, we can lighten our parents' burdens.
I want to be smart and make money to support my parents.
See?
We all have our duties.
Gong has his duty too.
The village chief raises him so that one day he can be our food.
Aren’t you going to let Gong perform his duty?
Goodbye, Gong.
We should commence now.
Guys, you’ve done great.
Now close your eyes.
We thank you so much, Gong.
We wish you a heavenly afterlife.
Hey!
Teacher Prince.
Teacher.
Hey.
What is this?
Welcoming party for the four of you.
It’s our tradition.
We throw a party to officially welcome new visitors.
Thanks for taking care of me when I passed out.
Thank you for helping me with the check-up the other day.
I guess he'd never seen anything like that.
That’s why he passed out.
You can continue what you left off.
I’ll take it from here.
All right.
Thank you, Doctor.
Thank you.
Mesa should see you now,
Mr. Perfect.
Wow!
Expensive perfume.
It smells authentic.
A designer bag.
Who exactly is this guy?
What’s wrong?
I’m worried about Fah.
Fah has never lived a tough life like this before.
They don’t have electricity.
They barely have phone reception.
Do you think he will make it?
Don’t overthink it.
Should I call his dad?
Tell him to move Fah back here for the community service.
Dao,
I know you’re so concerned about Fah.
But you said it yourself
Fah should spend more time for himself.
It might be his true rest time.
Right?
Yeah.
I hope so.
Don’t you worry.
I made lots of your favorite food today.
Can I get a reward?
No.
No?
Fine.
Phang.
The pig has been slaughtered.
Don’t you want to make roasted pork for everybody?
You guys go ahead.
Please do.
I know you’re the best when it comes to roasted pork.
Right.
Please do it for Gong.
He must be happy if you’re the one that cooks him.
Phang.
Please, Uncle Phang.
- Please, Uncle Phang.
- Please. I want to eat your roasted pork.
The villagers love your roasted pork.
You’re the best around here.
Be confident.
I love you because of your roasted pork, you know?
Stop talking. Starting roasting now.
Finally awake?
Did I faint?
You did.
If you have a fear of blood, don’t look at it.
No more acting cool and watching people kill pigs.
What time is it?
7 p.m.
What?
We’re late.
For what?
Come on. Follow me.
We’re late for the party.
Took you long enough to come.
What is this?
Welcoming party for the four of you.
It’s our tradition.
We throw a party to officially welcome new visitors.
Let’s join them.
The party is about to start.
Come on.
Why don’t you wait for me?
Come dance with us.
There.
You look cool.
Dance with me.
Only him?
The locals are so nice.
They are.
Are you done dancing?
Dance with me.
Dao.
Uncle Phang’s roasted pork is so good.
When I go back to Bangkok, I’ll ask him to make some for you.
Would you like that?
Really?
This is odd.
You sound happy somehow.
Because Uncle Phang’s pork is just so good.
(Yeah?)
(But I think there’s more to the story.)
Tell me honestly.
You’re not flirting with someone up there, are you?
Are you crazy?
Oops!
I’m being loud again.
Dao, I gotta go.
The house owner is coming.
(Sure.)
Okay.
Talk to you later.
Hey.
Is this your house?
Of course.
You brought me here this evening.
Don’t you remember?
Really?
I don’t remember.
So…
Did you just talk to your lover?
Why do you want to know?
Are you hitting on me?
No.
You talk to someone so sweetly every night.
I’m just curious.
A fainted guy can talk back now.
I guess you’re feeling better.
Of course.
I ate Uncle Phang’s roasted pork.
I’m completely healed.
That’s good.
Uncle Phang said he’d quit drinking.
And you’re fully recovered.
That means nobody in this village is sick now.
No.
Who?There’s one person left.
Who?
This one.
You meant me?
Yes.
You take care of other people
but forget to take care of yourself.
It's hard to convince people to take care of themselves
when you drink a lot
and don't eat when you work.
I get it now.
I will take care of myself.
So…
Will you excuse me now?
Thanks for taking care of me when I passed out.
Thank you for helping me with the check-up the other day.
Hey!
Hold on.
I saw a branded perfume in your room.
Is it yours?
What?
You saw it?
Why?
Are you afraid people will know you’re rich?
It’s the opposite.
It’s a fake one from a market.
Only 300 baht.
I don’t support fake perfumes but…
the merchant kept pushing me to buy.
Will you excuse me now?
Almost busted.
When our minds are at ease, all we want is for time to slow down.
Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul
The villagers say Dr. Fah and Teacher Prince are dating.
The locals are saying you’re dating Teacher Prince.
What?
What if I really like him?
Will you be mad?
I wish the pain…
turns into butterflies
and fly away.