Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
My mom…
is inviting you to come over.
I don’t mind at all no matter what your house looks like.
Na Chiang Dao.
The last name of the ancient monarch of the North.
Dr. Fah, I like him a lot.
When will you two become boyfriends?
Hey, Prince.
Coming to Knot’s party too?
I just wanted someone here to know whom Prince is talking to.
I’m not trying to steal Prince.
Because someone like him needs a guy who has time for him.
When we both go home one day,
I might not have time to take care of you.
What?
I forgot my umbrella?
I knew you’d forget it.
When did you become so thoughtful?
After I met you.
If I’m noting thoughtful,
you will not stop nagging at me.
Are you complimenting or picking on me?
Complimenting, of course.
I bought this umbrella in Chiang Mai downtown.
I knew I’d need it.
Just didn’t know I’d need it this soon.
Well, It’s been pouring lately.
I didn’t mean it like that.
I meant I didn’t know I’d get to use it with someone I care about so soon.
Let’s go already.
Before it’s getting heavier.
Hey! Slow down.
Wait for me.
Thank you for walking me home.
I should get inside.
Hold on.
I walked you home.
How about you give me a reward?
What reward?
Well…
Like what we did in the car.
Every time I think about it,
I get so excited.
Close your eyes.
I knew you wouldn’t agree to it easily.
What?
Why so easy?
Do you want your reward or not?
I do.
Ouch!
Excited enough?
I’m leaving now.
Bye.
Thank you for walking me.
You don’t have to do it every day.
Why not?
You don’t want to see me?
It’s not that.
I don’t want to bother you.
Because you have to wake up earlier.
Seeing you one minute longer makes me happy.
Besides,
I’m here to get my reward.
What reward now?
This.
What are you doing?
Getting my reward.
I now have enough energy to work all day.
Just go already.
He looks happy.
Well, well.
What a sweet morning.
This is school, not a lavender field.
Be more shameful, will you?
You, cheesy doctor!
Right.
Yayah, waiting for someone?
I’m waiting for you, Teacher.
My dad asked me to give these snacks to the children.
Thank you so much.
Please tell the village chief I said thank you.
How do you feel?
About the snacks?
I’m so thankful.
Not that.
I mean getting kissed by Dr. Fah.
I saw everything.
Since you returned from Bangkok, you guys have been lovey-dovey.
Are you two boyfriends already?
Not yet.
What?
You two aren’t boyfriends yet?
You guys will leave this mountain in three days!
Why hasn’t Dr. Fah asked you to be this boyfriend yet?
I haven’t got a chance to say it.
I feel like things are going fast.
And I just knew his family was of royal descent.
I think we need more time to get to know each other.
I know you’re waiting for him to say it.
He’s probably finding the right moment in these three days to say it.
Dress up nicely for that in the meantime.
Dress up what, Yayah?
Nonsense.
Let’s do this.
I’ll help you plan your confession moment.
Make it grand.
You rappel from a chopper with a big flower bouquet in your hand.
How does that sound?
Does it wow you?
Yeah, wow.
Wow, what an absurd idea.
Rappel from a chopper?
How on earth could you come up with that?
You don’t like it?
Hello, Dao.
This is Fah.
I…
got something to ask.
I mean Mesa is making a confession to someone he likes.
Any advice?
Wow! Kuafah who has flirted with tons of girls is asking me this question?
It’s different.
I’ve never seriously hit on anyone.
(You just talked about yourself.)
No.
I mean Mesa.
Forget it.
What’s your advice anyway?
Be honest and clear.
Be honest and clear?
How?
Suddenly say it while walking together?
(That’s too blunt.)
Come on.
Take the person on a date first.
To somewhere nice.
At the right moment, hand out a present.
Then make the confession.
That’s pretty honest.
(I wish you…)
(I mean I wish Mesa good luck.)
Hopefully.
Thank you.
Moonbahte the stone and that’s it.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
I brought the stone here to moonbahte it.
I thought I’d do it for my brother before I leave the mountain.
I’m here to make necklaces for the children too.
Yeah?
What a coincidence.
Should we do it together?
The moon tonight is more beautiful than that night.
What night?
That…
That night.
The night you helped me make the necklace.
The moon is gorgeous.
The stones must be getting so much charm.
Besides, I’m sitting next to you.
When you wear it, you’ll think of me.
You said you’re doing this for your brother.
Yes, I’m doing it for my brother.
He’ll think of me when he wears it.
Ah!
Yeah?
You know it’s cold.
Why didn’t you bring your warm clothes?
I hurried out and forgot.
Here.
Thank you.
Ever since I lived here,
I haven’t got to explore the mountain yet.
I work so much that I don’t have time to get around.
Without knowing it,
it’s time to go home.
There are still things I want to do here.
I want to cook on the mountain.
I want to grow vegetables.
I want to try building a house up here.
And…
There’s one thing I want to do the most.
I want to have a date with you up here on the mountain.
What?
Tomorrow will be the last day we’re here.
I just want to have a date with you where we first met.
Up here on this mount.
Will you go on a date with me?
Yes.
I will.
You’re looking good in this outfit.
We thank you so much for taking care of the villagers’ health.
Bad news.
The villagers are having bad diarrhea.
They’re having a stomachache.
Come take a look.
Wow!
This is more beautiful than I imagined.
What?
It’s your first time here too?
I’m just like you.
I always work.
I don’t have time to explore.
Then I’m gonna take you on an extremely fun trip.
Come here.
Hey!
What is this?
What are you doing?
Hey!
No.
These are pretty.
Hey.
Let me show you a magic trick.
Ta-da!
Hey, when did you pick it up?
So cute.
This is easy.
Let’s go.
Wait. I’m coming.
You’re looking good in this outfit.
What are you saying?
I wore Yayah’s outfit before.
They are similar.
I didn’t get a clear look at you back then.
Because…
I was on top of you.
On top, my foot!
Let’s go.
The villagers are waiting for us.
The locals are so nice.
They threw us a welcoming party.
Now we’re leaving.
They’re throwing a farewell party for us again.
I’m starting to get why you love it here.
Come on.
On my first days here,
I always counted down the day I would get to leave.
But after I got to know everyone,
after I got to live here,
I wanted to be a better person.
Surprisingly, I don’t want to leave anymore.
When there’s a chance,
I hope we get to meet again.
Thank you so much for having me all this time.
Anything else you want to add, Dr. Fah?
What is it?
If you want to say anything to anyone in particular, do it now.
Everyone is waiting to hear it.
Well…
My speech for everyone has ended.
I should keep the rest personal.
This is not fun at all.
Thank you.
Doctor, would you like to try this?
What is it?
Raw Beef Spicy Salad.
I think I’ll pass.
But thank you so much.
Doctor.
We thank you so much for taking care of the villagers’ health.
We all wish you good luck in life.
Thank you very much.
Please enjoy the party.
Teacher Prince, are you leaving?
When I’m away, don’t be naughty, Wee-ah.
Teacher Prince.
Will you go for a walk with me?
Aw!
Can I borrow your teacher for a while?
You can take him.
Where are we going?
They say there’s a nice place for watching fireflies up there.
I’m taking you there.
Be careful here.
Don’t get lost in the woods like the last time.
I’ve studied the route.
I assure you we won’t get lost.
Why?
Don’t you trust me?
No.
You don’t trust me.
Then why are you holding my hand?
If you do something bad,
I’ll crush your hand till it’s broken.
Crush till it’s broken?
How strong.
I’m so scared.
Fah!
Bad news.
The villagers are having bad diarrhea.
They’re having a stomachache.
Come take a look.
Ouch! My stomach hurts.
From what I checked,
I think they’re having food poisoning.
Probably the Raw Beef Salad.
Did you eat it, Doctor?
No, I didn’t.
I was afraid of food poisoning.
We should find out who ate it.
Everyone was at risk.
That’s right.
Please help take those who have serious symptoms to the health center.
Help each other.
If you can, proceed to the health center.
Are you okay?
The doctor is coming.
You’ll get better soon.
The doctor is coming for you.
Where is the pain?
You’ll be given this first.
Please give the meds to these three patients.
How is this patient doing?
What do we do?
You’re getting better.
Take these medicines home and get some rest.
Yes. Thank you so much.
Sorry. I fell asleep.
Did you get any sleep at all?
It’s good you got to rest.
I always work the night shift like this. I am used to it.
Are you two traveling with me to Chiang Mai?
What?
Your volunteer time is up.
We don’t want to keep bothering you.
So I’m asking if you want to travel with me.
Not today, I guess.
The villagers are still sick.
When they are fully recovered, I will go myself.
Right.
I will stay and help him.
Thank you very much.
I’m going to run an errand in Chiang Mai then.
Sure. Thank you so much.
You’re going home later than scheduled.
Will your mom be worried?
She will complain if I leave you behind.
That means your mom is starting to warm up to me, yes?
That means my mom teaches me to be nice.
Come on.
If you’re worried about me, just admit it.
Let’s eat.
Uncle Phang made us grilled pork and sticky rice.
You go ahead.
I need to do prescriptions.
I told you
you can take care of others but don’t forget to take care of yourself too.
Your hand is burning hot.
Are you sick?
This is not okay.
Why don’t you tell me you’re sick?
Teacher Prince.
Hey.
Let’s eat.
Uncle Phang made us grilled pork and sticky rice.
You go ahead.
I need to do prescriptions.
Eat first.
You haven’t eaten anything since the morning.
Hold on.
Here.
I told you
you can take care of others but don’t forget to take care of yourself too.
Why should I take care of myself
when I have you to do it?
What are you saying?
Eat it yourself.
What?
What should I do?
I haven’t eaten anything all day.
I’m starving
I’ve got my hands full.
What should I do?
You!
Ouch! My stomach hurts.
I think I’m having gastritis.
Here.
Acting like a child.
Thank you.
So…
Everyone is getting better.
What a relief.
Right.
Should we continue what we left off?
What is it?
If we take a right turn here, we will reach the place to watch the fireflies.
Is it okay with you if we stop by for a little while?
Yes,
it is.
Come on.
Hey.
Your hand is burning hot.
Maybe because the weather is hot.
No.
The weather isn’t hot.
Are you sick?
No.
I’m doing okay.
Hey.
This is not okay.
Gosh!
You’re burning up.
Why don’t you tell me you’re sick?
Come on. Let’s get back.
Can you walk?
I’m sorry.
I didn’t know it’d be this bad.
Of course, it’s bad.
You are burning up.
Next time,
if you feel sick, let me know immediately.
You complain about me, but you don’t take care of yourself either.
I really want to spank you.
I’m sorry.
Get some rest.
I’ll take care of you.
Prince is sick?
Yes.
What is it?
JJ asked me to come fetch you.
There are more people having stomachaches.
But I have to…
You go.
I will watch Teacher Prince here.
Hurry back when you’re done.
Okay.
Hey,
I’ll be right back.
Just go.
I will get some sleep.
Please take care of him.
Just go.
Damn it, Fah.
Seeing you now reminds me of the old you.
How?
Workaholic.
All he did was work.
He didn’t even eat.
He barely went out to see his friends.
He didn’t have time for his ex either.
But
it’s in the past.
He’s better now.
Sorry, I keep talking.
You should get some rest.
[Huen Soontaree Vechanont]
Hi.
Hello, ma’am.
Hi, village chief.
Is this Sincere?
That’s right.
You’ve grown to be a handsome man.
Sincere, this is the village chief
who is taking care of Prince up on the mountain.
Hello.
Teacher Prince is very nice.
He takes care of the children and everyone so well.
Really?
Recommending him to you is a great idea, isn’t it?
How is he doing?
He’s doing fine.
He should be back in a couple of days.
The villagers are having diarrhea, so Teacher Prince stays on and helps out.
Have you been doing well?
I have.
What about you, chief? Are you doing well?
I am.
Prince, are you okay?
What’s going on?
I have no clue.
His body is so cold.
He’s shivering.
Let me see.
Hey.
Can you hear me?
I can.
Do you have a headache?
Do you feel like puking?
A little.
I wanted to throw up just now.
But it wouldn’t come out.
No.
Fah!
Fah, where are you going?
Hey,
why are you back here?
To get the medicines.
What medicines?
If you’re looking for antibiotics, I moved them outside.
No.
I’m looking for medicines for malaria.
So Teacher Prince is…
If he doesn't get cured now, he can be dead.
We have no choice.
I’ll carry you down the mountain.
Look at him.
Let me take care of him.
We can clearly see here you can’t take care of him.
Hey, why are you back here?
To get the medicines.
What medicines?
If you’re looking for antibiotics, I moved them outside.
No.
I’m looking for medicines for malaria.
Mosquito-borne disease?
So Teacher Prince is…
Yes.
If he doesn't get cured now,
he can be dead.
My car broke down. I’m still fixing it, Doctor.
Do we have any other cars?
I need to send Teacher Prince to treatment.
The village chief has one.
But he’s now in Chiang Mai downtown.
How do we contact people outside the village?
Hello.
Where are you?
Are you somewhere my heart belongs?
(That’s right.)
(I’m right where your heart is at.)
(How are you doing over there?)
I’m doing fine but missing you so much.
Yayah!
What is it?
Can I borrow your walkie-talkie?
What is happening?
Teacher Prince is deadly sick.
What?
I’m contacting someone to send an ambulance here.
All right. Of course.
Tonnam, talk to you later.
Thank you so much.
Hi. Is anyone there?
Hello.
Can anyone hear me?
You haven’t reached anyone down the mountain yet?
No.
I asked Yayah’s husband.
There’s no car in that village either.
Are you cold?
Let me get you a scarf.
This necklace
you haven’t given it to the children yet?
I lied.
I wasn’t going to give it to the children.
It’s for you but…
many things happened.
Well then…
Can I give it to you now?
In case I’m away for treatment for so long.
Thank you.
Here.
Get well soon.
After your recovery, I have something for you as well.
Of course.
Get some sleep.
Uncle Phang should be done fixing his car by tomorrow morning.
Fah has been silent for two days.
Don’t know if something happened to him.
Don’t worry.
Let’s do this.
If he doesn’t reach out by tomorrow,
I’ll take you to Chiang Mai to see him. Okay?
We don’t have to do that.
Just stay with me.
Eat then.
Good boy.
You’ll be rewarded when we’re in our room.
Kluen!
What did you say?
Why are you turning red?
I’m not.
I meant I’d kiss you on the cheek.
What were you thinking?
Nothing.
I didn’t think of anything.
Okay. You didn’t.
Let’s just eat.
How is it going, Uncle Phang?
The rain is pouring.
For me to get it done, the rain must stop first
Hey.
Teacher.
We have no choice.
I’ll carry you down the mountain.
Please bear with me a bit longer.
Can you really handle that?
I must.
I can’t let you stay like this.
It can take your life.
You trust me, don’t you?
I’m in your hand.
I’m sorry.
Are you all right?
I am.
Does it really have to rain now?!
Come on.
Let’s go.
I should walk so you don’t have to carry me.
Are you sure?
Hey!
Prince!
What’s happening to him?
He is having malaria.
He needs to go to a hospital now or he might die.
Get in my car.
Now!
You’re nearly there.
Hold on.
Let us travel alone.
Why?
Do you need to ask?
Look at him.
Do you have any idea how fragile he is?
I never wish for him to get sick.
Enough.
Let me take care of him.
We can clearly see here you can’t take care of him.
Fah,
what are you doing here?
Aunt Cham’s condition is getting worse.
She throws up everything she eats.
Her grandchild is having the same symptoms.
I can’t go.
I’m sending Prince to a hospital.
No. You go.
I’ll be fine.
But the villagers might not be without you.
(Because Buai can’t live without me.)
(But you can just fine, Fah.)
The Fah that I know always chooses work over me.
So no matter how many times we start over, you will choose work every time.
It’s your job after all.
Fah.
Please take care of him.
I will. You don’t need to tell me.
Hey!
(I said this before, didn’t I?)
(I climb the Himalayas to see someone waiting for me up there.)
Fah.
- (Today, I realized…)
- Hey! Come on.
(The person up there is just me.)
(Me who never changes.)
I will climb the Himalayas to see you once again.
Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul
Do you realize you slept the whole day?
So…
Where is Dr. Fah?
Dr. Fah left the mountain already.
He’s probably on his way back to Bangkok.
Do you still keep in touch with him?
I got his number from the village chief but it’s not reachable.
He might work hard and forget all about me by now.
What?
Are you giving up already?
Life is that simple.
You don’t need reasons to like something.
I just want Prince to be with a good guy.
Someone who can really take care of him.
From now on
please take care of him.