Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
There will be a ritual slaughter tomorrow.
It’s Gong, the children’s pig.
- Hey!
- Teacher Prince.
Thanks for taking care of me when I passed out.
Thank you for helping me with the check-up the other day.
Hey!
Hold on.
You two look perfect together. Congratulations!
Thank you.
Hey, Kuafah.
I’ll go greet him.
You can take her inside.
Sure.
I’ll see you inside.
Thanks for coming, Kuafah.
I thought you wouldn’t come.
May.
Do you remember…
the day we broke up?
(You don’t remember?)
Hey.
Doctor.
I asked if you remembered or not.
Today,
we need to give the village chief’s son a welcome.
I forgot.
You go ahead.
I don’t feel like it.
You must.
He’s bringing lots of snacks for the children.
I need a hand with those. Come on.
Quickly.
Who the heck is he?
A politician?
Why does he get such hospitality from everyone?
Hey, keep it down.
You can complain but not so loud.
People might tell the village chief.
Who the heck is this guy?
- Relax, man.
- You’re louder.
Het gets an umbrella too.
Sorry to keep you waiting, kids.
I’ve brought you tons of snacks.
Yeah!
Wee-ah, go get it.
Stand right here.
Here you go.
Let’s get a picture.
A picture with that crappy snack box?
Smile.
1 2 3.
The umbrella.
Okay.
Share these with your friends.
Enjoy.
Can you carry them?
Those are for the kids.
This is for you, Teacher Prince.
To thank you for always taking good care of them.
But…
Who are those three guys?
They are new volunteers.
My apologies.
I didn’t know that.
If I’d known, I would have brought some gifts for you too.
It’s okay.
Actually, you can have my photo as a gift.
Let’s do it.
Come here. Don’t be shy.
Okay. I’ll airdrop it for you.
Would you excuse me? I’ll go feed the children.
Let’s go, Teacher Prince.
Want to take a photo?
Who is this Aou guy, anyway?
He seems close to Teacher Prince.
Ah!
They’re boyfriends.
What?
Boyfriends?
Yes.
They’re always together. They must be dating.
Fabby!
Fabby.
Not fabby.
My Teacher Prince.
Right.
And he just walked around side by side with the teacher.
He’s just a show-off.
Why do you sound jealous of the teacher?
That’s nonsense.
(Where are you anyway?)
Of course, I’m at our place.
Dao,
I finished showering.
Whose voice was that then?
Khabkluen’s, wasn’t it?
Eh...I’m studying.
I gotta go. Bye.
What?
Almost caught.
Was that Fah?
Yes.
I didn’t see you there in the shower.
I missed you so much.
Too much.
Can I have a kiss?
That’s so random.
Come on.
Did you really take a shower?
Why?
You still stink.
Seriously?
Yes.
Sniff again.
Go back and take a shower again.
- Really?
- Yes.
But why does someone who hasn’t showered smell so good?
Of course, I do.
Well, if I’m smelly,
how about you give me a shower?
No. I will take a shower first.
What? You said I was smelly.
Yeah, you wait until I finish.
I haven’t been completely clean yet.
Yes, but you need to wait.
Kids these days.
They just can’t be left alone together.
You’ll see.
I’ll chew you two out when I go back.
Hey.
Hi, there.
Looks who’s here.
You came home quite late tonight.
I get you though.
Your boyfriend is finally back.
What boyfriend?
Don’t play dumb.
The kids told me.
I never knew you liked that type of man.
I think you’re misunderstanding.
Aou is an older friend I respect.
Besides,
he always takes care of everyone who volunteers here.
Everyone?
He only takes care of you.
He didn’t care about my friends and me.
He just got back. There are tons of things for him to do.
Taking his side, I see.
And why do you call him Phi?
I’m also a lot older than you.
‘Phi’ is reserved for people I respect only.
If you want me to address you like that, behave.
Well then…
Address me like you already do.
Teacher Prince. Dr. Fah.
My son is sick.
He has bad stomach pain.
Can you please come take a look?
I gave him digestive tablets.
He should be fine really soon.
He must have had too many snacks.
But it still hurts.
You will be fine.
How about…
I give you magical treatment?
Abracadabra, I wish all your pain turns into butterflies
and flies away.
So?
Wow!
Dr. Fah surely has magic.
Don’t tell anyone.
It’s my secret.
Thank you so much, Dr. Fah and Teacher Prince
for coming to see him.
Would you like some drinks?
Well then
I’ll go with you and help out.
Of course.
Dr. Fah, would you like some snacks?
Aou gave us a lot.
No, thank you.
Ever since Teacher Prince came, Aou has been giving us lots of snacks.
I want them to be together for a long time so I will get unlimited snacks.
Wee-ah.
What if I tell you Teacher Prince isn't dating Aou?
What?
Then who is he dating?
Wanna know?
Get your ear closer.
Hot news!
Dr. Fah and Teacher Prince got together in April.
What an unfaithful man.
I gave you all my heart.
Yayah.
How did you get into my house?
Yayah, get up.
No.
I won’t.
What are you guys up to?
Hot news!
Teacher Prince is dating Mesa.
What?
It’s top secret. Do not tell anyone.
Really?
Oh, boy! This is big news.
Okay.
These are your medicines.
I don’t think there’s any problem.
I do!
Is it true, Dr. Fah?
What is it, Yayah?
Stop playing dumb.
I know everything.
What an unfaithful man.
I gave you all my heart.
You’re just a lying city man.
What are you talking about, Yayah?
I didn’t do anything.
A lying city man.
Prince.
How could you do that to my heart?
What did I do?
I was away for just a while.
I trusted you.
You fell for that sweet talker from the city.
I’m sad.
I’m so sad.
Don’t talk to me.
Goodbye, Teacher.
Hey,
I need to talk to you about something.
About what?
The villagers have been calling me weird names.
Really?
Me too.
You too?
What is happening?
Well, well.
A sweet couple here.
What do you mean, Sompor?
The villagers say actually Dr. Fah and Teacher Prince are dating.
That’s not true.
I’ve been observing.
Teacher Prince always helps Dr. Fah with work.
Because the village chief told me to.
Then why do you call Dr. Fah mister but call other people Phi?
Because…
Dr. Fah is the special one.
I mean…
Specially annoying.
Specially spoiled.
And specially whiny.
That’s why I address him that.
That means Dr. Fah isn’t a good man, is he?
That’s right.
A very bad man.
Wait a minute.
What are you telling the kids?
I’ll get out of your way then.
Bye.
Get home safe.
A very bad man.
VILLAGE CHIEF OFFICE
Doctor Fah.
Why is he doing this to me?
Will you eat or cry? Choose one.
Well, I’m sad.
You’re not a teenager.
You don’t get me.
Come on.
I’ve had so much experience with love.
Don’t be bitter.
Because I just found you a perfect marriage prospect.
What?
Here.
Eat.
Hey, Fah. There you are.
Want a drink?
Hold on, master.
I have medical check-ups for the children tomorrow.
Are you really my friend Kuafah?
Who are you?
Give me back my friend.
Are you nuts?
Give back, my ass.
It’s nothing.
I just don’t want a problem with the teacher.
Tired of hearing his complaint.
Fah,
are you dating Teacher Prince?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
The locals have been gossipping.
They even say you two are getting married in April.
That’s absurd.
I just hated Aou
so I started a rumor that you and the teacher were boyfriends.
I have no idea how the guy in the fake news turned into me.
I get it now.
You reap what you sow, man.
I didn’t sow for me.
I did it for my friend here.
Good then.
Mesa.
What if Teacher Prince and I become boyfriends for real?
Will you be mad?
Beat up.
You will beat me up?
Beat JJ up.
Asshole.
Kidding.
I think I should be okay with that.
At least it’s you, not Aou.
That’s so true.
That Aou guy is such a bragger.
Come on. Let’s drink.
Good idea.
Wait! No.
I told you I won’t drink.
Don’t you deceive me.
Well, we always drink together.
Maybe next time.
Bye.
See you.
How did the rumor turn upside down?
Sorry. I’ve come to the wrong place.
This is my place.
Yayah?
Yayah, wake up.
How did you get here?
I walked here.
Don’t bother me. I’m sleeping.
Yayah, get up.
If people see us, they might get the wrong idea.
No. I won’t go home.
Yayah, get up.
No.
I won’t.
I don’t have anywhere else to go.
No.
Get up!
No!
- I’m not going home.
- Get up!
What are you guys up to?
An arranged marriage?
Yes.
He’s the son of the chief from another village.
And why don’t you like him?
Is he a bad guy?
Not like that.
We knew each other as kids.
I remember he wasn’t good-looking.
And he ate my snacks so much that his belly got fat.
Well, I don’t like people for their looks.
I like their personalities.
Hot and masculine personalities.
Just like Kuafah.
I should tell your dad you're here.
Please don’t.
I don’t want to get married.
But
we can’t be alone together. It can be scandalous.
Come on. Let her stay.
I just said I couldn’t be alone with her. It’s dishonoring.
I didn’t say you two would be alone together.
Thank you for letting me stay over.
Tonight only.
We will discuss this again tomorrow.
Yayah,
I have a question.
Why don’t you meet him first?
Maybe you two will fall in love after spending time together.
Prince, love isn’t about time.
We can feel it once our eyes meet.
Right, Kuafah?
I think I should sleep in the middle.
Otherwise, things might get messy.
Prince!
You’re such a blocker.
Get some rest.
As for you,
you need to work tomorrow.
(Love isn’t about time.)
(We can feel it once our eyes meet.)
I’ll tell the village chief to come fetch her here tomorrow.
Are we sending her home?
Yes.
Hey, Doctor.
Yayah disappeared.
Yayah disappeared?
The villagers said they saw Yayah running away from the village.
What?
Yayah.
We haven’t found Yayah yet?
We haven’t.
She might be at one of the relatives’ houses as always.
She should be back once she gets over it.
Can I help you?
I heard Yayah ran away.
She did.
She needs to get married soon so she’s making little waves.
I don’t know what she’s afraid of.
The groom is someone she’s known since a young age.
It might be too soon. She hasn’t prepared for that.
I think…
They should get to know each other more.
Then they can get married later.
We can’t do that, Teacher Prince.
When a man and a woman meet and don’t get married,
it violates our beliefs.
Besides, it’s our tradition.
Tradition?
That’s right.
For generations, our village and their village have bonded by marriage.
Yayah’s mother is also from that village.
That’s quite reasonable.
But
old days have passed.
Marriage should be built on love.
That way they can live a long and happy married life.
Bravo.
I agree with every word he said.
As someone who loves…
and understands Teacher Prince,
I support the idea of marrying someone we love.
Right, Dad?
And someone I want to marry is…
Hey!!
I just realized that Teacher Prince and I need to run an errand.
Will you please excuse me?
Wait.
What errand?
Just go with it.
Follow my lead.
Goodbye.
Teacher Prince is blushing because of me.
So we didn’t get the conclusion because of Aou?
I’ll yell at his face.
You go home now and you’ll be trapped in a marriage.
Yeah, I forgot.
Go rest inside.
We will try to find a way out.
Seriously, why did you lie to her?
You know we can never change the village chief’s mind.
What do you want me to do then?
Send her home?
Yes.
Each place has its own tradition.
Can you take responsibility if something happens to Yayah?
Whatever.
I’ll tell the village chief to come fetch her here tomorrow.
Hey, Doctor.
Yayah is gone.
No, Dao. I need five more minutes of sleep.
No!
Yayah disappeared.
Yayah disappeared?
She must have heard what we said last night and ran away.
It’s not safe for a girl to travel alone.
Let’s go find her.
Let’s search separately.
I’ll look at the village chief's house.
You look around here.
Yayah.
Yayah hasn't been back yet?
She hasn’t.
Aou is now searching for her in our relatives’ houses.
This daughter of mine always causes trouble.
Dad, I have bad news.
The villagers said they saw Yayah running away from the village.
What?
Where? Let’s go.
From what they said, she shouldn’t be far from here.
How about we go different ways?
Sounds good.
Yayah.
Ouch!
Dad. Are you okay?
Ankle sprain.
Yayah!
Yayah.
Yayah, stop running.
Come here.
You.
Get up.
You’re heavy.
What are you doing?
I told you not to get involved with other people’s business.
Yayah.
Are you here?
Are you in there?
Meow
This cat has such a high-pitched voice.
Show yourself.
How did you know?
Why are you running away?
I don’t want to marry someone I don’t love.
You guys are taking me home.
I don’t want to.
I’m sorry.
I have no clue what to do.
I know you’re the only one who understands me.
Can I ask you a favor?
I feel sorry for her.
If you were her, would you do it?
Marrying someone you don’t love.
Enough with the word ‘Love.’
Love. Love. Love. Love.
I don’t believe in love.
Many couples declare their love but break up anyway.
Not every couple.
No, not every couple.
But…
People who love each other don’t always get a happy ending together.
Forget it.
You’re still young.
You won’t get it.
I do get it.
Let’s talk about this in the village.
It’s about to rain.
We should hurry back.
Why are you standing there?
Take me back to the village.
I kept running away from you.
I don’t remember the way back now.
What?
We’re here again.
What the heck?
I thought I walked straight.
How come I end up in the same place?
I think we should go left.
Go right.
I have a feeling we just went that way.
Your feeling got us here three times already.
It’s somehow my fault?
You’re the reason we ended up here.
Who would think you’d chase me this far?
I just wanted to buy Yayah more time so she could get in Uncle Phang’s car.
Now we’re stuck in the woods.
Freakin’ unfortunate.
Hey!!
What?!
What?
Nothing.
I just wanted you to stop talking.
Have you ever got kicked by someone younger?
Bring it on.
Shit!
I didn’t do that.
I know.
Must have been the wind.
Keep walking.
I think we’re nearly there.
If we turned right as you said, we’d be nowhere.
Shut it.
Wee-ah.
What are you doing in the woods?
It’s not the woods. This is just behind the school.
What?
Behind the school?
That means we’re close to the village, aren’t we?
By the way…
Are you picking up flowers for girls?
No.
These are wedding decorations.
Wedding?
Whose wedding?
Yayah’s wedding.
She finally agrees to the marriage.
What?
I wish you a long happy relationship together.
Grow your family with lots of children.
Seems like someone is in pain.
I guess being in a wedding just triggered his misery.
Is it wrong that I don’t love myself?
Since I already gave her all my love.
Did you meet your future husband?
I did.
He paid a visit to the village and we accidentally met.
And why do you agree to marry him now?
After we talked, I knew right away he’s a good man.
Unlike before.
Yeah?
How?
His personalities are handsome and masculine.
He’s such a sweet talker too.
The second I looked into his eyes, I fell hard.
I’m so blushing.
Those things don’t sound like personalities but congratulations, Yayah.
From now on, Dr. Kuafah is free.
You can date Teacher Prince. I don’t mind.
Wait.
Did you say date, Yayah?
Rumor has it you two are dating.
No.
That’s nonsense.
They say you two are getting married in April.
That’s absurd, Yayah.
Hey, help me.
Stay cool.
They will find out eventually what’s true and what’s not.
Why?
You want it to be true?
Come on!
To be honest, you look kind of cute in a sarong.
That’s right.
I wish you a long happy relationship together.
Grow your family with lots of children.
Love and take care of her.
You have a husband now. Please behave.
Take good care of each other.
Love and cherish each other.
Learn to forgive when needed.
Welcome all of you to Buai and May’s wedding.
I have a question for both the groom and the bride.
What I like the most about May is her cuteness, delicacy,
and consistency.
Seems like someone is in pain.
I guess being in a wedding just triggered his misery.
Whatever. Just shut up.
Let’s just drink.
You didn't learn the lesson, did you?
But we’re safe here.
We don’t drive.
Don’t be shy.
Cheers.
Get drunk all you want.
♪ Where could I move on to? ♪
♪ My heart is set on you ♪
Why did you bring me home?
I want to drink with JJ and Mesa.
They both passed out.
They got carried home already.
Passed out?
Those two lightweights.
Losers.
Lo-sers!
Before calling them names, you should see yourself.
Why?
What’s wrong with me?
I’m this way.
I’m still cool.
I…
How did I get here?
Your bed is a mess because you threw up on it.
So I brought you here.
If you don’t like it here, you can go to your friends’.
No. I’m too lazy.
I don’t want to nestle with them.
Here.
Why did you need to drink so much?
Are you in love with Yayah or what?
No.
I was just thinking about my ex.
Your friends told me about that.
You went to her wedding.
Yeah.
How dumb, right?
No.
At first,
I wanted to congratulate her.
Gave her a smile because she has someone good in life.
But I couldn’t get over her.
May, do you remember the day we broke up?
Yes.
You asked me if I still needed you.
What if I say I still do?
You don’t need me, Fah.
You just don’t want to lose me.
Can I ask you a question?
Why are you marrying Buai?
When we were in school,
he was a burden to you.
He never worked on anything himself.
You were always the one helping him.
How is he better than me?
You’re right.
He’s not as good-looking as you are.
He’s not as smart as you are.
He’s not as rich as you are.
Then…
Why?
Because Buai can’t live without me.
But you can just fine, Fah.
After hearing the answer,
I was sent to repent my sins here.
Is it wrong to be smart?
Is it wrong to focus so much on building a life that I didn’t have time for her?
Is it wrong that I don’t love myself?
Since I already gave her all my love.
You will get better.
Abracadabra, I wish all your pain turns into butterflies and flies away.
This feeling is priceless.
I just want to feel it and hang on to it for as long as I can.
Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul
Dao, I can go see you on your birthday this year.
These are the presents I gave my brother for his previous birthdays.
Why don’t you try to make something by hand?
Can you try it on for me?
You and my brother are around the same size.
Fah normally has girls over.
But tonight, he only drank. He didn’t bring any girl home.
He’s become a different person after he came back from the mountain.
Hey!
I have news for you.
Teacher Prince is sick.