Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
If you let someone down and don’t apologize,
you will grow up to be a bad adult.
Teacher Prince told me he had a terrible ex.
And what you’re doing is repeating what his ex did to him.
I’m sorry for being unreasonable.
There’s no reason for me to be angry with you about that night.
But if my actions give you the wrong idea,
from this moment on,
can I hit on you?
That gunshot was a signal to start.
This game isn’t going to be as easy as the one we competed in today.
We’ll see about that.
Because I never lose.
Hey!
You.
How did you get here?
I walked.
What do you want first?
Food or milk?
Milk.
Wait!
No.
What are you doing?
Hitting on you.
What?
You gave me permission to hit on you.
From now on, I’m going to hit on you non-stop.
Be ready for that.
Because…
I am so flirty.
Teacher
Prince
Is
Grumpy.
Oops!
Lovely.
What is going on, children?
Aw!!
[Teacher Prince, keep fighting!]
Here.
This is for you.
What is it?
If you want to know, open it.
[The reader is loved.]
[Sweet dreams.]
♪ The stars tonight ♪
♪ are so beautiful ♪
♪ I’d like to know ♪
♪ if the person inside is already sleeping ♪
I am sleeping.
♪ Are you lonely sleeping by yourself? ♪
♪ Do you want some company? ♪
♪ You closed the window ♪
♪ Are you shooing me away? ♪
♪ You might regret it ♪
♪ If I’m gone ♪
You don’t want to regret it later.
Hey!
You!
♪ I knew someone would warm up to me ♪
♪ I guess he’s letting me spend the night finally ♪
There’s only one blanket.
You need to use a towel.
This is good enough.
You letting me sleep here is enough to make me happy.
Don’t be so happy!
One night only.
But in one night…
we can do many things.
I mean in one night,
we can talk about many things.
What are you thinking?
I’m done bickering with you.
Just sleep.
If you’re cold, just say it.
No need to play cool.
Well,
I thought it could help get your sympathy.
Was it just an act?
What do you think?
My hand is frozen.
Alright. I get it.
Let go already.
Why?
Are you blushing?
I’m not.
Let’s do this.
An ice-breaking activity.
I ask. You answer.
But you must do it quickly.
Such as…
What do you like to eat?
Salmon.
Me too.
Where do you like to travel to?
General natural attractions.
Me too.
Hey.
You can’t like everything I like.
There is something we like differently.
What?
If I say
I like you.
You will say you like me.
Nonsense.
I’m going to sleep.
Hey!
Hold on.
I haven’t done asking.
But I’m sleepy.
Last question then.
Will you go on a date with me?
Didn’t you just say you’d sleep?
Why getting up?
Who told you to whisper in my ear like that?
Don’t change the subject.
So…
Will you please go on a date with me,
Teacher Prince?
Don’t go.
I will just go put it back.
No.
Dao.
Can I hug you a little longer?
Here.
I’m willing to get sick with you.
All right?
Get well soon, baby.
Teacher, I’m all packed.
[I need to run an errand downtown.]
[I’ll see you at noon at Chiang Mai Bus Terminal.]
[I’ll pick you up. - Prince]
My mom…
is inviting you to come over.
But if you don’t want to, it’s fine.
I don’t mind at all no matter what your house looks like.
I’m even thankful you invited me.
You’ve finally come?
[Chiang Mai Bus Terminal]
Wow.
That car is luxurious.
If Teacher Prince gets out of that car, I’ll be shocked.
Don’t think so.
How’s that possible?
Who knows?
Don’t think it’s him.
Shit.
Guys.
That’s Teacher Prince.
Don’t tell me he comes from money.
Did I keep you guys waiting?
It doesn’t matter if you did.
What matters is that I didn’t know you are loaded.
Loaded?
Because I’m wearing a shirt?
No.
He meant the car.
You’re pretty wealthy. We had no idea.
Hey.
The car is moving.
What?
Isn’t that your car, Teacher?
Of course, not.
Mine is the truck over there.
The one next to that bus.
Yes.
Well, you dressed up quite nicely.
Let’s go.
Sure.
Prince, can you make the birds fly?
Yes.
Ice cream!
May we get some ice creams, please?
You guys want some?
Hey.
You got ice cream here.
What a mess.
You got ice cream too.
What should you do then?
Here.
You’re clean.
Get this!
Are you messing with me?
Stop it!
Stop cleaning it for me.
1, 2, 3.
What is this?
A heart.
Come on. Let’s take a photo.
Can we join?
What are you two doing?
What are you doing?
I’m taking you traveling but you’re messing with me.
I’m not messing with you.
Just giving you a drink.
As a thank-you for taking me out.
Okay.
Let me feed you.
I can feed myself.
If you don’t let me feed you,
I will…
You will what?
shout “Teacher Prince is so cute.”
Do you think I won’t do it?
Teacher Prince --
You!
What is this?
You’re blushing?
Can’t you tell if I’m blushing or annoyed?
Freakin’ cute.
Still have a headache?
Just a little.
Are you sure?
I have such a caring doctor here. Of course, I recover fast.
Here.
Next time, if you don’t feel well, let me know.
Don’t wait until it gets bad like this.
Roger that.
You always make me worry.
Hey!
Yeah!
This is a real paradise.
I will never leave this bed.
Mesa, what about our trip to Tha Chang?
Damn you!
My bed is still available.
Would you like to share it with me?
No.
Hey,
I’m not doing anything bad.
It’s not that.
I’m meeting my friends tonight.
I’m going home to freshen up.
You’re already cute.
No need to freshen up.
Shut up!
I’m leaving now.
Let me walk you out.
Yes, Mom.
Yes. I took them to the hotel already.
Dr. Fah just walked me to the car.
What?
Are you serious?
Okay.
Sure.
What is it?
My mom…
is inviting you to come over.
Really?
But
if you don’t want to, it’s fine.
I get it.
I do.
Let’s go meet your mom.
Hey.
My house is probably unlike any other house.
I don’t mind at all no matter what it looks like.
I’m even thankful you invited me.
This is it.
Wait.
Where are you taking me?
Hey.
Where are we?
Don’t tell me this is your house.
It is.
But it’s not the main residence.
The main one is being renovated.
Na Chiang Dao.
That sounds familiar.
The last name of the ancient monarch of the North.
The last name of the ancient monarch of the North?
Are you descended from the Northern royalty?
Why didn’t you tell me?
I could have dressed up more properly.
It’s fine.
We’re a laid-back family.
Have a seat.
You’ve finally come?
What, Mom?
Do you think I can’t tell?
Every time you call me, you always say Dr. Fah this, Dr. Fah that.
When will you two become boyfriends?
Hey, Prince.
To be honest, I still miss you, Prince.
Is it okay if we get back together?
Hello, Mom.
Your house is very nice.
Prince,
didn’t you tell your friend we don’t speak the way other people do?
I’m terribly sorry, my lady.
My apologies.
I’m not familiar with this kind of stuff.
I didn’t mean to.
I was just kidding.
Please speak normally.
Yes?
Don’t be shocked.
I said you can speak a normal language.
I was just messing with you.
Please make yourself at home.
Where did you get this outfit from?
It’s gorgeous.
I ordered it online.
There were lots to choose from.
Very easy to wear.
I’m going to get changed now.
Make yourself at home.
I’ll be right back.
What is this?
I’m so confused.
My mom loves to prank visitors.
I told you we’re a laid-back family.
This is my office.
I like to read and work here.
Wow.
So you literally are a prince.
I thought it was just your name.
Who would have thought ‘Prince’ was a real prince?
It’s not what you think.
I live a normal life.
That means the perfume and the designer bag are authentic.
I’m sorry.
It’s okay. I get you.
If I were you, I wouldn’t want people to know either.
Dr. Fah,
I have a photo album of Prince as a kid to show you.
Wanna see?
Of course, I do.
Look at this one.
Prince was walking around the house naked.
Mom!
Not that one.
Not this one?
This one then.
He just peed his bed.
Look. He’s in a basket.
Mom, these photos are embarrassing.
Why are you showing them to him?
Don’t be embarrassed.
You guys are boyfriends. No need to be embarrassed.
Do you think I can’t tell?
Every time you call back from the mountain,
you always say Dr. Fah this, Dr. Fah that.
If you’re not boyfriends, then what are you two?
You’re misunderstanding.
How?
Help me correct her.
So…
What did he say about me?
He called and told me
“Dr. Fah helped get the spider off my hair.”
“Dr. Fah helped me when I passed out.”
“And Dr. Fah–”
That’s enough, Mom.
Come on. I need to go somewhere else.
Fine. Let’s go then.
Are you shy?
Mom!
Dr. Fah, please take care of Prince up there.
Of course.
You too, Prince.
If you want any help up there, send someone to inform me.
Let me go get the car for you.
So mother and son can have more time to catch up.
You’re handsome and lovely.
Thanks a lot.
You can follow the butler.
Please, Mr. Kuafah.
Detch, not the truck.
Chot will need it for the farm work.
Of course, ma’am.
Let him lead the way.
You choose wisely.
What are you saying?
Dr. Fah.
I like him a lot.
When will you two become boyfriends?
Boyfriends what?
Don’t be shy.
Everyone can tell you guys are not just a ship.
You guys are real.
Mom!
I hope you two are boyfriends soon.
Yes?
Don’t be shy.
Wait! You have to meet up with your friends tonight, don't you?
Yes.
Knot just got back from the states so we’re gathering to welcome him home.
But you probably see Sincere there.
It’s all right.
Sincere and I have nothing to do with each other anymore.
Uncle Detch told me to take this car.
Are you sure about this?
I am.
Sorry. The other cars are at the car wash.
Drive safe.
I’ll see you later.
I missed you, Mom.
I missed you too.
Travel safe.
Please look out for him, Dr. Fah.
Absolutely.
Bye-bye.
Goodbye.
It’s just a time-killing meal.
You don’t need to take me to a fancy restaurant.
Consider it a treat.
Hey, Prince.
You’re coming to Knot’s party too?
Yeah.
Okay.
Very good then.
I can just talk to you here.
Do you mind leaving us so we can have a private talk?
You can just say it, Sincere.
You can stay.
Come on, Prince.
We haven’t met for so long.
I hope your friend won’t be so mean.
Of course.
Since old friends get to meet once in a while.
What is it?
Wow!
That’s harsh.
Just came to say hi.
My mom told me you’re a volunteer teacher up on the mountain.
Yeah.
How are you doing? Is the job okay?
Okay.
Nice weather.
Did you meet that guy up there?
Something like that.
I should go straight to the point.
To be honest,
I still miss you, Prince.
I have always missed you.
Is it okay if we get back…
You!
Let’s go.
Slow down.
What are you doing?
Getting us back together.
So you intended to make me jealous?
Are you jealous?
I’m so jealous that I doubt you’re able to make it up to me.
Was it good enough?
My friends are expecting me.
I’m coming with you.
So that they know you have a doctor taking care of you up on the mountain.
Come on.
Hi, everyone.
I’m Kuafah,
Prince’s close friend.
Don’t worry.
I’m not trying to steal Prince.
I just want Prince to be with someone who has more time for him.
Prince, this way.
Hi, Prince.
Have a seat here.
Hi, everyone.
I’m Kuafah,
Prince’s close friend.
Hi. Cheers.
What a big entrance there.
Just want someone here to know
whom Prince is talking to.
Don’t worry.
I’m not trying to steal Prince.
Because someone like him needs a guy who has time for him.
What do you mean?
I heard you’re a doctor.
You must be very busy.
And?
It’s nice when you’re together.
But when you guys are apart,
you won’t have any free time at all.
I’m not judging or anything.
I just want Prince to be with someone who has more time for him.
I hope you understand.
Hey.
Are you okay?
I am.
Enjoy your drink.
Let’s drink.
For Knot who just got back
and for Prince who is taking a break from the mountain.
Until we’re drunk.
Cheers!
How’s your study?
Good?
Not really.
I should take this call.
Yes?
(Where are you?)
(JJ and I are dressing up for Tha Chang.)
You guys go ahead.
(What?)
I don’t feel like going.
(Where are you?)
Doesn’t matter where I am.
I’m going back to rest now.
Okay.
Hey!
Are you okay?
I…
can’t…breathe.
Waiter!
What is going on?
She can’t breathe.
We can take her inside.
There’s a first aid room here.
Damn! Prince is drunk already.
He starts dancing.
I’m not drunk.
Bottoms up!
Hey!
Doctor!
You can’t even walk.
Stay here.
But Kuafah…
I think that’s the real him.
Let him go.
Just drink.
Cheers!
You want more?
Yes.
Keep going, guys.
Cheers!
Your pulse rate is getting better.
Don’t drink so much next time.
And get a good rest.
Okay.
Thank you, sir.
We will take it from here.
Sure.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Prince.
You’re drunk.
Should we go home?
You can crash with me tonight.
Where is Fah?
Fah?
I guess he’s occupied.
Might be having fun with the girl over there.
You better not say what you don’t know.
Because if it’s not true,
it’s shame on you.
Thank you for saving my life.
Prince,
let’s go.
Go?
I’m not going.
Don’t be stubborn.
Come on.
Not going.
May I please take Prince home?
Sure.
Come on. Get up.
Bye.
Bye, guys.
You all right?
I’m fine.
Why did you come back?
Why didn’t you spend more time with the girl back there?
She couldn’t breathe so I gave her first aid.
But you suddenly changed.
I got something on my mind.
Don’t you think our relationship is weird?
Weird, how?
Today, I just learned about your family.
And you know nothing about mine.
You have no idea what I am or what I do.
When we both go home one day,
I might not have time to take care of you.
Can you handle that?
That’s hard to process.
I don’t follow.
I don’t think I make any sense now.
When I fall in love, I never have to do anything like this.
I've never felt the need to pursue anybody.
He must be the first prey to make a tiger like me fall.
Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul
Since you returned from Bangkok, you guys have been lovey-dovey.
Are you two boyfriends already?
I haven’t got a chance to say it yet.
I feel like things are going fast.
You two are not boyfriends yet?
You guys will leave this mountain in three days!
Fah, bad news.
The villagers are having bad diarrhea.
Hey, your hand is burning hot.
You’re burning up. Why didn’t you tell me?
Why are you here?
To find the medicines for malaria.
If Prince doesn’t get cured now, he might be dead.
Let me take care of Prince.
We can see here that you can’t take care of him at all.