Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Fah, are you dating Teacher Prince?
What if Teacher Prince and I become boyfriends for real?
Will you be mad?
Marriage should be built on love.
That way they can live a long and happy married life.
I guess being in a wedding triggers his misery.
Is it wrong to focus so much on building a life that I didn’t have time for her?
Is it wrong that I don’t love myself?
Since I already gave her all my love.
Abracadabra, I wish all your pain turns into butterflies and flies away.
Damn!
What is this?
I must have been so drunk last night.
That’s why Teacher Prince took me here.
What time is it?
Seven.
Hey.
Last night,
did something happen?
What do you mean something?
Like…
I didn’t do anything weird, did I?
No.
You were crying and talking about your ex all night long.
Yeah?
That’s all?
Yeah.
Anyway,
if I did anything terrible to you,
I’m sorry.
I was really drunk.
Bye now.
Pull yourself together, Fah.
Why did you kiss him?
I will drink less next time.
No.
I will never drink again.
Hey.
Where did you sleep last night?
What do you mean where?
My house, of course.
Your house?
Yes.
Bullshit.
You were wearing the same T-shirt last night.
Spill the beans. Where did you crash last night?
And that route you’re using isn’t the route from your house.
Tell us. Where did you sleep?
Whatever.
I just came to take a shower with you guys.
A shower with us?
Yes.
And you took a detour around the mountain to get here?
Do you have a bathing cloth I can borrow?
No.
What is it around your neck then?
This?
My scarf.
Argh!
Mesa,
I have a question.
When you realized you liked Teacher Prince,
how did you feel?
Why do you ask?
Nothing.
Just curious.
I’ve never had feelings for a man before.
Are you having feelings for Uncle Phang?
I knew it.
You take care of him so well.
Are you nuts?
I’m just curious.
How did I feel?
I don’t know.
But when I see his face, I can’t help but smile.
Tag!
Hello.
Dao?
It’s me, Fah.
I’m going back to see you on your birthday.
No, I’m not running away.
I asked for permission.
Yeah.
I’ll see you then.
kiss kiss.
Was that your lover?
I asked you the other day.
You didn’t give me the answer.
Who do you call every single day?
Not telling.
Your lover, of course.
So what if I call my lover?
Are you jealous?
No.
Why would I be?
If you’re not jealous then…
Yes,
that was my lover.
If you’re not jealous, why are you making a face?
What are you rambling about?
What face am I making?
This face.
I’m not.
I’m not dating anyone.
In case that’s what you want to hear…too.
The one I just talked to
was my little brother.
And why are you smiling?
What?
You tease me when I smile.
You tease me when I don’t smile.
Talking to you gets me a headache.
I should just go.
Wait up.
Just realized something.
I'd like to hear your opinion.
Here.
These are the presents I gave my brother for his previous birthdays.
I don’t know what I should get him this year.
Any ideas?
You have bought him a present every year.
Why don’t you try to make something by hand this year?
I can’t.
I have zero artistic skills.
It’s not that difficult.
I’ll teach you.
Really?
Yes.
I taught the children to make gifts in art class.
People here love to make gifts from lucky stones.
Lucky stones?
The stone accessories believed to be good luck charms?
Yes.
We have a lot here.
Why don’t you follow me?
You might get some ideas.
Ah!
They’re beautiful.
Right?
Hey.
Your brother is still a student.
If you wish him academic success, give him the purple stone.
If you wish him success in love, go for the pink one.
Education only, I guess.
He doesn’t need love enhancement.
So…
What are they mostly made into?
People usually make necklaces or bracelets out of them.
Then…
I will go for a necklace.
Can you teach me?
Of course.
500 baht for the lesson.
Dang!
That’s why you offered to help.
You want to extort the money from me.
Don’t be such a whiner. I’m kidding.
Come on. I’ll teach you.
Pay attention.
I’ll explain it once.
First of all,
choose the color.
This one.
Then…
I pick the white one.
It should be a bit longer than the actual length you want.
Like this.
This is the length I want.
Allow more length.
Okay.
Cut here.
What?
I cut the wrong string.
Let’s do it again.
Okay.
Start from one end first.
See?
I got it.
How is that a necklace?
I’m putting you to sleep.
Hey.
We’re done.
It wasn’t that hard.
It wasn’t.
Compared to these five necklaces you ruined.
Come on.
I’m a beginner.
This is great enough.
By the way,
can I try it on you?
You and my brother are around the same size.
So?
Do you like it?
I do.
Thank you so much.
We’re all set, right?
Then,
I’ll be out of your hair.
Hold on.
We’re not done.
Why?
We are.
What is left to do?
One last step.
Moonbathe it.
When are you coming back?
I’ll be away for just two days.
Will be back in no time.
I promise
I will be a good boy.
Hey!
What are you two doing?
The locals believe that
moonbathing it for an hour
will increase its charm power.
What are you laughing at?
At myself.
I have never made such a serious gift for anyone before.
Come on.
I heard you dated lots of girls.
It’s hard to believe you never did it.
When I had a girlfriend,
all I did was study and work.
Since we broke up, I’ve never gotten into a serious relationship.
It was all casual.
Did that help you forget?
If it did,
do you think I would be here?
You have a point.
What’s your story?
You always ask about mine.
You never tell yours.
What do you want to know?
Well…
Love.
Like…
Your ex.
Let me guess.
You’re a man with lots of experience.
That’s how you know so much about love.
Haven’t you heard
we're always experts in other people's businesses?
I wouldn’t be here if I were that good.
It’s raining.
We should find shelter in the school.
Come on.
BAN KHUN OM HAET NOK SCHOOL
It’s pouring.
I don’t think it’ll stop until the morning.
We can’t moonbathe the stone now.
I’ll just…
buy my brother something.
I need to leave tomorrow.
♪ Journey starts no matter how far the distance ♪
♪ No matter how high or steep the mountains ♪
♪ But too fast and too soon the love I seek is gone ♪
Thank you.
Hey!
What are you two doing?
I asked him to help me with my brother’s present.
All night?
It was pouring last night.
We couldn’t leave the school.
Are we living on the same mountain here?
When did it rain?
I was dead to the world.
I didn’t know that.
Whatever.
I’ll just leave.
I’m gonna get ready to leave.
I’m taking off now.
Okay then.
See you later.
Wait!
What?
Bring me lots of snacks.
Fine.
I’ll even bring you beers.
Thank you.
Well.
Will you excuse me?
Wait.
Get home safe.
Took you so long, Uncle.
Oh! It’s you.
I’ve brought you a food box.
In case you’re hungry on the way down.
Is this from the village chief?
No.
I made it.
Omelet and Rice you have been wanting to eat.
Are you…
hitting on me?
What are you talking about?
If you don’t want it, give it back.
I do.
Thank you.
So…
When are you coming back?
Monday.
I’ll be away for just two days.
Will be back in no time.
Are you sure?
Are you planning to run off and party?
I won’t do that.
I promise
I will be a good boy.
And?
And…
And I’ll behave.
I wanted to say…
And you’re telling because?
We’re not boyfriends.
How can we not?
Last night
we slept together.
What are you saying?
I’m going to kick your ass.
Do it.
The children will see how wicked their teacher is.
I will.
Go on.
Do it.
Ahem.
Uncle.
When did you get here?
A long time ago.
I just didn’t want to interrupt.
Youth is just so nice.
Get in.
He must be drunk.
He’s saying weird things.
Say no more.
Get in already.
Bye-bye.
Just go.
Really?
- Go.
- I’m going.
I’m really going.
Yes.
Bye-bye.
Go already.
Goodbye.
Get home safe, children.
Prince.
Are you all right?
I am.
But you look pale.
Do you have a fever?
Excuse me.
Prince.
You’re burning.
Why didn’t you tell me? Why came to work?
I’m okay.
Might be the rain last night.
I should be fine after taking medicines.
I think I should take you home.
That’s okay, Mesa.
I can take Prince home.
Come on, Prince.
That’s fine.
I’ll do it.
Don’t you get it?
I said I will take him home.
You don’t get it. I’m sending him home.
I have a car. Do you?
What do you want?
You want a problem?
Bring it on.
I said I will take him home.
Hey!
It’s you!
I told you I’d take him home.
Prince, are you okay?
Prince.
- You, move.
- You, let him go.
You, let him go. I’ll get him home.
Do not touch him.
What’s your problem here?
I told you I’d take him home.
We’re ready, Fah.
Where are we going?
You said we must buy you drinks when you’re back in Bangkok.
You never get serious with anyone.
Do you still live by that?
Or maybe someone up on the mountain has changed you.
No one can change Kuafah.
Teacher Prince
Slowly.
Sip some warm water.
It helps.
Thank you.
I will just take a rest.
I should feel better soon.
I can’t leave.
What if your fever is getting worse?
I and my two henchmen will take care of you.
Can I borrow your phone?
Three phones, for what?
Well, choose one.
Yeah?
(Hi, boss.)
We have news for you.
In short,
Teacher Prince is sick.
Aou is nursing him.
What?
Don’t let him.
You must interfere.
How?
Get the teacher some congee or hot food.
Don’t let him be alone with Aou. Got it?
Yeah.
Why do you sound angrier than us?
I’m angry for Mesa.
(Do as I said.)
Okay then.
Angry for me.
Why so moody?
Who is moody?
You are.
I’m not. You’re wrong.
You want a mirror?
We’re ready, Fah.
When you’re done eating, we can head out.
To where?
You said we must buy you drinks when you’re back in Bangkok.
You said you missed the nightlife and girls.
Really?
I said that?
You did.
I reserved the table.
The table with the best view.
I don’t think I can go.
I have a stomachache.
Come on, Fah.
Kluen asked a favor from the club owner to get that VIP table.
Let’s go.
It might lift your mood.
Please.
Teacher Prince, I’ve brought you Rice Soup.
Hey.
Someone got here first.
Sorry.
And thank you both for your concern.
How are you doing?
Feeling better?
I’ve taken some medicines.
Feeling much better now.
I’m about to have dinner.
That’s right.
You should start having the rice soup before it’s cold.
I also made you ginseng soup for your health.
Let me walk you out.
So Teacher Prince can eat comfortably.
We have so much food here.
He can’t finish all by himself.
That’s right.
You’ve brought a lot.
These are for us too, right?
Thank you.
How kind. Let me try some.
You just hit my hand.
These are for Teacher Prince.
But I really can’t finish them all, Aou.
See?
Let’s eat together.
Right?
How generous. Thank you so much.
It’d be nice if someone here is as generous as Teacher Prince.
To Kuafah.
Cheers.
Excuse me.
Do you mind having one drink with me?
Sorry, I do.
I just love my boyfriend so much.
What are you doing?
This is embarrassing.
But this guy is single.
You can drink with him.
You look familiar.
Do you come here a lot?
Hey, Kuafah.
Haven’t seen you in a while.
Fah.
Are you interested in coming to my place tonight?
No. I’m sorry.
I’m going to use the bathroom.
So much temptation here.
Kuafah, focus.
You gave him a promise.
I saw that, Fah.
Kitty.
You saw what?
A changed Kuafah.
You didn’t flirt with anyone. Didn’t drink with anyone.
It’s like you’re in a relationship.
I’m not.
Will you excuse me?
Hi. What’s up?
(Listen. Listen. Listen.)
(We’ve got a situation here.)
We tried to block Aou by having dinner with Teacher Prince.
But he kicked us out after dinner.
He even said he’d spend the night at Teacher Prince’s.
How could you guys let that happen?
We didn’t want to.
But his men didn’t let us in either.
And Teacher Prince agrees to spend the night with him?
(You know Prince has high respect for the village chief.)
He couldn’t just shoo his son away.
(Shit! We gotta go now.)
(His men are watching us.)
Wait.
Mesa!
Aou!
Gotcha.
You just called your lover.
I told you
I’m single.
That’s right.
Because Kuafah’s motto is
“Never get serious with anyone.”
Do you still live by that?
Or maybe…
Someone up on the mountain has changed you.
No one
can change Kuafah.
Prove it then.
Sure.
Now that’s the Kuafah I know.
Thank you all for your concern.
But I’m fine now.
Just say it, Teacher Prince.
I and my men can guard your house out front.
That’s okay.
It’s late.
You all should go home.
Alright then.
Take care.
It’s good he managed to send him home.
We should leave too.
Bye.
Thank you.
Mesa doesn’t mind.
He has three phones.
Okay.
I gotta go, Dao.
Hey.
It’s too quiet here.
[Kuafah]
(Hello.)
(Are you the one Kuafah met on the mountain?)
(I’m Kitty, his girlfriend.)
(What did you do last night?)
A girl called this number.
Teacher Prince took the call.
If one of your friends is having a fight with someone he’s talking to.
He needs to make it up to that person
so he can’t attend your birthday party.
I’m not okay with that.
(Hello.)
(Are you the one Kuafah met on the mountain?)
(I’m Kitty, his girlfriend.)
(I see he’s specially close to you.)
(So I called to let you know he’s doing fine.)
(And he should be busy with me all night.)
(Don’t call unless there’s something necessary.)
(Goodnight.)
Seriously, why brought three phones?
Teacher Prince, is something wrong?
Nothing.
Doctor Kuafah’s girlfriend just called.
Girlfriend?
Kuafah doesn’t have a girlfriend.
Someone like him must have a girlfriend everywhere.
You two just don’t know.
Will you excuse me?
Tell me if I’m wrong.
I think Teacher Prince is jealous.
Probably.
Let’s discuss this later.
Let’s go.
Dao.
Is he usually this wasted?
No.
This is unusual.
How?
He normally drinks a few glasses
and has a girl over.
But tonight, he kept drinking.
He didn’t bring any girl home.
By the way,
when you went to get the car,
something weird happened.
What?
I was carrying him.
A girl approached.
She’s the one Fah drank with.
She asked him to go over to her place.
Fah insisted on not going.
He wanted to come home with us.
He’s become a different person after he came back from the mountain.
He must have met someone good there.
Yeah
(Fah, you asshole.)
(What did you do last night?)
What?
A girl called this number.
You know what’s shitty?
Teacher Prince took the call.
(She claimed she was your girlfriend.)
(JJ and I tried to correct it.)
Why do you keep staring at your phone?
Are you expecting a call?
Nothing.
You okay?
Are you the one Kuafah met on the mountain?
I’m Kitty, his girlfriend.
Shit.
She must have used my phone when I was in the bathroom.
Are you with Teacher Prince?
Let me talk to him.
Why?
I don’t want him to think I have a girlfriend.
Let me be frank here.
Do you like Teacher Prince?
It’s not that.
How long have we been friends?
You think I cannot tell who you like?
I don’t know if I like him.
I’m just happy to see him smile.
That isn’t a necklace.
And I like to spend time with him.
Mesa
I’m sorry.
(Why are you apologizing?)
Because I know you like him.
I shouldn’t do this.
Honestly,
I did like him at first.
But after a while,
I realized I might just admire him.
So you’ve been playing me?
(I could tell a while ago you like him.)
I kept bugging you so that you know
that you really like him.
(It’s good you finally realized it.)
(Congratulations, my friend.)
Yes.
Thank you.
But it would be better if you could help me set my record straight.
Why would I?
Your problem. You solve it.
Bye now.
No more talking. I have a class to teach.
What?
Mesa.
Come on.
Is he really on my side?
And I spilled half of my popcorn.
People were all staring at me.
Fah
Fah, are you listening?
I am.
Where were we?
So you're stuck in the elevator and then what?
I spilled popcorn. I didn’t get stuck in the elevator.
Are you really listening?
Are you okay?
I am.
I’m fine.
Should I just squeeze it out of you?
Dao.
Let’s say…
one of your friends is having a fight with his lover.
Wait. Not lover.
He’s having a fight with someone he’s talking to.
He needs to make it up to that person
so he can’t attend your birthday party.
Will you be mad at him?
And…
How mad is that person?
Pretty mad.
And is my friend worried?
He is.
Very much.
Then you should go, Fah.
Book a flight and go now.
But the friend…
Wait a minute.
Did you just say Fah?
I was mentioning your friend.
Enough with the lies.
This is definitely your story.
Will you be okay if I go?
I won’t be at your birthday party.
I attend your birthday party every year.
Right.
I’m not okay.
I brought you food.
Actually,
you don’t need to attend the meeting today.
I will inform my dad about that.
That’s all right.
I’m feeling better now.
But I think we should…
No. I insist.
Will you please let me get changed?
Thank you so much, Aou.
Sure.
I’m truly feeling better, Aou.
You.
Will you be okay if I go?
I’m not okay.
I’m not okay because you only care about me.
You don’t care about your own feelings.
I’m worried about you.
My birthday party happens every year.
But if you let the one slip through your fingers,
you might never have another chance.
I will be so happy if you can climb the Himalayas again.
You remember that story?
Yes.
You compare your life achievement to climbing the Himalayas.
You want to take someone up there and share the view with you.
After your heartbreak,
you never mentioned any mountain again
If that person can inspire you to climb again,
don’t let the person go.
I’m back.
This is the first time in my life that I've been so concerned about someone.
But it’s all right.
Directed by Siwaj Sawatmaneekul
If you let someone down and don’t apologize,
you will grow up to be a bad adult.
Are you speaking of me?
You come when you feel like it.
The next minute, you go with someone else.
You refuse to express your feelings.
It's not always simple to speak up.
It's not always simple to wait either.
From this moment on,
can I flirt on you?