2 YEARS AGO
2U TRADITIONAL FOOTBALL MATCH 16 SPECIAL GUEST: SCRUBB
After I saw you at the Scrubb concert,
I looked for you at every concert that Scrubb played,
and I saw one guy that looked exactly like you.
Yes?
Hey. Did you find that smiley guy of yours?
I didn't.
I looked for him everywhere.
I guess I failed again.
I started questioning myself about what I was doing.
Why do I bring myself disappointment over and over?
It's time for me to get over you.
2U TRADITIONAL FOOTBALL MATCH 16
PRESENT DAY
The coming traditional football match, as well as the music day, is called 2U.
Our university will compete against the other participating universities.
The event is held once every two years.
It's a chance for us to make friends through football matches,
music shows, and cheerleading activities.
Winning or losing is not the point.
We can let our sucky football team lose, but our cheerleading team…
must win!
Don't take it as a serious competition.
Just compete with yourselves and beat them up.
This is just one
of the most important events for our club.
Don't worry about the prize. It's only a few hundred thousand.
Though we can use it to better our club.
I'm not pressuring you guys,
but don't let many years of the great reputation of our club
-end with you. -End with you.
-Ready? -Ready. Three, four!
-Louder. -Come on.
Stop.
The guitar and the bass weren't synchronized. Start over.
Ready. Three, four!
Faster.
Louder, please.
Ready. Three, four!
Bass and guitar, turn the volume up.
Louder.
Ready?
Ready. Three.
Four!
Louder!
Ready. Three, four.
-Stop! -Screw it!
Goodness.
Green.
It's our turn to be noisy today.
But we need to rehearse for the 2U event too.
And we don't even use microphones.
What are the rules for if you come up with an excuse?
Wat, you tell them.
Tine, sort it out.
Wat.
-Yes? -I have something to talk to you about.
There. I knew it.
You're so easy to read.
You've been glancing at me.
Right. I feel so uncomfortable here.
My club is behind schedule,
so I'd like to ask for more time to be loud.
Can we change from "every other day" to "two days for me and one day for you"?
Dim was thinking about "three for us and one for you."
What? Are you serious?
I just told you earlier that we're so behind.
That's why I didn't tell you.
But you just did, Wat.
-You… -Look.
It's the card of truce.
You said that we wouldn't talk about work at home.
I…
Fine. We can talk later.
Where is my facial foam?
-Hmm? -I forgot.
-It's in my bag. -Go get it.
Okay.
I know you like it.
Someone once said,
"If you want to use my stuff, you need to ask first."
So much for keeping to the rules.
I see. Are you picking on me because of the club?
That's right. We already passed the honeymoon period.
It's not that.
Good, then.
Because I see that my body lotion always gets stolen too.
That thief must have nice skin.
You haven't washed your face yet. Let me help.
Very clean.
It's clean now?
You haven't brushed your teeth either.
Not my neck!
Wat.
Stop it. I'm not talking about work.
I know.
I just can't sleep.
How about we play the guitar?
I want to hear that song.
"Everything."
No. I'll play Desktop Error's song.
That's right.
Our relationship has passed the honeymoon period.
Back then, you played me any song I wanted to hear.
Quit whining. How about you play it yourself?
Fine.
-I'm kidding. -Challenge accepted.
It's a joke.
Back then,
the most serious argument we had
was about what we're going to eat.
Look at us now.
Work,
the club, and the juniors…
Everything is just so messed up.
Even choosing a song to play can be an issue now.
Being a grownup is not easy.
Wat.
I'll have my Cheerleading Club practice on the field tomorrow.
Your Music Club can be as loud as you want.
No need.
I've thought about it.
My club can practice anywhere.
No, you can't.
They've been in a room with AC.
If you drag them down to practice outdoors, how will they think of you?
It's okay. I'll talk to them.
I'm sure they'll understand.
Don't worry. I can handle them.
Phukong.
How is it going?
The competition is near. I still can't remember the moves.
Not that.
We're wondering about you and Mil.
Oh.
I haven't seen him since the day we had the profile photoshoot.
He didn't bring you snacks or makeup remover?
Did he follow your IG or want to grab your boobs?
Not at all.
If he's Wat,
you'd be testing the bedsheets together by now.
Come on.
Don't be sad.
If you want love, you need to fight for it.
-Hang in there. -Hello. How are you?
-Hello. -Keep it up, guys.
A little bit.
-Boss, what brings you here? -Holy…
Hello.
Keep it together, man.
What nice weather.
But you're sweating so much.
Am I?
Boss, you just told him to fight for love, but you're crappier than him.
Can I see these moves first?
Practicing outdoors is not so bad.
-The weather today is perfect. -I'll teach you.
Phukong has improved a lot.
Seeing them like this makes me feel relieved.
They're all fast learners.
How about we call it a day?
-I think so. -Again.
Can I see these moves? Three, four, and one.
-Two, three… -All right, guys.
Let's call it a day.
Don't forget to practice at home.
We might need to practice outdoors for a while
because it would be difficult for the Music Club to move somewhere.
Let's say we are doing this for our university.
But when I walked past their room, they were strangely quiet.
Welcome to call back service.
When did you get home?
I feel really sticky.
Where have you been?
I couldn't reach you.
My phone died.
Well…
We rented a studio off-campus to practice.
What?
Wat, I know you want to practice off-campus,
but look at this place.
I don't think it'd work.
This is the best we've got around here.
I don't want to practice at the club.
You don't want to fight with him.
I can tell.
That's why I want you guys to practice in a nice place.
If you win the contest,
you can spend the prize money on a soundproof room. Problem solved.
What are you suggesting?
So we all agreed…
to practice at Dim's house for two weeks.
Two weeks?
That's right.
It's not like I want to go,
but it's a good idea.
We can both focus on our club activities.
Don't be upset. Come here.
Miss me already?
-It's two damn weeks. -It's just two weeks.
It's not like I'm dying next month.
I'll come back to you.
You do your job,
and I'll do mine.
When we win, we'll be together again.
But it's two weeks.
There, there. Someone is pouting.
-See you. -Bye.
-Take care. -Okay.
Make time to play football with me too. Don't forget me.
See you.
Hey.
When you're done, keep it in my workshop room. Here's the sandpaper.
Do you think my makeup is too thick?
No.
Your shampoo?
I'll use Temp's.
What about a toothbrush?
I'll just…
buy a new one.
Does Dim have a spare towel for you?
I have my own. I'm not borrowing his.
Give it here. I'll pack the bag for you.
You're helping me pack?
Yes.
Here. I'm taking this with me.
-Are you serious? -Yes.
It's a rare item.
You can't just buy it anywhere.
Come to think of it…
We've never been apart for this long…
except when we fought.
Dim has already graduated. Why is he still here messing with things?
I think…
it's not a coincidence I decided to join this contest.
What do you mean?
Well…
It's…
I'll tell you.
Well…
I saw you at the Scrubb concert.
Remember?
I went looking for you
at every concert that Scrubb played.
University concerts,
temple fairs, bar concerts, and high school events.
I went literally everywhere,
but I never found you.
Until this last one.
I saw one guy.
He looked exactly like you.
He was wearing a white shirt and jeans.
Yes?
Hey. Did you find that smiley guy of yours?
I didn't.
I looked for him everywhere.
I guess I failed again.
I started questioning myself about what I was doing.
Why do I bring myself disappointment over and over?
It's time for me to get over you.
That's when I heard Dim's voice.
To those who are discouraged and have given up.
You might have just a one percent chance.
So what?
If your heart still wants to keep going,
that chance will never be reduced to zero.
This song is for those who are fighting for that one percent.
One day, your fight will pay off.
TRADITIONAL FOOTBALL, MUSIC CONTEST
I've been so tired, I can hardly breathe
I've come a long way, weary
But found no finish line
Where my dream lies
Should I go back since the path gets…
You know what?
What Dim said that day
encouraged me to go on.
I applied to this university
because it's the place I met you.
And I got to see you again at last.
Wait.
So the event you were talking about is 2U, right?
Right.
Dim signed up for the music contest that year.
His band lost.
That's why I'm doing this for him this year.
More importantly, he wants us to win,
so we can get a soundproof studio.
That way, we don't have to fight.
Damn.
I feel bad now.
I just talked shit about him.
Hey.
Yes?
That's very touching.
Come on. Don't worry.
Dim has good reasons.
By the way,
the guy I saw at the last concert,
was it you?
I can't remember.
I went to many Scrubb shows as well.
Well, don't think about it.
Right now,
we are together after all.
I don't want to go to bed.
Would you like to take a walk with me?
Sure.
Wait.
What are you filming?
I'll watch it when you're not around.
No way.
-Come on. Say something. -Something?
Say anything. Do it.
Come on.
-Give it to me. I'll film it myself. -Hey.
Give it back.
Wait there. Just a sec. Do you want it or not?
Here.
-Wow. Thank you. -Sure.
Does it look yummy?
Yes, it does.
I was going to cook green curry for you this Saturday.
Too bad you'll leave before that.
Let's do it when I get back.
Let me taste it.
Wow.
Have I told you your instant noodles are the best?
Perhaps it's a new flavor.
I didn't add anything.
It's not about the flavor.
It's because you added your love to it.
That's why it's better than any restaurant.
Good.
Did you forget anything?
I did.
I forgot to grab your boobs.
You leave bruises all over them.
What's the problem?
Do you want me to grab your boobs
or knock you out with a kiss?
Knock me out with a kiss?
I've heard that countless times, and I haven't been knocked out once.
-Is that a challenge? -Yes.
Since you ask for it…
I shall grant it to you.
Wat, I'm here to pick you up.
I have to go.
Just call me when you have time.
Even if I don't have time, I will.
If you miss him,
call him.
"With great power comes great responsibility."
Ohm, you asshole.
He's sad. Stop teasing him.
I didn't tease him.
I'm reading movie quotes.
It's from Spider-Man, you know.
Why did I get kicked?
We talked.
If he has time, he will call me.
If he doesn't, that means he's busy.
I've got so much work these days too.
We don't have partners just to be with them all the time.
"We have partners,
partners to remind ourselves that someone loves us."
Now you know how to comfort your friend.
What are you talking about?
It's a quote from a movie.
Bangkok Traffic Love Story.
It's the female lead's line.
You guys don't have to worry about me.
We talked it through.
Both of us will focus on our work so we don't think of anything else.
Eat up.
I'm full.
I'm heading out first.
-See you. -Aren't you going to eat this?
No. I'm already full.
-Can I have it, then? -Go ahead.
-What are you doing? -Shit.
You scared me.
Here. When I'm not here, make sure you drink something healthy.
Wow.
Fruit juice from an organic farm.
High in vitamin C.
It's healthy just like you said.
Of course.
Look.
My surprise is ruined again.
Damn you.
What are you laughing at?
Wat.
Wat, wake up.
As of lately, the bed is just too big.
Tine.
Hey.
Come on.
I bet you're lonely.
We started a war every day,
and now you're gone.
SARAWOW
I told you to turn your clothes inside out before washing.
It's my shirt. Why bother?
Stop talking.
Hey.
Someone forgot to turn his shirt inside out.
Three, four.
Phukong, you're far behind.
-I'm sorry. -If you can't do it, just leave the team.
Tine, he's doing his best.
Don't put pressure on him.
We've given him so much time. Why…
-Pear, you're in charge. -Tine!
I hate myself today.
I miss someone with fat fingers.
Let's go!
Damn you.
Come on.
Phukong.
What's up?
Why are you guys practicing on the football field?
It's Tine's idea. He wants us to be familiar with the place.
Did you know Mil will play a warm-up match here today?
His team against mine.
And?
Well, You can just…
pretend to faint and see what he'll do.
Imagine you're running and passing out…
And then Mil comes in, asking if you're all right.
-Mil. Like this. -Like this.
No.
If he liked me a bit, we'd be together by now.
Don't back off now.
Look at your big brother.
He spent a year trying.
I appreciate your help.
I don't think I'll be as lucky as Wat.
Bye now.
-Hey, kid. -What's wrong with you?
Don't give up.
I'll take care of the team. You can handle the costumes, Tine.
Don't worry. Talk to you later. Bye.
Guys, the break is over. Get to your positions.
Let me see your pose. Now.
Smile.
Give me a smile.
Smile like we're about to win.
Good.
Hey.
Phukong, are you okay? You seem kind of pale there.
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Hands down.
Your face is really pale. Are you all right?
Just a bit tired. I stayed up late working last night.
Do you want to take a break? You can.
It's okay. I'm good.
Fine. Let me know if there's anything at all.
Boss.
Sorry I tackled you last year.
It's all right. It's in the past.
Warriors and wounds always come in the same package.
-Damn. -But this year, just be nice.
Sure. Don't worry. It's just a warm-up match.
Okay.
I want to see "Who Are We?" Put all your effort in this time, okay?
"Who Are We?" Ready?
Ready. Three, four.
One, two, three.
Shit.
Boss, damn it. This is just like a flashback.
-It hurts. -Are you okay?
Ouch.
A warm-up match, my ass!
I'm sorry.
Phukong!
-Phukong? -Phukong!
-Phukong? -Are you okay?
Hold him.
Phukong!
What's wrong?
Step back.
Phukong.
What's wrong with him?
I don't know. He looks pale. I think he might have a fever.
One second he was dancing, and then he fell to the ground.
Let's go to the hospital.
Phukong, come here.
Let me help.
It's okay. You guys go on. I'll take care of him.
-Are you sure? -I am.
Please take care of him.
Hey.
Come.
Mil.
Green said you stayed up so late working.
Welcome to the Faculty of Architecture.
I warned you before.
I'll let him know you woke up.
-Did you bring me here? -Yes.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Phukong.
What's wrong with you lately?
Nothing. Nothing is wrong.
Ever since you became a cheerleader, you've been acting weird.
Isn't it good for you?
You can play football all you want
without a kid like me bothering you.
When did I ever say you were bothering me?
Hey. I'll be right back. Phukong!
I played football every night waiting for you to show up,
but you never did.
You wore too much makeup so I got you a remover.
But you were gone.
Now tell me what's wrong.
Please don't do anything like this to me.
If you don't like me,
just stay away from me.
One-sided love is painful, you know.
What do you like about me?
I don't know.
You're like my big brother, I guess.
Are you saying I'm crappy?
Yes. I kind of like crappy people.
When will you like me back?
It's tiring to chase after you all the time.
If you don't like me, let me move on.
What do you want me to do?
We've always been like this since the beginning.
Do you want me to kiss you and act lovey-dovey?
Wouldn't that be weird?
Well…
What do you mean, exactly?
After all the things I just said,
don't you get it?
Well, I'm not sure about that.
At this moment, am I still a little brother to you?
You haven't…
just been a brother for quite some time now.
All right.
Not there. It's the brother zone. You should pat here.
Thank you for looking after Phukong.
Green will be there soon. You can go home and rest. Thanks.
Damn it.
Does it have to update now?
HBD TO NUISANCE
-Give it to me. I'll film it myself. -Hey.
What are you doing?
Just stay right there.
Wait there.
What are you doing?
Wat, are you done? You're wasting my phone battery.
Wat.
Why do you keep calling me?
-What are you doing? -Take it back.
Did you just snoop around my phone?
What's there to see? Your gallery is full of my pictures.
Wait.
Watch it later.
Save it until…
until you miss me really badly. You can watch it then.
I doubt that day will come.
We'll see about that.
No way.
What should I say?
Should I sing a song?
You'll make me sing Scrubb songs for sure.
I'm sick of your list already.
Let's hear a secret I've never told you.
You know what, Tine?
The day I saw you again,
I freaking cried.
How could I not? I lost 1,000 baht to Man.
I told him
that if I saw you again,
I'd pay him the amount.
I'm glad I did, though.
What else?
You and I…
We never really talked about our feelings.
That's right.
Never.
I said I liked you once in the "Your Smile" video
that I recorded for you.
You too.
You said you liked me once, and you've never said it again.
All you do is bug me over and over these days.
Hey.
You think I'm going to confess, don't you?
Listen carefully.
I will say it only once.
I bet you're listening so carefully now.
Okay.
Though you like to nag me,
steal my food,
always demand what you want,
and like to think it all in your head,
I still…
Wat.
Are you done? You're wasting my phone battery.
Look at yourself.
This is just how you are.
Fine.
-Wat. -Just a moment.
I won't say it.
I'll say it when I get back.
What a crappy guy.
Why is it so hard to say?
You have dragged me to this point…
where I'm talking to your doll all alone.
When you were around,
all I did was nag,
but you always did something that bugged me.
You didn't turn your clothes inside out,
you liked to steal my stuff,
and you wanted to grab my boobs all the time.
Now that you're not here,
you know, I'd let you do anything to me…
in exchange for you coming back.
Just like you said…
I must be patient.
I must be strong.
I'll wait until this event is over.
I'll wait until we meet again.
But there's something I want to tell you.
I miss you so bad, Wat.
I miss you so much too, Tine.
Type.
I didn't know you could take days off.
I came back to get my documents.
Man told me you're alone.
I knew right away you'd be upset.
I thought I wouldn't be.
But after being alone for a while,
I started to feel kind of empty.
How can you even do it?
Only a few days without him makes me suffer this bad.
You don't get to see Man for months.
How can you not go crazy?
This is real life.
You'll need to go through such tests.
My test is the distance.
For some other couples, it's the people around them.
And yours…
It's your duty.
No matter how much you love each other,
it'll find a way to come between you two.
It's worse than the yellow tape I once used with you.
Right.
When he was here, I wanted to do many things for him,
but never had time.
Same here.
When he comes back,
I'll make him green curry every day until he's sick of it.
You only say that when he's not around.
I bet you'll become lazy again when he gets back.
Is this the truth of life too?
Yes.
Thank you for staying with me,
but you should stay with Man tomorrow. I'll be fine.
It's good you're okay. Besides…
I never intended to stay with you for two nights.
You fell real hard, huh?
Don't tease me.
I'm your brother. I never got to taste your green curry.
-You can cook it yourself. -What?
I didn't know you could cook green curry.
I learned it from an online video.
I'm about to practice. How about you?
I'm about to get to guitar practice.
They're calling me now.
Hold on.
Before you hang up,
what should you say?
What? No.
Come on. I want to hear it.
What's with him?
I miss you.
Come again? I couldn't hear you.
I miss you too.
Okay. See you.
See you later.
Well, well.
-You're like a teenager in love. -What are you talking about?
I'm envious.
I'm so in love. That's why.
Why are you envious?
Though your boyfriend is far away, you still have a friend here.
Don't worry. I'll treat you to a pork BBQ buffet today.
-You give your word? -Of course.
That's awesome. Thanks, my friend.
-Do you want to join us? My treat. -I can't.
I have practice.
Come on.
Since he's a cheerleader with a boyfriend, our pork BBQ is abandoned completely.
Is he really busy practicing?
-Of course it's a practice. -Okay.
Fine. You just saved me money. See you later, kid.
-See you later. Next time. -See you.
-Are you all right? -I am.
-Totally fine. -Hey, Boss.
What happened to your leg?
I played football with Mil, and I got tackled.
Let me see.
Aren't you going to clean it? It might swell if you leave it be.
Do you want to go to my faculty's infirmary?
Are you sure about that?
Should we go now?
How about our pork BBQ buffet?
It's not good for my wound.
I can't eat it. It might worsen my condition.
-It's not good. -All right.
It hurts!
It hurts.
-Does it really hurt? -Yes, it does.
Are you really in pain?
Ouch!
-It hurts. -You seemed fine just now.
It hurts so much.
-Come here. -I'm sorry. It hurts.
-Ouch! -Does it hurt that much?
-It hurts. -Take it easy.
Ouch!
-Please be gentle with me. -Good for you.
Did you bring anyone here while I was away?
When did you come?
The familiar scent of you…
This is the familiar scent of you too.
-Really? -Yes.
You stink as always.
Go take a shower before having dinner.
I don't want to have dinner.
I want to have you.
Did you miss me?
No, I guess.
See? You never said sweet words to me.
Answer me nicely, and I'll let you go.
I miss you.
What?
I miss you too.
You said you'd let me go.
No. I miss you so much.
Let's eat.
-You said you'd let go. -No. Let's eat first. Here.
One, two, one, two, three! One, two, one, two, one!
Okay, guys. Good job.
Let's gather around.
Tomorrow is the big day we've been waiting for.
I know it's been exhausting for all of you.
Some of you even had a fight with your loved ones.
Some of you missed nice trips with your friends.
Some of you were on a strict diet to look perfect.
And, Phukong,
you overworked
and practiced so hard that you collapsed.
Thank you all for your dedication.
Thank you so much.
Tomorrow is the day, guys.
It's time to show them
how great our team is.
Are you ready?
-Yes! -Yes!
-Are you ready? -Yes!
Okay. Great.
See you tomorrow. Get home safe.
-Thanks. -Bye.
-See you. -Thanks for your work.
-Let's go home. -Take care.
-Good luck. -Get home safe.
-Go to bed early and sleep tight. -I will. See you tomorrow.
-Bye! -Bye!
-Bye. -Bye. See you.
-I'm heading out. -Bye.
See you. Take care.
-Sure. -Bye. Good luck.
Bye.
Hello.
It's the final rehearsal today, and they need an audience.
So I just called randomly.
I can't help it.
You happened to be the lucky one. So please spare your time for them.
Do your best. Don't let your audience down.
One, two, go.
I'll do everything
I'll do anything
I know where
All this is leading to
It doesn't matter who is in your heart
As long as you look my way
My heart is filled
With joy when you do
I don't care who you love
I don't care about reality
All I know is you're the one
In my heart
I don't care who you love
I don't care about reality
All I know is you're the one
In my heart
Subtitle translation by: Peeraya Moonjun