MUSIC CLUB VOLUNTEER CAMP
Phukong.
Have you got your seat?
I heard the third years are busy.
-How do you have time for this? -It depends on who's on the trip.
Have a seat.
-Hey. -Hello.
-Hello. -Hi.
-Hi, Boss. -These two seats aren't taken. Sit down.
-Pear. -Have a seat.
Come sit here.
Hold on.
-I'm hungry. I haven't eaten yet. -They'll stop somewhere.
-Hello, guys. -Hello.
Welcome, everyone, to the Music Club's volunteer camp.
Last year, we went into the woods.
This year, we will go to the beach.
We're going to celebrate the success of the 2U event on this trip.
Right.
Starting now, there will be no Music Club or Cheerleading Club.
It will be just…
-Us. -Right.
When we get there, I'll need to check in, hand out the Wi-Fi password,
ask for the hotel receipt and…
What are you mumbling about?
I'm reminding myself of what to do.
Being a leader just spoils the fun of this trip.
But I'm having fun.
Of course you are.
You've got nothing to do because you throw all your duties at me.
I didn't even have time to have breakfast.
No worries. I've got that covered.
Here.
You take care of work.
Let me take care of you.
What a jerk.
I'm just opening it for you.
I take the best care of you. I don't deserve this attitude.
Right. How about you drink it for me, then?
No need. I've got mine too.
I'm excited, actually.
It's our first trip to the beach.
Trust me. I'm more excited than you are.
Guys, I have something to ask.
Well, I…
No, it's my friend. He wants to surprise his boyfriend on their anniversary.
-What do you-- -Stop.
Do you really think we don't know that it's you?
We've known each other since forever.
Don't be shy.
So have you known it all along?
-Fong knows. -Ohm knows.
Everyone knows.
Whatever.
I want to throw an anniversary surprise for Wat at the beach.
But privately. Just the two of us.
How about some explicit activities on the beach?
Any idea, Fong?
I hope Fong the Philosopher won't disappoint me.
How about beach activities?
I already said that.
-Seriously? -I'm not finished.
I mean playing guitar on the beach.
I see.
-Along with the sound of the waves. -Wow.
-Under the stars. -Great.
You can spend your club's budget on that.
Right.
As expected of Fong the Philosopher.
-That's awesome. -Brilliant.
By the way, what song should I play?
Hold on a second.
Before you discuss the song,
you should make sure your boyfriend remembers the anniversary.
-Otherwise, it will blow up. -You mean the plan?
Your face, maybe. Of course I'm talking about the plan.
Why do you need to ask?
Damn it.
It's our anniversary.
He can't miss it.
Are you sure he'll remember it?
-Wat. -Yes?
Do you know what today is?
Of course I do.
I've spent this year waiting for it.
What a relief.
I've got only one concern left, then.
What is it?
About Dim and Green.
They're still fighting.
-Dim and Green? -Yes.
They seem happy to me.
-Look. A good drummer… -It's been so long since we had a trip.
-Don't touch me, or I'll slap your hand. -You slapped my hand.
Yes, they do,
but they aren't happy together.
-Hey. -That's awesome.
Remember the contest we're in?
Why do they have to fight now? We're going on a trip here.
We can't avoid them forever.
What should we do if they fight again when we get there?
They're a couple after all.
They'll make up in the end.
Just like us.
You're being cheesy again.
Everyone!
The club president will commence the beach cleaning activity now.
Here.
-Why do you always make me talk? -Just kick off the activity.
Guys!
Clean the beach.
Get in the water
and get as drunk as you like.
-Are you thirsty? -Hey.
-Drink up. -No. Stop fooling around.
Better, little fool?
Thanks.
Let's go.
What about you?
Don't you need it?
The sun can't hurt me. Come on.
MUSIC CLUB VOLUNTEER CAMP THEME: SEA AND SAND
Are you guys ready?
Ready?
Ready.
Give me some noise. One, two, three.
-Yeah! -Yeah!
Very nice.
Where are Dim and Green?
Here we go again. How could you say that?
No way. I won't let you do that.
-You're always like this. -I won't do this anymore.
How could you say that? Both have the same number of people.
You're always like this You always have excuses.
Easy. What's happening?
Just talk nicely.
The big house we booked has electricity problems.
So they're giving us two smaller houses instead.
That sounds okay.
One house has an air-con and the other doesn't.
Green wants the house with the air-con for the Cheerleading Club.
-That's unfair. -Right?
Calm down first.
Have you forgotten? The Music Club is the host of this activity.
We should get the house with the air-con.
Have you forgotten?
This hotel belongs to my friend.
We get to stay for free because I'm her friend.
You always come up with your connections.
I'm so done. If we can't negotiate, I guess we need to fight.
-You're dead. -Fight him.
It's not just you who knows how to fight.
-Come on. -Take it easy.
-Fight me. -Bring it on.
Don't stop me! Let me go.
-Come on. Go ahead. -Bring it on.
-Crappy. -You'll lose.
No, you will.
I'm going to beat you.
I thought they would beat each other up.
Exactly.
Things escalate every time they fight.
Wait and see. When they're done fighting, they'll make us take sides.
Everyone, be in your position.
Winners get the house with air conditioners.
Losers get their asses out and sleep with the mosquitoes.
Fine!
What the hell?
Green.
I think we can all sleep together in one house.
If he talked to me nicely, things wouldn't come to this.
He challenged me.
He clearly looks down on us. We can't let him get what he wants.
-But… -No, Tine.
Think about what I had to live with.
Every time he went out,
he promised to come home before midnight. And what happened?
-He came home in the morning. -Exactly!
Today, we'll show them and make them realize
who we really are.
I can tell he's feeling bad.
Not likely.
Of course. Believe me.
He wants to say "I'm sorry" so bad.
You guys can't go soft on them.
Beat them up. Understand?
-Okay. -Are you sure?
-Understand? -Yes.
All right. Now that everyone is ready,
welcome to a beach volleyball match
between the Music Club and the Cheerleading Club.
The winner will get the air-conditioned house.
Wat!
-Get the ball. -That's it.
MUSIC 2, CHEER 1
I'll get back at you for sure.
Leave me alone.
MUSIC 4, CHEER 3
Wat.
Use your force.
-I saw you did this. -I don't know how to play.
You're pulling your punches.
I'm not good at this.
MUSIC 14, CHEER 16
Boss, receive the serve.
-Boss. -Boss.
Yes?
What's wrong with you? That was an easy serve.
Go get the ball.
It's over there.
Damn you.
MUSIC 17, CHEER 19
-Mil. -Block it.
The cheerleading team gets the point.
Mil!
What was that?
I wasn't quick enough.
What is wrong with you guys?
Come on, Dim. They're all boyfriends.
If you want to fight us, spike hard, gentlemen.
Boyfriends?
Sarawat is the only one with a boyfriend here.
Mil.
Could it be…
Wait.
I thought my senses were sharp.
Since when?
When did you become my brother's boyfriend?
You should ask your brother.
Right.
-Hey. -Calm down.
-Easy, boy. -Wat, don't be mad.
Phukong was about to tell you.
You knew about this too, Man?
No. It's not like that.
Boss told me not to tell you.
You said I shouldn't tell him.
No. You said I shouldn't tell him.
You knew this too, Boss?
Boss, you asshole.
-And the game is over. -Man!
The cheerleading team wins!
Man, get down here. Come here!
-Don't run away. -Over, my ass. It's not over yet.
-We get an air-con. -We get an air-con.
Nice.
Perfect!
Give yourself a big round of applause.
They messed with the wrong ones.
It's their fault to challenge iron ladies like us.
Guys, it's going to be so cold here,
because this is an air-conditioned house.
We have rooms upstairs and a big room over there.
Let's get our spots, people.
-Pear, come here. -Let's go upstairs.
-Let's stay downstairs. -Okay.
-I'll take this bed. -Sure. Go ahead.
Better, little fool?
I want to throw an anniversary surprise for Wat at the beach.
Tine.
What's wrong?
Isn't it nice to stay in this cozy room?
It's nice, but the surprise I've prepared for Wat is now ruined.
Do you need my help?
How are you going to help me?
Let's talk about you and Mil.
What's going on? You've never said anything.
-It's nothing. -Spill it.
I'm going to take a nap.
Nice.
Good luck, then.
We lost because of you guys.
What a bunch of suckers.
You're all hen-pecked.
What?
We're screwed because of you.
If you talked nicely, we'd all be in that house.
-Right. -It's hot in here.
Do you want me to talk nicely to him?
Not a chance.
What?
What are you two fighting over anyway?
We're on a trip here. Let us have a good time.
You caused such chaos.
It's so hot in here.
You don't need to know what the fight is all about.
Let's say my dignity has been trampled.
Dignity bullshit again.
Dim!
The seafood you've ordered is here.
Here we go.
Here.
There's another box.
Damn.
All from the market.
-Great. -When did you order this?
Just a while ago.
I bought it all from the market. Nothing left for them to eat.
You're such a kid.
So what?
They get the house with the air-con.
We get the seafood here.
-Are you happy? -Very happy.
What the hell!
What was that sound?
Seriously?
-It's because of you, Wat. -No, it's you.
It's your fault.
Sorry. The breaker broke down because of a short circuit.
Our electrician will fix it tomorrow.
Do you have any rooms left?
We are fully booked.
Can you please stay with your friends tonight?
I'll bring you guys extra beds.
Sure!
What do you say?
No need. We can stay here just fine.
Come on, Dim.
-It's burning inside. We can't sleep. -Right.
We need a fridge for the seafood.
We can't stay here.
Dim, you better make up with Green.
How about this?
You share the seafood with Green.
He loves good food. He'll come around.
True.
I know that deep down you want to make up with Green.
Why are you pretending you don't want to?
You still have his picture on your phone screen.
Swallow your pride. It's no big deal at all.
Right.
Are they sold out?
Okay. Thank you.
They said a guest here bought it all.
It must be Dim who bought all the seafood before us.
See?
Green.
Well…
We'd like to share the house with you.
We didn't come empty-handed.
We have all the seafood from the market.
We can share.
I'll give you one-third of the seafood.
I'm okay with the house sharing.
About the seafood, I want two-thirds of it.
No.
I'll give you one-third. Take it or leave it.
I won't.
Then no seafood for you. Let's go, guys.
-Hey. Calm down. -Let's go back.
-Look at him. -Dim.
This is who he is.
He's always like this.
He can't stand losing. He just has to win.
He always gets what he wants.
Even our online channel too.
What? An online channel?
What are you talking about?
Well, we were naming our channel together.
We agreed to name it GreenDim at first,
but Dim changed his mind.
He wanted to put his name first. He wanted DimGreen.
I'm the leader. My name must come first.
What?
We had to compete in that stupid volleyball game
just because you wanted your name before his?
It's a big deal. It's my dignity.
-Unbelievable. -Right, everyone?
Guys, bring this inside. Let's eat seafood together.
-Let's do it. -Bring it inside.
Give me a hand.
Let's get inside. Come on.
-What a stupid fight. -Let's grill it.
-Green, let's eat. -I paid for it.
It's the club's budget.
-Wat, that's my money. I paid for it. -Let's eat.
-Wat, these crabs look yummy. -Right.
It's GreenDim, then.
It's unfair.
I always please you when you pout.
Why can't you do the same for me?
Who are you looking for?
Your brother.
Seriously.
When did you two get together?
When he became a cheerleader,
but I had liked him long before that.
Are you serious with him,
or do you just want to get back at me?
Why would I do that? It'd be a waste of time.
I'd rather spend my time playing football with your brother.
So you are serious.
If I wasn't,
I wouldn't be here talking to you.
Take good care of him,
or I'll take him back.
You're using my words against me?
Fine.
-Go find him. -Is he over there?
Phukong, here you are. I looked for you everywhere.
Where have you been?
Well…
I've asked for your brother's permission to date you.
Are you kidding me?
I have no reason to do that.
I don't know. You've always fooled me.
You tricked me into playing football and building models with you.
All the time.
I wasn't tricking you.
I just wanted to get close to you.
I told you a million times that's the brother zone.
-Huh? -I know.
-Here. -You just can't remember, can you?
But for me,
patting the head is like "I like you."
Can I get your hand?
Hand, please.
Look at me.
What are you doing?
Holding hands is like…
"you're my boyfriend."
Aren't you feeling embarrassed?
Why should I be? My boyfriend is so cute.
Did you just realize that I'm cute?
Right. I got something for you.
-What is it? -I drew it the best I could.
Where is it?
Are you sure you're an architecture student?
Is this the best you've got?
Wait. Let me see.
Wow.
It's not so bad. Judging from the eyebrows, I can tell who this guy is.
Give it back.
Come on.
You gave it to me. It belongs to me now.
And to whom do I belong?
To whom?
To the one sitting with you now.
Boss.
It's your chance now.
Confess to her already.
Right.
What should I say?
You can start with your football jersey.
Tell her they printed it wrong.
It was supposed to be her name.
Go ahead.
-Come on. -I don't think so.
Trust me one last time. Please.
Don't back off. Go on.
Go ahead.
That's it.
Boss.
Why are you here by yourself? Are you okay?
I'm fine. It's just…
I'm a bit worried about school, and I don't want to spread the flu.
-I see. -Right.
About school, you can talk to me.
I may not seem like one, but I'm a real nerd.
-Are you serious? -Of course.
And about the flu,
are you going to spread it to me?
No. I won't do that.
By the way, how is it going with you and that Cute Piggy?
It wasn't supposed to be "Cute Piggy."
What should it be, then?
Take a guess.
CUTE XXXXXX
Cute Bear?
No, it's not.
Try again.
Cute Puppy?
Why would I print that?
I don't know.
I'll give you clues.
She is very cute.
She is also kind.
When she sees someone get hurt,
she always helps them.
Who could it be?
Cute Doctor?
Who is it?
Do you like one of my friends?
Right? Which one? I'll introduce you.
He likes you, Pear!
-What? -He likes you!
I can't hear you!
Boss likes you!
-Hello, Type. -Hello.
-What are you doing? -I'm just thinking about you.
I'm at the beach.
There are many couples here,
but I'm all alone
without my boyfriend.
I can't listen to your complaint.
-I have to meet someone. -What? Who are you going to meet?
With a man who has thick eyebrows, a mustache, and a lustful face.
With a mustache and beard?
He sounds suspicious, though. Don't go near him.
-Do you hear me? -I think so.
But it's too late now. I do trust him.
Hello? What did you say?
Type, can you hear…
Type, how did you get here?
By plane, of course.
But I can stay for one night and go back tomorrow.
-Just one night? -Right.
That's okay. One night is enough for me.
Enough for what?
Well…
All right.
While I was away, did you have your eyes on someone else?
Here we go again. You always ask me that.
Who would I lay eyes on?
I have eyes on you and only you.
I told you to trust me.
I'm kidding.
I do trust you, Man.
You told me yourself that it was difficult to get me.
I don't open my heart to anyone so easily, you know?
Why are you being romantic today?
Are you sick?
It's kind of weird.
-What I'm telling you is… -Is…
A long-distance relationship is tough.
It requires trust and patience.
And I want you to be patient.
I'll do the same for you.
That's it. Let go of my hands.
Type.
I miss you.
Okay.
"Okay"?
Just "okay"?
Okay.
How could you respond to me with that?
I've always missed you. We are so far apart.
-We get to meet once in a blue moon. -Man.
You can't say I don't miss you now.
Okay.
So we have…
just one day, right?
Yes.
Should we just…
do it now?
Do what? No.
Do what we always do.
Come on. Don't be shy.
Where are you going?
Should we start?
Hello, Green Grub Grub's fans.
Long time no see.
As all of you know,
Green and I had a fight.
That's because I forced him to name this channel DimGreen.
I wanted to put my name first.
So I want to say I'm sorry to him.
Louder.
I'm sorry.
From now on, this channel will be called GreenDim.
No, it won't be.
Our channel's name isn't GreenDim.
From now on, this channel will have a new name.
It's Sunshine and Daisy!
How did you come up with that?
Why?
It's your band's name.
Sunshine Daisies and Butter Mellow.
You will be Sunshine,
and I'll be Daisy!
So you let my name come first.
Yes.
Why are you so cute?
Let me give you a kiss.
-Stop. We're still doing a live video. -It's fine. Let them know.
Wait. It's embarrassing.
Let's start our first video properly.
Everyone, our first episode will be
"Sunshine and Daisy on the Beach."
See you later.
-On the beach? -Yes, on the beach.
I'll do it till you drop. Let's take the camera too.
Help me. Anyone!
Smelling the earth out of the wind Blowing towards me
From very far away
On this gigantic planet We are just small people
Looking up to the vast sky and ocean
Smelling the earth out of the wind Blowing towards me from very far away
On this gigantic planet, just choose
Your desired
Path
How was it?
Did you feel the love?
How would I feel that?
It's not a love song.
How is it not?
Every song I play for you,
I play with love.
Yuck.
You're being cheesy.
Where did you go earlier?
To get you this towel.
Your hair is wet.
You might catch a cold.
Why don't you take good care of yourself like you take care of me?
Why?
I'm your boyfriend.
I need to take good care of you.
Right?
But a relationship is about give and take.
Let's do this.
When you're too lazy to take care of yourself,
let me take care of you.
Okay?
Taking care of me is easy.
Just let me grab your boobs.
My boobs?
All right. Go ahead.
Put your hands here. Do it.
Grab them.
-Do it. -Hold on.
I thought you were bold. Very disappointing.
SARAWOW GLOWING BRIGHT
Earn.
We have plenty of squid here. Get some.
Come here.
Don't go anywhere.
-Well, well. -Why don't you say something to them?
Is Boss all right?
-Boss. -Are you that thirsty?
-What's with him? -Talk to them.
We're going now. Don't get drunk.
-Really? -What is it?
You suck.
You had a very good chance this evening. Why did you run into the water?
What happened?
Look.
-Wat. Tine. Did you know-- -Shut up.
I'm telling them.
This evening, Boss had a chance to confess his love to Pear,
but he just ran into the water.
Were you that shy?
It was hot.
-Hot? -Yes.
-I went for a swim. -Are you sure?
What's wrong with that?
-Why do you keep looking at your watch? -What?
Have to go somewhere?
No.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You can talk to me.
I'll get some ice.
We ran out of ice cubes here.
Tine.
We still have a lot.
-Boo! -Hey!
Why did you guys come?
Because we wanted to.
We're here to witness your little surprise for him.
One more thing, I'm going to film a video for Phuak to see.
So how is it going?
It's going nowhere. Look.
He's still drinking with his friends. He might be drunk already.
I'm not sure if this will work.
I've got a plan. Don't worry.
Just take him for a walk along the beach.
Leave the rest to us.
We'll take care of it.
You're so smart.
-Are you sure? -Just trust us.
It's so good here.
With you, anywhere is good.
Wat.
Have you ever thought
about what you would've done if I had turned you down that day?
Not really.
Were you that confident?
I wasn't.
But when I love someone,
I don't keep my heart in reserve.
The worst-case scenario
was I got hurt
and got over you.
Then you're lucky I didn't turn you down.
Right.
I was lucky enough to see you cry too.
Hey.
Don't rub it in.
Since that day,
we have been through a lot together.
Yes.
Wat.
Come.
The football game is on.
Can I go watch the game?
But today is…
It's Manchester United versus Liverpool. It's about to start.
Let me check it out.
Where is Wat?
He went to see a football game.
Oh.
So much for a smart plan. It failed.
I'm sorry.
Hey. How about this?
Since he's gone,
let's get drunk by ourselves.
Yes?
Now we all learn that
not everyone can remember their anniversary.
Keep that in mind.
-Guys. -Yes?
I read this somewhere.
Scrubb once asked his fans.
If they listened to the same song 100 times over,
would they still be into the song?
For me, I would.
But him?
I'm not so sure.
You're not sure.
-Do you want to know his answer? -Yes.
-Then go ask him. -What?
-Ask him? -Yes.
You promised him, didn't you?
That whatever is on your mind, you'll speak out.
I did.
If you want to know whether he's still into you or not,
you have to ask him.
-Right. -Go ahead.
You have a point.
-Tine. Let me help you. -Tine.
Have some water.
What happened to you?
I went out for a walk,
and I just tripped over.
Did you hurt yourself?
Let me see.
Just be more careful next time.
Do you have anything to say to me?
I can always tell when you're being weird.
Please tell me.
You said we'd have a heart-to-heart talk.
Fine.
I didn't trip over.
I fell because I was drunk.
The reason I was drunk
is because you forgot our anniversary.
I asked you to take a walk
because I wanted to surprise you.
I was going to play guitar for you.
Okay.
It's good you got it out.
I have something to tell you too.
I…
didn't forget our anniversary.
I prepared you a surprise as well,
but Dim ruined it.
I had Boss pretend to call me out for a football match.
Do you get it now?
It's all screwed.
Did you really remember?
Are you doubting me?
You are my first boyfriend.
How could I forget our day?
You're overthinking it, Tine.
So…
Is it too late to ask for that surprise?
Would you like to go to a concert with me?
Wow.
Good evening, sir. May I see your ticket, please?
Mr. Tine.
This way, please.
Follow me.
What are you doing?
-Good evening, Mr. Tine. -Please have a seat.
Good evening.
Here.
Welcome, all honorable guests, to the celebration
of having this nuisance in my life for one whole year.
He didn't even know…
that he had been revolving around my universe long before.
Million stars in the sky
Is there any star that stays still?
The one that doesn't revolve around Any other stars
I have never seen any
My star is traveling so far off
Every star is just so far apart From each other
I guess your star is just the same
They can take many light-years to meet
But when two stars see each other
Seasons change
So do the orbits
When you and I meet each other Our lives change
It all changes Our hearts beat in the same rhythm
You revolve around me I revolve around you
And the two stars rotate themselves
You attract me, I attract you
The two stars shine beautifully On each other
You attract me
I revolve around you
And the two stars rotate themselves
You attract me, I attract you
The two stars shine beautifully On each other
You revolve around me I revolve around you
And the two stars rotate themselves
You attract me, I attract you
The two stars shine beautifully On each other
Thank you.
-What is it? -No.
-It's a secret. -What are you doing?
-What's going on? -I wonder what it is.
Happy anniversary.
Let's grow old together.
-Let's hear some noise. -Yeah!
Hello, Wat.
I got a surprise from you that night.
So you'll get this video from me instead.
Wrong.
When did you come?
Since you started recording.
What song are you playing?
Last year, you wrote me a song.
So I was trying to write you a song this year.
Do you want to know what it's called?
-Can you even write a song? -I tried for you.
-What is it called? -It's called "Sarawat."
Let's hear it.
For someone I get to meet For the first time
Some words are suddenly clear in my heart
Those words are telling me You are the right one
I can't even find the reasons
For someone who is not like The person in my dream
But you know what?
It must be you, just you
That's all it takes To stop me right here with you
Though I could turn back time
I'm sure I'd pick you every time
I know it right away At the first glance at you
You're the one I've been waiting for
You don't need to be like The person in my dream
Being who you are is already enough
The one who stands right beside me And ready to walk together
If I'm asked who is good enough for me
My answer is you
My answer is…
You
Was it good?
Keep looking at me like that,
and I'll knock you out with a kiss.
Are you challenging me?
Keep looking at me like that,
and I'll kiss you till you moan.
He's taken. Sarawat.
Sarawat has a boyfriend named Tine.
Let's grow old together.
Fine. I'll grow old with you.
Subtitle translation by: Peeraya Moonjun