Welcome, everyone, to our Music Club.
This year is so special.
We have a legend here with us.
People call her the legendary electric guitarist.
She's joining us today.
Let's meet her, guys.
MUSIC CLUB
Why is no one attending?
-Who is she? -Jennie.
The legendary electric guitarist.
She's from the Hot Wave Contest the same year as Toon.
-Toon Bodyslam, you know. -Come on, Dim.
Not just Toon, I just dined with Ohm from Cocktail yesterday.
-How was it? -I paid for dinner.
Let's focus on the present.
I'm a fan of you two. I press "like" on every post of yours.
By the way, did you guys dance to the Spider song?
Yes?
That's all right.
Let's skip to the highlight.
The snack-feeding game.
Let's do it.
-Jennie, the thing is… -What?
The university bans such games.
What? Why is it like this?
Who bans them?
I can't believe it.
I took a day off just to see you guys play this game.
Can't you just proceed with it? I will take full responsibility.
We can't. If these juniors report it to the board,
our club could get shut down.
All right. Let's do this, then.
You juniors don't need to do anything.
Wat and Tine will be the ones playing the snack game.
Just the two of them.
Give it up for them.
Sarawat and Tine will play.
They will feed snacks to each other. Give me some music.
Here we go! Feed the snack.
Snack.
WatTine! Everyone, together.
WatTine!
That's right.
This game will live on forever.
Who will be the feeder?
Wat? Tine?
-I will. -Good.
Just stand still. Let me handle it.
Goodness.
Oh, my heart can't take it. He said he'd handle it.
"Let me handle it."
Drumroll, please.
A bit closer.
A little bit closer.
A professor's here.
Everybody knows it. My fans know it.
I live my life just to see their moments.
I'm dying happily.
What did you just do?
A professor was passing by. I had to destroy the evidence.
You're my secretary. A little kiss from me won't hurt.
Jennie, you're heavy.
What should I get Tine for his birthday?
I want something…
simple…
yet special.
How about you turn a university hall into a surprise party?
Don't you get what "simple" means?
I just don't know what he likes.
-I can't figure it out. -He likes you.
I know that. He likes me. He likes me very much. But…
How about you tie yourself with a ribbon? It'll be a surprise.
-Good. -Right?
I'm being serious here.
What's the color of the ribbon?
-Pink. -Pink.
I can't stand you guys anymore.
You guys aren't kids.
Such crappy ideas.
Here we go.
Do you have a better idea?
Sing him Scrubb songs.
Scrubb again?
Will you ever let my friend move on from this band?
But Tine really loves their songs.
Go on.
Throw him a Scrubb music festival of your own.
Play him a song every night until his birthday.
This way, he'll know you're paying attention to him.
Put your heart into it.
Fong the Philosopher strikes again.
I think it's his fling.
Good morning.
I've looked into your latest marketing analysis.
Well…
It's so good.
Management loves it.
Thank you.
One more thing. There's good news for you.
Our company is looking for a new marketing team leader.
Would a hardworking young man like you be interested, Type?
I'm interested.
But you'll be sitting in the Phuket office.
Oh.
-Phuket? -Yes.
I know it's far,
but this is a good opportunity for you.
All right. Just think about it.
When you make up your mind, just let me know. Okay?
Sure.
"Together," "The Sun," and "Eternal Love."
He'll love it.
Hey.
What happened?
You seem cranky.
I just got back from the hospital.
The cheerleading team had a car accident.
What?
Fang.
I heard your car overturned.
I thought you were badly injured.
I'm glad you're all right.
Come on. I have a ruptured tendon.
Doesn't it sound serious to you?
A ruptured tendon?
-What about the others? -Over there.
I'm okay.
Oh…
Damn.
As you can see.
I've told you many times to drive carefully. You never listened.
It hurts.
Right.
What about our cheerleading club?
What should we do?
That's why I called you.
We're about to hit the audition day.
And the person I trust the most with this job is you, Tine.
Tine.
Be the club president for me, please.
Please.
I told her I'd like to be your secretary,
but she wanted me to think it over.
You don't have to.
Just be the club president.
Wait. Why so easy?
Then don't. Be my secretary.
What? You're confusing me.
No, you're confusing me. I found an easy way out for you.
What do you say?
I've been practicing the guitar so hard
because I want to work with you.
I know.
I don't want to let you go,
but what else can I do?
My boyfriend is smart,
responsible,
hardworking, and good-looking.
Everyone wants to have him.
You spoil me.
You're my boyfriend after all.
It's my duty to spoil you.
You're very sweet.
Should I reward you?
Hey.
What song do you like?
I'll play it for you.
Damn.
You just ruined the mood.
How was your day, darling?
Stop with these sweet words.
Are you online shopping again?
What are you talking about? Don't accuse me.
You're wrong.
You always forget to log out of your e-mail. I see everything.
Oops.
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
Please don't be mad.
Okay?
Okay. I won't be.
It's no big deal.
I'm taking a shower.
What?
Our company is looking for a new marketing team leader.
But you'll be sitting in the Phuket office.
-I'll scrub your back. -Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm taking a shower with you so you won't be lonely.
Let me scrub your back.
Do it gently, then.
I'm always gentle with you.
Let me.
If Tine's skin is super bright,
then yours should be duper bright.
-Hey. -Type.
Will you tell me what's going on?
Do you think I can't tell?
You're overthinking. I'm all right. Just a bit tired.
Go on. Scrub my back.
Are you sure?
I am.
Hey.
Are you going to stir until it evaporates?
No, I'm not.
You're zoning out.
What's on your mind?
Today is the kick-off day for the Cheerleading Club.
I'm nervous.
This is the first time I'm doing things without you by my side.
Get your head closer.
What?
Come closer.
Why?
Get closer to me.
Dear God.
I wish my boy all the best in work,
that he's loved by many people,
and that he's respected by his club members.
So be it.
Wow.
Your skin is so soft.
Wait.
You didn't make one for me.
Right.
Come on.
What happened to your generosity?
It's gone. You don't have it anymore.
Quit complaining.
Do I look good enough?
Do I look trustworthy?
You look great. Come on.
I'm here, Fang.
See you later at home.
What? We got a club room?
Yes. I'm on the fourth floor. Which room?
Okay.
Sure. I'm about to get there.
I found it.
-The door isn't locked, right? -Hey.
What?
I thought your club was far away,
but you're just next door. That's good.
Are you sure it's good?
What are you doing, Boss?
Liking Pear's photos.
I see.
I know that. You've been liking hundreds of her photos already.
What's wrong with that?
I'm doing it until I hit her first post,
so that she knows I like her.
Master Nicky taught me this trick.
Master Nicky?
-That's right. -What crap.
How so?
Take Phukong for example. He's writing a song for the one he likes.
You should be ashamed.
All you do is check out her photos.
Do you think it works?
Dumbass.
Say whatever you want. You have a boyfriend.
Of course I do.
-Look, dude. -What is it?
It's Phukong.
-Hello, Pear. -Damn.
-Where's the phone? -Oh.
-Is this the one? -Yes, it is.
Hold on.
Don't tell me the senior he likes is Pear.
Right.
They're saying goodbye.
Boss, you brat.
-Boss, calm down. -Don't hold me back.
-Oh, hello. -How about you go to hell?
-What does it mean? -No idea. I heard it in Korean dramas.
Calm down, man. Keep it cool.
Phukong.
Wat told us you had a crush on a senior.
We didn't think it would be this person.
You guys knew?
Come on.
It's so obvious. You two are really close. There are millions of people out there.
-Why are you hitting on Boss's sweetheart? -What?
-That's right. -Do you like Mil?
Of course I do. Her skin is so bright. How can…
Did you just say Mil?
You like Mil?
Well, the thing is,
Pear's little brother is studying architecture.
Her brother and I are close friends,
but the one I really like is Mil.
Don't worry.
We live in a modern world where love knows no boundaries.
I don't care about that at all. I'm worried about my brother.
Wat and Mil don't like each other.
Oh.
-Well, guys… -What?
Please don't tell Wat.
I won't.
By the way, which level are you on with Mil?
Level? I'm stuck right where I started.
Poor you.
He knows how I feel,
but he regards me as a younger brother.
All he does is ask me to play football with him.
There, there.
You're in the brother zone. It's fine.
Been there, done that. I understand.
We're going to help you.
That's right.
I helped your brother once.
I'm sure I can make it happen for you.
Really?
Of course. Rest assured.
Just smile and things will be fine.
Don't worry, kid.
-You sure you don't like Pear that way? -I'm sure.
-You can hit on her. -Good.
Now you don't have to worry.
APPLY FOR CHEERLEADING CLUB
We've come to the last member.
Palm, would you mind telling us why you want to be a cheerleader?
I was a cheerleader before in high school,
and I want to carry on the job here as well.
I'm Tine, the Cheerleading Club president.
Thank you all for your interest in joining our club.
We will have an audition coming in a week,
so I'd like to know if any of you was a cheerleader before.
Oh.
Sorry to interrupt.
Get out.
There's one more person who wants to join.
You mean Phukong?
Yes.
He wants to be like Tine, Mr. Chic.
Who knows? He might get a football player boyfriend too.
Is that right?
Yes.
You can fill out the application form later. Come on, then.
Please take care of him.
Thank you. That was a joke.
All right.
You need to learn our basic pose.
This is our basic pose.
Let's try again. Take a look at this.
Excuse me.
Wat.
You said you'd lower the noise.
With the juniors, I can give them orders, but take a look at this.
-Dim? -Right.
He's still looking for a job. That's why he's always here.
Tine, what are you doing here?
I came to talk about the noise.
You guys are loud. We can't practice.
I talked to him. He said it's your problem.
What can I do?
Dim.
Why aren't you at home?
You're bothering these kids.
Watch your mouth.
I didn't bother anyone.
Our practice session bothers the Cheerleading Club next door.
This is a music club.
Do you want me to meditate or what?
-Should I start chanting now? -Come on.
What an ass.
Don't forget that this is the Student Affairs Center.
We have to think about other people sharing this building.
Green, whose side are you on?
Any side with no bullies like you.
You like to force people. You've been like this since that time.
Shut up.
Dim.
What is he talking about?
Stay out of it.
I'm going to play my way.
If you aren't happy, get out.
-You too. -Fine. I'm going. No need to fire me.
Tine! Can I join your Cheerleading Club?
I'm sick of being around this jerk.
Did you just insult me?
-I did. -Hold on, Dim.
Take it easy.
I just asked you to keep it low.
Easy, Dim. Calm down.
-Don't be mad. -Wat.
Wat, you are the club president.
You carry everyone's dignity.
Now, you tell him if we should lower the noise for them or not.
We shouldn't.
I'm sorry.
-Please don't be mad. -No.
I'm so tired.
I killed my throat just to be louder than your club.
And here I am being sorry.
Let me put the lotion on for you.
Please forgive me.
Your lotion smells nice.
Here.
Don't be mad. I was in front of my club members.
I had to go with the flow.
I need to take care of my club members too.
Damn it.
I thought working separately would do us good.
It's even worse now.
Come on. Don't be angry.
I'll sort it out with Dim tomorrow. Okay?
-Don't be mad. Let me give you a massage. -No.
I'm going to bed.
Hey.
Tine.
So you won't forgive me?
Fine. Wait a second.
This song is for my beloved nuisance…
Again?
Type, can I borrow your laptop and put on some music?
Sure. Go ahead.
Someone forgot to log out of his e-mail.
You're finished.
"Details on the marketing team leader position, Phuket office.
Dear Mr. Teerasup.
Please be informed about your promotion and transfer
to the Phuket office."
Will you tell me what's going on?
Do you think I can't tell?
You're overthinking. I'm all right. Just a bit tired.
Oh!
-My name is on the list. -Yes.
Good job, kid.
Are you sure that I will get his attention if I'm a cheerleader?
Believe me. If you keep playing football with him,
he will only see you as his junior.
But if you're a chic and lovely university cheerleader,
you will have his full attention for sure.
-Really? -Really.
Be confident.
Girlfriends.
-Everyone has a girlfriend. -Hey.
Phukong.
We miss you on the football field.
I have practice.
Practice?
Practice what?
I am a university cheerleader now.
For real?
Good for you.
Anyway,
make time to play football with me too. Don't forget me.
-See you. -Well…
I'd like to have some B2 papers.
He doesn't seem to be interested.
You're stupid.
He kept it inside. Can't you see that?
Poor kid.
Let me tell you. My next plan is going to work for sure.
Which store?
I think it's in the alley.
Hey.
Hi there.
How many songs has he played?
A dozen.
His bass was so loud, we couldn't even practice our moves.
Wait.
I'm not talking about the club. I'm talking about things at home.
What? What about my home?
About your birth…
Look, Ohm.
Well, he…
He's curious…
if you two have sweet moments at home.
That's right.
If you had any idea how seriously our clubs are fighting,
you wouldn't ask that question.
Who on earth put the Music Club next to the Cheerleading Club?
Right.
It's a mess. Green just exploded the other day.
Guys, be ready for "Who Are We?"
So you're doing this.
You want to do this?
I thought things were over, but Dim struck back.
He didn't back down.
Let's go.
Enough! I won't live with this.
Guys!
Let's go.
Dim, you jerk.
Is this how you want it?
Yes. What's your problem?
This is my club.
These speakers are also mine. I'll play as I please.
You can play.
Just pay back the money you borrowed from my dad to buy them.
Wait.
Dim, you said you spent the club budget.
Do you think we had a lot?
We could buy just one Bluetooth speaker with it.
It seems we can't be at peace.
Guys, let's take back these speakers.
-Let's do it. -Okay. Take them.
Tine.
Talk to your friends, please. Phukong.
-What are you doing? -Sorry, bro. My club comes first.
Are you mad?
-I'll make you regret tonight. -Tine, please talk to your friends.
-Come on. -Green gave the order.
You're the club president. We can't practice like this, Tine.
Tine.
Green! I miss you, baby.
I want to kiss you on the cheek.
I haven't started my Scrubb music festival yet,
and his birthday is tomorrow.
I have one night left.
A love guru once said, "Never let work conflicts
ruin your love life."
The thing is,
you should do something nice for each other.
Your work might get smoother, and your life sweeter too.
Anyone who's finished with makeup, come over here for the profile photoshoot.
Hurry up.
We still have time.
Excuse me.
Can you put on the wrong foundation and make it really thick for him?
-Sure. -Hey! Are you crazy?
Trust me.
When Tine had makeup on, Wat cleaned it for him.
If you wear thick makeup, I'm sure Mil will clean it for you.
-Are you sure? -Yes.
Let me know if it's too tight. Can I see the outfit?
Pear is here. Why is she here?
Take it easy, man.
Green asked her to help with the costumes.
Damn.
It's your chance, my friend.
If I were you, I'd make a move right now.
Are you carrying a perfume bottle around?
-Make it real thick, okay? -Hold on.
They just ignored me.
Hey. What are you doing here?
-See you later, then. -Sure.
We're shooting profile photos.
I see.
Mil.
Do you think my makeup is too thick?
Well…
No.
Not at all?
Take a look again.
No. It's fine.
I'll see you later.
He couldn't see it, could he?
How was it?
It didn't work at all.
Oh.
-How come? Let me see. -Right.
Could it be that your makeup isn't thick enough?
-Don't you agree? -Yes.
-Put on some more. -It's too much already.
How about you two wear it yourselves?
I'm going to clean up.
-Wait. -You…
Green, don't forget to send me the pictures you took.
I'll talk to the adviser again about the 2U event budget.
I'm home now. Bye.
What a long day.
I'm starving.
You're the king of complaints.
But I'm really tired.
I had to shout louder than Dim's guitar.
Would you like to listen to a song?
I'll play it for you.
Come on. You're home now. Stop talking about work.
Tine.
Let's talk about us.
I'm weary. I'll take a shower and go to bed.
How about one song? Just one.
I heard your club playing all day. My brain is turning into mush.
But I…
I tuned my guitar since noon for you. Aren't you going to listen?
Please.
A love guru once said, "Never let work conflicts
ruin your love life."
Care to join me in the shower?
Come on.
Just listen to this one Scrubb song.
I've prepared it for you.
It's your call.
Will you play a Scrubb song or scrub my back?
Take your pick.
Tine, wait for me.
HBD TO NUISANCE
Damn. You're a real pervert.
You lost to your sexual desire.
-Let me see. -Fine.
Good.
In the end, you bought a cake just like I said.
How is it for a simple surprise?
We'll have a cake no matter what.
But I just want it to be a little more surprising.
Yes. What a surprise.
-You're hopeless. -Stubborn.
-Here we go. -Call Tine for me.
Wat.
Come out and talk to me.
Did your club just request for my club to move away?
No, it wasn't me.
Who did this?
I did. Get out of my way.
What did you do?
We can't play music because you have a soft spot for Tine.
So I need to take care of it myself.
Fine.
You aren't the only one who can file a report.
We're going to complain that your music club
has been creating loud noises too.
-Let's file a complaint. -Hey! Calm down.
Take it easy, everyone.
We can talk things out. We don't need to report anything.
I think so too. Let's not make this a big deal.
Please, I beg you.
I'm doing this for you two.
Let's draw lots.
Whoever gets the shorter lot
can get out. Ron, give me some lots.
-Okay, Dim. -Ron, wait.
Dim, what are you doing? This isn't what I meant.
-I mean, we should negotiate. -Okay.
If you dare challenge us, we're ready to accept it.
Tine, go ahead.
-Go on. -Fine. If you insist.
Wat, you draw it.
-Please don't do this. -Take it easy.
Green.
-It's annoying. -You don't have to do this.
Please don't be mad. I'm sorry.
-Let's talk things out. -What's that smell?
-It's fire! -Shit.
Dim! Fire!
Green, don't leave!
Help me put it out.
Get the instruments out!
That's super cool.
-Cool, my ass. There's a fire! -Help me get the stuff out.
Hurry!
Hurry up!
-We need water. -Quickly. Go in.
We're screwed.
Hey! Get the costumes in that room.
The costumes are in there!
The costumes! Hurry up!
Everyone, the fire is out now. Luckily, it didn't spread out.
How did it start?
It's my fault.
It was supposed to be a surprise.
This is what's left of it. I'm sorry.
Damn you, Wat.
I have no energy left to yell at you.
You see these people?
-They're in trouble because of you. -I'm so sorry.
Sorry, everyone.
Thanks for your help with the instruments, Cheerleading Club.
We have to thank your club too.
I don't think we need to draw lots anymore.
If we do that, one club needs to move away.
Let's find a way to live together in peace.
Agreed.
We don't practice loudly every day, actually.
How about…
we schedule when we can be loud?
If the club president is okay, then I'm okay too.
It's fine with me. How about Dim?
Well, it's up to the club president.
Okay, then.
If we're all good now, let's take the stuff…
back to our rooms.
Thank you all.
Let's help each other.
Green.
If I stop being an ass,
will you come back to the Music Club?
I don't know.
-I'm taking things back. -Please. I'm sorry.
Don't. I'm helping my friends.
Thank you.
Look at this. What a surprise indeed.
I'll buy you a new one. Okay?
Let's go.
Dim.
This is your ex's guitar, isn't it? You said you sold it.
Keep it down. People might hear.
Why? They all know we're together.
So you still miss your old sweet times?
-Green. -Fine.
Just spend your time with this guitar. Don't come see me anymore.
Wat.
My dear brother, please help me.
Brother. Green.
Get lost!
What should I do?
The cake is ruined.
I didn't even get any pictures with you.
It's okay. You can always buy a new one.
I know. I'll do that later.
Right.
Fong asked me to join him for a hot pot. Do you want to come?
You go on. I think I'll go home.
Why?
So you can celebrate with your friends.
We can celebrate later at our place.
-Do you mean it? -Yes.
-Are you sure? -Of course. I'm going. Take care.
-See you. -See you.
Tine.
Hey, Type.
Are you here to see Man?
No. I'm here to see you.
-Me? -Right.
Here. Happy birthday!
Wow! You've got me a present.
I may be in Phuket on your next birthday, so I wanted to give you this myself.
This plant is a hot item right now.
-Really? -Yes.
Taking care of plants can relieve your stress.
Thank you.
By the way, have you told Man about Phuket?
Not yet.
I don't know how to do it.
Why? What are you afraid of?
Tine, long-distance relationships are scary.
The distance is one thing, but a third person is quite another.
Though we don't have those problems, we still fight every day.
What if I tell him I'm going to Phuket?
He might break up with me.
Well…
I don't know about that, but if I were you,
I'd tell him straightaway.
And if he's not okay?
At least you tried.
Surprise!
What's with this costume?
Isn't it cute?
Yes.
Can you tell what I am?
I'm a shark.
A sea animal to match the Phuket theme.
Who told you?
Was it Tine?
Between the two of us,
I'm not the only one who forgets to log out of his account.
I'm sorry…
I didn't tell you earlier.
Are you okay with it?
Of course.
It's a great job opportunity for you.
I understand.
I can follow you there after I graduate.
Thanks a lot.
Oh! I've got something for you.
I went online shopping the other day
and bought two pairs of shoes.
We can wear them and run together.
We're both on a diet, aren't we?
Let's try them on.
Sure.
Aren't they cute?
They are.
There are dolphins on them.
Are you crying?
They're so cute.
Do they fit?
-Perfectly. -Good.
You should wear them too.
Why?
You said we could run together.
When I'm gone, you'll be running with someone else.
Type.
Just put your trust in me.
You should know how hard it was to win you over.
I will never leave you.
You, on the other hand, will get to meet new people
and live in a new place.
I remember one time when you ditched my motorbike for a car.
I can't forget that.
It's still in my head.
It hurts, you know.
If you want me to trust you, you have to trust me too.
Sure.
Of course I do.
Thank you.
See you at the pool.
GLOWING BRIGHT, SARAWOW
-Come on. Help me. -Okay.
I wish you a lot of happiness.
And…
I wish for you to stay with me forever.
How did the big cake turn into this?
This is more than enough.
Thank you so much.
Actually…
I was going to play you a Scrubb song every day,
but the plan failed.
I hope this is okay with you.
-Look. -What?
It has a disturbing face just like you.
It's my doll. It has to look like me.
Here.
Let me check this.
-Wow. -Hey.
It's Sarawat Expo.
It's authentic.
You're nuts.
Come here.
I have a bonus for you.
-Would you like to hear it? -Of course.
My heart goes to you
Our hands are held tight
We get it all by just one glance
No words needed
Walking hand in hand
Sharing our love
Pay no attention to other people
I'm right here next to you
My heart is full of love for you
May this love of ours
Live on forever
Be everlasting love
May this love of ours
Live on forever
Be everlasting love
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Subtitle translation by: Peeraya Moonjun