Hi, guys. I'm Tine, Mr. Chic.
This guy next to me is…
Tine's boyfriend.
What? Am I wrong?
Hi, guys. I'm Tine, Mr. Chic,
and this guy is Sarawat.
Want to know how we met?
It started out when I was hit on by someone.
I rejected him and turned him down so many times,
but he never left.
So I asked this guy to pretend to hit on me
and be my shield.
Not only did he refuse to help…
If you keep staring at me,
I'll knock you out with a kiss.
Look at him.
I didn't give up, though.
I tried to join the Music Club just to pursue him.
He didn't know he failed the audition.
I was the one that begged the seniors to accept him.
Truth be told, I've had a crush on him for so long.
So I was fooled big time.
I thought he was pretending, but no, he hit on me for real.
In the end…
this little fool is mine.
We've been together for over a year now.
Many things have changed.
We moved into a new place that is closer to the university.
I got a new guitar. And he got… See it for yourself.
Do you like it?
Of course.
I like it too.
-You mean the speaker? -No. I like you.
-Wat, have you seen my laundry basket? -It's in the same spot.
You can use mine. We live together now. What's the problem?
In the same spot, you say?
Tine, what the heck are you playing?
Our loving moments, which are usually few, slowly hit rock bottom
and were replaced by chaos.
Wat, get up.
Wat!
Damn it!
You're like this again!
Tine…
Come closer.
Stop.
I already washed my face.
-I don't want to eat frozen food. -Quit complaining.
We're blessed to have food on the table.
Nope.
You used to cook me green curry
and stewed pork with eggs every day.
Are you going to eat or not?
Yes, dear.
Hey.
Come on!
Tine, have you seen my sausages?
-They can't just disappear. -Maybe you already ate them.
Tine. Give it back.
Hey!
It's mine now. Spit it out, then.
Wat?
What is it?
I told you to turn your clothes inside out before washing.
Do it now.
It's my shirt. Why bother?
Stop talking.
Hey.
Sometimes I wonder if other couples in a long-term relationship…
are like us.
Type.
I have finished the washing. Do you want me to hang them now?
I told you a million times, before washing clothes,
you have to make sure the pockets are empty first. Look.
Bits of paper are all over.
Get rid of them.
I get you now, Wat.
They are so much alike, these two brothers.
What did you say?
Nothing. I'm just cleaning them.
I wonder if other couples are like us.
You are such a good kid.
Yes.
I tricked you to help me build the model.
I thought you wanted to see a movie.
What are you mumbling about?
Nothing.
All right.
There's too much glue. Put it down.
I think dating each other
is only the beginning.
We will have to face a lot more.
As long as we keep holding each other's hands,
no matter what is there waiting for us, we will go through it eventually.
Because we are together.
No. Because we are still together.
And that was the story of "WatTine,"
the hottest couple in our university.
Before we say goodbye,
can you please do a cute couple pose for the fans?
So they can capture and enjoy your sweet moments.
Like this.
What are you doing?
Sarawat, come on.
Your fans will love it.
Why do I need to do this?
All right, everyone. Let's say goodbye right here.
If you don't want to miss the hot issues, follow Green Grub Grub channel.
Don't forget to subscribe and hit the bell button.
See you in the next video.
Have a great day, guys.
Sarawat.
Can't you just do this one thing? The fans want to ship you two so bad.
Ship what?
We are a real couple. Our love is real.
We don't need to put on an act.
Whatever you say, boss.
When we earn some money or get sponsored,
I'm going to share them with you, okay?
Green.
How about you pay me first?
I'm a cameraman and an editor.
-Come on. -I should be paid.
But I already paid you with my body, dear.
By the way, Tine,
when you are free, can I get a solo interview with you again?
I think I've said everything.
No.
Well…
There's still one thing people want to know.
They are curious
about Pam.
Huh?
They want to know how things actually were.
I heard some say that Sarawat was hugging that girl.
And when you were in a hospital, Sarawat didn't look after you, Tine.
Green, who said Sarawat didn't look after him?
Right?
You were there taking care of me?
Well, the thing is…
I just realized I forgot to shut off the gas valve at home.
No, you didn't, but you're about to start a fire here.
Oops! It's catching fire.
Hurry, Dim. There's a fire!
Here. We should go too.
Wait.
What did Dim mean?
Did you come to the hospital?
I did.
Is there anything else I don't know about?
What do you want to know?
I know it was a long time ago,
but it's still stuck in my head.
Why did you hug Pam that day?
It was a difficult situation for me.
Pam is my close friend.
She was crying in front of me.
I just meant to comfort her and then follow you.
Right. That's true.
So you let Mil take me to the hospital instead.
You were sick. Did you really want me to start a fight?
Actually, I was there sitting next to you all night.
I went home and changed the next morning.
When I came back, you refused to talk to me.
It was not funny.
Not just that. When I got home,
I found your bracelet left in our place.
So I thought you didn't want to see me again.
Why didn't you tell me?
Well, you didn't ask.
Let bygones be bygones. We shouldn't bring it up.
Tine.
You are my first boyfriend.
Sometimes we don't realize we made a mistake until it's already happened.
I make mistakes from time to time,
but I never intend to hurt you, Tine.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I am sorry I jumped to conclusions so easily.
From this day on,
whatever is in our minds, we need to have a heart-to-heart talk.
-Okay. -Promise?
Promise.
Now I'd like to be frank with you.
-Can I grab your boobs? -Hey!
Not again. Come on.
What a perv.
Wait.
I'm meeting Fang for lunch. It's a meal with codeshare students.
Shit. I'm running late. I have to go now.
-Okay. -See you at home. Later.
Eat up.
It's my treat, but don't order too many meat dishes.
Order vegetables. Veggies are good for you.
Pass that over here.
That's right.
Could you pass some to me? Why are you late?
I'm sorry.
Hold on. Who said you could sit?
-Oh. -You kept us waiting.
You'll be punished for that.
Come on. I'll be punished anyway even if I'm on time.
Everyone!
This is Tine, the legendary chic guy from our codeshare.
He will show us his moves. Do you want to see?
-Yes! -Yes!
Fang.
You made me do it last year.
Do I need to do it again?
Of course. Now get up.
-You do it with me. -No!
-Let's dance. -Just you. Hurry up.
-Do it fiercely. -You should do it with me.
No. Just dance already.
Now.
-Come on. -Goodness.
Show us your signature moves.
My name is Tine. I am a chic guy.
I like to act cute.
I can be top, but bottom is also fine.
I like to strike hard!
Strike!
Do it again. Make it harder.
-Strike! -Right.
That's it.
I couldn't hear what you said.
Sarawat.
Wat, why are you here?
What was that dance?
It's like a kid's dance.
Oh, I can see that you're shy.
You've got a backup here. Look, Wat.
If you love him, dance with him.
-Splendid! -Come on.
I left my phone somewhere.
Sarawat, come here.
-Just go. -Go on.
Give it up for them.
-I'm leaving. -Hey!
Don't go just yet.
Ready?
My name is Tine. I am a chic guy.
I like to act cute.
Come on. Be cute.
My name is Tine. I am a chic guy.
I like to act cute.
Cute.
Try to be cute, will you?
That's cute.
I can be top, but bottom is also fine.
I like to strike hard!
Strike!
Why are you smiling?
I just…
smile for a cutie.
He gets a head pat.
All right, guys.
Come and have a seat. Please.
Should we go now?
-Okay. Drive safe. See you. Bye. -I'm waiting for Tine.
-I'll see you later, then. -Hold on.
What is it?
I have something to talk to you about.
Here. Pillowcases.
They're in different colors.
Come on. It doesn't matter.
They don't go well together. Just get new ones.
Blue is pretty though.
No. Get the ones in the same color.
By the way, Fang asked me something earlier.
Dim asked for my opinion too.
-Really? -Yes.
You go first, then.
You know that Dim already graduated.
And he said…
he doesn't have much time for the club,
so he asked me to be the club president.
-Is that so? -Yes, it is.
What did you say?
He asked me personally. What else could I say?
But I have one condition.
You have to be…
my secretary.
I'd love to.
But…
But Fang also asked you to be the Cheerleading Club president.
Yes.
It's hard to say no to her.
Hey.
I really want to work with you.
Okay.
It's fine. I understand.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Testing the bedsheet.
Soft as always.
-Testing the bedsheet? I'll go-- -Hey.
Let's do this.
I will help you make the decision.
You just have to choose between two choices.
Your first choice is that I'll become your secretary.
And the second one,
you'll make me your secretary.
Whichever choice I make,
I'll end up being your secretary.
Now you get smarter, little fool.
What a cheater.
What do you say?
Yes or no?
Fine. It's a yes.
Well, should a secretary start working tonight?
You may start now.
Hi.
Well, hello.
Hurry up. Take a seat.
Sit right here.
Tine, come with me.
-Sit. -Wat, move a bit to the left.
To the left.
-Is it okay now? -A bit to the right.
-I mean, to your right. -Sorry.
That's it.
Now pick up the guitar.
Pick it up.
Thank you two for taking this job.
Let's not waste any more time. Let's shoot.
-Okay. -Here's your script.
Don't worry too much about it.
What are we doing exactly?
It's a live video to promote our club.
But the seniors didn't have to do anything like this.
Come on.
It's a new normal, you know. Social media is a must.
Don't fuss about it.
Especially you, Wat.
-You need to be friendlier. -Hey, people are joining our live session.
-They're coming in. -Be friendly.
-Should we start now? -But I don't want to.
-Be nice and friendly. -Five, four, three, two…
-What? -Say something.
Introduce yourself. Anything.
-Anything? -Seriously.
Tine, please say hello.
Greet the audience.
Hi, guys. I'm Tine, Mr. Chic. I'm the club secretary.
This is Sarawat, the club president.
Today, we're going to tell you what is special about our club.
We have so many likes. Can you make some cute gestures?
Like a mini-heart or something.
A love sign.
A lot of students from our university are watching.
This one goes, "Tine, can I be your fan?"
-Wow. -Sure.
Please join our Music Club.
"You two look so handsome."
"Tine is adorable."
Go on. Give them more love.
Oops.
I may not be so smiley as him,
but I can play the guitar.
Wow.
There's a new comment.
"Sarawat, can you play a song to hit on us?"
Of course, dear.
Okay.
Time has brought us
Together
The bond we create each day
Is getting more and more meaningful
I'm back.
Did you miss me?
-Huh? -I do…
I do wonder when you'll stop putting used paper in the printer.
It's good that I saw them first.
If I brought these to my boss, I'd be doomed.
I'm sorry.
I just thought we could use the other side.
Look. I bought you your favorites.
See? We have plenty.
Aren't you aware that I am on a diet?
-Fine. I can take care of them myself. -You can't.
I'm on a diet,
and so are you.
Look at this one.
It's your ultimate favorite.
This is also delicious.
Type…
Take off your shoes.
I dance every single day. I'll never be fat.
I may not be so smiley like him,
but I can play the guitar.
-There's a new comment. -What is it?
"Sarawat, can you play a song…"
I'm watching the club president entertain his fans.
Are you jealous?
Don't be silly.
You're just playing a Scrubb song for your fans.
Why would I be jealous?
Why don't you just throw a concert already?
Look at this.
You sent them a lot of mini-hearts.
You also smiled from ear to ear.
Did I get to say anything?
I simply did what I was told.
I see.
Then why are you being mad?
You said we should have a heart-to-heart talk.
Just admit you're jealous.
No, I'm not.
-You shouted. That's not convincing. -I'm not.
-It's high-pitched. -I'm not jealous.
You get jealous just because of a mini-heart.
Huh?
You're so cute.
I told you.
For other people,
they have to ask me to do it.
But for you,
I do it by heart, not by duty.
Yuck.
So cheesy.
Here.
Well…
Can I request a song, Mr. President?
Any song, Mr. Secretary.
It's late. Get some sleep.
I'm reading comments from today's live.
A lot of people are interested in joining our club.
IS HE THE ONE WHO GOT IN BECAUSE HE HAS CONNECTIONS?
I HEARD HE DIDN'T EVEN PASS THE AUDITION?
HIS BOYFRIEND IS THE BOSS. THAT'S WHY.
Just don't read them.
It's full of rubbish comments.
Don't think about it.
I know.
You get some sleep. I'll listen to music.
No way.
I won't let you get sad all alone again. Let's sleep now.
Or do you want me to knock you out with a kiss?
I've heard that for over a year now.
And I haven't been knocked out yet.
Are you challenging me?
I'll knock you out.
I'm kidding.
I'm going to sleep now.
I mean it.
-Still can't sleep? I'll help. -I'm sleeping. I am.
You're safe tonight.
Good night, then. I'll turn off the light.
What?
You said I was safe.
Don't ask for it. Now sleep.
Good night.
Stop reading it already.
Why are people so good at criticizing?
You realize that, and you're reading them anyway.
Enough.
Hey.
Phuak just yelled at us through his post.
He's mad because we didn't see him off.
But we had a test.
We threw him a farewell party yesterday. Why so demanding?
It's an exchange program for a few months. Don't be dramatic.
-Here. Let me yell back. -See?
You guys get hot-headed too.
Well, this one is our friend,
but those comments you're reading are from people you don't know.
Even their profile pictures are fake.
With fake profile pictures, their comments are so harsh.
Exactly.
It's like what I told you before.
Couples shouldn't work together.
It causes a lot of headaches.
Why is that?
These trolls are all on Team #SarawatsWives.
They see you guys spending time together and get envious.
So they dig up your past to sabotage you.
Unbelievable.
If I were him, reading these comments, I'd quit immediately.
Ohm, you brat.
Don't suggest to him to quit his relationship.
-I mean quit being his secretary. -Oh, I see.
Quit?
Yes, quit being the secretary.
Okay.
Hey.
-Mine is empty. Can I have a sip? -No way.
Damn. What a jerk.
-Sorry. -Happy, huh?
Like, four times.
Sorry about that.
Sorry, Boss. I'm sorry.
I'll see you later, then.
Boss, you've had eyes on her for a year.
When will you make a move?
A girl like her won't be single for long.
Today, I will join the Music Club.
Last year, WatTine couple happened.
This year, everyone will learn about…
BossPear!
Pear resigned just now.
What?
She wants to find what she really likes.
Do you still want to join the club? Go and figure out yourself.
Guys, let's gather around.
Hurry up.
Why do you look so serious? Let's be cheerful.
Yeah.
First of all, congratulations to everyone
who passed this year's audition.
This year, we get a new club room because the old one is under maintenance.
We also have a new club president and club secretary.
Want to meet them?
Please step out and welcome our new members.
Hello. I'm just here to kick off the event,
so I'll skip the introduction.
I'm Tine.
I'm the club secretary.
IS HE THE ONE WHO GOT IN BECAUSE HE HAS CONNECTIONS?
HIS BOYFRIEND IS THE BOSS. THAT'S WHY.
Well, as for today…
-I think-- -Many of you might be thinking…
I'm here because of the connections I have.
That's true.
I didn't pass the audition.
I was accepted because I got some help.
At my first stage performance…
I couldn't even finish the song.
So I'm thinking it's not fair to all of you
if I become the secretary of this club.
So I'd like to ask from you…
one week for me to practice guitar,
and I will audition for this club again.
What?
As…
Long…
As long as I have…
You…
I have…
I don't want anything else
Tine, just stop.
I don't think it works.
Why?
Did Wat ask you guys to talk to me?
-No. -No.
-Really. -Really.
Fine.
He is worried about you,
so he asked us to talk you out of it.
Does he think I won't pass?
Not that.
He doesn't want you to care about those negative comments.
Look.
Don't care about what others think.
Just care about those who care about us.
Wow. As expected, from Fong the Philosopher.
Who said I cared about those comments? It's Sarawat that I care about.
I don't want anyone to talk behind his back that he's biased.
Tine speaks like a philosopher too.
Now I'm being left behind.
Who are you talking to?
Mil, you know what?
Of all the models we have built, this one is my favorite.
It sure is.
I designed it just the way you like it.
It's our home.
What do you mean?
You once asked me to open my mind.
I got the answer now.
Phukong.
-Phukong! -What?
I have the answer to your question. It's that the door is too large.
-The door is too large? -Yes.
-Let's make another one. -Here.
-Phukong. -What?
Why do you study architecture?
I guess I have a certain motivation.
Well, Mil.
-After we finish this model-- -Mil.
-The football court is available. -Oh.
Great. Let's go.
Can you take care of the rest? I don't think I can come back in time.
Hey. Hold on.
When you're done, keep it in my workshop room.
Here's the sandpaper.
-Let's go. -Okay.
When will I get to hear the answer?
Hey, Praw. About the song you like, I learned all the chords.
Really?
-Yes. I'll play it for you next time. -I can't wait.
Hi. You came so late.
Why are you here at this hour?
Well…
I came to borrow your guitar.
-You want to borrow my guitar? -Yes.
What for?
For playing a song
and recording a video, of course.
All right. Here.
Who are you hitting on?
No one. What are you talking about?
Really?
Really. I just want to record one to watch later.
I am your brother. You can talk to me.
It's nothing.
I just want to play.
-I'm thinking of writing a song too. -Yeah?
Not just recording a video, but also writing a song.
What is it about?
It's a song about…
someone whom we do everything for,
but we get brother-zoned in the end.
Are you really talking about the song?
Of course. What are you laughing at?
Are you aware you're so into the song?
Into what?
You seem so hurt. How about we open bottles and drink?
I can drink with you.
No. I'd better hurry back and write a song.
What are you doing anyway?
The club's budget paper.
-I'm the club president. Remember? -Yes.
Where's Tine?
He's practicing at the club.
He said he couldn't focus here.
It's so late already.
Is he still practicing?
Hey. You're home.
Yes.
I told you not to wait.
I'm not waiting for you.
I'm hungry, so I'm just filling my stomach.
Hungry?
You must be starving. You already had two cups.
Thank you.
How was your day? Did the practice go well?
I'm so tired. Look at my fingers.
They're worn out.
-Just like old times. -There, there.
How about this?
I'll let you grab some milk to relieve your tiredness.
How is that going to help?
I mean condensed milk, not my boobs.
You always have dirty thoughts.
-Unacceptable. -No, you are.
I'm pouring it.
Go ahead.
Thanks for the food.
Thanks.
-It's so good. -Of course it is.
Now that you've grabbed what's mine, it's my turn to grab yours.
Hey.
What?
-Here. Take this. -It's already mine. I want your boobs.
No way. I'm still tired from practice.
-I can give you a massage. -No.
-Come on. -No.
I've been taking care of your brother since he was this small.
-And now? -He's this big.
-Really? -Of course.
Hey.
-Why are you with these assholes? -Oh.
-We are assholes now. -Just you, I think.
I came here to return your guitar.
We're just having a little chat.
Your brother told me that these days, your boyfriend
demands you to turn clothes inside out before washing.
Don't believe anything he said.
Be on your way already.
Don't sit still. Come on. Go to class.
Go on.
Tell your friend to keep going.
Sure. If he succeeds, he will treat you guys to one big meal.
-Wow. -We'll look forward to that.
Of course.
-See you later. Bye now. -Good luck.
-Bye. -He didn't take the plate, this brat.
"Keep going"?
Just keep going.
Well, your brother asked us for love advice for his friend.
-His friend? -Right.
In short, his friend loves someone, but he doesn't love him back.
-Same old stuff. -Yes.
I don't think it's his friend's story. It's his.
He borrowed my guitar to write a love song the other day.
Huh?
He must have a crush on someone.
Could be a student from his faculty.
Those architecture folks, they're so hot.
Well…
Must be one of his seniors.
I went home the other day and heard him talking to someone on the phone.
When he saw me, he did this.
-He knocked on the table? -He hung up.
Oh.
I don't want him to get hurt. He's so clueless.
Before worrying about your little brother,
you should be worried about yourself.
Why?
Who's teaching Tine to play the guitar?
-He's playing on his own. -Well…
My friend walked by the Music Club the other day.
He heard Tine talking closely to someone.
They were practicing music together.
Not practicing by himself obviously.
It might be his friend. He has friends, doesn't he?
All right. That's good.
We're just afraid it might be someone else.
Imagine a late-night practice with just the two of them.
-Goodness. -I don't want to see that.
Wow.
-Can you teach me some? -My pleasure.
It's his friend. You guys are overthinking.
Hey.
-And then G. -Not so fast. I can't follow.
-It's C, right? -Yes.
Not G, but C.
What are you watching? Porn?
I'm not a pervert like you.
All right. I'm off to my guitar practice.
The food is on the table.
Wash the dishes when you're done.
You can practice here. I won't disturb you.
I'm not afraid of that. It's just…
I don't want to bother you.
I'm off now.
Don't wait for me.
I'll be late.
You can go to bed first.
See you.
Take care.
Can't sleep?
What?
You can't sleep?
No, I can't. You only let me eat a salad.
I'm starving right now.
Can I go grab something to eat?
No, you can't. Save it for breakfast.
Come on. Boiled eggs will do.
No. Get some sleep. I have a presentation tomorrow.
-Just boiled eggs? -Go to sleep.
What are you doing?
Well…
I'm hungry. I'm fixing myself something to eat.
Go ahead and curse me.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
It's just amusing that you're falling off the wagon. It's cute.
Aren't you mad at me?
I won't mind as long as you share it with me.
Okay.
Just wait for a bit.
-Hurry. -Sure.
-Done. -Wow.
What a cute dish.
These are heart-shaped.
-Let's eat. -Okay.
Here.
Oh, you're so fast.
You must be very hungry.
Feed me.
I cooked for you.
Do I have to feed you too?
Hmm.
I'm a good cook, aren't I? It's delicious.
It's good. May I have another bite?
-So tasty. -Enough.
Cook it yourself.
Come on.
You said you would share.
-Can I have some? -I'm hungry.
Let's share. Pretty please.
Hey!
Can I have some? No? Are you going to share or not?
-Hey. -Hey.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Here.
I'm returning Tine his notes.
He hasn't come back yet. He's still practicing.
Is that so?
I'll leave them with you, then.
Didn't you see him at all today? I thought he was practicing with you.
Are you nuts?
Do we look like we can play the guitar?
Then who is he with?
What are you watching?
Porn?
Didn't you see him at all today?
-I thought he was practicing with you. -Are you nuts?
Do we look like we can play the guitar?
Then who is he with?
My friend walked by the Music Club the other day.
He heard Tine talking closely to someone.
They were practicing music together.
Not practicing by himself obviously.
C.
A minor.
-And G. -Slowly. I can't remember.
-Okay. This is G. -G.
-What's this? -This is A minor. See?
Wrong. Start over.
That's wrong. Press harder.
Why don't you play it?
-Record it, will you? -Okay.
Here's the C chord.
Just play and think of yourself
as a rising star
who's been practicing very hard for your guitar solo,
and this is the scene where you have to play for a lot of people.
Everyone is clapping to your brilliant performance.
It's like a happy ending scene. Do you see it?
As long as I have you
You are all I ask for
Just you
I need nothing more
No matter
How cruel this world is
No matter how gloomy it is
With all the darkness
And sorrow
Though I have to go through
All difficulties in life
It seems unbearable
But it's fine
It's totally fine
Never, ever do I feel scared
Never, ever do I feel shaken By anything coming at me
As I'm ready to accept everything
As long as I have you
You are all I ask for
Just you
I need nothing more
Do you like acoustic or electric guitar?
An acoustic one because someone just bought me one.
Do you play any other instruments?
Bass, drums, Electone, and ukulele.
Is there anything you can't do?
How to be a club secretary.
Your fingers are ruined. You should've let me teach you.
I wanted to do it myself.
Was I good?
-Did you like my performance? -No, I didn't.
Come on.
You should've let me help.
But I pulled it off, didn't I?
-People were clapping for me. -Yes. You did great.
-Are you happy now? -Yes.
Fingers.
Will you marry me?
Having me as a secretary is not enough?
I want you to be my partner.
Many people have warned me not to work with someone I love
since duties might put us in difficult situations.
But I want to try.
We might have conflicts,
but it can help us understand each other more.
More importantly,
no one can stand the craziness of this club president like I can.
Subtitle translation by: Peeraya Moonjun