Do you want me to grab your boobs…
2 WEEKS BEFORE THE 2U EVENT
…or knock you out with a kiss?
Knock me out with a kiss?
I've heard that countless times, and I haven't been knocked out once.
Is that a challenge?
Yes.
Since you ask for it…
I shall grant it to you.
Wat, I'm here to pick you up.
I have to go.
Just call me when you have time.
Even if I don't have time, I will.
Get the door for me.
I see that I'm very welcome here.
-Hey. -I'm out now.
See you.
Want some help with that?
Take care of him for me, Dim.
Don't worry.
-I'll do my best. -I'm sure I'm in the wrong hands.
What did you just say, Wat? I can take care of you just fine.
Stop with that sad-ass face. What's wrong?
Who would have thought
that my first relationship would become a long-distance one?
Damn.
Sathorn and Ladprao? Is this your definition of long-distance?
Unbelievable. Ladprao is not Las Vegas.
But I miss him.
We see each other every day.
He's not in the mood.
Wow.
Is this really your house, Dim?
Make yourselves at home.
Pay respects to my house spirits too.
-Okay. -Look.
-What? -This is the yard Green told us about.
Really?
-Right here. -It's hardcore.
-They did it outdoors. -Right here what?
-Nothing. We're talking about dogs. -Yes.
It's nothing.
Let's go inside, you assholes.
I don't have dogs, by the way.
-In front of the house spirit shrine? -Damn.
Yuck. Stop it already.
-Did they really do it here? -The gate is always closed, you know.
We know.
Let's go.
-Someone can climb anyway. -They weren't ashamed.
-Damn. -Wow.
They're all new.
I've set up this room for you to practice for fun.
For fun?
Why didn't you take us here in the first place?
-These instruments are not mine. -What?
I borrowed them all.
This electric guitar belongs to Jennie.
Damn. It's a legendary guitar.
-Let's take a selfie, guys. -Sure. This is cool stuff.
-Let's capture the memory. -Yes, we must.
Come here. Let's make memories together.
Wat, come here.
-This is the last chance. -I see.
-Take a snap. -What?
Are you done?
What now?
-I'll keep it for you. -Why?
Good musicians must focus on their music.
If I don't do this, you will chat with your partners all day.
Hey.
I'll take care of your phones for you. Give them to me. Don't argue.
-What if my mom calls? -I'll pick up for you, Non.
Wat, come on.
Don't buy your time.
Give it to me. Now.
Everyone is waiting.
-I'm an exception because I am single. -Really?
But you're on TikTok every day. I'm following you.
Ms. TikTok Star.
Give it to me.
Seriously?
-Quickly. -Fine.
When will we get them back?
After practice, of course.
-You mean today? -No.
After this schedule is completed. After two weeks.
-What? -Really?
This is your practice schedule.
Hold on.
Do we even have breaks?
-Are we allowed to eat? -Oh, god.
We don't have any days off. Isn't it too tough?
-Right. -Will we be able to do it?
If you guys can't do it, then quit.
Go home.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Go ahead. I'll return these musical instruments.
Okay. Fine. We'll do it.
-We'll follow the schedule. -Are you sure?
-Yes. -Yes.
-Good. I'll lock the house. -Lock the house?
Then you all can start practicing.
-Do you need to do that? -Of course.
-For two weeks? -Yes.
-How are we going to eat? -I'll bring you food.
-One, two, three. -It doesn't matter
Who is in your heart
As long as you
Look my way
Non, you're not consistent. The beat goes up and down.
Sorry. Let's do it again.
All right. Try again. Go.
One…
It doesn't matter who is in your heart
As long as you look my way
Non, you're too slow.
Go and practice your strokes without the drums.
Boom. Your bass didn't go well with the drum pedal.
Listen to more songs and learn the basics carefully.
Wat, you're fine, but you just couldn't concentrate.
Put on some light music and calm your mind.
As for you, Earn, you made lots of mistakes.
Ask Wat for help. He could be your teacher.
You're good, Temp.
You can sing now.
Sing with who?
You shooed them all away.
They will be back. Just wait until they're okay.
That's all for today.
I'll see you again tomorrow.
-Our phones? -Right.
You did poorly today. How dare you ask for your phones?
I'm not giving you anything.
Come on.
Right.
All men sleep in the same room.
Earn, you sleep in my room.
No way. Who wants to sleep in your room?
How can I contact Tine?
-And my mom? -What about my TikTok?
-Can I call Tine, please? -Mommy.
Take care of yourself.
Well, well…
Sarawat, when you're done flirting with your man,
turn the light off for us.
Everyone is sleeping now.
You go to bed.
-Turn the light off. -Okay.
See you soon.
Will you all get back inside?
-We're just going to get some beer. -I have plenty inside.
Hey.
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Can I hug you?
Good night.
Night.
Get some sleep.
-Is he all right? -I don't know.
I think he's losing it.
Guys, hurry up.
We need to learn all the songs tonight.
We finished just now.
Quickly, Non.
You're the slowest one.
Temp, why don't you eat?
I've been having heartburn since last night.
Then you'll say you're sick. Am I right?
I'm feeling sick.
See? You just want to slack off.
-Did you guys plan this together? -We didn't.
Hey.
-Temp. -Temp.
Are you okay, Temp?
Hey.
-Are you really sick? -Nice acting.
Don't use this trick.
-You're wasting time. -Drink some water.
-Are you all right? -I don't think so.
-Not good. -Dim, he's not faking it.
I think he's sick.
Fine.
You guys continue your practice here. Temp, can you walk?
I can.
Come. I'll take you to the hospital.
You all must practice. Don't ever goof off.
-Sure. -Let's go.
-Please take care of him. -Okay.
Hey, guys.
Dim's gone. What should we do now?
I have two hours. I can make it.
-Where are you going? -I'm going to see Tine.
No, you can't.
Someone needs to go with you, otherwise you won't come back.
-Wait for me here. -Hurry.
-Let me get my bag. -You stay here.
It's nice. Is this your new place?
Yes, we just moved in.
Slow down. Tine won't go anywhere.
We're running out of time. I miss him to death.
When it comes to your boyfriend, you're very active. Damn you.
Tine!
Tine? Where are you?
Tine.
His laptop is here.
Where has he gone to?
He's not here, Earn.
What do we do now? Should we go back?
What a crappy guy. Why is it so hard to say?
You have dragged me to this point…
where I'm talking to your doll all alone.
When you were around,
all I did was nag,
but you always did something that bugged me.
You didn't turn your clothes inside out.
You liked to steal my stuff,
and you wanted to grab my boobs all the time.
Now that you're not here,
you know, I'd let you do anything to me…
in exchange for you coming back.
Just like you said…
I must be patient.
I must be strong.
I'll wait until this event is over.
I'll wait until we meet again.
But there's something I want to tell you.
I miss you so bad, Wat.
Hey.
We should go.
Come on.
I miss you so much too, Tine.
I didn't know you had a romantic side.
Why?
-Of course I do. -All right.
All you wanted was to see his face.
What a whipped boy.
Tine is trying his best to be patient.
I'll do the same.
Good.
At least the distance…
makes our longing for each other more worthwhile.
Damn.
Is that your new song?
You just love Tine so much, don't you?
Isn't it normal?
No. I don't think so.
Let's suppose…
Let's say I like girls.
I don't know if I'd be open like you.
It isn't about being open or not.
We're just two people who love each other.
Just like other couples.
It's not about courage.
It's all about love.
I guess you're right.
It's up to the ones loving each other.
It's their call if they want to be open or not.
-Exactly. -Right.
You got it right.
Where's Temp?
We have a problem.
He has gastritis and was admitted to the hospital.
But…
The contest is two days away.
You be the front man.
I'll find a new guitarist.
What?
Hey.
2U TRADITIONAL FOOTBALL MATCH DAY
Guys, don't be nervous.
Take it as a normal event we've attended.
Well…
Is this the building?
It is.
Come on, Tine.
You just told them not to be nervous.
You seem more nervous than they are.
I'm trying to keep cool,
but it's the biggest event for me as the club president.
I'm just hoping for the best.
Don't worry.
You can do it, Tine.
-Good luck. I'm rooting for you. -Come on.
You've been hugging me a lot lately.
Shut up. By the way, Pear…
I think we should do this.
SPECIAL GUEST: SCRUBB
Tine, what are you doing?
Oh, it's nothing.
Right.
About that day, I'm so sorry I yelled at you.
It's all good.
I know you did your best for the club. No hard feelings.
Have you eaten anything?
Did you get enough sleep? Will you be okay?
I'm good.
Tine.
Just so you know, I'm not wearing heavy makeup today.
Sure. I'll tell the makeup artist to put on light makeup for you.
-Really? -But you look good wearing a heavy one.
Thanks.
It's like taking a speed boat.
Hurry up.
This event is surely big.
I'll play to my heart's content.
Are you looking for Tine?
Your boyfriend is in that club too. Aren't you going to wish him good luck?
Watch your mouth. I don't have a boyfriend.
And where is our last member?
Oh.
He's sleeping.
Hey! Wake up.
Sorry.
Let's go.
-Hi there, Man. -Type.
Jib let us print any name on the jersey. Take a look.
Here.
Did you see it? It's you.
Look. Isn't it cute?
It's "Duper White."
Who is Jib?
Can you just pay attention to my jersey here? Look.
Did you see it?
Yes, I did.
Who on earth is Jib?
Type, my jersey is the point here.
I have a meeting soon.
You must tell me who Jib is when I get back.
Type, wait. What's with him?
I showed him my jersey. Why did he keep asking who Jib was?
-What's on your jersey? "Duper White"? -Cool.
Lame. Mine is better.
Did you have "Dr. Pear" printed on it?
That'd be too simple.
-What? -Look.
I printed her cute nickname.
Three syllables.
Dear Doctor?
-No. It's too basic. -What?
It's Cute Doctor.
That's nice.
Just wait and see.
I'm coming.
Great. You'll blow her mind today.
It'd be a bit tight.
-Guys, your food is here. Let's eat. -Great.
The food arrives.
Take one.
-It looks good. -Hurry.
Wait a moment.
Don't eat too much. You might get side stitches.
We have to be on the field around 12:45.
-Got it. -Sure.
What's on the menu?
Okay, Mil.
I'll be there shortly.
-Phukong. -Yes?
Aren't you going to eat?
I'm not really hungry.
Right.
Tine.
If we're all set now,
can I stop by the Music Club for a bit?
Are you going to see Wat?
Right. I'm going to see my brother.
Who else could it be?
I want to go with you,
but I have the final rehearsal with people on the bleachers.
Well…
Oh.
One moment.
Here.
Can you take this to Wat for me?
-What is this? Can I look at it? -No.
What?
It's for Wat, not you.
Can't I just take a peek?
No, it's for Wat.
You're being possessive.
I'm his brother.
-Take it to him. -Okay.
-See you later. -See you.
-Thanks. -Sure.
Dim, can I see Boom?
Anything urgent?
If you want to give him anything,
leave it with me. I'll give it to him.
Damn.
I just want to see my boyfriend. Why are you such a love blocker?
You can't eat this. You're being a jerk because you fought with your boyfriend.
Watch your mouth, or I'll eat them all.
-Damn you. -Stop it.
Dim.
Is Mil here?
Why? Are you his boyfriend?
No, I'm not. Someone wanted me to give this to him.
I'm just kidding.
You two will never be a thing.
I'll get him for you.
-Mil. -Yes?
-Sarawat's brother wants to see you. -Phukong?
Yes.
What's the matter?
I don't know. He's here to see you.
I'm going to have lunch.
It's your watch now. Don't let the lovebirds see each other.
-Just like I did earlier. -I see. Okay.
My eyes are like scanners.
-I can tell who's dating who. -Right.
-You're a genius. -I know.
-Have a seat. -Okay.
Here.
Tine wants to give this to Wat.
Can you give it to him?
What about mine?
That's all I'm here for.
Really?
But I can smell crispy pork with kale.
Well…
You're as good as a dog.
Are you picking on me?
No.
Here.
I got it right.
Thanks.
Is that all?
All I get is "thanks"?
Here.
I told you many times, this is the brother zone.
Why don't you remember?
I'm going to kick your ass.
Come on.
Are you happy now?
Yes.
You're not wearing much makeup today. You look good.
If I did, someone would need to clean it for me.
There's something in your hair.
There.
Right there. I got it for you.
All right.
You can go now. I'll see you later.
-See you. -See you.
-Dim, bye now. -Bye.
What is it?
Well, I didn't know brothers would pat each other's heads.
Well… There was something in his hair. That's all.
I see.
-We're like brothers. -Brothers?
I can pat your head too.
Brothers. I see…
Mil, you little…
I'm sorry, bro.
Wat. Here.
It's from Tine.
Thank you.
Why did you agree to be our guitarist?
If this was last year, I wouldn't do it,
but everything has changed now.
A good drink will make you fresh and give you energy on stage.
Wat. Sorry, I'm so busy
that I can't bring this to you myself.
I cooked this because you mentioned it all the time.
This chicken green curry from Chef Tine is full of love.
When the cheerleading contest is over, I'll be there supporting you.
I miss you.
Hey.
Your food looks kind of special.
Well…
It's the new menu from a nearby restaurant.
Just what I thought.
It's their special lunchbox to boost sales, right?
It looks good, though.
When you guys do the soundcheck, do it slowly.
Do not rush it, okay?
It's refreshing.
I'll stand by near the stage and help you get it right.
-This is the best. -We still have time.
-I'll stand by near the stage. -We're going to win.
And I'll help you get it right.
-Look at me. -We did great last year.
-I'll guide you with the volume. -This year will be better.
Green, you lead them to the field.
Wat, do you understand?
Okay. Look.
Hold your drumsticks tight.
Good luck.
Good luck!
Good luck to you too!
Wat.
Thank you.
Wat, hurry up.
We're running out of time.
Tine!
Let's go.
Wat. Come on.
2U TRADITIONAL FOOTBALL MATCH 17
Hello, everyone!
Welcome to 2U,
the 17th Traditional Football and Music Day.
Apart from the fun football match to watch, there's another highlight.
Which is?
The cheerleading contest, of course.
They are super gorgeous.
I saw the cheerleaders in the purple costumes. They're great.
-What is great? -The cheerleaders.
They are breathtaking.
I think just the same.
Look at them.
-They're so natural. -Be serious.
We're about to play now.
Hey, Boss.
Yes?
That's Pear, your Dr. Pear.
-Oh, that's your beloved doctor. -Shut it.
I'll wait until the match is over.
-It's your chance, man. -No!
-It's now or never. Pear! -Don't.
Go ahead.
Pear!
Pear.
Yes?
We're allowed to print the names of someone we like on the jerseys.
-Pear, look at Boss's shirt. -Where?
Here.
"Cute Piggy"?
-What? -Who do you have a crush on?
It's really "Cute Piggy," man.
That's cute.
They spelled it wrong.
I'm going to check out the cheerleading team.
Bye, guys. Good luck to both of you.
-Good luck. -Good luck.
Let me check your costumes.
Let me see.
There, there. Don't cry.
I shouldn't have encouraged you.
2U TRADITIONAL FOOTBALL MATCH 17
When this band is done, you can proceed with the soundcheck.
Is it okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Hey.
I heard your band changed the vocalist.
That's good.
When you lose, it's on you. No excuses.
Stop barking.
Keep your mouth shut and just sing, dumbass.
Let's go, Wat.
Okay, guys. Let's gather around.
Come.
We've practiced for so long just for this event.
These past two weeks,
I know you guys have condemned me silently,
but it's nothing compared to what I've carried for two years.
Forget all the struggles we had. Just go out there and do your best.
I admit that, at first, I just wanted to get
what I missed last time.
But spending time with you for two weeks gave me a new idea.
No matter what happens, smile away.
Just play it with your heart.
No matter what the result is, I'll be happy with it.
-Are you ready? -Ready!
One, two, three.
-Ctrl S! -Ready.
Ready!
Boss, you can do it!
I will do everything
I will try every possible way
It makes me know
How we are going to be
It doesn't matter who you like
Just look at me
That's all That's all it takes to make me happy
I don't care who you like
It doesn't matter what the reality is
All I know is that you are the one
In my heart
The referee just blew his whistle to end the first half.
-What happened? -They're now tied at 1-1.
We will see who wins this game in the second half.
-Let's take a break here. -Sure.
You can use the toilet in the meantime.
Come back again for the second half.
Damn it.
Is the contest over? We came to see your team compete.
It isn't. We've just reached halftime.
I just saw Dim earlier.
He said his band is about to perform too.
What are you going to do?
Too bad the football match started late.
I'm not sure I can make it there on time.
Tine.
You can go and support Wat.
I can take care of things for you here.
It's all right. Don't worry about me.
Just do the best you can.
I will do my best here as well.
-Hey. -It's fine.
You sound cooler than Fong now.
Is this possible?
You're so cool.
Right.
Fong. Ohm.
You two should go and see Wat.
-Us? -Right. I'll catch up with you later. Go.
Thanks, guys.
-Go ahead. -Okay.
Let's go.
That one with the Duper White jersey is as good as a Japanese player.
-They're neck and neck. -Of course.
There are three minutes left.
-Right. -If they still tie, it's going to be fun.
-How so? -We'll need to go for extra time.
Boss, you can do it!
It's number two, Cute Piggy. He has the ball.
-He speeds up and runs to the goal. -Yes.
He shook one player off.
-He went on and shook another off. -Wow.
He's now in the penalty area.
And he just got tackled there.
-Will the referee give a yellow card? -I think so.
There's a call for a penalty kick towards the end of the game.
Goodness.
A penalty kick!
-Right now, we only have one minute left. -Yes.
If he can make it, we sure have the winner of this game.
But if he can't, we'll need extra time.
This kick will decide the result.
-Goal. -Goal.
And…
With you
-Awesome. -Hey.
This is our last song.
Do your best.
When will Tine come?
I'm so happy to be here again today.
I was here once, looking for someone,
but I didn't find him.
He's also here today,
but I don't think he can make it on time.
That's okay, though.
No matter how far apart we are,
we always feel close to each other.
This song is called "Together."
GLOWING BRIGHT
Walking past people They were merely strangers
This was how I felt Whenever I looked at them
Every time
All the time
Looking back into the memories I had
There used to be just me The only one I knew there was me
Always me
Time used to be nothing more than a breeze
But a person has made my time
Become more meaningful
A person has changed
Everything in my life
That person can make me smile
No matter how sad I am
You are that person Who has changed my view on love
I may not totally understand why
Maybe we are meant to be together
Thank you.
They all forgot about me.
Here.
How is your leg? Does it still hurt?
A lot, actually.
I can't feel my knee.
How are you going to get home in this condition?
Well…
I don't know.
I don't think I can go by myself.
Well, how about…
I call a cab for you?
A taxi.
-A taxi? -Yes.
I'm willing to help.
Good idea.
Okay. One moment.
And the winner of this year's 2U Music Contest is…
-Ctrl S! -Is…
-Back Off! -The winner is…
-Ctrl S! -The winner is…
Back Off!
And the winner is…
Ctrl S!
Congratulations to Ctrl S.
Give it up for them, guys.
Type.
Look. Am I cool?
I scored the winning goal.
Can you tell me now who Jib is?
Not again.
She is a staff member of the football team.
Pay attention to me. I just won a big game.
I know. I was just teasing you.
What reward do you want most?
I don't want any reward.
I just want you to see the goal medal yourself.
-Okay, then. -There you are.
You came at the last minute, Tine.
I ran as fast as I could.
Hey.
Thanks for your support today.
You too, Ohm.
See you. Bye.
Bye.
-What are we going to eat? -How about hotpot?
She just thanked me.
But she touched my arm.
She looked into my eyes.
But she grabbed my shoulder. She likes me.
-Are you sure? -Yes.
What's with you guys?
She likes me. You can ask Tine. Do you agree with me, Tine?
She likes me.
Are you free this Saturday?
-You're tricking me into building a model? -No, to see a movie.
-Really? -Yes.
It's my turn to play hard-to-get.
So this is how you're going to be?
What a perfect day. Our cheerleading team and band won.
-Bye. -Bye. See you.
See you later, kids.
Where should we celebrate?
-At the pub? Are we going to dance again? -Sure.
How about Thong Lor?
The band is going to celebrate at Jae Tun's tonight.
If you guys don't have plans,
you can come and join us.
Are you just saying that or what?
I can go, but I get to make the call about that thing.
Again? That thing again?
No way!
Then get lost.
Guys, let's throw our own party.
Bye!
What are you looking at?
Why did you tag me when you posted a picture of yourself?
Who told you it's just me? It's a picture of us.
A picture of us?
I somehow got the familiar vibe being here.
So I looked it up in my gallery.
I didn't expect I would find a familiar face in there.
Is that me?
Me?
That means…
the guy I saw at that concert was you.
Thank you for looking for me.
Thank you for coming back to me.
You looked so hot that day.
I look much hotter now.
I saw you from behind back then.
What a shame. The other band performs the last act tonight.
If today was that day,
we'd get to hear Scrubb songs again.
You can hear it tonight.
Again?
Same old trick.
It always works, though.
Your ear, please.
Thanks.
I think I get it now.
What?
Do you want to know?
Come closer.
Damn you.
There are many people around here.
Where are they?
-I saw no one. -They're all inside.
I'll just show them this.
But no one saw us.
You're unbelievable.
Are you blushing?
No.
I now get
how good it is to have you by my side.
Two years ago, we bumped into each other.
Last year, we waved our hands at a concert together.
This year, we stand next to one another.
The years to come… It can be anywhere as long as we're together.
Subtitle translation by: Peeraya Moonjun