There it is, our stage.
Do you guys have anything to say
before we go inside?
Like what?
Whatever you want to get off your chest.
I think I do.
WEDNESDAY, 16 FEBRUARY 2000
Don't let anyone wrap their arms
Around these shoulders
Don't let anyone hold these hands
Just think of me as a cat
Who is so easy to take care of
I'll be waiting around for you
To see how cute I am
I was born looking Chinese
You don't like it, right?
That's too bad
I look Chinese, so what?
Very good! Okay, you get full marks.
Please go back to your seat.
Who's next? Who wants to sing next?
Let's see. Have you prepared a song?
SINGING CLASS
If you can't think of one,
just sing the alphabet.
Who did that?
Koong! You did it!
"I just want to see your face.
Your face."
Hey.
Tuang, Koong, what's going on?
-What?
-Koong threw a paper ball at me.
"Your face."
Koong...
What did you say?
No!
"I just want to see your face."
You threw it, right?
Tuang.
Tossapol.
You're a big boy now,
but you can't even sing a song?
Come on! Just sing!
I just want to see your face
All right. You can go back to your seat.
Okay.
Since you're mouthing lyrics
to your friend,
you're going to sing next, Earn.
What the hell was that?
I don't love you that much
I just want to see your face
I don't like you that much
I don't miss you that much
I just want to see your face
That's all
We're just neighbors and nothing more
Nothing more, that's all
I just want to see your face, that's all
That's all
Koong, can I ask you something?
What kind of song is this?
JUST WANT TO SEE YOUR FACE
You asked the right person.
It's a rock song.
So how are rock songs like?
Rock songs are fast.
I see.
But what if the song is slow?
If the song is slow, it is a love song.
So rock songs and love songs
are the only two kinds of songs, right?
No, there are two kinds,
but they're either from RS or Grammy.
If you don't believe me,
listen to the radio.
The songs will be either one of the two.
What about country music?
Thai classical
and Northeastern-style songs?
Are they fast?
If so, then they are rock songs.
That's bullshit!
Bullshit!
This is none of your business, Kay!
Mom is here.
I'm leaving.
Tossapol.
You're free, right?
Earn!
What's up, Ped?
Your grandma is here.
I was asked to come and get you.
Okay.
Hey, Earn.
Your family sells
music cassette tapes, right?
You must have lots of music
to listen to, then.
Yes.
That's so cool.
But I don't want to sell cassette tapes.
Actually, I want to be a singer,
so I can release my own album
and sell it at my shop.
Really?
Your customers will probably think
it's funny
that the person selling the tapes
looks like the artist on the cover.
So why do you like listening to music?
I don't know.
When I listen to music,
I lose myself in it.
I guess it's like having company.
Listen to this.
Before the sky clears up
Before the warmth of the sunlight
Before the flowers bloom
Before your sweet dreams
You can feel it, right?
Yes.
Earn, your grandma is here.
Okay.
Oh, Ped.
This tape has the song
I was trying to tell you this morning.
Listen to it.
I would like to hear you sing that song.
-Goodbye. Be safe.
-Goodbye.
Bye.
Earn!
When do you want the tape back?
Before this Saturday.
I'm moving to Bangkok soon. See you.
My heart and my soul belong to you
I promise that for the rest of my life
I will be here to fight for you
My heart belonged to no one
Until your love came into my life
Now, I see everything
So brightly and clearly
I never had someone to call my own
Until your love gave me
The strength to live on
My heart belonged to no one
Until your love came into my life
Now, I see everything
So brightly and clearly
I never had someone to call my own
Until your love gave me
The strength to live on
What's going on?
It's loud enough to bring the house down.
Why didn't you take off your shoes?
Look, you've stained your sheets!
Go and take a shower now.
It's time for dinner.
Then do your homework after.
Come down now.
PAWNSHOP
This is heaven on earth
For you to rest and sleep
Hello, ma'am.
Don't look back
What happened to your face?
Don't mind it.
Anyway, what's up?
Oh, I want to borrow
your guitar and songbook.
What do you need them for?
I thought you looked cool
when I saw you playing,
so I want to play too.
Okay.
You can borrow it.
I'm sick of a person here
who's trying to copy me all the time.
I don't love you that much
I just want to see your face
I don't like you that much
I don't miss you that much
I just want to see your face, that's all
DIAMOND SOUND
I don't love you that much
I don't like you that much
I just want to see your face
May I please speak to Earn?
Earn?
She is already asleep.
Don't you know what time it is?
It's bedtime.
I'm sorry.
When you call someone next time,
be sure to remember your manners.
By the way, who is this?
Who is this?
It's Koong, sir.
Koong?
Koong, it's already late.
We're about to sleep.
Next time, don't call this late again.
You're late.
How can I not love you?
If I can't love you
What is the use of having a heart?
Good job!
Very good.
Who's next?
Tuang, you're next.
I would like to dedicate this song
to the newest couple in our class.
Bang Earn! Bang Earn!
Bang Earn! I'm here
Can you hear me?
-Ped.
-What?
Koong likes Earn. Spread the word.
I'm just really down to earth!
Bang Earn! Bang Earn!
Bang Earn and Koong!
Koong likes Earn!
You got it all wrong. It's not true.
-We're just friends!
-Koong likes Earn!
You got it all wrong. It's not true.
Koong, I don't want anyone to like me
and I don't like it
when people do stupid things.
You got it all wrong. It wasn't me.
-What?
-Then who was it?
It's not me. You've all got it wrong.
It's not me.
It's not true.
Hey, no. It's not true. It's someone else.
Bangkok, really?
You believe me, right?
That I didn't call Earn?
Yes.
Let's go home.
Let's go, Ped.
So often that my heart
Koong, where are you going?
I'm going to practice playing the guitar!
I will learn all the songs this summer!
I cry
For no reason
I am lost
Among all the people and chaos
I look for you and find no one
Since you walked away
20 MAY 2006
FAREWELL CHETTU CLASS 46
Summer is not the same without you
I look at the sky
Ped, I don't see any hotties.
Did you check the front of the stage?
Summer is not the same without you
You're so cool!
Let's go!
Thank you, everyone,
for having fun with us here tonight.
I would like to thank Kay as well.
-Where do we go next, Koong?
-I don't know.
Hey, look at that girl.
Which one?
That one.
Is she cute?
CHETTUPONBURANA SCHOOL
I would like to place a card here.
My turn is over.
Did you hear about the new student?
She's in Class Two.
She transferred in her last year.
Yes, and she's cute, too!
The new semester just started
and you're already messing around?
Don't you want to see who the new girl is?
Can't you see what I'm doing right now?
Don't talk to me.
You are a senior,
yet you still play cards.
You don't know anything.
It's the era of card games now.
I guarantee that you'll be stunned
when you see her.
I'll smack your head if I'm not.
She is the girl
I told you about the other day.
Earn.
Ped
Tossapol Angkasetwittayakom
from Class One in sixth grade.
You still remember him?
What about this guy? Do you remember him?
He's the one who played
the guitar at the party, right?
I was there, too. It was awesome.
No, that was Kay, his twin brother.
This is Koong, the guy everyone teased
for liking you, which made you upset.
Bang Earn! Bang Earn!
Oh, I remember now.
And this guy sang...
Hey!
Gosh, you still remember that!
Oh, I have to go.
I'll talk to you guys later.
Earn has grown up to be quite cute!
What kind of girl grows up to be so cute?
Everyone says she is really cute
What kind of girl grows prettier
The more you look at her?
The more I look, the prettier you get
Your beauty has no mercy
What kind of girl grows up to be so cute?
Why are you so beautiful?
Everyone says she is really cute
The more I look, the more stunning she is
What kind of girl grows prettier
The more you look at her?
Why are you so beautiful?
The more I look, the prettier you get
Your beauty has no mercy
With every glance, you get prettier
I've been thinking all night.
I think we should form our own band.
What about your cards?
Card games are out.
It's now the era of music bands.
Do you realize how many times
you went from one thing to another?
It's now the era of the yo-yo.
Damn, yo-yos are lame now.
Hey, Ped!
The era of roller blades is coming!
Hey, why can't I get up?
The era of roller blades is over.
I think this is the year for dancers.
But I'm serious about this era.
This is my guitar pick.
You'll play the bass, okay?
I'll pass.
You know, girls love bass players.
You see that guy who's playing basketball?
He will be our drummer.
His name is Ex.
Just by listening
to how he dribbles the ball,
I can tell that he is really skillful.
Look.
He springs off his feet.
When he steps on the bass pedal,
it trembles.
Look at his powerful wrists.
He can pound the drums really hard!
Gosh! Look!
Judging from how he plays,
he must be a drummer who is...
-Shit!
I think we should wait until Ex recovers
before we start practicing.
It's too late.
Attention, all students.
This Saturday, June 10th,
will be the debut concert
of the band Koong and Friend
at the first floor of Kad Suan Kaew
Central Mall at 3 p.m.
The band is composed of Koong and Ped
from Class Three, and Ex from Class Four.
Koong would like to inform everyone
that it will be an awesome event.
It will definitely be a wild party
where you can scream and let loose!
We can't let our fans down.
It's him instead of me
You just have to pluck the top string.
When you pluck the string,
just keep following this rhythm, okay?
-You have one hour, okay?
-Okay.
One. Two. Three. Four.
Okay?
Koong and Friend, ready!
Three. Two. One.
Why the hell did you take your shirt off?
I'm thirsty. I'll grab a Pepsi.
-Hey, get me some snacks, too.
-Okay.
-What about mine?
-What?
-I'm hungry.
-Here you go.
Three. Two. One.
Hey, wait. I got goosebumps.
Hey, no need to be nervous.
No, I need to take a shit!
Sorry, it's the cast.
Taking my pants off took a while.
Hello, Mom. I'm really busy now.
Why don't you tell Kay to buy it?
Soy sauce?
Which kind? What's the difference
between number one and five?
I've turned my mobile phone off.
Turn off yours, too. Such a waste of time.
Hey, Ped. Hurry up!
Koong and Friend, ready! Three. Two. One.
Time is up, guys.
Hey.
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
TEACHING SKILLS FOR JUNIOR ART MASTER
Hello, everyone.
Today, we will have Koong and Friend
from Chettuponburana High School
to play for us.
Please raise your hands
if you want to hear them.
Very good.
Please give them a big round of applause
as they kick off with "Busaba."
My name is Busaba
Busaba's birth came with joy
Her world is filled with blossoms
In her heart
Every day, she makes beautiful garlands
The world is beautiful due to her garlands
-Not "Busaba" by Nicole Theriault?
-No, not that one.
Various colors and types of flowers
And the smell is so tempting
Decorate this world and make it beautiful
It's blood!
She makes her garlands with all her heart
Always and every day
Never tired of making garlands
Hey, let go of me!
So lame.
How was it, Koong and Friend?
Oh, you look upset.
I better talk to Koong.
I heard that Hotwave Music Awards
will be accepting applications soon,
so will Koong and Friend apply?
Music is not for competition.
It's for making kids cry, right?
Right?
Let's go.
Where are you going? Don't be mad.
The band is upset now.
Hey, are you mad? Damn it!
You're mad at me?
When will we get to practice again?
I don't know. I'm starting to get bored.
Just an arm's length apart
But I feel so far away
You are like my best friend
So I can't risk telling you
Just an arm's length apart
But I feel so far away
You are like my best friend
So I can't risk telling you
That I love you
Tell Ex to meet us in the music room.
I told you, music isn't for competing.
It's for flirting with girls!
Sorry, I got carried away.
Amazing!
You should have told me you're this good,
so I could invite you to join the band.
Like at the Art Master event?
Hey, I think you guys really rocked there.
I could feel the vibe.
Hey, you've got good taste.
You can really see talent.
See, I told you. We're cool!
Hey, the school band will practice here,
so stop playing now.
Kay.
Didn't your band break up already?
Yes, this is my new band.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
We have to practice
for the Hotwave Music Awards.
If you guys just do this for fun,
then please play somewhere else.
We're not doing this for fun.
We're competing as well.
Are you?
Surprised, aren't you?
Now,
we have a really talented guitarist.
Your band can't compete with her.
Let's go practice somewhere else.
Let the amateurs play here.
Wait!
Where are you going?
Oh, Mr. Surakiat asked me
to film Kay's new band.
What do you know about them?
Tell me everything.
Sure, listen.
After the senior band members graduated,
Kay started to gather
all the best musicians in our batch.
It started with the best bass player,
Ratchamung!
PLUCKING
Then came the drummer
who can hit like thunder, hence the name,
Dome Thunder.
BANGING
The lead singer with a high-powered voice
goes by the name
Tem Impact.
SHATTERING
And their guitarist,
Kay, who can make the audience cry.
SCREAM
They formed the band known as The Arena.
I think he reads too many comics.
Hey, Koong.
I think we shouldn't join the contest.
What the hell?
Why do we have to be scared of them?
We've already got Earn.
Wait a minute. Did you even ask her
if she wants to be in it?
I'm in.
When I was in Bangkok, I was in a band
that competed in the Hotwave Music Awards.
It's the biggest contest
for high school students.
The band that makes it to the final
might get to release their own album.
But my band didn't make it.
When I found out
that we had to move back here,
I accepted the fact that I won't be able
to compete this year.
But when Koong invited me,
I became hopeful again.
No worries, Earn.
When Ex gets better,
we will practice really hard
and make it to the final round together.
He just told me
that he is already bored with it.
What?
-Nothing.
I'm leaving.
Let's pack up and go home.
What did you say?
-We're all booked.
-What?
All booked?
Let's go to my family's bakery.
-Is Dad here?
-He's gone out.
Hey, are you taking us to Bakery Music?
Yes, something like that.
Where is your drum set?
It's somewhere here.
I think this place will do.
Only you
If you look deep into my heart
There is only you
Time stops for you
You ignite my soul with passion
You break my heart in the blink of an eye
Just looking at you
Takes my heart away
My love has blossomed
During the time that has passed
If tonight, I have only you
Hold my hand, my heart quivers
There is only me and my love for you
I will love you forever with all my heart
Only you
Please let me stand by your side
At this moment, there is only you
Who is dancing with me
I think Earn made our band cooler.
Don't be silly.
The contest rules say
that all bands must play
one original composition.
How do we start writing a song?
Ped, can you write one?
No, I don't know how.
Yes, you do. You won a prize
for song composition in second grade.
Gosh, that was for a poem.
Shit!
"The song must be a love song
without the word 'love'."
A LOVE SONG WITHOUT THE WORD "LOVE"
How can it be a love song, then?
I don't think it will be hard.
All we need is to be in love to write one.
But I'm not in love.
So you didn't like me back in sixth grade?
What is with the two of you?
Tell me.
Well, back then...
Hey, don't interrupt.
Go on.
Back then, everyone thought
that Koong had a crush on me,
but it was just Tuang
who started the rumor.
-So what happened?
-One night,
someone called me really late
and said his name was Koong.
Hey, Ped. Why are you playing it now?
But, really, I wasn't the guy
who called you that night.
So, I'm sorry
for accusing you back then.
No worries.
That was a long time ago.
Earn.
By the way, do you have a boyfriend?
Why did you ask?
If you are in love,
then you can write a love song.
No, not yet.
Aren't you a lesbian?
You're crazy.
I just asked
since you seem to be quite the tomboy.
What about you, Ped?
Do you have someone you like?
Ped? No way.
How do you know?
Ever since I've known him,
he has never hit on a girl.
Are you sure?
Yes, I haven't had a crush yet.
What about you, Ex?
Me? None.
He does!
Dad!
He likes a girl named Som.
You know, "Oh, Som."
Dad, no!
One day,
I heard him talking to himself
in his room.
Oh, Som...
At first, I thought something was wrong
with him.
It wasn't until I saw him
that I knew exactly what happened.
Gosh, even during the middle of the day.
You can borrow one of my DVDs next time.
Don't listen to my dad. The truth is,
I didn't dare approach Som.
All I could do was look at her photo.
I accidentally spilled orange juice on it
and cried out.
Som!
No...
I then got some tissue to clean it.
I was going to throw them away,
but I ran into my dad at the door.
That's all there was to it.
Hey, there's more.
Did he ever tell you about the doughnut?
-Shit.
-Please tell us.
-Customers are waiting downstairs, Dad.
-Well...
-No, Dad!
-I passed by the bathroom--
Leave, Dad.
-Come to me if you want to know anything.
-Leave now.
Hey, why don't we let Ex write the song
since he is in love right now?
You don't know anything.
The one in the love is usually
the most clueless one about it.
GREAT KNOWLEDGE
GOOD DISCIPLINE
You can observe how Ex flirts with Som.
Write down anything that works.
It's bright and sunny this morning.
She arrives early.
The weather is cold. I arrive early, too.
I walk straight to her, my dream girl.
I turn the faucet on.
The water is wonderfully refreshing.
I hammer the nails,
watching her move her arms.
She's beautiful when she kicks
her left leg and moves her right arm.
Oh, shit! She's coming my way.
I act brave and stand up...
Move out of the way!
...to shoot some hoops.
2009 CHETTUPONBURANA HOMECOMING
I've traded blows in this boxing ring.
There's no turning back.
A punch to the lower torso, the body,
followed by the one to the ears.
There she is.
She's headed this way, my darling.
Our eyes meet.
Oh, my God!
Stop!
Shit!
I begin seeing stars.
How is it?
It's rubbish.
I didn't see him do anything.
I'm shy.
If you like her, just tell her.
Really?
Yes?
It's nothing.
Otherwise, how will she know?
See, even a girl can speak her mind.
You are such a wimp!
If you are so skillful,
then show me how it's done.
All right.
After Som finishes her dance
in the event tomorrow,
bring her a gift and use that opportunity
to talk to her.
That's it. It's that simple.
If I did that, she would be mine already.
So cocky!
-Get him, too!
-Hey.
You idiot.
You guys are free, right?
Can you come help move some stuff?
MUSIC ROOM
What kind of gift should I give to her?
Well, it can be flowers, dolls,
or something similar.
If I can't use the word "love",
then which word should I use?
Well, you can use "like",
"miss",
"care."
Something like that.
I think we all have our own words for it.
For Ex, I guess it's probably the word
"wimp" or something.
I think "horny" suits him more.
What about you, Ped?
Which word would you use?
"Lovely..."
I guess.
Hey, you can't.
It still has the word "love" in it.
Don't cheat.
Oh, right.
DIAMOND SOUND
This should be enough for now.
I made you a list of songs
that don't have the word "love" in it.
It's in this bag.
Wouldn't it be better
if you write the song?
Well, I don't know.
I think the song should be about
a guy's perspective.
Besides,
Koong will be the one singing it.
It's better if you write it.
Come on, it won't be that difficult.
Just write about your feelings.
My feelings?
Like how you feel when you like someone.
You have never liked anyone before?
EARN
SONG
What's up, Koong?
Be honest with me.
Do you like Earn?
No.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Why did you ask?
Are you sure?
I am.
I don't like her.
I knew it! Tuang is so full of it.
He said that he saw you guys flirting.
Plus, he said he saw you guys
holding hands, too!
We were carrying a drum.
Shit! I shouldn't have listened to him.
Is this what you came here for?
Are you writing a song?
How far along are you?
-It's not finished yet.
-Let me see.
Hey, Koong! Don't look at it.
It's not done yet.
"The song that you hear,
do you know that I didn't write it?
I don't dare to confess, my darling.
Do you know who wrote this song?
Remember, that person is you."
-Did you write this yourself?
-Yes.
What's the title?
It doesn't have one yet.
It's not bad.
Man, it really hits home!
Damn! It's exactly how I feel!
Holy shit!
Damn!
I like Earn!
You are the first one to know.
Remember that day
back in elementary school,
when everyone was teasing me
that I liked Earn?
I couldn't get her crying face
out of my mind.
When she moved to Bangkok,
I tried to forget her.
But who would have thought
that she would come back?
This made me realize how much I like her.
Look.
It's the paint she got on me.
I still haven't washed it off.
Here.
I won't bother you anymore.
I just wanted to let you know.
Hurry up and finish the song, okay?
So I can sing it
and let her know how I feel.
Good luck! Later!
SONG...
EARN
2009 CHETTUPONBURANA HOMECOMING
I'm standing alone
-It's so lonely inside my heart
I'm all alone, can you hear me?
My heart is so lonely
Earn.
No, thanks. You can give it to Ped.
But I already bought it.
Please help me finish it.
I need someone
Who will take care of my heart
I've got sensitive teeth.
I can't really drink cold drinks.
Thanks.
I have love in my heart
Kay is really cool, right?
No way. You are much cooler than him.
He just likes to strike handsome poses.
He's not even that good-looking.
Then that applies to you, too.
Come on.
We don't look alike. Look carefully.
Yes, that's true.
Kay is more good-looking.
Earn!
I'm all alone, can you hear me?
Hello, Dad?
My heart is so lonely
Ped.
What?
You can leave when the concert is over.
Why?
I need someone
Who will take care of my heart
I'm going to confess to Earn.
I can't take it any more
I just want to say something
Then, I better leave now.
Hey, why are you in such a hurry?
I want to finish writing the song.
I have love in my heart
Thanks, dude!
YOU ARE THE ONE
Disappointment
Has already found its way to you
Right?
The defeat
Must be almost unbearable
When you are hurt, just cry out
Until you are left
With only the tears
To fall back on
Let your tears flow freely
Don't hold anything back
Let it go
Let your tears help your heart remember
How much you were hurt
EARN
There is no one
Except your tears
To help you get through this
Remember
No matter how bad it hurts
Let the tears rub the pain away
Ped! Koong is calling you.
Ped.
What's up?
Can you come see me?
Where are you?
I'm on the train. I'm going to Bangkok.
Hey!
Why are you going there?
I have to go...
because I can't stay here.
You had better come now.
And bring some money.
I already bought the tickets.
Mom, I'm staying over at Koong's tonight
to study for an exam.
Liar!
So?
It's my first love
And my heart is broken into pieces
Is it too soon for this kind of sorrow?
After I finished watching Som dance,
I invited Earn to come over
to the tree people talked about.
They said that whoever confessed there
will have a happy ending.
Once I got there, I gave it my best shot.
Earn.
I'm not a smooth talker
But I love with all my heart
Whatever you like, I will find for you
I'm not a smooth talker...
Why did you let me listen to this song?
I like you, Earn.
Instead of accepting my love,
all she did was talk about the band.
I tried my best to persuade her,
but she said...
You should give up, Koong.
So I told her
that I don't want to play music anymore.
If you want to play,
then do it with someone else.
And?
She just walked away.
Shit! Why are you such an idiot?
I'm glad you came, Ped.
Did you invite Ex as well?
I called, but his dad picked up the phone
and said he would tell Ex that I called.
Oh, there you are.
Please take care of him.
It seems like he's in pretty bad shape.
What happened, Ex?
BOBBING FOR EGGS
Come on, Ex!
Ped, you know that I went bobbing for eggs
to win a stuffed bear for Som, right?
What did he get?
A pen!
Gosh!
I did that until I ran out of money
and my hands were all numb.
But I managed to win that bear for Som.
Hey.
Look!
That tomboy's bear was bigger than mine!
I have orange juice, soda, and beer.
Cold drinks to refresh you.
Anyone want a drink?
How many cans of beer do you have, sir?
I have a lot.
I'm buying them all.
You drink beer, too?
Straws, please, sir.
You left without a word
I didn't get to prepare
I can't eat and I can't sleep
Even sugar tastes bitter to me
You hurt the one who loves you
You almost killed me
-I'm like an injured tiger
-Whose wound hasn't been healed
-If you don't mind...
-Sorry, my friends are drunk.
-Bring him here with you
Let's openly talk
Hey! You're disturbing other people!
About you and that guy
-I have only one thing to ask of you
-How could he take you away from me?
-Let's meet at our usual place and time
-Please don't forget
Sending off the pain and sadness
That hurt me
Bidding you farewell
And wishing you a long-lasting love
Good luck to you as you distance yourself
From the man you don't want to be with
Let me ask for the check
So I can pay for all the sadness on my own
YOU SUCK
Hey, Koong.
You dragged us
all the way to Bangkok just for this?
For guys like us,
checking out an all-girls school
is as important as getting ordained
or drafted into the army.
Som.
Earn.
You girls! I'm going to punish all of you.
Where are you going this evening?
Shit! Something is wrong here.
Just wait and see.
I think these girls
all have good-looking friends.
Look!
Hey. Good-looking girls mostly have...
Crap!
Calm down! Close your eyes!
Don't look anymore!
Here we are.
What is this place?
This is where the final round
of the Hotwave Music Awards will be.
The era of music bands is not over yet.
I will forget about Earn!
From this point on,
I will only focus on this contest
and we will succeed together!
I will forget about Som, too!
But I will never forget that tomboy!
Let's shake on it.
Hey, Ped. Do you have anything to say?
-Like what?
-Anything you want to get off your chest.
I do.
-It's about the song.
-Gosh.
It's just one song. We've got each other.
We can all help write it.
All right.
From this moment on,
we're going to be reborn.
We will be rid of all our problems.
Soon,
our band will get to be in there.
ENTRANCE 1
The place behind those doors
is where our heroes had performed.
Kala.
Clash.
Labanoon.
-Bodyslam!
I've been so tired, I've almost given up
I couldn't stand it anymore
I've walked until I could no longer do so
Because my dreams still seem so far away
Should I turn back
Because the road ahead
Is so difficult and cold?
My whole life, I believed in myself
But maybe I was wrong
Toon.
Bodyslam.
And now I'm the one who is lost
We have to follow our dreams
Hey, Koong!
No matter how many times we fall
Where will it end?
No matter how far you walk
You never get there
Promo for "Save My Life"
cut two, take two. End slate.
Who let this fair-faced boy in here?
Staff, please show them out.
The feeling isn't there yet, Toon.
Toon!
I'm Koong!
I will perform here one day!
That's right! And I'm Ex!
You will definitely see me!
Toon! I'm Ped!
Please don't mind my friends.
Help me, Toon!
Don't listen to them, Toon.
Nobody wants you here.
Please leave.
Toon!
Take my guitar pick.
I will make it here one day!
Please remember me!
-We have to follow our dreams
-Toon!
No matter how many times we fall
Let me sing him a song first!
I love you, Toon! Don't forget me.
KOONG &amp; FRIEND
The era of sadness has already passed.
Starting today, our band will be reborn.
We freaking suck, man.
I got my heart broken.
JUST GIVE UP
TRY HARDER
Ex was heartbroken as well.
PSYCHOPATHIC BEAR
Ped didn't get his heart broken
because he has never hit on any girl.
Asshole!
PED RED SODA
We all suck.
LOSERS
But we won't give up.
We will form a band named SuckSeed,
which actually means "succeed."
This is for everyone
who has once failed like us,
so that they can stand up and be reborn.
It's going to be like the seeds
that will grow on this earth.
Now, I know why The Arena is really good.
It's because they don't waste time
on stupid things like you guys.
The Arena isn't even on my radar anymore.
It's just a typical band
that's trying to be cool.
It's nothing.
Well...
why are you sitting here alone?
Got your heart broken?
No, I broke someone's heart.
That's just Koong.
Don't mind him.
I don't, but I'm upset.
I want to say sorry for him.
Why are you saying sorry?
You didn't do anything wrong.
Don't you want to join us again?
No, I shouldn't.
I don't want to cause any trouble.
Are you waiting for someone?
No.
I should go now.
Earn.
I still want to see your face
on the cover of an album.
It's time to get serious now.
What about this one?
It's a signature model,
NC70 Model Pro Series.
Many famous musicians use this.
Can I have a look at that one?
It's a Flying V. You've got good taste.
Try it.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Can I have a look at that amplifier?
You really have good taste.
It has great sound.
A very clean sound. No hissing at all.
If the sound cracks,
it has a limiter and an equalizer.
Many famous musicians use this.
Do they usually step
with the right foot or the left?
I don't know. Left, I guess.
Good. I will use my right foot, then.
Salute!
Let me hear some noise!
Rockers!
I love everyone.
This is it.
You have decided? That one, right?
No, I want that bass.
You definitely have good taste.
Here.
Are you really buying this for me?
Hell no. I bought it for myself.
But I'll let you borrow it.
When people notice how cool the bass is,
they won't notice that you suck.
Carry it.
Believe me. We are like kings.
It's so cold
My heart is almost torn
Because I am without the warmth
Of your love
I have written over ten songs
and he didn't like any of them.
I want to punch him so bad.
Hey, take it easy.
You know that he is really talented.
Talented, my ass. He sucks.
If I wasn't the lead singer of our band,
the girls won't go crazy over us.
Oh, come on.
At least, we've been playing together.
We don't need him.
Kay is an idiot.
He's really ugly, too.
I'm going to kick the shit out of him.
Damn it! Who the hell are you? Asshole!
What's going on?
Drench him, Koong!
Why did you say my name?
Oh, it's Koong. You asshole!
Wait for me there.
Don't run away.
Hey, stop fighting.
I'm not going anywhere.
Get your ass out here now!
I will smack you with this!
Don't! I'm not Koong!
I'm Kay.
Kay?
You came just in time!
Who did you get into a fight with?
Forget it.
I kicked Tem out of the band.
Whatever. I don't care.
Fine, then. I don't need
to tell you things anymore.
We're dead!
Let's go.
Where?
To practice, of course.
Gosh!
I'm here to return your CDs.
There's no rush.
I should return them now,
in case you move away again.
Don't be silly.
How is The Arena doing?
I happened to pass by the music room.
It looked like a lot of fun.
Yes, I had a lot of fun,
but I'm not used to it yet.
I often called Kay as Koong.
Earn!
How is your song coming along?
I'm still working on it.
Do you want to borrow these CDs first?
No, it's okay.
I'm leaving, then.
7. JUST WANT TO SEE YOUR FACE
I don't love you that much
I don't like you that much
I just want to see your face
I don't love you that much
I don't like you that much
I just want to see your face
I don't miss you that much
That's all
We're just neighbors and nothing more
Nothing more, that's all
I just want to see your face, that's all
I HAVEN'T HEARD
"JUST WANT TO SEE YOUR FACE" IN A WHILE.
DID YOU LISTEN TO IT?
I DID.
IS IT GOOD?
Why don't you sound like Seak,
the singer of Loso?
Go figure.
Ped.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
How do you feel about me?
What do you mean?
Do you have a crush on me?
I used to.
What about now?
Not anymore.
All right.
I'm hanging up.
Wait! Don't open it yet!
Listen!
The song that you hear
Do you know that I didn't write it?
I don't dare to confess, my darling
Wait!
Let me finish.
Do you know who wrote this song?
Remember, that person is you
It's finished.
The song that you hear
Do you know that I didn't write it?
I don't dare to confess, my darling
Do you know who wrote this song?
Remember, that person is you
Something like that?
It's better than I imagined.
You can write a song.
Actually, I didn't write it for the band.
Do you remember the phone call
when we were in sixth grade?
Actually, Koong wasn't the one
who called you.
It was you?
So why did you lie?
Because your dad sounded really mean
on the phone.
So why did you call, then?
I like you.
I really like you.
I still like you.
I know.
So what about you and Koong?
No worries.
Koong has been reborn.
I mean, he said
he doesn't like you anymore.
And...
I also like...
this song.
What about me?
Figure it out for yourself.
Ped...
What's going on?
Hey, Ped.
Where were you last night?
Why do you ask?
I called you all night.
Your mom said you went out.
Where did you go?
I went to find inspiration.
I still can't come up with anything.
Hey, don't worry.
I already thought of something.
Our band's song can't be
about a hopeless romance
because girls don't deserve
our love.
The song must be about friendship.
The kind that women
won't be able to understand.
Cool!
Guys, isn't this a bit too much?
You still don't get it, Ped.
I have been with many girls.
Listen to the hook of this song.
Girls are bitches!
You son of a bitch!
What if no girls like our song?
That's fine, Ped. You know why?
Because all girls are selfish!
Hey, your mom is a woman.
Fuck you!
I was talking about teenage girls.
They don't make sense!
AMPHA CHICKEN RICE
How come there is only chicken rice
and no duck rice?
But I still like girls.
You guys don't like girls anymore?
I still do,
but I hate girls who are sellers!
This CD is very hard to sell.
Can you buy one?
Not only that, women are--
Hey, enough already!
I believe you now!
There you go!
Come on!
Let's do it!
One. Two. Three. Four.
Five. Six. Seven. Eight.
Five. Six. Seven. Eight. Go!
One. Two. Three. Four. Five. Six. Seven.
Yes! One. Two. Three. Four.
Five. Six. Seven. Eight.
One. Two. Three. Four.
One. Two. Three. Four. Five. Six. Seven.
EARN: CONCENTRATE!
"Girls are nonsense!"
Are we doing this for real?
It sounds kind of shitty.
Yes, it's really shitty.
Come to think of it, we haven't done
anything meaningful in our lives.
Heartache.
A lot didn't make it.
No one even remembers. No one cares.
The only thing we can do
is endure the pain.
Girls turned us down.
We are always last.
Whatever we do sucks.
It's all over the place.
We really suck!
But it's okay, we still keep walking
There is hope waiting for us
We might be born to lose
But we aren't born to give it up!
At least, we will succeed once
Even though we really suck
And our lives suck even more
At least we will go down together
We should try at least once
We must succeed at least once
Even though we really suck
And our lives suck even more
At least we will go down together!
EARN: KEEP IT UP!
SuckSeed!
And now, it's the moment
that everyone has been waiting for.
It is a special day today.
We will be announcing the bands
qualified for the regional semi-finals
of the 2006 Hotwave Music Awards
The first band that made it
to the semi-finals is
from Chettuponburana High School!
It's The Arena!
They're so great today.
No surprise there.
Don't be excited. There are 19 bands left.
Who's next? We are now on the fifth band.
The competition is really fierce.
The tenth band is...
And the 13th band is...
GGR!
Don't worry, guys.
Chill, I know we will make it.
And this band has the initials "S.S."
Let's hear it for the band
who goes by the name
So Sad from Lampang Kanlayanee
High School.
Congratulations!
Let's move to the next one.
The 15th band is really cool.
There are three members in total.
It's Uncle's Condominium
from Montfort High school.
Oh, sorry. I made a mistake.
Actually, the band consists
of four members, not three.
If a band with that name can make it,
then we can make it, too!
Dumbass!
And now, we're at the last band.
The last band is...
-SuckSeed...
...is...
I am so excited to announce the last band.
Congratulations to...
to...
What the hell are you doing?
I don't want to know anymore!
Damn it! Let it go!
Koong!
Turn it on, Ped!
Don't turn it on!
We have announced the 20 bands
that made it to the semi-finals.
That must have been nerve-racking.
Koong, you asshole.
What the hell have you done?
I got too excited!
So now, how will we know if we made it?
I don't know! That DJ pressured me!
He talked too much.
Congratulations for making it, Earn.
Gosh! He just kept going on and on!
Congratulate me for what?
What are you happy about, Earn?
We are the last band!
Earn said SuckSeed made it as well!
Koong, are you ready?
-Are you ready?
-Okay.
Three.
Two.
One.
SuckSeed!
Fuck it.
That's awesome!
I think we should do it again.
Let's go.
Hey.
We don't have time to mess around anymore.
If we want to win,
we need some special moves.
If nobody laughs at this,
I'll become a monk.
That was almost perfect.
Let's try it one more time.
Shorty, you need to froth
at the mouth more.
Fatty, add more of this.
Thank you.
What is" EPED"?
It's my guitar's name.
That's cute.
Yes, I think so too,
but I was going to make it
look fiercer at first.
It's not the guitar.
I meant her.
Silly.
-They're flirting.
-Yes.
Hey, have you listened to my band's song?
What?
They played my band's song on the radio
after the announcement. Do you like it?
Yes, I like it. It's cool.
It's very beautiful and catchy.
-You haven't listened to it, right?
-I like it a lot.
Sorry. I haven't.
You can play it for me after this.
Don't.
Are you mad? Just for this?
Hey, be careful!
-I'm leaving, Mom.
-Good luck, honey.
Let's rock it!
UNCLE'S CONDOMINIUM
How is it?
We will play after The Arena.
That's good, so we can compete closely.
Where are the guitar and bass?
Oh, I was too lazy to carry them around,
so I put them...
Ped.
Can you get the guitar for me?
So did you get some sleep last night?
Yes, right after I hung up.
Do I look tired?
No.
Ped.
Hurry up.
The Arena, please stand by
beside the stage.
GIVE IT YOUR BEST
Please give a round of applause to So Sad!
-Hello!
-Yes?
Kids these days are so talented.
-They really are, right?
-And the next band is
-The Arena!
Hello, we are The Arena!
Damn good!
This song might not be
As beautiful as other songs
But it is so meaningful to me
Every word that is written here
Is from the smile I got from you
It forced the pen to convey the meaning
-Earn is the freaking best.
-They're the words that speak for my heart
-Goddess.
-Do you know
-I didn't mean that.
-Why I can do this?
I think
I still can't forget Earn.
The song that you hear
Do you know that I didn't write it?
I don't dare to confess, my darling
Do you know who wrote this song?
Remember
The song that you hear
Do you know that I didn't write it?
I don't dare to confess, my darling
Do you know who wrote this song?
Remember
That person is you
Do you know why I can do this?
You...
wrote this song for Earn?
The song that you hear
Do you know that I didn't write it?
I don't dare to confess, my darling
You...
like Earn, right?
Remember
The song that you hear
Do you know that I didn't write it?
I don't dare to confess, my darling
Do you know who wrote this song?
Remember
That person is you
Please give a round of applause
to The Arena!
Wow! That was really amazing!
We were dancing so hard backstage.
Who wrote this song?
We'll have to ask our lead singer.
He said to ask you.
So are you smiling because of
someone special or a personal experience?
I know just from your smile.
I'm sure it came from her experience.
She's probably feeling shy.
All right. We won't dig any deeper.
Please give a round of applause to them!
Thank you very much, The Arena!
You teased her
until she didn't know what to say.
Hey.
Let's give it our all.
She's blushing.
I won't talk anymore.
Rock it, Ped!
-Let's meet the next band.
-Yes.
Please give a round of applause
to SuckSeed!
Brokenhearted repeatedly
And hurt again and again
No one remembers
No one cares
We have to endure the pain
We failed badly at getting girls
We are always the last
And we suck at whatever we do
But it's okay, we still keep walking
There is hope waiting for us
We might be born to lose
But we aren't born to give it up!
Hey, where are you going?
Koong, what's the matter?
I know you are mad
that I wrote the song for Earn,
but I didn't know that The Arena
would use the song.
What song?
And I thought
you didn't like Earn anymore.
Just say whatever you want.
Fuck you! You've always been like this.
-Hey, calm down.
-You never care about how others feel.
You always did whatever you wanted
and invited people in whenever you wanted.
When you were not happy,
you kicked her out.
Just like how you stopped playing now.
And you're so great?
You had been waiting
to snatch her away, right?
I liked Earn way before you did.
Why didn't you say a word
after all this time?
When is the final round?
It's after the exam.
That's cool.
If you make it to the final round,
you will definitely become famous.
I'm so jealous. I want to play
on a big stage like that too.
Just say what is on your mind, Ped.
I'm so sorry, Earn.
I don't know.
I still feel the same for you,
but...
I don't know.
I think I understand.
We can go back to the way we were before.
Koong is lucky.
This is not about Koong.
Are you gay?
Are you crazy?
Good luck then, Ped.
I LOVE EVERYONE
WE ARE FROM CLASSROOM 6/3
ARE YOU MAD AT ME?
CHETTUPON SCHOOL
CLASS 47, CLASSROOM 6/3
WE WILL MISS EACH OTHER
I remember sitting next to you and...
You went to poop.
-You went to poop.
-You went with me.
Brokenhearted repeatedly
And hurt again and again
No one remembers
No one cares
We have to endure the pain
We failed badly at getting girls
We are always the last
And we suck at whatever we do
But it's okay, we still keep walking
There is hope waiting for us
We might be born to lose
But we aren't born to give it up!
At least, we will succeed once
Even though we really suck
And our lives suck even more
At least we will go down together
We should try at least once
We must succeed at least once
Even though we really suck
And our lives suck even more
At least we will go down together!
SuckSeed!
GET READY FOR THE LATEST SINGLE
FROM THE COOLEST ROCK BAND, THE ARENA
REUNION PARTY, CHETTU CLASS 47
MEET THE ARENA
Ped!
Why are you spacing out over there?
Why don't you go drink inside?
-Okay, I will be there.
-Hurry up then.
-Miss you, Ped!
-Come quick.
-See you inside.
-Hurry up, okay!
How is love?
We used to promise things together
Back then when we were apart
Do you remember?
-Ped!
-The sky always changes
-Am I right?
-I still remember that promise
Ex! I almost didnt recognize you!
-Shit! I miss you, asshole!
-How is our true love?
-Come here.
-I've been missing you
The world looks so cold
When I don't have you here
Whenever you are right now
Could you please come back to me?
I've been missing you
And that was The Arena!
You want one more picture?
-Thank you, Earn.
-It's okay.
Hey, Ped!
You arrived so late.
Can I have your autograph, please?
I thought you would download it.
If anyone buys the CD at your shop,
they would probably get confused
because the girl who sells the CD
looks like the one on the cover.
Earn, can I have a photo with you?
MISSING OLD DAYS, EARN.
How was it?
I thought it was very beautiful
and catchy.
You haven't changed at all.
Really?
But I think things have changed,
except for the fact
that I'm still a loser.
But I feel that nothing has changed.
So do you have anyone special yet?
Not yet.
I am still the same, Ped.
Can you sign this for me?
All right. We are now nearing the end
of tonight's reunion party.
-Whoever is sleeping, please wake up now.
-Ex, wake up!
Whoever is going to the after party,
please be patient,
because today, I have prepared
something for you all.
DO YOU STILL REMEMBER?
Oh, my god. How could we do that?
It's embarrassing.
Actually, SuckSeed's song is awesome.
I'll be right back.
Hey, do you still play music sometimes?
I forgot it all already.
FOREVER CHETTU CLASS 47
We have come to the end
of the reunion party.
Thank you very much, everyone.
See you next year!
HOMECOMING
23 OCTOBER 2010
Ped, why are you on the stage?
Come down.
Hey, that's mine.
Brokenhearted repeatedly
And hurt again and again
No one remembers
No one cares
We have to endure the pain
We failed badly at getting girls
We are always the last
And we suck at whatever we do
But it's okay, we still keep walking
There is hope waiting for us
We might be born to lose
But we aren't born to give it up!
At least, we will succeed once
Hey, Koong!
Even though we really suck
And our lives suck even more
At least we will go down together
We should try at least once
We must succeed at least once
Even though we really suck
And our lives suck even more
At least we will go down together!
Hey!
Brokenhearted repeatedly
And hurt again and again
Kay.
Can I borrow your pick?
It would take a real jerk
to forget a loser like you.
But it's okay, we still keep walking
There is hope waiting for us
We might be born to lose
But we aren't born to give it up!
-At least, we will succeed once
Even though we really suck
And our lives suck even more
At least we will go down together
We should try at least once
We must succeed at least once
Even though we really suck
And our lives suck even more
At least we will go down together
-SuckSeed!
You really suck!
SuckSeed!
Asshole!
-Shit!
One day, The Arena became the opening band
for Bodyslam.
Congratulations!
Toon remembered me,
but he thought that Kay was me.
Are you ready?
Do you know what's trending now, Ped?
It's organic farming.
Chemical farming is completely gone.
FARMER MARKET
CHAING MAI, 2011
Next, please welcome a band
that I have invited
for all of you to enjoy.
Please welcome...
SuckSeed!
It's unplugged.
This is the melody of our past
When I hear it, I miss those old days
No matter how much time has passed
I'm telling you, Ped.
Our song...
This is our era!
...is in our heart!