Good afternoon.
My name is Kobori.
I came to Thailand in 1941
at the beginning of World War II
as a dockyard engineer,
to send supplies and support to Burma.
At the time, Japanese-Thai Army relations
were filled with a great suspicion
because we first wanted
only to pass through Thailand.
The given order was that
if Thailand resisted, we would occupy.
But when Thailand yielded,
then the Japanese Army headquarters
in Thailand
would have to protect Thailand instead.
My duties included commanding the Japanese
Army to be able to stay with Thais.
This was a very delicate issue.
When the war started, there were
many misunderstandings
between the Japanese and Thai armies.
I didn't know whether an attempt
to fix a broken glass
would be a worthless attempt.
Hey!
Miss. What are you looking at?
Can you speak English?
No.
I see. You cannot speak English.
"No."
Miss!
Miss! Can you go home?
Already grown up. Can go home myself.
Goodbye.
Playmate? Am I your playmate?
Playmate?
Playmate.
Goodbye, playmate.
Hey!
Hello, playmate.
Miss!
Playmate.
Ang, who is he?
Do you know him?
Don't know, Mom.
I saw him calling you "playmate."
Who is he?
I can't say, Mom.
I want to investigate.
Investigate what?
How to get to the route of the rear dock?
Just walk.
Walk how?
Just walk as you normally walk.
Roger.
Please, stop!
Get out! Stop!
Get out now!
Please, stop!
Don't do it. Ang, don't do it.
Enough.
Stop it!
Gather!
I'm sorry for this situation.
You think you Japanese soldiers
can do anything?
Speak slowly. I'm not good at Thai.
All problems were caused by my men.
I'll take responsibility.
How?
Enough! Enough!
Enough!
Apologize to her!
Yes, sir!
Straight!
We are very sorry!
Back to the base!
-Yes, sir!
-Go!
Just an apology?
I guarantee I'll "tri" my best to be fair.
It's pronounced "try".
Try.
Well...
I want some anti-malaria drugs.
I don't know what you're saying.
What do you want? Where does it hurt?
Mr. Engineer! Mr. Engineer!
Could you please speak to the doctor?
Because I want
some anti-malaria drugs.
I've just gone to the health center
and was told it had run out.
But someone said
it's still available here.
I talked to the doctor,
but we couldn't understand each other.
So I would like your help, please.
I will double-check.
Are there many people who want the drug?
There are quite a few.
Excuse me!
Is anyone there?
Hello!
Is that the one?
She is cute.
Why are you here?
Hello.
We've heard that your grandma is unwell.
May I help?
No need to help. Won't be off the boil.
But now the vaccine is in short supply.
And it's needed by your grandma.
Who's that, honey?
Take nutritious food with the medicine,
such as milk or butter.
I can't understand Japanese well.
Oh, I see, sorry.
I can be your interpreter.
Hey,
I'll talk to her!
Nutritious food with the medicine,
such as milk or butter.
Yes, sir.
Take the drug
and nutritious food, milk, butter.
During the war,
it's difficult to find milk.
I can get it for you.
No, I don't want to trouble you.
We will get it ourselves.
Trouble? No. I'll get hold of it.
Hey, Azuma!
Milk and butter, okay?
Milk, milk!
Milk!
This is milk. Nutrition for Grandma.
I also brought some other necessary items.
Many thanks, young man. I'm about to cook.
Stay and eat with us.
Ang, tell him to have dinner with us.
My mother told me that
You should go home
because it gets dark soon.
What?
I just heard the word "dinner."
How come you translated it differently?
Mom, he's leaving now.
No need to cook for him.
Are you leaving?
Fine.
I'll take you there on my boat.
Don't worry.
I can walk through my home to the dock.
I'll take the boat there.
No worries. I don't want to trouble you.
I said I'll take the boat there.
Don't worry.
Goodbye, Playmate.
Fucking Jap!
Enough! Pol, Bua.
Enough. Please, stop.
I'll take you back on my boat.
How are you doing?
I'm lucky but I only have a little luck.
What's a little luck?
It's...
You knew that someone wanted me dead.
What about being lucky?
You don't want me dead.
Where are you going?
Going to the dock.
Not hurting?
It's all right.
Teriyaki, teriyaki.
Hello, Mother.
Good afternoon.
Angsumalin is not here.
How are you doing?
Have you already recovered?
Much better now.
Today, we intend to cook
to pay you back for your help.
But it's not convenient at the dock.
Would you allow me to cook here?
What do you want to cook?
-Teriyaki.
Teriyaki?
Mom, what are they doing?
They're cooking for us.
Allow me to borrow your kitchen.
We're cooking for you.
Young man, what's your name?
My name is Kobori.
Difficult to pronounce.
Let me call you Mali instead.
What does "Mali" mean?
Mali is the name of a flower.
What does "Angsumali" mean?
Mom.
It's Angsumalin.
Angsumalin means "the sun."
The sun?
What's the sun?
Ang, tell him.
I won't say.
Over there, the sun.
Oh, sun or sunset?
I don't know. It's your language.
Enough, Mom.
You are Hideko, right?
Can I call you Hideko?
Hurry up and cook teriyaki. Get it done.
Hideko-san is hungry?
I will quickly cook it.
What is that noise?
What, Mom?
Azuma!
An air raid. Please go back to the dock.
Understood.
We need to return to the dock.
-Hori.
-Thank you
Excuse us. Let's go.
Where're we going?
To the orchard, quick.
Quick, quick.
Wait here. Come sit here.
Quick.
Sit down. Sit down.
Sit down here. If there's any bombs,
duck down low. Understand?
Be strong.
I have to go back to the dock.
Don't go.
Hideko, you must be strong.
It's all right. Don't be scared.
Hideko, you have to stay strong.
Extinguish a fire!
Bring the carrier!
Brace yourselves!
How are you doing?
Is anyone here?
Good evening, how are you?
It's all right now. We're safe and sound.
What about you?
How are things at the dock?
Several boats got damaged.
Many people were injured.
I'm sorry.
In the end, we couldn't have teriyaki.
It's okay. Ang boiled it.
It was delicious.
I see.
Hideko.
Do you want to visit Japan after the war?
You could have authentic Japanese food.
I will not go there.
Why?
I'm waiting for someone here.
Has he joined the war?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I hope you two will meet up after the war.
Go!
Go, hurry up!
What's happening?
A prisoner escaped last night.
People say he's hiding in this area.
We need to search every house.
Oh, no. He's not here.
Allow me.
What is it?
We need to search the house.
The escaped prisoner's around here.
You're saying I'm hiding the prisoner?
I'm sorry. I have to search.
Search upstairs!
Yes, sir!
Mr. Tobori.
Please come with us.
Need to search my room?
If you allow it.
If you dare, go ahead.
Allow me.
Why did you allow Japanese soldiers
to search my house?
It's the superior's order.
One prisoner, dead or alive,
the Japanese Army
will neither lose nor win.
For you...
I seem worthless.
My life is worth less than his, isn't it?
They dropped the bombs here.
Don't trade your family's lives
just to save his.
It's not that.
Is she coming?
Gather!
We move forward!
Yes, sir.
You can get out now.
I got you into trouble.
I'm sure that Japanese man saw me.
What do you think he'll do?
Don't worry.
We'll take you to another place.
Why didn't they arrest me?
He loves you, right?
Follow me.
Ang, this way.
What are you doing here?
This is my home.
Wherever and whenever I go,
it's my own business.
I don't understand.
I came here
because I want to build a friendship
with everyone.
But why do you hate a friendship?
You are heartless.
I'm not.
No way!
A heart is not cold like this.
As a heart is tender than this.
That's enough.
Run! Quick!
Good.
Next!
You're all right. Don't worry.
You still have two arms and two legs.
Doctor. Thank you so much.
By tomorrow?
Your body is fine.
You feel quite distressed about Kogori.
People say...
You two are playing around
behind their back.
To go out with a Thai woman,
that is the worst thing.
What?
What do you mean?
Right. Get well soon!
Here is a letter from home.
The villagers are gossiping
about Kobori and Angsumalin
having a secret affair in the orchard.
No! No way.
I need to report this to your commander.
March forward!
To regain friendly relations
between our Imperial Army and Thailand,
we must have a wedding
ceremony to unite Japan and Thailand.
Yes, sir. I couldn't agree more.
Hello, Father.
Hello.
Haven't seen you for ages. I heard you got
into an accident. How are you feeling?
I'm okay now.
It's nice that you came,
so we could finally talk.
I also have something to discuss with you.
Or why else would I have come here?
If you're hot-tempered like this,
I think it's better we not talk.
Yesterday, headquarters called me
to a meeting with a Japanese commander.
So, I went.
Didn't think it would be a personal issue.
Upon arriving, I met a cultural ambassador
and journalists.
After a brief talk, they asked
for permission to marry our daughter.
My superior explained that it's a matter
of international affairs.
What does it mean?
And what did you reply?
I'm afraid to make a decision.
I'll talk to our daughter, then.
I'm sorry
for causing this to escalate.
Then, what?
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
The grand relations between
Thailand and Japan
will grow even closer.
I'm not interested
in the relationship between the nations.
But I want to know...
what you think.
I hate you.
I hate you. Are you happy?
Even though I'll marry you,
I'll hate you.
Hideko.
Hoy no yossa
Hoy no hoy
When you sleep with an only child girl
You need to ask her parents first
Hoy no yossa
Hoy no hoy
When you sleep with a girl
with another sister
You need to sleep with
her old sister first
Hoy no yossa
Hoy no hoy
When you sleep with a girl
in someone's house
You mustn't make any noise
Don't enter. You can't enter.
-Can you speak Thai?
-Yes, I can.
First, you have to give us an envelope.
Envelope?
An envelope with money.
Then you can enter.
Hello.
Yes.
Hey, smile!
Pol, Bua.
What're you doing here?
I'm waiting for you.
If you've come to meet someone,
he's already left.
What do you mean?
Oh, Hideko.
I'm probably a fool to you again, right?
You probably don't hate me
because you're Thai.
But you hate me
because you're Rengokoku.
What's Rengokoku?
It's the Allies.
You shouldn't have worked today.
Today is our engagement day, Hideko.
Why?
You really made me sad, you know?
But never mind. You've succeeded.
Apart from me, nobody knows.
The war is changing every day, Hideko.
Perhaps, I might not return.
The wedding might not happen.
That would be nice.
I knew you would say that.
If I died,
you would be very happy, wouldn't you?
Yes, I will wait for it.
I'm not afraid of dying.
Perhaps,
death might be the last thing
that makes me happy.
Good.
Take on your responsibility
as a soldier and as a man.
What you've done is exactly the same
as what our Imperial Army has done.
We must keep maintaining
friendly relations with Thailand.
Well, what a great joy your marriage is!
Right.
You can go home now.
Yes, sir!
"Attention now!
Message number one!
Our Imperial Army will reach Yangon soon.
Thanks to our troop's accomplishment
of their duty,
our commander will be very satisfied.
Message number two!
Be proud of being in our Imperial Army
and continue performing your duty! Over!"
I'm sorry about the wedding.
I couldn't decline.
The Japanese might aim to hit me
with this issue.
Let it be.
They could force us only into the wedding.
The Japanese soldiers probably don't
understand the importance of love.
Love is equally important for everyone.
When I didn't known love,
I had opportunities.
Since I have known what love is,
I haven't had the opportunities.
Azuma! Go ahead without me!
Go!
Right.
Hideko!
Why're you standing here?
Why must you be here
when I need someone?
Why?
Why're you here?
And why must you be here now too?
We need to get away from the bridge now.
Let's go.
Come!
Leave me alone.
Hideko!
We need to get away from the bridge now.
Let me go.
Stay away from my life.
Go away!
We need to get away from the bridge now!
Hideko, no! I'm not leaving you.
Vanguard...
Port, arms.
Present arms!
Order arms!
I can't return to the dock tonight.
If I do, others will know.
Please allow me to sleep here.
You can just place a blanket
wherever you want me to sleep.
Any corner is fine.
I'll wait outside.
So you can change clothes.
Hideko, you can trust me.
What's going on?
Ang, I need you to ask the Engineer.
I already told you to stay away from them.
You'll get into trouble.
Do you have any idea?
Germany is my ally,
but it's your enemy.
If you got arrested, you and your family,
and the villagers here
would all be in trouble.
I'll help you.
But you have to promise me
that you won't get involved
with those two guys again.
-What are you searching for?
-Calm down!
-What did the fucking Jap come here for?
-To inspect.
What's wrong?
Mr. Kobori, we'll search around here.
We received information
from the German army,
a secret agent is hiding here.
No. Not in my house or around here.
I'm certain that it was here.
Hideko.
Your consideration...
I appreciate it...
Cheers!
Be quiet!
Yeah.
Hideko!
Do you know?
I've just betrayed my honor.
Betrayed the honor of my nation.
Just for you.
Hideko.
You're so drunk tonight. Sleep!
Why haven't you ever spoken nicely
to make me happy even once?
Let go.
Hideko.
I'm sorry.
You should leave this house.
I'll do you whatever you want me to do
to soothe your anger.
No need.
I pity myself.
Please move somewhere else.
-I beg you.
-Hideko.
Hey, Kobori.
Hey.
What's up?
Aren't you going home today?
I've got it!
You've had a fight with her or something!
Well...
Have you done something stupid
to make her angry?
Wake up!
The air raid siren!
Turn it off!
Turn off the light!
Air raid!
Ang!
Help Grandma downstairs, quick.
Have we forgotten anything?
No, let's go. Quick.
Hurry! Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Tobori! Where are you going?
I must go home.
Hideko.
Why are you still here?
I forgot to turn off the lights.
What about Mom and Grandma?
Already gone to the bunker.
Let's go to the bunker.
Let's go.
If possible,
I want to freeze this moment forever.
If you could keep the promise,
I would also give you a promise.
Hideko, I don't want anything in return.
But I'll give you one.
While you're here, I'll be good to you.
I know you're waiting for him
to come back.
And it won't be long.
But if it's your wish, I am pleased.
Even though the happy time is short,
I'll embrace it.
Today's memories will comfort me.
One day I will explain to you why.
No worries, Hideko.
Any explanation will hurt us even more.
You have your own reason.
I have my own heart and that's enough.
If I die,
I'll take my loving heart with me.
When that day comes,
I will still be loving you.
Hideko.
Please say this.
I love you.
Hey, Kobori.
Head to army headquarters
to interpret urgently!
This is an order!
Understood, sir!
The traitors who parachuted
into Chainat province
were arrested and transported
to the capital city this morning.
"A foreign traitor
was arrested and transported
to the capital city this morning.
Thai police..."
The police are handing the traitors
over to the Japanese Army
for investigation as Japan had requested
of the Thai government.
Excuse us.
Why are you home so early?
I came to change clothes.
Don't worry about Pol and Bua.
They just came to visit us.
You'll be in trouble, Hideko.
It is best that they go home right now.
If the police see, you'll be
investigated and have problems.
Did the army want them arrested?
No.
But I don't want you to be involved
with them.
Perhaps, they were involved
in bombing the dock.
They wouldn't have done that.
How do you know?
Yesterday, the police arrested
three underground parachuted men.
What did you say?
We arrested three underground
parachuted men.
Two of them died.
Do you know where they came from?
I don't know.
You know, but you don't want to tell me.
Please, did they come from England?
England?
I've just learned that from you.
I don't know yet.
I'll have to be an interpreter
at the headquarters.
Would you please ask
if there is a man named Vanus?
Vanus?
So that means he'll come back.
You're waiting for him, aren't you?
I only want to know
if there's a man named Vanus.
I told you I don't know.
Could you ask about it?
Why? Is that something I should do?
Don't worry. I am safe.
Vanus
You can forget about what I begged you
to ask this afternoon.
You already know, don't you?
What do I know?
That one of the three
underground men is Vanus.
The Thai police asked us
to interrogate him today.
You don't have to tell me.
I don't want to know your secret.
I don't need to tell you anyways, Hideko.
Because you had been informed.
You sneaked around and read my letter.
I didn't. Where did you leave it?
I always thought you were a gentleman.
But I was wrong.
The promise I made you,
I want to take it back.
Hideko.
-I can't explain this to you.
-Get out!
-Hideko, listen to me.
-Get out of my life now!
What's your name?
My name is Vanus.
How come,
after the war had begun,
you didn't come back?
Why didn't you return
once the war had begun?
The routes were cut off.
Because I had no way to get back.
You, from where did you board the plane?
Where did you board the plane
before coming here?
I don't know what the place is called.
I don't really know where it was.
What is your objective in coming back?
Your objective...
What is it?
I came to see my lover.
For a person I love.
Who is that person you love?
Your lover.
Who is she?
In any words
I can't describe
how I feel now
That is, you
You'd understand
My heart
The voice of your heart
Please let me listen
No, I cannot
Even to listen to
the voice of my heart
is not allowed
for me, right?
It's me.
Not the man you're waiting for.
I'm going to sleep at the dock. Just came
by for a shower and a change of clothes.
Not any longer.
You'll meet the person you love.
How was he?
I was just an interpreter.
My job was to translate
what the underground said.
And translate the questions from my side.
Could you help him?
I'm just a soldier.
I only take orders from my commanders.
I beg you.
Would you please help Vanus?
Why do I have to help him?
I can't tell you.
You must give me a reason first.
Now your heart wants a reason, doesn't it?
Hideko.
-It's not--
-That's enough.
You used to tell me
that I have my own reasons.
You only have your heart. And it's enough.
You don't understand, Hideko.
I'm just a soldier. Just an interpreter.
There's nothing I can do.
I can't help you.
I can't explain it to you.
You know I am Japanese.
Hideko!
Stay still.
-How is she?
-She is fine.
Doctor Soma said Hideko is safe.
But she shouldn't move.
Because it's not good for her baby inside.
A baby?
Yes, that's right.
The baby?
Yes, it is.
She shouldn't move
because it could harm the baby inside.
The baby, congratulations!
Don't move for now.
You're going to have a baby.
The person she has been
waiting for is not me.
My time as promised is running out,
isn't it?
I'll have to leave. Now I'm working hard,
so everything is complete
before going to Burma.
Perhaps, it is long enough
to see the baby's face.
But if you don't want the baby
like you don't want me,
I'll send him to Japan.
I have told my parents in the letter
that they are getting a grandchild.
Uncle.
I came here to say goodbye to you.
I'm going to go to Burma.
However...
I'm worried about my baby.
If...
there aren't any Thai living there,
would you please
take my baby to my father and mother?
Kobori.
Angsumalin.
Vanus.
You managed to escape.
I didn't escape.
Thai people know that we are detained
by day to deceive the Japanese,
but by night, we are released to work.
I have to get to Bangkok Noi tonight.
How are you doing?
I'm fine.
Do you miss me?
I do.
But, Vanus...
everything has changed.
-I'm sorry.
-No need to say.
Your dad told me all about the wedding.
He was my interpreter on the day
I was interrogated.
But I don't know if he knew who I was.
He knew.
He told me you were arrested.
Vanus.
I'm so sorry
that I couldn't keep the promise.
That's fine. Don't worry about it.
You should make a decision now.
If you want to love someone,
love him wholeheartedly.
Ignore other concerns.
Don't think about them.
I came here so you could say it out loud.
And let yourself free.
Thank you.
Say it out loud. Believe me.
And you'll be free.
I'm leaving now.
Ang, where are you going?
I'm going to the dock.
Hideko.
That way!
Go!
Not that way!
Don't be scared.
Leave!
Hey, are you okay?
Is anyone injured?
If you are, respond!
Is anyone injured! If you are, respond!
Is anyone there?
Kobori!
Wake up!
I'll get you out of there.
You'll be fine.
I feel just gutted.
Gutted...
I can't do anything for you.
A painkiller...
Azuma...
Painkillers...
You use them for someone else...
Kobori...
Go ahead to Yasukuni
and wait for me.
I'll be there soon!
See you again.
See you then.
I wonder how it is at the dock.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Yes.
Is Mr. Kobori here?
No, he is not.
Where did he go?
He left to get on a train
bound for Bangkok.
By night, we are released to work.
I have to get to Bangkok Noi tonight.
Doctor!
Have you seen Mr. Kobori?
Anyway,
we couldn't save him...
What do you mean?
For Kobori...
I couldn't do anything...
Where's Kobori?
I couldn't do anything to save him.
I did my best.
But...
Where's Kobori?
I couldn't help him...
I just couldn't help him...
Where's Kobori?
Kobori.
Can anyone help?
Doctor! Can anyone please help?
Doctor!
Can anyone please help?
-Hideko.
-Help!
Hideko.
I'm so glad to see your face.
You wait right here.
I'm going to get a doctor.
Nobody would come to the rescue.
Someone will come to help.
You'll be fine.
Don't comfort me, Hideko.
No.
We'll live together for a very long time.
Don't fool yourself, Hideko.
Now...
I'm with you.
Hideko!
Could you smile for me?
You like my smile?
There's nothing about you that I dislike.
That day,
why didn't you accept my love?
Not because
I've just realized I love you...
I realized that a long time ago.
But I'd promised someone
that I would wait for him.
I understand.
All this time,
I tried not to love you.
I know you tried not to love me.
I can't lose you.
Nothing else matters.
I only want to love you.
And you will have to love me too, Kobori.
I love you.
You love me, Hideko!
Yes.
Don't ask me how deeply.
You're the first
and the last for me.
Keep talking.
When our baby is born,
I want him to be like you.
I want our baby to be like you, too.
Because I like everything
about you, Hideko.
When he grows up, I'll pray
for him to live long
with someone he loves.
Yes.
May they live long together.
But you can rest assured, Hideko.
I'll be around.
My heart will be with you forever.
My heart will also be with you forever.
My heart will be with you forever, Hideko.
Hideko!
Why is the sky so dark?
I can no longer see your face.
I can no longer see your face, Hideko.
I'm right here.
I'm right here. I'm not going anywhere.
I'll be up there,
always looking down on you from heaven.
Hideko.
I love you, Hideko.
I love you.
I love you...
I... love you...
I... love... you...
I love you...
You...