I never get how they can stand it.
Wake up before dawn,
get stuck in horrendous traffic,
only to arrive and toil away
in cramped cubicles all day.
Vacations?
Only on long weekends
when the whole country is overrun
by holiday-hungry mobs.
If they've had enough,
they can't just jump ship.
Why? They have bills to pay.
Their fate is sealed
until the day they retire.
Well,
the only consolation along the way
is the year-end bonus.
Today's stock market report.
Dow Jones is going through a little bump…
PAN: MARKETING DIRECTOR
125,000 BAHT
…and investors eyeing
the American stock market
are advised against
making any decisions for now.
NUCH: SECRETARY
16,500 BAHT
Damn it!
JUE: TEMP
11,500 BAHT
The 7:00 p.m. screening is better.
Firstly because we'll get there at 7:20
just as the movie starts,
and secondly because when we leave,
the rush hour will be over.
Oh, and I've booked a hotel
for our long weekend trip next year.
It's green.
We have time.
NUN: FINANCE OFFICER
27,800 BAHT
-I mean the light, not your eyes!
-It's green!
Sorry!
Did you make an offering to the Buddha?
Well, you do that at the shrine,
not at the temple!
Why did I even bother
sending you to college?
You're as dumb as your dad!
Stop right there!
Don't throw them away!
We can use the other side, see?
JIT: HOUSEKEEPER
8,250 BAHT
Mom, I'm not sure if I can make it.
I may have to go abroad for a meeting.
Yes.
Mom, I have to hang up.
My driver is already here.
Look, a 70% discount on Botox injections!
Should I buy it?
That's dirt cheap, go for it!
-I'll buy one too!
-You can save it for later!
Hey, Pan's here.
Hi, Pan.
Play the petroleum short,
dump it this afternoon.
Hold on to the coal stocks
and wait for the dividends.
THAILAND STOCK EXCHANGE
AUGUST 2012, SEPTEMBER 2012
OCTOBER 1ST
THREE MONTHS LEFT
Success…
comes from teamwork and unity.
If your hearts
beat as one…
we can overcome every obstacle in our way!
Are we all here?
Mr. Anan, please.
CHAI: HR ASSISTANT MANAGER
38,700 BAHT
I've called a meeting today.
It's really nothing urgent.
Our executive board in Korea…
MR. ANAN: MANAGING DIRECTOR
312,000 BAHT
…wants us to launch a new product.
They want
it to come out by
the beginning of next year.
Is that too soon?
Of course!
Usually, it takes us a whole year
to come up with a new product.
And we have so many public holidays
coming up. We won't make it.
If you guys can't make it,
the board probably won't approve
your year-end bonuses.
Shall I tell them now
that we can't make it?
Can we?
Or can we not?
What do you think?
I think
a super-tight deadline
can push us to try harder
to achieve our goal.
We can go through our old projects
and develop some of them.
Excellent,
that's exactly what I'm thinking!
Right, I'll let you set up a team
and head the project.
Yes, sir.
If you trust me.
Of course…
I do.
I know I can count on you, Pan.
Yes, sir.
Pan, I've got you that assistant
you've been asking for.
Where are they?
Right there.
Mr. Anan approved her himself.
Ready to work?
Sure!
Do you have a thumb drive?
I'll transfer some files
for you to work on.
Ta-da!
Don't worry, it works.
Where's the cap?
It doesn't need a cap.
The data isn't in the cap, right?
FAKE EYELASHES 800
ARMPIT HAIR REMOVAL 4,500
LEG WAX 800
MONTHLY CONDO INSTALLMENT 12,000
All that? It's only
the beginning of the month!
Squeezing yourself dry so soon!
Believe me, you need a side gig.
-Come with me to an MLM seminar.
-No MLM for me!
He didn't get the printer fixed
and didn't reimburse your cab fare,
but he got himself a new home theater set?
You've got to be kidding.
I'm not!
Yesterday I went in to have
him sign a document
and he was coming in carrying
a brand new home theater set.
I saw it with my own eyes…
-Then what?
-Go on!
Well, if it's necessary,
then he's got to have it.
Necessary? An expensive home theater set?
You said it best,
that old fart only spends
money on himself.
Right!
You're insane! Where did you hear that?
I never said anything
like that in my life.
I, Nantapond, never said that.
You did!
You said it yourself that our company
would be much better off
without that asshole as the manager.
Blasphemy! How ungrateful you girls are!
Whose corner are you in, anyway?
It doesn't matter.
What matters is
that he's in your corner now.
No way!
Believe me,
he really is in your corner right now.
-What?
-I don't get it.
Press it!
What? We're stuck!
Bee, call building maintenance!
-Well?
-It's working!
Bee, why are you calling me?
Calling you?
Help! Please!
Tomorrow at 2:00 p.m.
Please don't reschedule.
It took me two months to book you!
Okay,
I'll try later then.
Sorry,
can you get off here?
I'm not going any further.
Get off!
OCTOBER 15
Function Drink,
a vitamin and mineral beverage.
Of our old projects,
that has the highest potential
for development.
We already have the market trend
and consumer study.
And here's what I want you to do.
Nan, Eiw, get me the cost analysis.
Arm, Chanop, follow up on the formula.
Oat, find 10 references on packaging.
Kae, Bee, work on the marketing plan.
Where to push this, and who on.
I want all of this done by Friday.
Look!
No! Gross! When was it taken?
Delete it now!
And I forget to tell you one thing.
No one can take leave
before the project's concluded.
If anybody can't do it,
I'll have you replaced.
Jue, did you get the pen I sent you?
Yes, but why did you send me this?
You need a good pen to sign your checks.
I got you the best one in the province!
Do you like it?
Yes,
but please don't send
things like this to me again.
I can buy them myself.
You like it but don't want me to send it?
Mom, I have to go now.
Good luck, son!
-Thanks. How much?
-100.
I don't think they'll give out
any bonuses this year.
Drinks, sir.
Okay.
Jue, I ordered two iced teas.
Where's the other one?
Are you daft or what?
Sorry, you can take this one.
Why are you three sitting
on the same side?
So, what you do think about the Red Army?
The front line is nothing special…
but the formation is magnificent.
And what about the White Witch?
The front is fine,
the middle is toned,
and the rear is firm.
But she's devoured by the Red Devil.
Dammit, I hate the Red Devil!
You guys are so funny!
Jue, are you a Red Devil fan?
I have no idea! Whatever you say, sir.
Jue…
were you late again this morning?
Don't tell me your apartment
was on fire again.
I know it's hard to believe,
but it was really on fire again!
-Three times already, right?
-Yes.
Three times you didn't pass the probation.
Don't think you can hide it from me.
It's year-end,
and if you keep at it like this
it's time for you to find a new team.
Excuse me!
No.
The Red Devil fan has to keep himself fit.
Show us you have the energy
to be part of the team.
Be there in time for the meeting.
NO SMOKING
You can smoke.
Wai!
Turn it up.
Let's rock!
FROM: WAI
USE YOUR FULL NAME
…TEENY BIT…
LITTLE BIT
You gave me two Timeline files.
"Timeline Latest" and "Timeline Final."
Use "Latest," it's the final one.
What about "Final"?
Final means finished,
but Latest means final.
The winning number is:
seven…
five…
three.
So I'll use "Timeline Latest"?
Wait! There's also
Timeline Latest-Latest, use that one.
Ready? Go!
Can't you make it simpler?
It's simple enough.
If it's too complicated for you, just ask.
FOR YOUR CONSIDERATION
ME (WHO ELSE?)
DO NOT APPROVE
MR. PANITHAN JANEKARNKIT
I know someone who knows the winning
numbers before the announcement!
Why can't we fire her?
Wai is my friend's daughter.
What?
She's my friend's daughter.
So she has connections.
Correct.
Just bear with her.
She'll only be here for three months.
Gotcha!
You're a fast learner.
Just correct this for me.
Sure.
Go look at the format on my table.
Okay, let me put this in the fridge first.
You have to put your name
on your food here?
Even with the labels,
some cheapskate still steals the food.
-Really?
-But I have a trick.
I put the names of the bosses.
So I write Boss Pan, and no one will dare…
Where is it?
Is this yours?
BOSS PAN DOESN'T LIKE SWEETS
Just wait till I catch you!
Bee!
NOV 1ST
Our beverage comes from the core concept
that men and women have different needs,
so we've designed two variations.
We should make the pattern less
complicated to show the details.
I agree.
What about the formula?
All done, we're just waiting
for the grape juice.
Wai, what're you doing?
Get the results of the flavor test for me.
-I want them tomorrow.
-Yes.
Everyone…
I have an announcement!
Bee! Taste, don't gulp.
Our company has won…
-No!
-Don't say that!
Listen up, everybody!
Ying is pregnant again!
She just came back
from maternity leave, and now
she's the perfect human resource manager.
She's good at making humans!
Stop it!
I'm here to tell you that
I'll leave the company to raise my kids.
But let's go to my farewell party tonight!
Let's have one final blast!
Karaoke party!
Yes!
Ying…
Don't worry about the company.
I'm worried about him.
Jit!
Mr. Chai!
What're you copying?
My son's homework.
Just a couple of sheets.
Please…
A couple of sheets?
Come back here!
Where are you going?
Please, spare me!
It's only for my son's studies!
Don't turn on the light!
-Please, I'm begging you!
-Electricity's expensive!
Stop!
It's great, where did you get it?
A friend in Japan sent it.
Let me have one!
Wait! We have to hand in
an assignment tomorrow.
Let's work really hard!
With your degree,
you won't be promoted to management.
And if you're not, the salary is capped.
You need a master's, at least.
Really? What about my years of experience?
It doesn't count at all?
It does, but not here.
You have to move to another company,
then you can earn more money.
Quit! I'll quit to protest
Against my stingy boss!
Easy, or your baby will come out now!
Quit! I'll quit! Let's get it over with!
FROM NAN: GET BOSS ANAN TO SIGN.
WE NEED IT TOMORROW.
Hey, beautiful. What're you doing here?
Get up!
Turn around.
Go on, turn around.
Fine and firm body…
Just need bigger boobs,
and the customers will line up for you!
Go fill out the application form
and we'll give you an appraisal later.
I'm not here for a job.
Mr. Anan!
Excuse me!
Boss, please sign this.
Goodbye.
Hey!
-We're off at the same time!
-Let's go.
Right, "we're off at the same time."
You can still change your mind.
Done!
It's great!
Thanks!
That's it!
-Nuch!
-Boss.
For the new project,
Pan would like you to help
book appointments
with agents around the country.
But your appointments alone already
fill up my notebooks…
Right, Mr. Suraksa is out of town,
he'll be back on the 13th…
Mr. Surachai…
What? A wedding?
Mr. Surachet is available every day.
From 10:00 p.m. to 4:00 a.m.?
Okay, let me check what time other people
sleep first. I'll get back to you.
PRESENT FOR TOB
BOSS' TEA-TIME AT 2
Mr. Surasak is back but
leaving for Hong Kong…
Traveling all the time…
All right, I'll call you at 10:00 p.m.
Wednesday, Mr. Surachai
has a wedding to go to…
What? Who are you?
10:00 A.M. PICK UP A NEW SUIT
CALL MR. SURACHAI AGAIN
Okay, I'm fine.
YOU'RE MY ANGEL.
A Romeo, huh?
She's only been here a few weeks.
How come her Thai is so good?
GO SCREW YOURSELF
Enjoy it!
Let me know if it's good!
"Go screw yourself."
Send it back to him.
-"Go screw yourself."
-Go screw yourself.
-Yes!
Function Drink Product Evaluation
VERY SATISFIED
SATISFIED
INDIFFERENT
UNSATISFIED
VERY UNSATISFIED
Why didn't you put it into tables
like in the example?
It works this way too.
Numbers are boring.
Do it again, just put the numbers in.
Okay, I'll add the numbers.
I want only numbers.
Yes, sir. I will comply with your order.
-Bee.
-Yes.
Summarize the test results for me.
No, I'll do it.
I want them tomorrow by 8:00 a.m.
I told you I'll do it.
Listen, we're working as a team.
If we succeed, we succeed together.
I won't let one person who only
wants to play around wreck our work.
Just change everything
into numbers, right?
If you don't want her to do it,
I'll do it.
Hi, Wai.
Hi, Mark.
Still hitting on my mom?
You've hit the bull's eye!
Your mom is a very charming lady,
a flower among the bees.
Men circle her like vultures circle a…
Where did you learn all of this?
I think he's just pretending
to be a foreigner.
Take off your disguise, now!
That hurts, darling!
I'd better not be a nuisance
and leave the two of you alone.
Farewell my darling,
my heart remains with you though.
Kisses.
Mom,
I think I'll quit.
It's exactly what I thought it'd be,
a load of nonsense.
Come on, think of it as a
break from your routine.
You ran around a lot,
now you're learning to stay in one place.
You ran around a lot too,
and you're doing fine now.
I'm just like you.
I don't like living in a box.
Before leaving a box,
you have to know what a box looks like.
Don't you want to at least get to know it?
Maybe you'll like it.
All work, no play makes Wai a dull girl.
You're a piece of work!
I tried a new formula today
and got a lot of orders from the office.
What do you think if
I quit and open a bakery?
Opening a shop is good,
but quitting your job is too risky.
You should keep doing both for now.
If the bakery thing really works,
you can quit your job then.
But if I do both I won't have
time to focus on the bakery.
And what if the shop fails?
You should have some security.
At least you'll have the money
to buy your materials.
Do you really have to go back to work?
Yes, there're some problems.
HAVE MERCY!
NOT APPROVED
This tastes good.
NOVEMBER 21ST
ONE MONTH BEFORE THE PRESENTATION
Here you are, take your envelope, please.
-This is yours.
-What's this?
Boss Anan's daughter is getting married.
His daughter's wedding?
And we're expected to give
him goodwill money?
But can we just not give him any money?
No! That'll badly affect your
performance evaluation.
How much should we give him?
500?
Are you loaded?
20?
Crazy! I give more to beggars!
-Let's put in 30.
-You're joking!
We don't have to decide now!
It says here they'll take credit card!
That's so cool!
It's a good idea.
What? Mine's already maxed out!
Let's take a break.
JOB OPENING: FINANCIAL MANAGER
Looking at dating sites?
Life Insurance. Are you getting it?
Of course.
Badminton is a dangerous sport.
What if I broke my leg?
You should get one for yourselves too.
That doesn't sound like you at all!
Well, I think of my future too.
You're applying for
the financial manager position?
Yes.
-You call this handwriting?
-12 years of experience…
Hang on, I have to take this.
You're prettier than in the photo.
Tell me, why should we hire you?
Just a sec… Hello…
Hobby, singing karaoke.
Can you sing one for me now?
What are your weaknesses?
Why do you want to quit your present job?
Where do you see yourself in 5 years?
Get off at Phayathai Station
and take the left exit.
You're coming for a job interview?
Not in the mood to sing?
Then you can dance for me!
I'll get back to you.
Don't call us.
I'll call you.
That's right!
Thank you.
JUE, WHERE ARE YOU? WE HAVE TO SPEND
THE NIGHT WORKING AT THE OFFICE.
It's so loud, can you talk?
I'm entertaining a client in Hong Kong,
Just speak up!
Hong Kong?
Well, remember Aunt Wan?
Aunt Wan, Bo's mother?
I can't, which Wan?
Just tell me what you want.
Bo's just graduated.
She wants to find work in Bangkok.
Can you help her?
Will you come home for New Year's?
I don't know, can I tell you later?
I have to get back to my client now. Bye!
I've saved up money to be with my honey.
But I have to work all night,
isn't it crazy?
Boss always keeps us busy,
that's my life story.
Boss wants us to work like buffaloes.
That doesn't rhyme!
Boss and buffaloes, they don't rhyme?
No playing, no sleeping, no Facebook.
Can't take leave,
can't get sick, can't do nothin'!
Can't leave early, can't be sneaky,
can't show I'm sleepy.
I want to be buried…
No, that's too much…
I just need more coffee!
It seems you still have lots of energy!
Is this a night of poetry?
Now that rhymes.
What about our grape supply?
Is it confirmed?
Let me check.
Just a sec, I'll check and let you know.
Jue, pick it up!
Jue, come here.
What's the matter?
Did you call to confirm
our order of grapes?
Did I have to call them?
Of course!
They didn't hear from us,
so they've already sold all the grapes!
We can't get any now!
I'm sorry… Last night, I…
-I came down with appendicitis.
-Cut the crap!
Last month you had that too.
How many appendices do you have, huh?
Get me some grapes now!
-Grow it, rob it, steal it, I don't care!
-Calm down.
Do we have any other suppliers?
No. They must've sold their supply by now.
We just lost our last one.
Still got some?
So I'll see you there, okay?
Well, I know a supplier.
If you still want it.
DECEMBER 7TH
2 WEEKS BEFORE PRESENTATION
We're going to a vineyard,
not going sailing.
Sure, this is my vineyard costume.
If you want me to help you drive,
just say, okay?
Full tank.
I'll get some snacks,
do you want anything?
Iced coffee.
Sorry, I can't go with you.
This trip is very critical to my project.
Are you at the wedding?
Yes. Look, it's so beautiful!
A gazebo by the sea, just like in a movie!
Everything is so casual and cool.
Let's do it like this!
But it's so far from Bangkok.
Not many people would want to show up.
We'd get little goodwill money.
But a wedding is
a once-in-a-lifetime thing.
Who's that?
Just my staff.
I'll go back this evening, see you soon.
Okay. Bye.
This is yummy, want some?
I don't eat junk food.
Where's my iced coffee?
You already got it.
No, I didn't.
Really?
I bought it! Where is it?
It can't have just vanished!
The market price at this moment…
We can make a higher offer than--
Yes, the Full Moon Party is so wild!
Sex on the beach, huh?
Not that wild!
I also went to sell postcards
in Chiang Khan, there!
Lots of sexy young things.
It's cold up there
so they're all wrapped up,
not to my taste.
Then you have to go to Phuket.
I took a Japanese group there.
The girls were super-hot!
That hot? If they sweat with me
I wouldn't mind at all!
You have to stay the night
so we can party!
Sure thing!
Joy, I can't go back tonight.
Let's get sloshed!
Yippie! Get sloshed!
So will you sell me your grapes?
I will, but don't talk about it now
or I'll change my mind!
No more ice? How can we party without ice?
-No ice, no deal!
What is it with women and snacks?
You're drunk and you still want to snack.
Snacks these days suck,
they don't give you free goodies
in the bag anymore.
So you like snacks
or you like the goodies?
It's not like those Japanese snacks
that come with cartoon stickers.
You know that too!
I thought you didn't eat junk food.
I never ate it,
I just bought it to get the stickers.
Really? Me too!
My friends at school threw away
the snacks and kept only the stickers!
Right! What were the popular ones?
Dragon Ball!
And the animal set!
The World Cup stickers too!
And there was this one
that was so hard to find.
I had to trade so many stickers to get it.
Then you know what?
It turned out to be a fake!
Did you ever get that?
Wai?
Come on, you just bragged about
your epic boozing in Pai!
Sissy.
A hangover?
No, but my stomach feels weird.
Who painted this?
It's very quirky.
That little drunk did.
She's always dreamt of being a cartoonist.
She talks about it all the time.
But this picture is an image
from my own dream.
In that shallow grave is my wife!
Keep dreaming, old bugger!
The third row? I'll follow you there.
HIS NOSE IS RED 'CAUSE
HE DIPPED IT INTO THE PAINT.
I'M BOILING…
Here, your dream.
Tell me, why did you come
to work at the office?
Mom made me.
But I'll quit soon.
Just bear with me for a while.
Do you write down
everything you want to do?
Yes.
Don't you get tired of doing
everything like clockwork?
And don't you get tired of being
so random and unorganized?
No. Your way is more boring.
"10 Things to Do Next Year."
You plan ahead into next year?
Do you already have a plan
for where to die?
You should try.
Maybe you can realize your
dream of being a cartoonist.
You don't know a thing.
If it were that easy I'd be famous by now.
What I need is some inspiration.
Whoa! That's deep!
And don't you have a dream?
You're obsessed with making money.
It's called "security."
Security? There's no such thing.
A truck might ram into this car
and kill us at the next curve.
The more things are insecure,
the more carefully we have to prepare.
Wai.
Wai?
What's wrong?
What?
So this is what an appendix looks like.
First time I've ever seen one.
-Look.
-Disgusting!
You have one in you too!
Bee, that's for the patient!
Next, you'll be eating the hamper!
No way!
Hello, Pan.
So, is this part of your "insecurity"?
I'm sure you didn't plan
to have your appendix removed.
It's not funny,
why don't you pay this month's salary now?
Payday is weeks away!
-Shouldn't you take care of your staff?
-I can lend you some.
SINCE WHEN ARE THEY BEST BUDDIES?
I thought the company
had welfare benefits.
HE MUST'VE ALREADY STORMED HER BARN!
You just joined us, you're not covered.
WAI!
I'll lend it to you first.
You can pay me back in installments.
You want to charge interest!
CUT OFF HER OXYGEN
Not in the first six months, okay?
SHE'S NOT ON OXYGEN
My mom will come tomorrow.
PUT HER APPENDIX BACK
They already did it!
THEY ALREADY DID IT!
Who did what?
The numbers for the project.
We just did the calculation together.
It's late, I should get going.
-It's just 7:00!
-I go to bed early.
I'm going too, take care.
Thank you. Bye!
You'll have time to read these.
GET RICH QUICK
Are you insane?
Who'd want to read these in a hospital?
I like this one.
And you should read this too.
"10 Things You Should Do Next Year."
Read it.
If I were you,
I'd plan ahead what to do
and what not to do next year.
Why?
We have freedom,
we can do anything or go anywhere
as long as we don't burden others,
isn't that enough?
Do you really think your life
belongs only to you?
Now, you can go backpacking
anywhere you want.
You have freedom, you're happy.
But what about 5 years from now?
What about in 10 years or 20?
Don't you want to be more
and do more for other people?
Take them back.
Excuse me, bath time.
DECEMBER 20TH
1 DAY BEFORE PRESENTATION
Boss Pan!
We sent the wrong file to the printer.
What's this?
A label for fabric softener.
This company sells beverages.
Haven't I told you not to do freelance
work in the office?
You know it's tomorrow, right?
Can we present the project
without the label?
I told you we'd need it!
No, I'll go!
-I'll come with you!
-Why?
You're a drag!
So we'll use this copy:
"The beverage that enhances your health."
Okay.
We'll also sell skin benefits
to female consumers, right?
Yes, and how many kinds
of minerals do we have?
16.
Why does it say 13 here? Who wrote this?
At first, you said 13!
When did it become 16?
It was always 16! Ask her!
Power out! We still haven't printed it!
We still haven't printed it!
Wait!
We need you to print something.
We're closed for the New Year.
Hang on!
This is urgent, please!
No, we're closed.
Did you turn off the air-con?
So it's you! We're still working,
why did you cut the power?
It wasn't me! The whole building is out!
It's back!
-Damn, it's a mess.
-Shit!
The power outage must've
knocked out the hard drive!
What's in there?
Every file we need for tomorrow.
Please!
Just pop in this CD and press print,
it'll only take a few minutes!
-Please, I beg you!
-No.
I'm in deep shit, please help me!
Have some mercy!
No.
Can't you say something else, huh?
Are you dumb? All you can say is "No"?
I apologize on behalf of my trainee.
What?
I'm the son of the managing director.
Huh?
Was the UPS on?
-It's broken.
-Why didn't you send it to the center?
I've requested a new one,
but the order hasn't been approved.
My team never got anything approved,
unlike their team!
-It's not true!
-How could you say that?
-I even have to buy my own pens!
-No!
My company has been your client
for a long time.
My dad is very close to your boss,
Sornchai.
This project is worth a billion baht.
What would your boss say
if he knew you closed the door on us?
Yes, a billion baht!
SORNCHAI PRINTING
Stop it!
We've lost the files,
so we'll do it again!
All right? We still have time.
Not again!
What's that noise?
Your dad's close to Boss Sornchai?
SIRACHAI PRINTING
And what's my boss's name again?
Sirachai, yes, it's a tongue twister!
Right, he didn't say it clearly.
SIRICHAI PRINTING
That's it, Sirichai!
I respect him like my own uncle!
Sirichai, of course!
Let's not push it.
My room has an entire
stock of office supplies.
Papers, staples,
printers, ink, everything.
But we lost the files
that took us a whole month to finish.
I don't think we can do
it all again in one night.
Luckily, I backed up
everything two days ago.
-Bee!
-Sorry!
It's broken!
Listen, some screws are loose.
-It's gone.
-We're finished.
Luckily,
I have two more backup drives at home.
Two more…
Go now.
I don't want to miss my last bus home.
Please listen to us!
Okay, I'll pay you
5,000 baht extra.
City slickers…
You think money can buy everything?
You always have to get what you want!
You never think of other
people's feelings.
Please forgive my trainee.
See what you've done, huh?
Hey, bro…
I know how hard it is
for poor country people
who've come to work in Bangkok.
But the reason you keep working hard
is because
of those who're waiting for you at home.
I'm…
I'm exactly in your shoes.
Stop it.
Well…
I haven't gone home in 5 years.
Hurry up.
I still want to go see my mother.
So you'll do it for us?
Shut up and come in!
So you're not from Bangkok either?
I look like a city guy
but I'm from the South.
Thank you so much!
Get the CD, the computer's in there.
Come in.
Power sockets are here and behind the TV.
Kitchen's here.
And the toilet.
Boss Pan,
I don't think we'll make it. We should
tell them to postpone the presentation.
I don't think it's worth
putting so much time and effort into it.
Yesterday,
Bee had a bout of dyspepsia again.
We're employees,
not slaves.
They can't order us around.
And the spare change called "bonus"
that they use to seduce us…
we're not begging for it.
I know…
that the reason you all come to work
is not just to get paid every month.
Every time
we launch a new product
we're excited
to see if it'll become a hit.
You know that feeling, don't you?
Think about it.
Besides money,
what're we doing this for?
Tonight, we're doing it for that thing.
Not for the company.
Let's do it.
So we'll use,
"Everyday drink for your health"?
-Yes.
-I'll print it now.
Wai! When did you get out?
Just this evening.
I called Nan and we came straight here.
-You're sure you're okay?
-I'm super-fine, look!
Blood!
Wait, lie down first!
Should I call an ambulance?
Easy, easy!
We got it!
-Great! Let's get the mock-up done!
-Yes.
Oat, let's finish the mock-up.
And the bottles?
Bee!
That's work, you can't drink it!
I'm sorry, I'm thirsty!
Snacks, everyone!
We'd better do it like this.
We should tweak this a little too,
don't you think?
Have some water.
Jue…
Thanks.
I know you're working,
but it's already midnight.
No, it's 2:00 in the morning!
It's a racket in there!
-My son couldn't go to sleep!
-Your boy's so cute!
-What's his name?
-Poon.
Look!
Come on, kiddo.
Scare her with a ghost face.
-Nice one!
-Scary!
Look who's scarier!
You're popping your eyes out!
Do it again, son!
Can you do better than me?
Super scary!
Brilliant!
You dazzled me with your numbers and data!
What did the board think?
They seemed to like it.
But they've decided to shelve it for now.
They want to wait until the price
of grapes goes down first.
And what about…
the bonus?
With the project shelved
and the economy being as it is,
I don't think we'll get any bonus.
But maybe we will…
-Or maybe not.
-Mr. Anan…
Pan…
This is the reality of office life.
Mr. Anan!
Pan, what's up?
We've been working so hard the whole year.
I think the company should reward us.
And the right thing to do…
is for you to go
and convince them to approve the bonus.
Pan. All you think about is money, right?
You're right, I want money.
And I think it's the same for everybody.
What's wrong with wanting
to earn more money to improve our lives?
And most importantly,
it's the money we deserve.
Okay, I'll think about it.
Mr. Anan,
that's what I say
when I actually want to say, "No."
Correct.
It's all right.
DECEMBER 24TH
CHRISTMAS EVE
I got it, sir.
But I only got the 1-meter Christmas tree,
the 2-meter ones are sold out.
Only 1 meter?
My son's party won't be so grand then!
So…
Can you try again tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Okay, Boss.
To Sai Noi.
-Sai Noi.
-No.
-At least take me to Kae Rai.
-I'm not going.
Take me to Mo Chit at least.
Okay, take me wherever you're going.
Not going?
Really?
PROJECT SHELVED. NO BONUS!
Taking a cab from Asoke to Sai Noi,
your job must be very well-paid.
I just got off late. No more buses,
I have to take a cab.
You're not turning here?
It's a detour if you go straight.
This is my job, I know what I'm doing!
YES! MY FIRST BOOK HAS BEEN PUBLISHED!
COME CHECK OUT THE NEW COLLECTION
AT MY SHOP!
THANK YOU, EVERYONE, I'M SO HAPPY!
COME TO THE NEW YEAR'S EVE PARTY.
FROM MR. ANAN: BRING GIFT BASKETS
TO OUR AGENTS ON NYE.
Dumbass! Keep left if you're so damn slow!
Can't you let me pass! Rich asshole!
These office people work
in air-con rooms all day.
Done at 5:00 p.m., have weekends off.
Long holidays during
New Year and festivals.
More choices. Good pay.
Bonuses every year.
Move! I'm trying to make a living here!
Damn it!
Everyone's making a living, get it?
Does it look like I'm begging, huh?
Making a living?
You didn't even turn on the damn meter!
Go left, trust me!
Are you dumb? Just drive as I tell you to!
Do exactly as I say, get it?
How do you know office work is cozy, huh?
It's a pain in the freakin' ass!
You want to quit driving
and try the office?
Left, I said left, left, left!
You missed it!
Make a U-turn! Step on it!
Go!
You have to wait until the board
meeting this Friday.
I'll refer it back to you
and we'll go from there.
Yes.
When can you start?
After the New Year.
Don't you have to clear
your work at the office?
To hell with it…
I mean, I don't have to.
-So you'll take me?
-Yes.
Thank you! Thank you!
Please don't change your mind!
DECEMBER 28TH
LAST WORK DAY OF THE YEAR
This is your evaluation.
I hope you understand.
Sign here.
JUE LAKSAMEEPONG, TRAINEE
MANAGING DIRECTOR
PLEASE APPROVE APPOINTMENT
OF NEW HR MANAGER
Yes.
Really?
Joy! The Korean headquarters wants me
to move there next year!
Come with me!
How can I do that?
We can move together.
We sell the car
and rent out the apartment.
And don't worry about work.
They'll pay me four times more
than what I earn now!
I can take care of you.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity, right?
It's time for the biggest prize!
Which team will win
our fancy-dress competition?
This is the "Uniform" category!
And the winners are…
Nan's team!
It's a great dress.
Must've spent a lot of money on it!
Mr. Anan will do the honor
of giving out the prize.
The prize from our MD
must be something special!
I think it's an iPad.
No, it's a water filter!
Nan, how do you feel?
I'm overjoyed!
A water filter is great.
Maybe things will flow
more smoothly around here.
See, everything's stuck,
especially the bonus!
Am I right?
Of course I am
because the manager
has spent all the profit!
Well, for our own safety
-let's move on to the dance floor!
-Music!
What's this uniform?
EXACT CHANGE ONLY
Look at this!
Easy, easy! Don't tear the plastic!
Wait!
Bee,
we can't put this in Eiw's car anyway.
-Just leave it here!
-No!
I got this from the draw.
How could I just dump it?
I'll go pee, come with me.
This is nonsense!
Why did they get a mattress as a prize?
How can we bring it back?
-Wai, you've been here three months.
-Yes.
So you're leaving us.
What's your plan next?
I'll help my friend
run a resort on Kood Island.
Sounds like a good life.
Good luck!
Thanks.
You can't fall asleep here!
One, two, three!
I can't do this!
I told you to leave it but you insisted!
Come on! One, two, three!
I've never seen Boss Pan
this lively before.
He must be so happy to be moving to Korea.
Look at this move!
Are you taking any trips
over the New Year?
I don't know.
Have you finished writing,
"10 Things I Have To Do Next Year?"
I don't know what to write down.
You? Don't know what to write?
Because of this Korean job,
you have to change your plan…
I'm not going anywhere.
Why not?
Let me ask you something.
When people talk about their "dreams,"
it's always about…
opening a bakery…
writing a book…
writing songs,
or making movies. Right?
Me, I want to make a lot of money…
so I can take good care
of the people I love.
Doesn't that count as a dream too?
DECEMBER 31ST
NEW YEAR'S EVE
HONG KONG TRIP
JOY'S BIRTHDAY
8TH ANNIVERSARY
CHOOSE A RING
Mom…
Is it okay if I'm not coming home?
I have some problems at work.
I have to go to…
It's all right, son.
I'll tell Aunt Wan you're busy.
You have to have some rest too.
I know work is important,
but don't get sick because of it.
Mom.
Actually…
about my work…
it's not as good as I told you.
It's all right.
I understand.
Bangkok…
is a tough place.
It's never easy.
Just do your best.
Don't care how others look at you.
Let them say what they want.
I don't care if people think
you're not as good as they are.
I'm so happy that you've tried so hard.
Look, I've made your favorite curries.
Lots of them.
If you can, come back to taste it.
Going to a countdown party?
-Good evening.
Mr. Surachet, it's me, Nuch.
Boss Anan asked me
to bring you the presents.
Here you are!
I've heard you on the phone so many times!
This is Surasak, Surachai, and Surachart.
Nice to meet you all.
I'd better go now.
Wait!
We were just saying
that since you took over
from the previous secretary,
everything has been running so smoothly.
Thank you.
Let me put it frankly…
Come work with me.
What? I was about to ask her!
You didn't!
I run a big business and
offer good benefits!
-I asked her first!
-I'll double your salary!
Plus a 4-month bonus
No traffic here on New Year's Eve.
But we'll get stuck on the highway.
We'll be in the mountains by sunrise.
-Stop the car!
-What?
Someone left the light on in my office!
So? Will you go and turn it off?
Tell me, all this saving you've
done over the years…
Has someone ever said thank you?
Stop! Stop!
Are you out of your mind?
I'm asking you, have they ever
thanked you for what you've done?
I told you to stop!
BEST ENERGY-SAVING COMPANY
Who turned off the light?
We're waiting for the fireworks!
Let's eat.
Go on, make it spicy.
What?
No, Mr. Chai!
To watch the fireworks,
you have to turn off the light.
They'll be even brighter.
Mr. Chai, please join us.
Have some grilled fish.
-Your plate.
-Give him some.
My husband.
-Good evening.
This is my daughter,
and this is my grandson.
He's a young man now!
We should go to the expressway
to watch the fireworks!
Shut up!
Don't shout into my ears!
Don't! Swallow it!
This is your car, and you're wasted!
You guys are hopeless.
If I weren't here who'd be driving you?!
Nan, from us.
Lovely!
Thank you!
I crack up just seeing Bee's face!
You can put it on your new desk.
So you know?
Yes.
And we don't want you to leave!
Please don't leave us!
Help me convince her!
It's for her own good!
And don't do that, it's dangerous!
You will cause trouble.
What's that light?
Nan!
Hang in there, I'll go get help.
Sargent!
Sargent.
Let my friend out!
We haven't been drinking!
Sargent, this thing is broken! Try it!
I'm a captain, not a sergeant!
If you won't let her out,
put us in there too!
Come on, lock us all in there!
We're coming, Nan, we won't leave you!
Throw us in there!
Do it now!
"10 Things You Should Do Next Year."
1. Name files in a way that
people can understand.
2. Remove the virus in your thumb drive.
3. Stop using slang in office documents.
4. Sort out your social security.
It'll help if you get fired.
5. Make a financial plan
in case of a family emergency.
6. Join a writer's workshop.
7. Don't go backpacking just
because famous writers
make it seem glamorous!
Bus to Trat is leaving now!
8. Even artists need to plan.
Draft your manuscript carefully.
9. It's hard.
But if you don't start,
you won't go anywhere.
10. If you fail, start again.
Don't lose heart,
because at least you know you've
done something.
Do it now.
Hi! Looking for your friend?
Yes.
He's on the rooftop
waiting for the fireworks.
Go on, my son's up there too.
Thank you.
You said you didn't know
what your New Year's resolution was.
So I wrote down some for you.
First,
be strict with yourself.
But cut other people some slack.
Do crazy things.
Because it can make people smile.
Snacking.
It's not healthy for the body,
but it is for the mind.
Make your plan flexible.
Because even when things go wrong,
it doesn't kill anybody.
And forget your past mistakes.
Because you've done your best.
That's all
I could think of.
Maybe
you want to try it.
APRIL 1ST
THREE MONTHS AFTER THE NEW YEAR
I never get how they can stand it.
Wake up before dawn,
get stuck in horrendous traffic,
only to arrive and toil away
in cramped cubicles all day.
Vacations?
Only on long weekends
when the whole country is overrun
by holiday-hungry mobs.
If they've had enough,
they can't just jump ship.
Why? They have bills to pay.
Their fate is sealed until
the day they retire.
SUPER SALARYMAN
The only consolation along the way
is the year-end bonus.
-It's green.
-So soon?
I mean your eyes, not the light!
I see.
INVESTED AMOUNT
When will you begin your master's degree?
Next year.
Hi!
SURACHET COMMERCE
She bought it!
Jit! I've told you not to dry
your salted meat here!
It's not mine!
Who else would do this? It's yours! Jit!
Two iced teas,
two black coffees, and two coffees.
Are you Jue?
Bo, Aunt Wan's daughter!
Didn't you recognize me?
I almost didn't!
I never get how they can stand it.
Maybe it's not just money
that makes them get up
to go to work every day.
STORY OUTLINE, CHARACTERS, SETTINGS
A package for you!
NO VIRUS, AND WITH A CAP!
THE STORY IS INTERESTING
THE DRAWING IS LOVELY AND UNIQUE
THE GAGS ARE SPREAD OUT
AND WORK JUST FINE
THE FIRST PART DRAGS A LITTLE,
BUT CAN BE PERFECT WITH SOME EDITING
ALL IN ALL, AN IMPRESSIVE FIRST BOOK
THINGS YOU SHOULD CONSIDER:
1. DESIGN AN ATTRACTIVE COVER
2. DON'T USE HIGH-QUALITY PAPER,
TOO EXPENSIVE
3. 100 BAHT RETAIL PRICE IS THE BEST
PERFECT TO PAY FOR WITH A 100-BAHT NOTE
ARE YOU FREE OVER THE LONG WEEKEND?
LET'S GO FIND SOME TASTY SNACKS.