[epic orchestral music playing]
[swooshes]
[swooshing]
[man] I'm not your average guy.
I handle pressure better than most.
Yeah, my parents are dead,
and I don't have any friends,
but God gives everyone a challenge, right?
I'm smart, talented, hard working.
Success should be just around the corner.
But I have this problem.
I…
I haven't been able to sleep in months.
[tense music playing]
[clamoring]
[screaming]
[clamoring continues]
[grunts]
[sinister music plays]
[clamoring continues]
[sinister music continues]
[groaning]
[screams]
[groans]
[panting]
[somber music plays]
[banging on door]
[lighter clicks]
[banging continues]
[coughing]
[coughing continues]
[banging on door]
[landlord] Hey!
Hey, I know you're in there!
Open the door or I'll break it down.
You're gonna hide from me, huh?
I've now grown impatient with you.
You artists are such freaks or just…
Well, I've had it!
Come out now! I have leftovers.
Eat them, get out! Don't you dare
starve to death in my house!
-[banging]
-Open this door!
Come on, open up!
Open up!
[man 1] Watch it!
[professor] What are dreams?
Some believe that dreams
are a kind of reality
that the soul encounters
when it leaves the body.
From that perspective,
our world is the true dream.
One out of many.
[shaman] You dream of someone
chasing you to collect a debt.
When they catch you,
-you pay with your life.
-[professor] In fact,
Sigmund Freud and Carl Jung
reached similar conclusions
as China's own Duke of Zhou.
[woman] This earth is a cage
that humans have been locked in
by a more advanced species.
They feared our intelligence.
We all have great wisdom and power
hidden deep within us.
Once we unlock it,
humans can re-experience the past,
change the future.
Become omnipotent.
That's why our jailers only allow us
to develop 10 to 15%
of our brain capacity.
The rest is off-limits.
In every brain, they have placed
a horrible monster
to make sure we never access
our true power.
punishing intruders with no mercy.
How can we reach our power
with the enemy lying in our nightmares?
[shaman] These charms can help you
ward off bad experience.
[thumping]
These practices have been
passed down by our ancestors.
You can believe in it, or not.
Like all of us,
your fate has already been written.
[professor] According to Jung,
dreams are the path to the subconscious.
Only in dreams can people go
into the darkest corners of their minds
and see their true selves.
Often what they find, scares them.
[woman] What is schizophrenics?
It's someone who's seen
what is not supposed to.
[atmospheric music playing]
Excuse me.
One, please.
[sizzling]
[gasps]
And no egg.
[gentle music playing]
♪ The drizzling rain with soft wind
Leaning onto the street at dusk ♪
♪ With the wind still slapping my face
With rain no longer blurring my eyes ♪
♪ I looked up to the lonely street light ♪
♪ Where a sad love story came to my mind ♪
♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like your breathtaking eyes ♪
♪ I like your delightful laughter ♪
♪ Just like yesterday ♪
-[tapping]
-♪ You and me ♪
Hey, I said no eggs.
It's on me.
[chuckles softly]
There you are.
Thank you.
Why aren't you answering my calls, huh?
-Are you pushing me?
-I'm not pushing.
-We're gonna talk now.
-I'll get back to you.
-Give me two days!
-Why are you running? Stop!
Get back here!
[grunts]
[lively beat plays]
[panting]
[groans]
[pants]
[sighs]
[retching]
[slurping loudly]
[slurping continues]
You really let me down, man.
You broke our contract.
I can sue you,
you want that?
[Sang Yu] San,
I something very serious to tell you.
This bowl
represents the human mind.
There's a fish moving around
that represent your consciousness.
The rest of the water, which is empty,
represents the subconscious.
[slurping]
When conscious mind
leaves the subconscious behind,
it's like a fish out of water.
I'm just like this fish.
-I'm dying here.
-[waitress] Enjoy your noodles.
Hey! Don't touch that!
Wait. Are you telling me this is all
because of your insomnia?
When I try to sleep,
my nightmares find me.
At first,
I even thought I was schizophrenic.
Or maybe cursed.
-It's something else.
-If you can't sleep, then write!
I can't barely concentrate on it.
Then give me back the advance.
I spent it already.
Spend it on what?
I think you're just lazy!
You don't even try to work,
you keep making excuses.
I'll give you ten more days.
Do you think your writing is so special?
I took a big risk
when I hired you to write this.
It should be easy money for you!
So, whatever you need to do, do it!
Just please make it quick.
Pull yourself together!
[gloomy music]
[rattles]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[somber music]
[thuds]
-[woman] I'm done.
-[man] Let's get of here.
Come again.
[stomach growling]
[stomach growls]
[yawning]
[keyboard clacking]
[stomach growls]
[whooshing]
[ominous music]
[footsteps thumping]
[grunting]
[choking]
[thudding]
[exhales]
[sighs]
[reflecting music playing]
[Sang Yu] San,
I'm sorry.
I can't write the script.
I guess I'll have to pay you back
in the next life.
I can't keep going like this.
If I can't fight the nightmares,
then I'll never be able to face
the reality there.
I don't think I can tell
the difference anymore between reality
and my dreams.
This feeling,
it's too much to handle.
[emotional music playing]
Everything I ever wanted
is getting further away from me.
My life doesn't mean anything.
Not anymore.
I wanna see my friends again.
Say goodbye.
[vendor] Hey! Want some breakfast?
This time with egg and sausage!
On the house!
[sobbing]
[emotional music rising]
[whimpers]
Tastes so good…
I definitely owe you for this,
but I'm afraid I can't pay you back.
We all hit a rough spot now and then.
Nothing we can't beat, huh?
I must have done
something horrible in my past life,
I think I'm paying for it in this one.
Paying day and night.
I'm paying all the time!
Come on, what are you talking about?
[chuckles]
What was so bad, young man?
Breakup?
You were fired?
Insulted?
[laughs]
None of those things owed your life.
I used my life every night
in my nightmares, it is horrible.
I can't sleep anymore because of it.
How do you expect me to deal with that?
How about next time you dream,
just wake up before you die?
[atmospheric music plays]
How will I do that?
Face it, I'm hopeless.
[sniffles]
You know,
it's strange that people wish to die.
They always say,
"I'm better off dead."
Then they keep on living
just the same, don't they?
[gentle music playing]
So, you see,
wishing for death
reminds us that we're still alive.
By the same logic,
if you wanna wake up,
just say,
"I'm only dreaming."
And you just might wake up.
[chuckles]
[both laughing]
[delicate music plays]
In this condition,
I'm gonna give you 20.
[woman] Sang Yu?
Is that really you?
What happened?
Do you need some help?
But don't you don't remember me at all?
Come on.
Let's go get something to eat.
It's okay.
[cracking]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[bang on window]
[tense music playing]
[gasping]
Hello? Ambulance here right away.
[gasps]
[grunting]
[squelching]
[vendor] If you wanna wake up, just say,
"I'm only dreaming."
I'm only dreaming.
[groans]
[intense choral music plays]
[groaning]
[panting]
[warbling]
-[thumps]
-[gasps]
[mysterious music plays]
[panting]
Ow.
[mysterious music continues]
-[clanks]
-[gasps]
This is all a dream!
I said I'm dreaming! I'm dreaming!
[eerie music]
[shouting]
[yelling]
[man] It's too crowded here.
Let's go over there.
[overlapping chatter]
Hey.
You got something? Let's take a look.
Hey, don't be shy. Come on.
Oh, she's heavy.
You made this?
Um…
I'll trade you
for this piece here.
It's famous, you know?
Stabbed someone royal.
Hey, he's not making that up.
All these swords have a story.
Hey, this is just some old piece of junk.
I'll buy it, thousand Yuan.
-How about you go bother someone else?
-How about my offer?
Listen, here's what we'll do.
You give me that sword,
I'll give you 2,000 cash.
-Hey, where are you going?
-Come back! I'll double it!
I can do 5,000.
30,000 Yuan, all right?
Or…
20,000 Yuan.
[store owner] Why are you so hunched over?
Stand up straight when you're mushed up.
[upbeat music plays]
[receptionist] Hi.
Hey.
I'd like a room, please.
[upbeat music continues]
Ah! Uh!
[sighs]
[knock on door]
[footsteps thumping]
[electricity crackles]
[eerie music]
[squeaks]
[clattering]
Hello?
I'm only dreaming.
This a dream!
[dramatic music]
[footsteps thumping]
[warbling]
[thuds]
[intense music plays]
[gasps]
[tense music]
[groaning]
[tense music intensifies]
[powerful music playing]
[growls]
It is only a dream!
It's only a dream!
[grunts]
[panting]
[gasping]
[upbeat music]
[heavy clang]
[hawks]
[swallows]
[lively electronica beat plays]
[people cheering]
[upbeat music]
[chattering, laughter]
[laughter]
[woman 1] I had so much fun! Thank you!
[giggles]
This is my room.
[chuckling]
[moaning, chuckling]
[door chimes]
[grunts]
What the fuck?
[giggling]
For your cab.
Mm!
Dinner's on me.
Good night.
-[woman 2] Hey, asshole!
-[thumps]
[sighs]
[groans]
[eerie music]
[gasps]
[bouncy orchestral music playing]
[chuckling, gasping]
I'm really dreaming now!
[whistling]
[cackles]
Hm?
[sighs]
[gasps]
[orchestral music continues]
[inhales deeply]
[ominous choral music plays]
-[gasps]
-[blast]
[gasping]
[glass shattering]
[gunfire]
[intense choral music continues]
[grunts]
[thumps]
[groans]
[footsteps thumping]
[grunts]
[gunfire]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[panting]
[foreboding music]
[intense music continues]
[cackling]
I'm dreaming!
[groaning]
[sighs]
[laughs]
[screaming, laughing]
[upbeat electronica music plays]
[laughs]
[man] What is it?
Right, right.
That's good.
Mr. Sang, I wanted to ask.
Where did you get these items?
And why that does matter?
Don't get the wrong idea.
In this business,
everyone has trick to up their sleeve.
Tomb raiding, or smuggling…
It doesn't matter to me either way.
Just as long as nothing comes back on us,
right?
When it's finished?
[laughs]
Please, I mean nothing.
It's my hope
you'll come to us again in the future.
See you then. We're looking forward to it.
[car horn honks]
Sang Yu?
Sang Yu!
What the…
[ominous music]
[scoffs]
What?
I thought you were gonna kill yourself.
Why aren't you dead?
-Hold on.
-Fuck you!
Let's grab dinner sometime.
You think I'm stupid?
San, really,
let me take you to dinner.
[clears throat]
If I end up having to pay, I'll kill you.
Why did you send me those insane texts?
It's almost like…
You know, I can't figure it out.
You're like a completely new person.
What happened
to that tortured genius writer I found?
I liked you better then,
at least you had my respect.
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Twenty grand. I wanna make it up to you.
It's my way of saying…
Well,
I hope you aren't upset.
[San] Dude,
if you found a way to get rich fast,
you gotta teach me.
[hiccups]
[mellow music]
Oh!
Hello.
What can I get for you?
-Latte.
-Okay.
[beeping]
Coming right up.
[machine whirring]
Can I get you anything else?
Do you remember me?
[chuckles softly]
I'll remember you next time.
Why are you selling your café?
No customers. No profits.
-How much do you want for it?
-Why do ask?
You want it?
Just give me a number.
Between rent, renovation, and equipment…
I think I need one and a half million.
[club music plays]
[Sang Yu]
I'm dying to tell her how I feel.
[San] Just go for it!
Look, I've analyzed the whole thing.
Firstly, you're a screenwriter.
You have a way with words,
No problem expressing yourself.
And secondly, you're loaded!
It's a done deal.
Money can, I'm sorry for speaking,
help a man a lot.
She can't resist you.
[laughs]
[panting]
[groans]
[groaning]
[panting]
Okay.
[sighs]
I'm outta here.
If you need something, just call me.
I'm leaving!
[quirky music]
[gasps]
[groans]
[sighs, groans]
I'm dreaming!
[whimpers]
[inhales deeply]
[clears throat] Uh…
So what now?
Dude, did you get crazy superpowers
somehow, huh?
I think God has chosen you.
This has to be some kind of reward
to make up for all
of the suffering in your life.
I… I… I…
I think I should be your partner.
That's enough, San.
Be cool.
If you need anything at all,
I will making it happen.
I swear, from this moment,
you're my brother.
-Get up.
-No, I won't. Never.
[scoffs]
This. What does this mean?
Well, I was hoping to buy this place.
But I want you to stay and run it.
I'll cover the losses.
And we'll share
the profit.
[taps]
Hey.
Are you busy right now?
[Sang Yu] This is the best restaurant.
They always find a table for me.
I think you're gonna love it.
Sang Yu…
I feel like I've heard
that name before somewhere.
The name is part of the saying,
"Lose something, gain something."
Now you know.
[chuckles]
Why do you wanna buy my shop?
Um…
I'm a pretty serious coffee drinker.
And the location is good.
I wouldn't know how to run it,
I'd mess up the good job you're doing.
That's why.
I'm not so sure.
I'm losing money.
It needs…
a little nurturing.
I'll say just it some time, it'll be fine.
Liking coffee
is just not the same as business.
I'll send over a contract tomorrow.
We'll bear the profits and losses equally.
I accept.
You should read the contract.
I already trust you.
I think you're interested in something
other than my business.
[coughs, clears throat]
I just wanna say, if you're married
or taken in any other way,
then don't waste your breath.
[traffic noises]
[Beethoven's
Symphony No. 5 in C minor playing]
[cackles]
Whoo!
[alarm blaring]
[cackles]
[door whirring]
[grunts]
[panting]
[intense music plays]
[cackles]
Whoo!
[continues cackling]
[grunts]
[intense music continues]
[yells]
[loud thud]
[loud bang]
Oh, wow!
[San] I just fell asleep.
-It's still hot, careful.
-Thank you.
[gasps softly]
Wow, seems our tables are full.
Mm, I'll get it to go.
[man] I want an Americano.
[Hua'er] Here you go.
I'll… I'll be with you in a second.
I'm sorry, we're really busy today.
There you are.
[machine whirring]
[atmospheric music playing]
Come on, people.
I'm literally handing out money.
-You got a crazy business model, man.
-Give me some more.
All right, go on. Get in there.
Thank you.
[locking]
[sighs]
Mm.
All those people in my shop…
I mean, our shop.
I've never seen anything like it before.
You must be my lucky charm.
No, no.
I've never had so much coffee before.
Five cups, I think.
It was six cups.
Ah, six cups?
[both chuckle]
Hey, I've never actually seen you
go into work.
Mm, I usually do my work at night.
Ah.
Night shift?
[both chuckle]
All right, you give me three good hints,
then I'll guess what you do for a living.
-You won't be able to.
-Come on, try me.
I think I'm going to get it.
[gentle music playing]
Dreaming.
Seeking.
Gaining.
[Hua'er] I've got it.
You're a screenwriter.
So, I was right?
How could you have guessed that?
Well, if you think about it,
the story is like a dream.
And the second hint, seeking.
The characters, always looking for love
or looking for themselves.
As for the gaining, people always expect
to gain something at the end of a story.
Maybe that would be success
or an adventure at the very least.
[both chuckle]
[chuckles]
[clears throat]
[rock music]
[hooting]
[tires screech]
[whooshing]
[grunts]
[laughing]
I'm dreaming!
Who's there? What's going on?
What's happening?
[laughs]
Thank you.
I guess you're planning
to walk me home every day?
[scoffs]
If you don't mind.
Since you're my partner,
it's the least I can do for you.
To be fair,
you also buy six coffees every day.
[Sang Yu clears throat]
[car beeps]
-This is your car?
-[chuckles]
Give it a shot.
I haven't driven in so long.
Go ahead. You can crash it if you want.
What? No way!
I could never afford to fix this.
[car revs]
[Hua'er sighs]
-It's fast.
-I see that.
Give me a sec.
[gentle music playing]
Ah, you know,
I got this car for you.
Okay, you must be super rich.
Then I guess
you're a very famous screenwriter.
Why don't we pretend
I'm one of your characters?
Do you want me to act sweet or assertive?
How about sweet?
I've been single for a while,
but it's not because I was holding out
for a car, a mansion, or anything else.
Hey, how rich are you?
You can tell me.
[chuckles]
[gentle pop music in Chinese plays]
No, you don't get it.
Trust me, you'll love it.
-I've never been inside this.
-Trust me.
Are you seriously still wearing
your school uniform?
Can you believe this guy?
♪ I looked up to the lonely street light ♪
♪ Where a sad love story came to my mind ♪
♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like your breathtaking eyes ♪
♪ I like your delightful laughter ♪
♪ I wish ♪
♪ To gently caress ♪
♪ Your lovely face again ♪
♪ To hold hands and talk in our dreams ♪
♪ Just like yesterday ♪
♪ You and me ♪
Who are you?
Sang Yu.
♪ Every night, I walk with my shadow ♪
♪ Wandering around ♪
♪ Feeling so cold ♪
[Hua'er] What are you looking at?
Get out of here.
[sobbing]
♪ I used to live in my own world ♪
♪ Without ever knowing ♪
♪ His pain ♪
[crying]
♪ I like you ♪
♪ I like your breathtaking eyes ♪
♪ I like your delightful laughter ♪
♪ I wish ♪
♪ To gently caress ♪
♪ Your lovely face again ♪
♪ To hold hands and talk in our dreams ♪
♪ Just like yesterday ♪
♪ You and me ♪
We should go and see one of the movies
that you've written, huh?
Wouldn't that be a good idea?
I wanna see a story you've written.
[both chuckle]
[keyboard clacking]
[dramatic music]
A mocha, please.
Hey, what's going on?
I thought you didn't need
to write these anymore.
[sighs]
[Hua'er] Why don't we pretend
I'm one of your characters.
Do you want me to act sweet or assertive?
-[Sang Yu] Assertive, I can take it.
-[Hua'er] You should know,
I usually dump three guys like you
every year.
[ominous music]
[crackling]
I'm dreaming!
[whimpers]
[San] This is amazing, yeah?
[gasps]
What's in your hand?
So, you read the script?
Did you find this story
in your dream as well? [sniffles]
It's wonderful!
So touching!
[announcer 1] Who wrote this?
This is gonna be a hit!
I'll make 200,000!
Only 200,000? That's funny.
The screenwriter doesn't want money.
But he wants it done right. That means
big stars for the romantic leads.
-[man] San.
-I want double this time.
Are you serious?
I'm only putting in five million.
I can't afford it.
What if I invest?
A hundred million.
[announcer] Sang Yu,
for many years, a promising young writer,
he is now in the middle
of an unprecedented wave of success
by being recognized as one of China's
most important filmmakers.
A once in a generation visionary,
he's become a major player
in the industry.
[San] If you're not interested,
I can find someone else.
I have other buyers.
For one,
I could sell it right at the price
and force you to pay
ten times more to get it.
[announcer] An avid reader
by the age of three, a poet by five,
a producer at seven.
He's been called
the Shakespeare of Chinese Cinema.
Already on the industry's radar
during his college years,
Sang Yu kept a low profile
working behind the scenes
with top directors.
Sure, let's do it.
[San] We'll get the contract ready
and expect the first payment tomorrow.
[announcer] Despite being offered
an easy act of fame,
he chose to reject it.
Instead, he focused on living
a fulfilling and simple life.
So he gave up ownership of all his work
and refused to participate
in media coverage.
Since then, he's traveled the world,
collecting thousands of stories
and honing his voice.
This year, he has over 20
top film projects set to begin production.
If think of Sang Yu
as a big shot in the business…
-Isn't this a little exaggerated?
-Fake it 'till you make it, bro.
[applause]
I wanna let you know
I'm not as good as all that.
For a long time,
I couldn't write anything good
because I didn't know why I was writing.
But I think that now,
I have found a pretty good reason.
Thanks to that reason,
I hope I never let you down.
Thanks again.
[applause]
[foreboding music]
[inhales deeply]
[intense music playing]
[grunts]
[intense music continues]
[grunt]
[rumbling]
[Sang Yu] Just incredible.
Not even Mike Tyson has one of these.
What's on your mind?
Lately, I've come to realize something.
Uh-huh?
There are two kinds of people
in this world who succeed.
First group,
they're traitors.
They are willing to betray the things
that most people wouldn't.
These people betray friendship, love,
even family.
In exchange for their betrayal,
they get empty rewards they call success.
The other kind were called thieves.
Who think they're geniuses.
What else do you call someone
whose invention changes the world?
But they haven't really invented anything.
All of their inventions are discoveries.
Made in a different reality
that exists around us.
Usually, you can't see it or feel it,
but if you get the opportunity
to see that world,
perhaps take something you find back home,
then you've really discovered something.
-[San clears throat]
-That was the door I went through.
[San] Oh.
[Sang Yu] But I feel there has to be more.
Something beyond myself.
That's it.
I see what's happening here.
Now, this is what God intended.
Huh? He chose you
to use this power to help others.
I think I'm about
to get philosophical myself.
Throughout all of human history,
there are few principal factors
that have been a cause of misery.
There are natural disasters, obviously.
and then there is war.
So tell me, what's the main cause of war?
Isn't it poverty?
Therefore, if you eliminate poverty,
you eliminate war.
Seriously,
you could be the one who does that.
We could build a skyscraper.
At least twice as tall
as any in the world.
We'll invite all the starving
and homeless people we can find.
I'm talking refugees and pirates,
everyone.
We give them food, shelter, education,
all free!
We could build more buildings
on every country!
We pull this off,
you'll win the Nobel Peace Prize
every year!
You say the word,
I'll get started on it now!
We're gonna change the world together,
Sang Yu!
[triumphant music]
[scoffs]
[Hua'er] I've never seen my shop
from this angle before.
[snickers]
Hey, look over there.
I once used to think it didn't matter
to the city whether I existed or not
But now, mostly because of you,
I actually think
I'm helping this city to shine,
even brighter than before.
[fireworks explode]
[gentle music soaring]
[gasps]
[screams]
[Sang Yu] These days…
I feel truly alive.
I never would have dreamed
I'd win you over.
But spending these days together,
is almost enough for me.
How long can we make this last?
Mm?
From the moment you appeared,
until the day you'll disappear?
[Sang Yu] I'm not going anywhere.
You probably don't remember me.
I use to skip class
to go to the movies with you.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
If I were that same boy today,
would you want to be with me?
Mm…
[sighs]
[water running]
[grunts]
[coughing]
[grunting]
[Sang Yu groaning]
Sang Yu?
[panting]
Are you okay?
Sang Yu?
[somber music]
♪ Making you love me ♪
♪ Is simple ♪
♪ But meeting you ♪
♪ Is so hard ♪
♪ You ride a boat with sails raised ♪
♪ To the opposite shore ♪
[elevator dings]
♪ It's so simple for men
And women to fall in love ♪
♪ When trapped
In their obsession with you ♪
♪ The boat overturns ♪
♪ And your wounds start to rot ♪
[muffled laughter]
Oh, Sang Yu?
Hey.
[chuckles] Here's the big man.
[chuckles]
Why are you doing
drinking in here all alone?
Hey, why don't you come
and join us out here?
I'll make sure you have a good time.
I'm tired.
You and Hua'er getting to fight
or something?
[cellphone chimes]
These women, right?
-[cellphone clacking]
-After their games playing hard to get,
suddenly, they want all your attention.
Just when you think you found true love,
suddenly, she was interested.
So easy to think
women are different, special,
started to think
she doesn't want anything from you.
-But then--
-Hey, San.
Huh?
You think after all we've taken,
there might be karma?
Well, when you took something,
you only took what was yours.
You never stole from anyone.
Where is the karma in that?
You didn't fight with Hua'er, did you?
Do you remember that door
I was telling you about?
I'm starting to think…
one day, I won't come back.
What are you saying?
That you'll got to sleep
and never wake up?
You've been way too tired lately.
You desperately need sleep.
Go to bed early tonight, huh?
[coughs]
-What are you doing?
-Mm?
Uh…
I wanna sleep alone tonight.
[chuckles]
Okay.
No problem, I understand.
Get some rest.
We'll pick this up tomorrow.
[suspenseful music]
[thunder roars]
[tense music]
[gasping]
[groans]
[grunting]
[mysterious music playing]
[groans]
[laughing]
[laughing continues]
[Qiang] If you wanna wake up,
just say,
"I'm only dreaming."
I'm only dreaming!
[grunts]
[groans]
[tires screech]
[Sang Yu] Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?
[tense music]
[hawks]
[sighs]
Stop fucking around, man.
I have important things to do.
You've been doing pretty well, huh?
You're a famous guy.
You don't need pawn shops anymore.
Why don't we just go straight to it,
shall we?
How much do you want from me?
Five million.
I'll make a call.
[Qiang] So, now,
you're bargaining for me, huh?
Mr. Qiang.
[grunts]
Hey, I was only… Hey!
I wonder how much do you think
you're worth?
Give me a price.
I'll give you…
ten million Yuan.
That in cash?
Give him the phone.
[motorcycle approaching]
[tires screech]
-Where is he?
-[man] Where is the money?
Yeah. Why don't you tell me where he--
Where is he?
Just so you know,
I'm not really part of any of this.
I'm just delivering
as a favor to a very good friend of mine.
The family was really pretty insisting
that I'd see the hostage
before you get the cash.
So, if you take the money without
my confirming my friend's safety, I mean…
don't you think
that would be kinda bad manners?
[grunts]
Who is Hua'er?
Your little girlfriend?
Give it back.
[Qiang] I underestimated you.
No wonder you're so full of yourself.
A million, ten million, a hundred million…
In your savings alone,
you have three hundred million.
What exactly do you do?
You know what I think?
I think I asked for too little.
Qiang.
There's something bad happening to me.
I won't be alive for long.
Take the money, just let us go.
Let me take care of one last thing.
You can do that.
[groaning]
What's going on?
Sang Yu.
You all right?
What did these fuckers do to you?
Do you have any idea who this is?
Oh, you'll regret this.
Wait and see what's gonna happen.
Talking to you, mother--
[body thuds]
[pants]
San? San?
All of your businesses and home.
Let's check out this guy's place.
[suspenseful music]
Hey, hello, Mr. Sang.
[chuckles] Oh, you're back early.
Is that Mr. San?
What happened to him, huh?
-He's drunk.
-Oh, he's just drunk. [chuckles]
Delivery.
[elevator chimes]
[suspenseful music playing]
You already made a good life up here.
This can't be right.
I don't buy it, Qiang.
There should be
way more merchandise in here.
You can show yourself out when you finish.
No problem. Maybe you can just
call the owner, he can come get it.
[intense music plays]
[sniffles]
[groaning]
[grunting]
-[squelching]
-[continues groaning]
[grunts]
Where the hell did you get
all of these from?
I traded my life for it.
Who hasn't traded their life for money?
Why is yours worth so much, huh?
[claps]
[Qiang] Hey, hey. Put that down.
Don't move anything.
[Sang Yu] It's all right.
You can take all of it. It's okay.
I won't call the cops.
But if you kill me,
you're in for it.
A time thief can steal so much
he could provide for the rest of his life.
And yet,
he's always a thief.
Who lies to himself
and betrays what he is.
He'll never control his own destiny.
[receptionist] Mr. Sang.
Mr. Sang, are you there?
Mr. Sang, are you okay?
-[beeps]
-[Sang Yu] What's the matter?
[receptionist] Mr. Sang, you have a guest.
She said her name is Hua'er.
-Should I let her up?
-Say I'm not here.
-Tell her to come later.
-Sang Yu?
Why can't you tell me
what you're hiding from?
I'm hiding from you! Get out!
Leave now!
Is something going on up there?
[receptionist] Mr. Sang,
I think you should let her come up.
-You can explain--
-Quiet!
Do you remember what you said to me?
How you can dump
three guys like me in a year?
You can add me to that list today.
[inhales deeply]
You know what I think?
I think this isn't about some regret
in your past.
[somber music]
Hang on, Ma'am.
He just opened the door.
[elevator dings]
Don't move! I'll snap you to death!
[tense music playing]
[Hua'er] Sang Yu.
Are you there, Sang Yu?
Are you okay?
Please, Sang Yu…
Wait, stop!
If you take that off, you'll die.
[Qiang] Young lovers.
What good is money
without a girl to go with it?
[Hua'er] Who are you people?
What do you want?
You want money, right?
I have a café, it's worth some money.
You can have it.
[both gasp]
-Hua'er…
-[Hua'er] Sang Yu…
[gasps]
Don't touch her! Get away from her!
-Don't you dare!
-[Hua'er] Sang Yu…
[grunts]
Qiang. Qiang. Qiang.
Qiang, I was wrong.
Please, just let her go.
You can take whatever you want.
I have more stuff.
I promise, there's more. Don't do it.
I'm begging you.
[inhales sharply]
[Hua'er] Sang Yu.
You've never been down here, have you?
Did he tell you what he does for a living?
Did he say he was a writer?
Do really think a writer
can afford all of this?
Qiang.
Qiang, you don't have to.
Didn't we agree we take the money only?
Come on, man.
Stop!
Qiang.
We don't have to kill them.
Qiang. Qiang.
-Come on, take the money. Qiang--
-[thud]
[grunting]
[beating continues]
[grunts]
Why couldn't you just shut up?
[sighs]
[panting]
There maybe people
who suddenly appear in our lives
they might seem like bad guys.
So we make noise,
and complain about our bad luck,
without ever really considering
how our own actions led us
to this very moment.
These bad men are actually the good ones.
They come into our lives
to teach us a lesson.
It's too late for him.
But you're a smart person.
[tense music continues]
[sighs]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[Qiang] Kill them. Kill them all.
[grunting]
-[clang]
-Get back!
You sons of bitches!
[groans]
[grunts]
Sang Yu!
Have you all gone crazy?
[grunt]
Don't move!
All of you, get back! Get back!
[gunshot]
Go after them.
[thrilling music plays]
[groans]
Sang Yu! Sang Yu!
[gasping]
We need to get out of here.
[gunshot]
[groans]
[grunting]
Hurry!
[screams]
[grunts]
[groaning]
[thud]
-[San] Go on!
-San!
[grunting]
[body thuds]
[somber music]
[grunts]
[gloomy music]
[grunting]
[groans]
[grunts]
[screaming]
-[clang]
-[gasping]
[grunts]
[intense dramatic music plays]
[choking]
[thud]
[grunts]
[screams]
[panting]
[groaning]
[swooshing, thumps]
[eerie music]
[rumbling]
[intense choral music playing]
[whooshing]
[choral music intensifies]
[eerie music]
[professor] Id, ego, and super-ego
together, they form the human psyche.
In everyday life, the ego controls
how you see yourself in other people.
But in dreams,
it's the id that takes over
and reveals our animal desires.
And then the super-ego,
the force that both holds the id at bay
and keeps the ego
from getting carried away with itself.
[applause]
[intense music]
[Hua'er] It's nice to have a lot of money,
but it doesn't define who you are.
[panting]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[gloomy music]
[warbling]
[thunderous bang]
[cracking]
I'm…
dreaming.
I'm dreaming.
I'm only dreaming.
[dramatic music]
[rumbling]
[gasps]
[cracking]
[warbling]
[intense music playing]
[bones cracking]
[landlord] Come out now!
I have leftovers. Eat and get out!
Don't you starve to death at my house!
[rumbles]
[thrilling music playing]
[clang]
Do you think your writing is so special,
huh?
It should be easy money for you!
Pull yourself together!
[screaming]
[cracking]
[thumps]
[thunderous choral music plays]
[thumping continues]
[rumbles]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[gunshot]
[crying]
[sobbing]
[gasps]
[gunshot]
[ominous music]
I'm… dreaming.
[thuds]
[all gasp]
[Hua'er] Sang Yu.
Sang Yu?
[delicate music plays]
Is it really you?
What happened?
You shouldn't eat this.
Come on.
Let's go get some real food.
You must be hungry.
You better eat up.
It'll be all right.
You know, I was reading a magazine,
there was a story
written by someone named Sang Yu.
And I thought that must have been you.
It's the right thing
for you to be a writer.
You're very special.
You only need a little good luck,
for a change.
[Sang Yu slurps]
I'm not able to help you out with much.
But if it's something you want,
you can work in my café.
[whimpering]
[gentle, emotional music playing]
[crying]
[emotional music continues]
Sang Yu.
This is for you.
[Sang Yu] I can't accept this.
It's too much.
Think of it as a kind of investment.
You keep the profits,
while I'll capitalize this.
[chuckles]
I'm not sure I can even write a script.
I can never write
what they want me to write.
Well, then just write for yourself, huh?
[San] Gotta hand it to you, man, huh?
[sighs]
I think I've heard every excuse
to extend a deadline.
Like those files getting lost.
Maybe you just got water on your computer.
That's what I get
for dealing with creatives.
But you are something else,
some other next life.
I wanna apologize.
It's just that…
I really can't write for you anymore.
So, I borrowed ten thousand Yuan…
to pay you back with.
I'm sorry, my friend.
About that script you wrote from before…
I sold it.
They said your writing was good.
Turns out…
you should have been
writing thrillers all along.
Here, take it.
Hey, who's the rich guy?
You won't even buy me a bowl of noodles?
[chuckles]
Hey.
[laughing]
[gentle, upbeat music playing]
[professor] Most people think
that time can only move in one direction.
But in dreams,
we all become time travelers.
Suddenly, there's nothing to hold us back.
Life contains infinite possibilities.
Even if we think we know
our own histories,
on some other timeline, you might be
living a completely different life.
[gentle music continues]
Hey there.
I'll have one with sausage, no eggs.
You can have this back.
Thanks for thinking of me.
I know what you traded for that money.
I can't accept that.
Hey.
[grunts]
I once made the same trade.
And I'm much happier this way.
[crackling]
[suspenseful music plays]
[rock music in Chinese playing]
[Hua'er] Sang Yu.
Sang Yu?
You shouldn't eat this.
Come on. Let's go get some real food.
[rock music continues]
[dreamy music]