My name is Nack.
I am an ordinary high school boy.
I am studying
in an all-boys private school.
I live a normal, unexciting life.
I am always with my gang.
There are four guys including me, and...
Nack, let me copy your answers
of the English assignment.
Here it is!
Okay. Okay.
After you finish,
me and Toey will copy too.
Okay. Okay.
They are just a few assignments.
Toh, have you seen this video clip?
Well...
Let me see.
Damn, Toey! Why do you always have
a lot of porno clips?
I'm in the chat group of my old friends.
You can name the girls you want to see,
I got it all.
Nack, Dook, you two want some?
No!
I prefer sexy cartoon characters.
Let's take a selfie. I want to upload
a new photo on my Instagram.
-All right.
-Nack, come here.
Come, come.
Let's see.
Dook, come closer.
You, come closer.
One more!
Toh! You always update your Instagram.
You got 40k followers!
Wow! You're really a Net Idol!
But recently,
the number of my followers
hasn't increased much.
Should I pretend to love a boy
for yaoi girls?
What? Why are you looking at me?
You, Nack. We can be a fake couple.
-Hey!
-Hey! Come on, Nack.
You know, a fake couple.
-You're crazy! No way!
-Why?
-Right.
-No way!
Wow!
-What's with him?
-Here comes the teacher.
Don't forget my number one rule.
When the class begins,
I won't talk to anyone.
I will focus on my studies.
Don't bother me.
-Understand?
-Stand up, please!
Attention!
Good morning.
First of all, I'll announce
the results of the latest Math exam.
The highest score goes to...
Tanapat!
Look at Toy,
he always sits with the bad boy gang
but still gets the highest score
in Mathematics.
That's because he sees a tutor.
No one in our gang does.
I am too lazy.
My mom works so hard alone.
I don't want to ask for her money
to pay for a tutor.
I think if I pay attention in class,...
a tutor won't be necessary.
But what if the teacher
doesn't teach well, like Miss Utai?
It's so boring.
Anyway, look at Toy!
He wears thick glasses like a nerd.
He's good at Mathematics
but he failed English.
I don't know. Anyway, I don't like him.
Mathematics is the only subject
where he's better than me.
Come on!
I'd like to announce the results
of the latest English exam.
The top score of this class goes to...
Narate!
Well...
Nack is so good at English.
You've got the highest score again.
I just want to be as good as you.
In my class,
there's one gay guy who I don't like.
It's not because he's gay.
It's because he's hypocritical.
-And he always tells a lie.
-Petch.
You know...
Nack is so cruel to me.
I just walked over to congratulate him
for his English score,
but he...
insulted me with bad words.
He said he's better than me.
Can you play nicely?
Please don't hurt me!
Kla, you're the most beautiful girl here.
Are you sure?
Nack! Nack! Let's play volleyball!
No, thanks. I don't play.
-Ouch!
-Nack!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean it.
It's okay.
Hey!
Do you want some?
No, I don't smoke.
If you don't smoke, you are a faggot.
Okay, then I am one.
Faggot!
I think Nack, my classmate,
is gay for sure but he tries to hide it.
-How pathetic!
Why does he have to hide? What for?
But I think he's handsome.
-What?
-You traitor!
Get the ball!
-Ready?
-Come on.
Go! Move!
-There he comes.
-Oh, God. Move!
-Move!
-Go for it!
-Go! Go!
-That's it!
Am I weird?
I don't like to play volleyball
like Thai gay boys
and I don't play football
like straight boys either.
My gang doesn't like
to play volleyball and football too.
My gang's popular activity is...
Shit!
Hey. It's below.
Yes. Come on!
Hey, Nack, why don't you use Line?
My mom doesn't pay for the internet fee.
She said internet is not necessary.
And there's no internet at my house,
but I don't care.
I want to say "Ni Xue Ouxiang."
-What does it mean?
-This is an idol.
-I see.
-Thank you.
Finally, do you have anything to say
-to your supporters?
-Yes.
My secret of getting good grades
is not limited to consulting
with teachers during class.
I also consult with teachers
at the teacher's lounge.
-Teacher Justin...
-Yeah?
-Yes.
-This one, what does it mean?
Narate, you're a quick learner. Superb!
Thank you, sir.
My life goes around in circles every day,
just like a goldfish in the fish bowl.
I always do the same things.
One day, during my senior year,
I felt inexplicably depressed and lonely.
Maybe because I just realized
that in less than a year,
I've got to leave this school.
NACK, DOOK, TOH
The place where I have studied
for 12 years.
I was just walking around
and pondering about many things
until I reached...
the school swimming pool.
There...
was where I witnessed a sex scene
for the first time.
It was the first time
I saw people having sex,...
and it was between two men.
Before this, when I hear the gay gang
chat about their sex experiences,
I thought it was disgusting.
But when I saw it,
why was I so excited?
Have you said a prayer?
Why must I warn you?
You don't come to church on Sundays.
That's why you've become negligent.
Dear God,
Jesus Christ.
Thank you, God.
For the food and beverage
that you give us.
Please take care of everything for us.
In the Name of our Lord Jesus Christ.
Amen.
Why do many celebrities
commit suicide nowadays?
Suicide is a sin.
Especially for those Christians.
They won't be allowed to enter heaven.
My pen...
-Tell me if you like it.
-Right.
-Come on!
Let me get your ass!
What the heck?
Watch out, man!
Sorry.
Sit here.
What are you laughing at?
What's so funny?
Petch!
How long have you been here?
I didn't notice you.
I've been swimming for half an hour.
How could you see me?
I saw you walk straight
to the shower room.
And you're not swimming?
I can't swim.
What?
I'm looking for someone
but it seems he's not here.
I haven't seen anyone in here yet.
Do you want to learn how to swim?
I can teach you.
May I have your Line? We don't talk much
even though we're in the same class.
I don't use Line.
My phone isn't connected
to the internet.
How about I give you my phone number?
You can call me
or send me a message.
Okay.
Hey! Let me see your phone!
-It's mine.
-It's the famous brand!
Hey, what are you doing?
What the heck, you nerd!
Hey!
Do you want to mess with me?
It's only a mobile phone.
-It belongs to him!
-I want it!
I won't let you!
-Teacher.
-Teacher, this way.
-He's here.
-He is running away!
-Teacher, come on!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you all right?
I am all right.
Good. Be careful next time you go home.
COME TO THE SWIMMING POOL TOMORROW.
I'LL TEACH YOU HOW TO SWIM.
BRING YOUR SWIMSUIT, PETCH.
Nack, aren't you wearing glasses?
Yeah. I'm wearing contact lenses.
They are fine.
Hey!
You're late!
-Are you wearing contact lenses?
-Yeah.
How sparkling your eyes are.
Hey, Dook. Do you want a snack?
It's in your bag.
Give me, please.
Come on.
Shit!
What the heck?
What's so funny?
Hey, Toh.
Your dick is smaller than Dook's.
I got a small body,
but a big dick!
He can't argue with that.
That's for the small one.
Nack, what are you doing in the toilet?
I got to pee.
Why don't you pee at urinals like us?
-Why are you shy? We are all men here.
-Right.
I'm not shy.
I was in there hiding from Draft.
I always see you pee in the toilet,
never at urinals.
-What?
-Don't say anything.
How was it?
Oh, God! Do you have a lot of homework?
-No, I don't have any homework.
-Whom did you send the Line to?
-Teacher, hi!
-Hi!
-Go to your classroom.
Hi. Your socks are too short.
I'll WAIT AT THE SWIMMING POOL
WHEN YOU'RE DONE CLEANING.
FOLLOW ME, PETCH.
Hey, Nack!
Won't you go play video games with us?
No.
-Bye!
-Hey! Wait, wait, wait.
You look cute without glasses.
Really?
-I will let go of my hands.
-Hey!
-Just try.
-Hey! Don't!
Are you gay?
No, I'm not.
I've got a girlfriend.
She studies in the all-girls school
nearby.
But I haven't had sex with her yet.
When I see your slim body,
I get a strange feeling.
Maybe I just want to try.
You idiot!
Nack! I'm sorry! Nack!
No, I can't.
What?
How was it? Did you like it?
It was good. I got so excited.
You're good at it.
What are you looking for, Nack?
My math book.
Where did you put it?
I put it in the drawer but it disappeared.
Is it with you?
No. This is mine.
Hey!
This is my book.
What? This is mine!
Prove it if this is yours.
I wrote my name on the cover.
But its cover is torn.
So how do you know it's yours?
Although its cover is torn,
based on the library principle I studied,
I secretly wrote my name on page 55.
There it is.
So you're saying Pong stole it from you?
It's just a book. If you want it, go on!
Hey, what the heck?
Hey! Let go of me!
Hey! Stop!
Damn, Nack, you talk too much!
Today I'll teach you a lesson.
Toey. Where are my snacks?
-What snacks?
-I put it in your bag.
Hey! It's ridiculous.
-Just look in your bag.
-We are going to take a break.
Hey, Nack.
Are you okay?
What happened to your face?
I was too careless.
I fell and hit my head in the toilet.
Pretty badly.
How clumsy you are
to fall and hit your head there.
It's lunch time. Let's eat.
-Okay.
-You guys just go. I'm not hungry.
Why?
Let's go!
Nack.
Won't you come and play video games
with us?
Yeah. Go on. I can't go.
What's wrong with you?
Let's go.
Go!
I'LL BE HOME LATE.
HELP YOURSELF FOR DINNER.
Hurry up!
We'll be late for the English test.
Hi. Your shoes are against the rules.
-Yes.
-Hi.
-Teacher, hi!
-Hi!
Hi!
Nack, are you sure
you left your phone here?
Yeah.
Yesterday you seemed absent-minded
the whole day.
Hey, Toh,
have you seen Nack's mobile phone?
No, I haven't. Why would I have seen it?
-Just in case.
-How should I know?
Hey, you! What are you watching?
Have you seen Nack's mobile phone?
He lost it.
No, I haven't.
Toh, look at this.
What is it?
Dook played three times.
Toh played just once.
Just once and he died.
-Really?
-No.
Just once and he died.
Hey, look at that girl. She's so sexy.
-See?
-Yeah.
Damn you! She's looking at us.
Just stay still!
Were you waiting for a long time?
It was really enjoyable.
I went home pretty late.
Didn't let me go back home.
Damn Toh...
Why are you looking at your camera?
-Can't you play? I mean, football.
-I can't play it.
What the heck?
-He just takes photos every day.
-Right.
So what?
Do you want to play again today?
Sure. Yesterday we got even.
-Just got even.
-Is that right?
How about the previous match?
Hey, I found my phone!
Congratulations!
Yesterday, we were searching
for a long time.
But yesterday
you already checked the drawer?
Yeah. How could it be here?
-You probably weren't looking carefully.
-Right.
I searched carefully.
-Now that you found it. Good.
-Right.
That's a relief.
My dear students,
I'd like you to tell me
which faculty you want to get in and why?
I'll give you some advice.
Yeah, Narate?
I wanna be in the Faculty of Arts
because I like to draw pictures.
Yes, that's true.
But your grades in other subjects
are good too.
I recommend you
to get in the Faculty of Architecture.
Why, Miss?
Architects have a much higher income
than painters.
You won't be wealthy
if you become a painter.
"Poor Painter." Have you heard that?
What about cartoonists?
They can't make ends meet.
What about the others? Which faculty?
I must prepare
for the entrance examination.
Studying in the class is not enough.
MODEL: HELLO, NACK
MODEL: I FOUND YOUR MOBILE
AND I PAID FOR YOUR INTERNET FEE
SO THAT WE CAN CHAT
NACK: WHO ARE YOU? WHAT DO YOU WANT?
MODEL: I JUST WANT TO TALK TO YOU
MODEL: I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU SAD
MODEL: GOOD NIGHT
-How was the game yesterday?
-Were you kidding me last night?
No. What happened?
MODEL: HELLO!
NACK: WHO ARE YOU?
IF YOU DON'T TELL ME, I'LL BLOCK YOU
MODEL: WAIT! DON'T BLOCK ME
I PROMISE THAT ONE DAY, I'LL TELL YOU
I MEAN NO HARM. PLEASE.
Do you have any questions?
I want to be good at English.
Do you have any suggestions?
Sure.
The easy way is to watch
a lot of English language movies.
Listen to the soundtrack.
Listen to English songs.
Especially those classic songs
with good meanings.
That would help a lot.
Look at you!
Nack, it's obvious that
you love Teacher Justin.
You seem to focus on his class.
I pay attention to every class.
What do you mean by that?
Nack.
Why did Pong say that?
Why does he think that
you like Teacher Justin?
I don't like him that way,
although he is handsome.
-Hey!
-Anyway, I'm not gay.
NACK: HELL NO!
HE JUST TAUGHT ME HOW TO SWIM
MODEL: THEN LET ME TEACH YOU
HOW TO SWIM
NACK: SO I'M GOING TO SEE YOUR FACE
MODEL: YOU REALLY WANT TO SEE MY FACE?
NACK: SURE
MODEL: IF YOU SEE MY FACE,
WILL YOU STILL TALK TO ME?
Toy!
It's me!
So funny!
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute!
Nack.
Don't you want to talk to me?
Hey! Model.
It's a nice necklace.
Did your girlfriend buy it for you?
No. I don't have a girlfriend.
And this dolphin pendant,
I bought it myself.
What about you?
Do you have a girlfriend?
Not yet.
Toy.
May I ask you something?
What?
Do you think I look gay?
I don't think so.
I think you're a nerd.
Sweet boy.
You're like a sweet boy.
What do you mean?
Well...
Isn't the English for sweet man
"sweet boy"?
It's too literal.
I don't care. I'll just call you that.
I'll call you "sweet boy."
Don't! Your English sucks,
so why use English words?
Does my English suck?
You are my sweet boy.
-When is your birthday, Toy?
-What?
It's on November 7th. What about you?
The same month but mine is on the 11th.
But...
I'm one year older than you.
That makes me your older brother.
Who wants that?
-What? Am I not good enough?
-I give up.
-Are you ticklish?
-No.
Hey! Hey!
MODEL: LET'S SWIM AGAIN TOMORROW
-Toy.
-What?
I've got something for you.
What is it?
Happy birthday.
What's this?
For your dolphin to be a couple.
Thanks a lot, Nack.
I've got something for you too.
What is it?
Wait a minute.
I know you're Christian...
so I bought this for you.
Actually...
Christians don't worship pendants,
even if it's a crucifix.
But I can wear it as an accessory.
So, are you going to wear it?
Really?
Let me do it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
-Toy!
-What?
Why did you have to hide
and talk to me through Line?
At that time...
I was too afraid to talk to you.
We're not in the same gang.
We don't talk much.
So why do you want to talk to me now?
Let me see your phone!
-It's mine!
-Hey! What are you doing?
What the heck, you nerd?
Toy, there was a guy
who tried to snatch my mobile,
but someone helped me.
Hey!
Why don't you answer?
And why are you smiling?
I won't tell you.
You won't?
Take this!
-Let's take a selfie.
-Okay.
That's cool.
What? A big guy eating so little.
Look at me. I'm small but I eat a lot.
Hey. When did you guys get so familiar?
Toh took Toy into our group for a moment.
He asked Toy to teach him math.
To be taught...
or to copy Toy's homework?
Yeah.
To copy.
Before this, when you were sad,
you didn't go with our gang after school,
so you didn't catch up.
Do you guys want something to drink?
I'll go buy.
Milk tea with bubble pearl for me!
Me too!
Longan juice, please.
-Please, don't.
-Longan or not?
-Longan juice.
-Just water for me.
Hey, Nack.
Nack, do you know
who helped you from Draft? It's Toy.
Hey, Draft. What are you doing?
I'm teaching damn Nack a lesson.
He told the teachers that I smoke.
It's not me!
Then, what is this clip?
That clip is when I went
to ask about the study.
I think...
Nack is not a liar.
Who told you that?
And who gave you that video clip?
Let's go.
Hey, here they are.
It's yours, Nack.
Hey.
Thank you.
Wow, longan juice. Different from others.
Is it good?
What? Something wrong with you two?
It's quite weird.
-Why?
-It's not your business.
Shit! Do you want to play?
Why? Why?
Shit!
-There are a lot of them.
-Right.
Ready?
Why?
Oh, crap.
I'm sorry, teacher.
-Damn.
-What?
I'll take the bubble pearl out for you.
Give it back to me!
Your face looks so pale!
The bubble pearl is...
stuck.
-Lay down.
I'll record the clip.
-Is it out?
-Yes.
Yes, it's out.
That is karma.
You played me first.
Hey, look at this clip.
I'll upload it to my Instagram.
It's so funny.
Damn you! Don't!
Hey, guys.
Let's go out somewhere and have fun
before the final exam.
I can't go.
I have to study for the entrance exam.
Moreover, my mom won't let me
stay overnight outside.
We don't have to stay overnight.
Just a one-day trip.
Okay. Where?
How about Siam Park City?
There are both exciting rides
and swimming park.
That's great. I'll go.
Say cheese!
Hey, guys, I'm here.
Guys, this is Act, my brother.
He wanted to relax from studying,
-so I took him here.
-Hello, guys.
Hurry up!
Let's ride the merry-go-round.
Oh, no.
That's too childish.
-No. Let's play.
-Why not Roller Coaster?
-Why not Roller Coaster or Viking?
-No, I don't like them.
Let's ride the merry-go-round.
-Let's go!
-Go!
Hey, let me take a break here.
Viking is next, okay?
Okay.
Sure.
Hey, Nack. Why don't you take the rides?
I'm nervous,
and I'm very afraid of heights.
All I can take is merry-go-round.
You chicken.
You guys, go on. Don't worry about me.
Okay. Take care of my belongings.
Okay then.
This too. Take care of them all.
-Don't lose them.
-Put them there.
-Let's go.
-You sure you don't want to?
No. You go.
Nack, why are you sitting alone?
I'm too afraid to go with them.
They want to ride the Viking.
I see. I'll sit with you then.
Be my guest.
Make room for me.
Why can't you ride the Viking?
It's too high and exciting.
Hey, Nack.
Hey, what are you doing?
-Hey.
-Where will you drag me to?
To the ride.
I'm with you. You don't have to be afraid.
No. I'm afraid of heights. I can't.
What?
Come. Don't be afraid.
-Ride with me.
-No.
-Come on.
-No way.
It's not that high.
Nack.
-Why don't you go swim?
-Yes, Act.
I'm tired.
I just want to take a break now.
But it's fun.
-But not now.
-No?
So why don't you go swim?
I'm bored. I'll go swim later.
Nack.
Let's swim.
-Where?
-To swim. There.
Hey, guys.
Let's take a photo.
-Come here.
-Take a photo.
-Come closer.
-For what?
-For my Instagram.
One, two, three.
Hey, Nack. I got to go now.
-I'll wait outside.
-Okay.
-Follow me.
-Yes.
By the way, before this,
why did I dislike Toy?
Maybe I was just jealous of him
because he's better at Mathematics?
How selfish I am.
If one person can do everything,
we don't have to live in a community.
And now without any prejudice,
I think,
I love Toy.
But in two months,
we will graduate high school.
I feel happy, but at the same time, sad.
Today, it's so much fun.
But...
after graduation,
we may not see each other again.
Hey, you idiot.
You talk like you're dying.
Although we're in different universities,
we can still meet, you know.
By the way, Nack...
may I go to stay at your house tonight?
Sure, but why?
I need you to teach me Arts and English.
And I'll teach you Mathematics.
I think you're not good at it.
And tomorrow is Sunday.
We can sleep late.
Hey.
Your room is so cute.
There are a lot of puppies.
If we take the red color...
and blue color,
then mix them together,
we will get purple.
Watch this.
I've got to mix it.
Here.
How was it?
But the most beautiful purple is this one.
But this purple,
you can't mix it,
you have to buy it.
Let's see.
Purple is my most favorite color.
Why do you like purple?
Well...
I don't know.
There's no reason.
But...
if I have to find one reason,
maybe because I find it beautiful.
Especially this special purple,
it's so beautiful.
I think you like it because you are gay.
Hey, no.
But maybe because
the purple is the middle tone.
Not female, not male.
People think it's the color of gay.
Maybe.
-There.
-Hey!
-Do you want to play?
-Got you.
Do you want some?
Hey, come on.
Hey.
That's enough. We're already dirty.
I'll go take a bath now.
Hey, Nack.
Help me hold my legs. I'll do sit-ups.
Sure.
Hey.
Grab firmly.
-Press my knees.
-Okay.
It's enough.
I think I should go take a bath now.
Here are the T-shirt and pants.
-Here is the towel.
-Okay.
Hey, Toy.
Why are you topless?
Your T-shirt is too small.
I can't wear it.
But it's okay.
When I'm at home,
I usually sleep without T-shirt.
Hey.
Nack.
You sleep on your bed.
I'll sleep on the floor.
It's all right. Today, you are my guest.
You sleep on my bed.
I'll sleep on the floor.
Then...
both of us can be on the bed.
It would be uncomfortable for you.
I am all right with it, if you're okay.
Okay.
Nack.
What song are you listening to?
Just listen.
It's very late at night.
Why hasn't your mom come home?
Well...
She always comes home late.
I'm used to it.
So don't you feel lonely,
to be home alone?
Yes, I do.
But...
I read comics,
and watch movies and dramas.
When I was a child,
and the first time I felt lonely...
I didn't even know what it is.
Someone...
may be able to describe them in words.
But...
I feel it more.
Every time,
when the credits come...
I feel desolated.
I feel like...
my body is stiff, especially my head.
my nose smells something so acrid...
that I want to cry.
Nack.
From now on...
if you feel lonely...
think of me.
Or...
you can call me.
Well...
you also have Dook, Toh, and Toey.
Toy...
could you do me a favor?
-What?
-Well...
can we sleep with the lights on?
I'm very scared of ghosts.
I can't sleep in the dark,
so I sleep with the lights on every night.
Are you serious?
That's why, at the pool,
when I wore a ghost mask to tease you,
it scared the shit out of you.
But...
with the lights on, I cannot sleep.
The lights get into my eyes.
Okay.
Just the lantern there, okay?
You can hug me...
if it will make you feel
you're not lonely.
You can hug me...
if you think of me as a friend.
Take care. Bye-bye.
Hello, Toy.
Are you at home?
Yeah.
Is it raining there?
Just a little.
If it stops, let's see a movie.
Today, I can't.
I've got to go with my family.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know.
I just feel like, I miss you.
Hey.
It's only yesterday when we were together
the whole day, the whole night.
Yeah, I don't know
what I'm feeling right now.
Sorry. Bye.
Mom.
Why are you home early today?
Nack.
Why did you sleep with a guy last night?
Well...
His name is Toy, my classmate.
We studied together last night
until it was late.
So...
did you have sex?
Mom!
Why are you asking me that?
We didn't have sex.
We are Christians.
God made a man
to mate with a woman.
God does not like gays.
Neither do I.
Although they are good people?
But you?
You only care about your work,
not your child.
And God wouldn't blame you at all?
How dare you blame me!
Did you know
that since your Dad died,
I've been working so hard,
and it's tiring me?
And you do this to me?
Tell me.
Are you a lady boy or a gay?
Answer me.
Answer me!
I miss you, Dad.
Dad never hit me.
Toy.
Nack.
What's wrong?
Where should I further my study?
What would you like to eat?
Chicken rice...
I want to eat some chicken rice.
We will eat some cookies here.
-I prefer some chicken rice.
-We'll eat chicken rice first.
Nack, would you like some?
-It still tastes good.
-Which flavor of cookies should we have?
-Is it your aunt's chicken rice?
-It must be delicious.
It's really chicken rice.
Are there a lot of them?
-Do you mean some soup?
-Yes.
Do you want to eat?
Hey, why did you do this to me?
Go away, faggot!
Let's go.
Damn you, Petch!
Hello, is this Toy?
Yes.
It's Nack's mom.
I have something to tell you.
I feel that, recently,
Nack has been obsessed with you.
He always calls you.
But I think he's not a lady boy or a gay.
He just feels lonely.
And I don't think you are either.
No, I'm not.
Good.
Now, the entrance examination is coming.
May I ask you to stay away from Nack?
Yes.
Thank you.
I won't take your time anymore.
Goodbye then.
GAT ENGLISH
GAT VOCABULARY
Toy.
Thank you for the answer paper
for Mathematics.
Why did you have to give Pong
the answer paper for Mathematics?
And let him kiss you?
Pong is my friend just like you.
But you know I don't like him.
You know what he did to me.
You hate Pong,...
so I must, too?
Listen to me, Nack.
Each person can't be 100 percent
good or evil.
Just like Pong and my friends
at the back of the class.
They might not pay attention to class,
but they are still my friends.
If I were you, I would be
on the same side with the one I--
Nack,
don't force anyone to like you.
When you are so nice to me,...
and spend some good time together,
those don't mean anything to you?
I act the same to everyone.
So...
it's all in my head.
What do you think it is?
I'm not...
I think of you as a friend.
You said I can hug you.
You said I can call you
when I feel lonely.
Only if you think of me as a friend.
Toy.
When two people talk to each other
more and more, and they hug,
who the heck will be able to resist?
Then you should not have agreed
that you would not think of me
more than a friend.
If I said I couldn't,
would you allow me to talk to you?
Or would you let me hug you?
Just think...
how contradicting it is...
when a couple talk more and hug,
but forbidden to feel love.
Do you know how much I suffer?
To lie and conceal this feeling.
Damn, Toh, you've got the power.
Hey, Nack. Nack.
-Hey.
-What's up with you?
-Are you okay?
Do you hear us?
Hey, Nack. What's wrong?
Relax.
I'm very worried about many things.
I didn't pass
the direct entrance examination.
My GAT/PAT scores are not good.
Hey, it's okay. Don't be serious.
If you can't get
into a government university,
you can join us in a private one.
Yeah.
I don't want to study
in a private university.
What's wrong with a private university?
I think it's not about the study.
-Right.
-It's about Toy.
Yeah, I think, recently,
you're obsessed with Toy too much.
You don't understand me.
Toy.
I'm sorry...
for what I did this evening.
I know...
I should not have called.
But I can't help it.
I'm glad...
you answered my call.
Nack, you should focus
on your entrance examination.
I can't concentrate on reading...
because I can't get you out of my head.
Enough!
If you cannot
think of me as a friend,...
I won't talk to you anymore.
And don't call me again.
Nack, are you home?
Are you here? Answer me.
If you're home, open the door.
Nack!
You try to open the door.
Go inside.
Nack, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
-Hey.
-Relax.
-Take it easy.
-Damn.
We heard about you from Toy.
Don't think too much.
We're still friends.
No matter what you are,
you're still our friend.
Toy still loves you as a friend.
He only needs you to prepare
for the entrance exam first.
He has to stay away from you for a while.
I know.
But I can't take it.
You must try.
Nack, what are you thinking?
If you had done it,
if you had really died...
Think...
You will not see Toy, us,
or your mom again.
I got it from a song.
You have to love yourself more, Nack.
I copy it from somewhere, too.
Nack.
Someday, you will feel nothing
about what happened in the past.
I'm sorry...
that I was angry and I shouted at you
that day.
It's okay.
I'm not mad at you.
Nack, whatever happens, you must fight.
Did you remember the handicapped beggar
that we met?
You felt so sorry for them
that you almost cried.
But they still live and fight.
You are lucky that you were born normal.
You must fight.
No one can really make you feel better
or move on
except yourself.
Chin up!
Thank you, guys, really.
Stay with us.
Where are you going? Are you nuts?
Why does time go slowly...
when you're sad?
But when you are happy,...
time flies so fast.
THREE MONTHS LATER
Nack, take a break and have some fruits.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I didn't pass the entrance examination.
It's okay. It's all right.
Let's try again.
Let's try again next year.
I'll have you go to a tutor school
for one year.
ONE YEAR LATER
Nack. Nack.
You passed the entrance examination.
I checked it from the Internet.
-Yeah?
-Here.
That's right, Mom.
Yeah!
Good job, my boy.
-You did it great.
-Thanks, Mom.
Hey, Nack.
I just heard that you've entered here.
I would have called you.
This is Kay, my girlfriend.
Kay, this is Nack.
-My old school classmate.
-Hi.
Hi.
Take your time, Toy.
I'll go to volleyball practice.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
See you.
Hey.
How are you, freshy?
Long time no see. You are more handsome.
How is your Mom? Is she fine?
Will you be available tomorrow?
I will give you a sightseeing tour
by bicycle.
Why do I feel less depressed?
That's why they say,
"Time heals everything."
I've got to go home now. See you tomorrow.
Okay.
Nack, if you're afraid to fall,
you can hold onto me.
In your life,
no matter how bad things happen,
we must fight and carry on.
Life goes on.
Subtitle translation by Patchara Laeka