[crowd clapping and cheering]
On the 18th hole,
she was leading by two strokes,
so close to victory,
that a dance troupe
was preparing for a celebration
[male announcer]
And the eyes of the nation watching on
and then you realize how tough this is.
[crowd cheering]
[female announcer] And it stopped.
[crowd cheers]
[male announcer] It stayed up there,
but we've already seen how difficult it is
to stop the ball
from all the way down there.
[female announcer] She knows now,
she knows this is...
[phone rings]
Get me a copy of the script, now.
[female announcer] ...a spectacular chip
on the most delicate climb down this hill.
[male announcer] And the other thing
she's got to do is compose herself.
Toh. Is the file ready?
They are rushing me.
-It's nearly there.
-Rendering?
Yes.
What is her name again?
Ariya "May" Jutanugarn.
-May...
-Move. I will handle it.
MAY - ARIYA JUTANUGARN
-Save it.
-Okay.
-Do it now.
-Five minutes.
Has someone edited the script
that she hit a hole-in-one on the 16th?
-I did.
-Great.
Listen, as soon as she sinks this putt,
she'll become the first Thai person
to win an LPGA tournament.
And because the tournament is in Pattaya,
this will be a historic home win
for Thailand.
Ready? We're going on the air.
[female voice] Quick!
Where is Nu?
[male announcer] The equation is simple,
to keep alive the dream of winning
in front of the home crowd.
[crowd gasps]
[newsroom audience]
Oh!
Nu. Nu?
We're all set.
[crowd in TV clapping]
-[female voice] What?
-[male voice] It was so close.
[male announcer] They were preparing
to celebrate, but she finishes...
[male announcer talking indistinctively]
TEE SHOT: ARIYA JUTANUGARN
[narrator] If you think
this is just a golf movie...
[chuckles]
That's my first reaction too.
In Thailand,
who would give a damn about golf?
But what if I tell you that
this is a story of an ordinary family
with two daughters in the top ten
of the Women's World Golf Rankings?
And one of them is the world's number 1.
You might ask, "So what?"
What if I tell you
that the whole thing
started from a crazy father?
So crazy that he thought
he could turn his two girls
into world-class golfers.
Now you wonder
how he could pull that off, right?
Let me tell you the whole story then.
10 YEARS BEFORE THE TOURNAMENT
[male voice]
The Thai flag and the Thai National Anthem
are symbols of Thailand.
May we all rise
to pay respect to the flag.
Take pride in our independence
and in the sacrifice made
by our Thai forefathers.
MO - MORIYA JUTANUGARN
MAY - ARIYA JUTANUGARN
[school bell ringing]
The time is 8 a.m.
[Thai anthem plays]
♪Thailand is founded on blood and flesh♪
♪Thai people share♪
♪Every portion of the land
belongs to us...♪
Good morning, sir.
Can I have a moment with you?
♪Is because the Thai people♪
♪Have long loved one another
And been united...♪
DISCIPLINE, LEARNING...
Skipping the morning flag salute,
attending class for half a day,
and no homework.
Don't you think that's too much to ask
from the school?
I...
I mean, are you sure...
that this won't affect
the development of your daughters?
Do you think I'll put my girls
through 15 years of school
and they'll graduate...
and then what?
They'd study hard...
only to get a piece of paper
then beg companies to give them jobs?
Do you seriously think
I should let them go through that?
I'm talking about their education.
Girls their age need proper education.
It's important for them to have friends
and join activities.
I only finished grade 4,
but now I have my own business.
I definitely have more money
in my bank account than you.
I'm training my daughters
to be world-class golfers.
So...
I'll decide what's important for them
and what's not.
Oh, I forbid them from eating sweets.
Keep an eye on them.
[alarm ringing]
[door creaking]
Stretch your legs.
The other one.
Enough.
Do 50 laps.
Don't cheat, or we'll start over. Go.
[panting]
My shoelace, Dad.
Tie it.
[footsteps approaching]
SCHOOL
YAKOO ICE CREAM
Sis, I want an ice cream.
Me too.
But we have to report our expenses to Dad.
He will give us hell
if he finds out we had ice cream.
May.
[laughs]
Ouch.
Hall, can I borrow some money?
I want ice cream.
Who are you?
Just give me some money.
When will you return it?
Where did you get the money?
My treat. Just eat it.
[clock ticking]
[female teacher] A subject is followed
by "do" or "does"
-or a helping verb plus "not" plus verb...
-[clock ticking]
[school bell rings]
[female teacher talking indistinctly]
[students chattering]
May.
Remember, the winner is the one
who can drive the longest.
Dad, I'm hungry.
One hundred more balls each.
Not counted if it's shorter than the last.
[clinking]
[clinks]
[alarm ringing]
[door creaking]
Faster!
How are you, champs?
They're more like prisoners.
It must be so heavy.
[breathing heavily]
I hate golf people!
[giggles]
[Dad] What took you so long?
What happened?
The teacher didn't let them out.
[Dad] Forget the teacher.
You ignored my instruction.
I said to come out at 12 p.m. sharp,
didn't I?
[Mom] The class wasn't finished.
How could they come out?
We've already got special treatment.
[Dad]
Shit. Just do exactly what I tell you to.
Never break my rules.
[Mom] They're just half an hour late.
[Dad] You're talking back now?
They slack off because you're weak.
My rules aren't flexible.
Drill and discipline, get it?
I'm so goddamn tired.
Don't be a dead weight, okay?
If either of you misses the flag,
I will punish you both.
Get ready.
That's why your chips suck.
Move your legs.
Line them up with the target.
Don't splay them. Close them.
Don't twist your palms
when you follow through.
Eyes on the ball. Don't look up.
Mo, you too. Don't lob it too high.
Just hit it solid.
Try again.
Now.
Not like that.
[car doors shutting]
In two weeks, I'll sign them up
in a professional tournament.
Get them ready.
Are you out of your mind?
They're children.
It'll take years before they can go pro.
You're such a loser.
Come out of your shell!
[applause]
[crowd cheering]
Mom, did you tell him?
I'll have my birthday cake, right?
May won today. Can we have two?
I told him. He didn't say no.
[ignition starting]
[motorcycle rumbles]
Do you want your birthday cake?
Too bad. You threw the vegetables
out of the car the other day.
This is the price you have to pay.
[whistles]
Move!
Faster!
[panting]
[narrator] That was how
their amazing careers started.
The girls had beaten everyone in Thailand
at such young ages.
But the amazing story
didn't just end there.
The amazing story that started
from their crazy father.
This was just the beginning.
THREE YEARS BEFORE THE TOURNAMENT
[photocopier beeps]
This tin can is a hole.
This desk is a golf course.
What is tee off?
-It's where the play starts at each hole.
-Correct.
A par-4.
How many strokes are you allowed to take?
Four.
Correct.
Sinking the ball in four strokes
on a par-4 hole
means you are okay.
But if you suck and have to take
the fifth shot, what's that called?
[stuttering] Bir...
Birdie?
[chortles]
[laughs]
Birdie my ass.
That's why your writing
has so many mistakes.
If you have to hit five strokes
on a par-4, it's a bogey.
And if you're good
and take only three strokes...
it's called a birdie.
Go fix your copy and file it again.
-Okay?
-Yes.
[sighs] And put my desk in order too.
-[May] Sis.
-[Mo] Hmm?
What do we do about the field trip?
Everyone has returned the form
to the teacher.
Shall we forge his signature?
[May] What do we do?
We have to tell the teacher.
-Yui.
-Please, Yui.
-Please.
-Please ask Dad to let us go.
-Please, Yui.
We've never been on a field trip,
like, ever.
Right.
It's just the planetarium.
The whole class is going.
-Please.
-Please, Yui.
Why me? You know he'll scream at me.
Why don't you ask your mother to do it?
[Mo]
No. You're the man for the job.
It has to be you.
You're a well-respected adult
and a business owner.
-Dad trusts you.
-Right.
-Please, Yui.
-Please.
Okay. Okay, okay.
I will try.
Yes!
Ouch.
[door slams]
You told Yui to ask me, didn't you?
You've agreed
not to interfere with my rules!
The girls need a break.
You force them to practice
without a day off.
What will they grow up to be?
They'll be professional golfers.
And all pros need discipline!
Don't you know how hard
world-class golfers have to train?
Do you have any idea?
It's not about golf anymore.
It's about our family.
This is too much for them.
Family?
Look at Yui.
His mother was also soft on him!
And he failed to reach the goal I had set!
I won't let it happen again.
Mo and May will go beyond Thailand.
They'll become international stars.
Remember that!
I know you have your rules and methods,
and I've done everything you told me to.
I just want them
to have a break sometimes.
They are still children.
They've got no friends.
They've dropped out of school.
Are you sure they're as good
as you think they are?
What if they fail? All will be lost.
We will have nothing left.
I don't have confidence in them.
I have confidence in myself!
In myself, get it?
All they have to do is practice, practice,
and practice.
Practice the way I tell them to!
I know you've cut Mo some slack
when I'm not looking.
Now she's falling behind her sister!
May has become a much better player,
you know that?
Don't pit them against each other.
I don't care!
I will do everything
to push May as far as possible.
If you think your approach
can help them improve,
you can take Mo, I give her to you!
May is mine. Mo is yours.
Then let's see
who'll take them to the stars.
[door creaks]
Faster. Go.
Keep moving.
Again.
[Dad] Again.
The winner drives the longest, remember?
The girls were spectacular today.
They stuck to my game plan.
Full swing.
Hit it harder.
Use your shoulders, not your arms.
Is that all you've got?
How can you be a champion, huh?
Again! Again! Again!
Hello?
Yui. Can you do me a favor?
May, did you remember your shot...
from the bunker that day?
Your follow-through was perfect.
Straight to the hole and a birdie.
I couldn't believe my eyes.
Go to bed early.
No running tomorrow.
I'll take you to get your passports.
We are moving to the US.
Mom, why are we moving?
To play golf?
Your dad has sold the house,
the car, everything.
We've got nothing left here.
[car engine rumbles]
UNCLE LAO NOODLES
Boss, what's so exciting about golf?
Hitting balls and walking for miles
in the sun.
It doesn't look fun to me.
Do you know who's the richest athlete
in the world?
Lionel Messi.
Do you know that in golf,
there are a dozen athletes
as rich as Messi?
How come?
Let's say, Usain Bolt,
he would train for four years
to race for ten seconds at the Olympics.
Those ten seconds will decide
how rich or poor he'll become.
But there are golf tournaments every week,
all year round.
So, you have a chance to win
on any week of the year.
Well, but who can win every week?
Even Tiger Woods wasn't even close.
Here's the thing.
In golf,
you don't have to always be number 1.
If you make the top ten
in every tournament,
you'll become the richest sportsperson
in this country.
Now tell me, if you have a daughter,
which sport do you want her to play?
Check, please.
Go back and prepare a scoop.
"The Jutanugarns are moving to America."
Moving to America...
-[phone ringing]
-Yes, Sport Channel.
TWO YEARS BEFORE THE TOURNAMENT
The program is in the morning.
[Toh] Tae, a call for you.
I am on this line.
-Yes, right.
-[Toh] He'll call you back.
Okay.
If the sponsors are interested,
I'll call them back.
-So, I'll leave producers phone numbers.
-[female voice] Hello?
Tae, check the results.
Bye now.
[phones ringing]
Guys.
Look at this.
[narrator] Well, the madman
was proving everyone wrong.
Moving to the USA was pretty mad.
May became World No. 1, Girls' Junior.
Who could stop them now?
Of course, when you're famous,
opportunities and sponsors
line up at your doorstep.
2012, IMG HAS BECAME
THE JUTANUGARN SISTERS' AGENT
Let me introduce you here.
This is Joe,
and he will be your caddie from now.
JOE, ARIYA'S NEW CADDIE
And this is Winny.
He will be your manager.
WIN, ARIYA'S MANAGER
Let's try this.
Do exactly the same as before
and may God be with you.
She's so powerful. She can drive farther
than other girls of her age.
But the driver makes it hard
to control the direction.
Let her try the 3-wood instead.
She'll have more control, right?
[narrator] When your star is on the rise,
it only keeps rising.
But when does it reach a limit?
We have to keep watching.
Yui, can you submit the petition again?
I want May to play in the LPGA this year.
She's phenomenal.
It's in the news everywhere.
[Yui] You're in the US, not Thailand.
They won't bend the rules for you.
She has to be 18 to play in the tour.
Darn it.
The girl has talent. Why make her wait?
She's just one year short.
What's the big deal?
[Yui] Look, there's a tournament
in Europe.
Why don't you take her there?
MAY COMPETED IN...
May, the par-4 18th is a tough one.
SIS, HOW ARE YOU THERE?
IT'S SO BORING HERE
Hey!
MO JOINED THE LPGA TOUR AT THE AGE OF 18
SIS, HOW ARE YOU THERE?
IT'S SO BORING HERE
When I go back,
I will eat everything I want.
Fatty.
Sis.
The next match in Pattaya,
I want to win my first tournament
in Thailand.
TOURNAMENT
[narrator] As I said,
everything that goes up must come down.
She was on the verge of making history
by becoming the first Thai
to win an LPGA championship.
But this ball betrayed her.
That fateful putt in Pattaya
would haunt May for a long time.
[Dad] You're not good enough for May
and for me too!
[Joe] I just want the best for May.
If you're not happy with me,
find another caddie!
[Dad] I'd like to thank all the sponsors
who've been supporting us.
Without the sponsors,
we wouldn't have come this far.
[screaming]
And a big thank you to the reporters
who've followed our journey.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Hi, Uncle Nu.
Hi, May.
It's all right.
Keep trying.
-It'll be yours one day.
-Thanks.
This is Tae.
Hi.
He's responsible for the golf scoop.
-He's been following your career.
-Thank you.
Uncle Nu, excuse me...
-I have to...
-Go on.
I understand you.
[spokesman]
All right, it's time to invite May.
Never give up.
I won't.
Goodbye.
[applause]
[cameras clicking]
ONE WEEK AFTER THE TOURNAMENT
[Dad] You're terrible at putting
and chipping.
That's why I've always pushed you
to drive hard.
If you had followed my plan,
you would've been
the first Thai LPGA champion.
I...
I did what I thought was best
under the circumstance.
And it's over.
Why do you have to rub it in?
You're pigheaded.
You've stopped listening to me.
And your caddie, Joe.
He's not good enough for you.
I'll fire him.
Dad.
It's my game. I'll choose my own caddie.
And Joe's been good to me.
Stop telling me what to do.
How dare you speak to me like that.
I've had your back all your life.
I've seen everything.
I made you what you are now.
Joe doesn't suit you anymore.
A caddie like that
will never get you near a trophy.
Is it because he's not good
or is it because he doesn't listen to you?
Stop dictating my life.
I'm not your little girl anymore.
I can decide for myself
what's good and what's not.
To tell you the truth...
I lost that match because of you.
If you hadn't bossed me around,
I would've scored.
[table thuds]
I am your father.
I created you.
You're here because of me.
You're my daughter.
You have to listen to me.
No.
From now on, I'll play the way I want.
You have no right to order me what to do.
You're not even a pro...
remember?
When you can play better than me,
then you can tell me how to play.
-Is everything all right?
-Fuck off!
[sighs]
-Miss, can I take these for you?
-Um, no.
I'm going to finish it.
[sighs]
[heartbeats]
[footsteps approaching]
[sniffles]
[Mom] May.
Your dad left.
He took all his stuff.
[sighing]
[coins chinking]
[Mo] This is all we have left.
Nine hundred and eighty dollars.
Wait.
[May] How long are we going to last?
We have a tournament in a few days.
We won't make it with just this much.
You two, stop worrying.
Focus on your game.
I will take care of everything.
[Yui] I'm trying to convince him.
But you know
it's impossible to change his mind.
Let him calm down a little.
You have to be strong,
at least for Mo and May.
Thanks, Yui.
[male voice] Hello? Is anybody in there?
This is your last day here.
If you don't pay rent today,
I'm gonna call the police.
You're gonna get thrown out in the street.
Do you understand?
Are you in there?
[indistinct female voice over PA system]
[indistinct male voice over PA system]
[May] From now on,
I'll play the way I want to.
When you can play better than me,
then you can tell me how to play.
[Nu] After her father left,
May suffered a slump in form.
Besides slipping down the world rankings,
a new star, Kristen Lee,
emerged as her rival.
From now on, you have to tell me
everything.
We are a family now.
[birds chirping]
This aisle. Go!
Woo!
Slow down, you crazy girl.
Stop. Stop.
I want this.
Watch my head.
Mo, May, brush your teeth first.
Eat now.
Hey.
-Again.
-Have some mackerel.
Ready to eat.
[Mo] May, what will become of us
if Dad comes back?
Sometimes I feel like...
I want him to stand behind me
when I'm hitting the ball.
But to come back into our family?
I don't know.
What about you?
No. I'm fine living with Mom.
-[exclaims]
-Hurry up, Fatty.
-You hit me?
-[exclaims]
-[May groans]
-[Mo exclaims]
[Mo]
Come on!
[May]
You hit me?
Take this!
[gasps] Darn it!
-[grunts, screams]
-Come back here!
[May exclaims]
[sighs]
-You're playing like a girl.
-[thuds]
May!
Are you all right?
May.
Where are you hurt?
Don't move.
I will go get help.
A dislocated shoulder
and rotator cuff tear.
Don't worry, you'll be back on the green
in three to four months.
Physical therapy is extremely important.
You have to be strict with yourself,
watch your diet.
MAY CAME BACK TO THAILAND
TO TREAT HER SHOULDER INJURIES
[sighs]
Excuse me, can I have the remote?
Thanks.
[news program's intro music plays]
[newswoman]
A new star player from South Korea
has made headlines everywhere.
Kristen Lee claims
the no. 1 ranking in such a short period.
So brilliant,
she's been called a genius golfer.
-[therapist] Lift yourself.
-[May groans]
[May groans, inhales sharply]
[grunts]
[pants, grunts]
[pants]
I do my best in every match
and every day in this match.
[breathes heavily]
I will increase the pressure.
When you're done,
can I have your autograph?
This win is one of my wins,
and to be the first of--
every day, or after this...
ARIYA - HIT OR MISS?
MISS THE CUT AGAIN?
[sighs]
[Nu] This is Tae.
He's been following your career.
[tapping on phone screen]
[line ringing]
Hi, this is May speaking.
[Tae] May who? The badminton player?
No, May the golfer.
Ariya Jutanugarn.
Well...
would you like to interview me?
Can we talk while I'm eating?
-Sure, let's be casual.
-Okay.
Okay, shall I start?
-Yes.
-Okay.
Could you update me on your injury?
[clears throat]
It's...
getting better.
Okay.
Will it affect your future performance?
[hums in thought]
[May]
Um...
DIG FOR DIRT ABOUT HER FAMILY DRAMA
Feel free to ask me anything.
I'll answer everything I can.
Right.
[Tae sighs]
What? Are you stopping?
Let's take a break. I'm hungry.
[chuckles]
Let's eat first.
Tae.
Let me tell you a secret.
This is...
the first time in my life
that I ordered noodles myself.
Can you believe it? It's so yummy.
I'm finishing it all.
I'll have another one later.
Let me tell you a secret.
The best noodle shop in the world
is right next to my office.
It looks like you'll be here for a while.
But when you're out, I'll take you there.
-Really? You'll take me there?
-Yes.
Let's go.
-I want to try it.
-Sure.
Can I have the cap?
-Go on.
-Thank you.
[newsman] All eyes in the golf world
are on you at the moment.
Beside your spectacular form,
you're also a beautiful woman.
What's your response
to those who say that you're no. 1
only because of the injury
with Ariya Jutanugarn?
I don't think like that.
I'm practicing so hard,
and I work hard a lot.
So, I'm here because of myself,
not because of anyone else.
It looks great.
I told you.
-Try it.
-[hums]
I thought you were hungry.
-I don't know how to use chopsticks.
-Use your hands then.
Go on. I won't sell your pictures.
-[May] Can I?
-Of course.
-All right.
-That's how they did it.
It's hot.
[May laughs]
-Take this.
-Thanks.
Taste it.
Look.
Awesome.
[May] Mm.
Mm. Where would you like to shoot
the photo for the scoop?
Hmm...
May, let me ask you something.
Why do you collect bottle caps?
Another egg noodle bowl, tom yum soup,
extra meat balls, and braised pork.
No veggies, no bean sprouts.
Make that two. Thank you.
I was reading the menu.
What's up? Not enough cash?
-No, eat your fill.
-Thanks.
You're welcome.
[shrieks]
Mom!
[May hums in delight]
-I miss you so much.
-Fatty.
[May exclaims]
Long time no see.
[May hums]
-What's this?
-What?
You're wearing makeup...
-And?
-and a skirt.
-You don't like it?
-Mm. Let's talk.
-What?
-A boy?
Watch your mouth, crazy girl.
Why are you dressed like this?
For a photo shoot,
at the 18th hole in Pattaya.
-Mm.
Now you both have to come with me.
Have you made peace with that cursed hole?
[Tae] One, two, three.
Ah, ah.
-[May] Like this?
-It's good.
-Thank you.
-Let's pack up.
-[May laughs]
[Tae chuckles]
Hurry.
Stop it.
[Mo] Maybe it's for the best
the ball didn't go in.
If you had scored,
Dad would've been here.
I don't know.
I like this life.
The life after you failed that putt.
[Dad] All they have to do
is practice, practice, and practice.
Practice the way I tell them to!
I know you've cut Mo some slack
when I'm not looking.
Now she's falling behind her sister!
May has become a much better player!
I'll do everything to push May
as far as possible.
If you think your approach
can help them improve,
you can take Mo, I give her to you!
May is mine. Mo is yours.
[door creaks, thuds]
[grunts]
I'll leave it all here...
at this hole.
When I recover...
I will become the world's no. 1.
And you...
you can take the second place.
[Mo]
Fatty. Wait until I show you my power.
Do you want to hurt another shoulder?
I'll have deep-fried snapper
in fish sauce,
crispy fried pork with basil,
and a carbonara.
Deep-fried snapper in fish sauce,
crispy fried pork with basil, a carbonara,
prawn sashimi in seafood sauce,
crab omelet, and fried rice.
And an ice tea bingsu.
Bring them all at the same time.
-Do you want something else?
-Nope.
ARIYA "MAY" JUTANUGARN
[May] Feel free to ask me anything.
I will answer everything I can.
DIG FOR DIRT ABOUT HER FAMILY DRAMA
[Tae] Let me ask you something.
Why do you collect bottle caps?
[keyboard clacking]
ARIYA "MAY" JUTANUGARN...
I've given you a month
to write about May Ariya.
And what's this?
A bottle cap campaign?
Nu,
I'm very disappointed.
May's the headline news.
There are so many things you can dig up.
The audience is ready to believe anything.
And you got me this?
Do it all again.
I'll take care of it.
[thuds]
RECYCLE BOTTLE CAPS FOR OCEAN HABITATION
-[Mo] Did you bring your passport?
-[May] I forgot.
Don't overact.
-You're so wicked.
-Stop.
[indistinct chatter]
Stop it.
-Mo, May, I have something to tell you.
-What?
Dad...
He's very sick.
Now he's in the hospital.
He has heart disease.
He's in the ICU.
He needs a bypass surgery.
But don't worry, I'm taking care of him.
[sighs]
MAY SUFFERED TEN MISSED CUTS
From now on, I'll play the way I want.
Joe, you told me it's 150 yards,
but you didn't tell me there's wind.
May!
May.
May is mine. Mo is yours.
-[yells in frustration]
-[metal clangs]
[Dad] A caddie like that
will never get you near a trophy.
And May God be with you.
May, are you all right?
[Mo knocks on door]
[Mo]
May.
He's gone.
My Dad.
No, he never left.
He's still somewhere deep inside you.
Do you know why I accepted
to be your caddie at that time?
Because everyone in the world of golf
should know you.
May Ariya.
But he's gone.
So it's your time to make your own choice.
What do you really want, May?
I want to be no. 1 in the world.
So...
what are we waiting for?
-Let's do this.
-Yeah.
[both laugh]
[newsman]
The Yokohama Tire LPGA Classic 2016
is approaching.
All top pros are coming
to this tournament,
including Kristen Lee, who said that
she's ready to win this championship.
[broken English]
My result is good. So, winner, it's sure.
[newswoman laughs]
I think you worked hard. You're a winner.
-Yeah.
-You're a winner today, you know?
And, uh, do you feel...
[sighs]
[Joe]
He's still somewhere deep inside you.
[sighs]
[inhales sharply]
[line rings]
[May]
Hello, Uncle Nu?
May I trouble you with something?
[news program's intro music plays]
Now, for sports news.
After suffering a slip
in form and world rankings,
Pro May Ariya Jutanugarn has a chance
to rebound this week
at the Yokohama Tire LPGA Classic.
Thai golf fans are sending her support.
Because I practiced so hard,
I'm gonna be a winner.
[audience laughs, applauds]
[audience applauds]
[female announcer]
The yardage is exactly right,
but the flight ball
is a little off target.
You are not her. You just think you are.
So, just get on with it...
and hit that ball.
[audience applauding]
[male announcer]
Wow. What a shot.
That's amazing.
That must be the shot of the year.
[female announcer]
Ha-ha, wow. I can't believe it.
[audience]
Aw.
[Tae]
Move left.
Set up properly.
[male announcer] Oh, wow.
What a beautiful smile from Thailand.
[camera shutter clicks]
[female announcer] Ariya's playing well
and will definitely make the cut.
Welcome to the day three live coverage
of the Yokohama Tire LPGA Classic.
May Ariya has narrowly made the cut.
If she wants to beat
World No. 1 Kristen Lee,
she has to play her best golf.
[audience applauds, cheers]
[newsman]
A phenomenal performance from Ariya.
With this form,
she has a real chance to win it
on the last day.
THREE WEEKS BEFORE THE TOURNAMENT
[May] Hi, this is May speaking.
May.
I want to ask you for a favor.
Can we meet?
Sure.
UNCLE LAO NOODLES
You want me to bring you to see your dad?
You're the only person he'll listen to.
I need to get over this.
If I can't get rid of this knot
in my heart...
I will never win anything.
You're just like your dad, you know that?
Do you have any idea
why he and I didn't talk for ten years?
We were once very close.
We came to Bangkok from the province
together.
But when we grew up,
our goals became different.
The day I realized that
he was using you two
to achieve his own goal...
I cut all ties with him.
In golf, the only person you have to beat
is yourself.
So, you have to go and see him yourself.
[female voice]
Five, four, three, two, we are live.
[news program's intro music plays]
Welcome to the final day of LPGA Tour
Yokohama Tire Classic 2016.
Today is the last day.
Ariya Jutanugarn will go head to head
with World No. 1 Kristen Lee.
Will Ariya win
her first LPGA championship today?
[male announcer] Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Kristen Lee.
[audience applauds, cheers]
And Ariya Jutanugarn.
[male announcer]
Hole 1, par-4.
Keep your eyes on the world's no. 1.
[male announcer]
She beautifully drives the ball
to the middle of the fairway.
Ariya is at the tee off
and is under a lot of pressure.
[man cheers]
[male announcer]
A brilliant first shot, straight and long.
The ball goes farther than Kristen's.
Superb.
[male announcer]
Kristen Lee's ball is in the bunker.
This putt line is tricky.
She has to sink this putt for par.
She missed. It's a bogey for Kristen Lee.
Wonderful. Ariya scores a birdie.
Yes! That's it.
After three holes,
Ariya is leading Kristen Lee
by one stroke.
[male announcer] It's a chance for her
to make history for Thailand.
TWO WEEKS BEFORE THE TOURNAMENT
Dad.
How are you doing?
[male announcer] She missed again.
The pressure is on Ariya.
The momentum has swung back
to Kristen Lee.
She turns the situation around
and now leads Ariya by three strokes.
[May] I'm concerned about your health.
You don't have to worry about my career.
I've had a lot of help lately.
Many foreign coaches have advised me.
You came all the way here to tell me this.
Did you know...
When you left me...
Mo,
and Mom...
did you know how much we suffered?
You built everything.
And all of a sudden,
you walked away just like that.
How could you be so heartless?
[male announcer]
An absolutely important putt.
She has to keep Kristen
from pulling ahead too far.
-[audience cheering]
-And Ariya's done it in a critical moment.
She's behind Kristen by two strokes.
It's still possible to catch up.
The Goddess of Victory
hasn't abandoned May.
Kristen Lee missed the putt,
and it's a bogey.
[male announcer]
Another birdie for May.
-Yeah!
-Woo!
[male announcer] Two birdies in a row
can turn the momentum in her favor.
She has a real chance to win it.
[audience applauds]
[male announcer] Ariya keeps making
birdies on the last nine holes.
We're now at the 17th hole.
If Ariya can save par,
she'll go into the last hole
with a one-stroke lead.
The championship is within her grasp now.
You won't achieve anything...
if you still have that mentality.
What a waste,
after I've taught you all my life.
[Dad] What happened in Pattaya
was just the beginning.
As long as you refuse to believe me...
it's hopeless
to dream of becoming the world's no. 1.
[male announcer]
Unbelievable.
Ariya dropped a stroke on the 17th.
Now the score is tied
with Kristen Lee at -14.
The championship will be decided
on the 18th hole.
[male announcer]
A wonderful first shot on the last hole
from the world's no. 1.
[Dad] Remember.
The winner is...
the one who drives the longest.
[male announcer] Ariya's drive is longer,
but the ball's in the rough.
A tough next shot for her.
Kristen Lee's approach
stopped in front of the green.
Five.
[male announcer] She picked this iron,
meaning she'll go for it.
But from the rough, it won't be easy.
-[audience] Aw.
-No. The ball landed in the bunker.
It's the same situation
as in the last hole
of Honda LPGA Tour Thailand in 2013.
[groan]
[male announcer]
It's Kristen's third shot.
She has all the advantages over Ariya.
Whoa, too strong.
The ball drifts beyond the hole
and down the slope.
It's not going to be
a walk in the park for Kristen.
[audience applauds]
Unbelievable.
Kristen Lee missed her third shot.
Now it's an opportunity for Ariya
and for all of Thailand.
[Dad] As long as you refuse to believe me,
it's hopeless
to dream of becoming the world's no. 1.
[May]
Thank you for taking me this far.
[May pants]
[pants]
But I won't stop here.
I will be the best in the world.
[audience applauds, cheers]
[male announcer]
A wonderful bunker shot.
May overcame the pressure and did it.
A decisive putt.
She has to save par with this putt
in order to remain in the competition.
[male announcer]
She missed.
Ariya has to save par now
to become the first Thai
to win an LPGA tour.
She'll write a new chapter
in the history of international golf.
[male announcer]
The most important putt in Ariya's life.
The shot that will make her a champion.
I know you can do it.
[golf ball falls into hole]
-[audience cheering]
-[male announcer] That's it!
Ariya Jutanugarn has won
the Yokohama Tire LPGA!
Bravo!
She's the first Thai in history
to ever win an LPGA tournament.
Ariya Jutanugarn!
The journey has been long
and full of obstacles.
But she finally did it today.
She's brought pride
to the people of Thailand.
[Nu]
All right,
that was the amazing story
of May Ariya Jutanugarn.
As we all know,
that victory wasn't her highest point.
After the Yokohama Classic,
she would go on to win
many more tournaments
and eventually become no. 1 in the world,
full of pride.
But that's not exactly
what I want to tell you.
The real story is about
how we overcome our failure
and how we move on
from the lowest point in our lives.
Because we have to keep moving on.
May also keeps moving on,
no matter how disappointing or painful
her experience was.
Likewise, her sister,
Mo Moriya Jutanugarn,
kept improving until she reached
the top ten in world rankings.
This is the story of two Thai sisters
who became phenomena in the golf world.
Now, you're curious,
how much truth is in this?
Hall is real,
and we hope he'd forgiven May
for extorting his money
and that the boy who hated golf people...
I hate golf people!
would end up becoming a scientist.
Tae is real.
Well, sort of.
Initially,
he didn't know anything about golf.
But the story of May and Mo
became an inspiration
that made him want to become
Thailand's no. 1 sports reporter,
which is impossible
because I'm still here.
Finally, am I real?
Well, just forget it.
In fact, there's a genius
in every Thai family.
How children can grow up
to become geniuses
depends on how their parents
prepare, support, and groom them.
No need to imitate the Jutanugarns' way.
Find your own approach,
commit to it,
and never stop
until you've found your genius.
[indistinct male voice over radio]
[indistinct female voice over radio]
Let's go practice.
Translated by: Patchara Laeka