I’m so glad that the Abbot
has sent an active monk
to Don Kanun Temple.
There’s someone ahead.
Please pick them up.
I don’t think we can.
It’s full. It will be crowded.
The Mercedes is quite big.
Be generous.
Come. Get in.
The one who has the most things,
sit on the inside.
Good Karma can be found
in this life, right?
Look at your big face, full of virtue.
Is that right?
Turn away!
-My ear!
-That’s a pig.
The pig is going to bite my ear.
Hey! Red lipstick.
Go sit in the back seat.
How can you sit with the monk like this?
It's crowded. I can't drive.
Go. Just go.
That’s not it.
You grabbed the wrong gear.
Who farted?
-Did you eat a rotten dog or something?
-Open the door.
Don't mess up the seat.
-Hurry!
-You've got an upset stomach. Go.
Go sit in the back.
So sad.
Mama is dead.
Move. Stop!
-Stop! Move out the way.
-Why?
-You move!
-Why should I? I won't.
Please give way to the monk.
Let me tell you,
my mama's body hasn't been treated.
If we don’t get there in time,
she will be rotten.
Me too.
If I don’t get to my wedding in time,
I will be rotten too!
Getting married? Take off your hat.
-No!
-Take it off.
No!
Let me see.
How many snakes are on your head?
You're crazy.
Please give way.
-I'm going to the wedding!
-I won't give in.
-So no one goes anywhere.
-No!
-Move!
-Go!
Please stop.
You don’t have to stop us.
I won’t give up either.
I didn’t come to stop you from fighting.
It's a simple thing.
You should disagree.
We are all Thai anyway.
Well, half-Chinese.
Do not give in. It's humiliating.
These big events,
let them destroy the bridge.
Before you two fight,
please let me through. It's almost noon.
Okay!
The cortege goes left.
That’s it!
The groom.
Aren't you ashamed?
They can go left. We can too.
To the left!
Why stand there?
Aren't you rushing to the wedding?
You take your mother to the funeral.
Aren't you coming back to the temple?
-Your lip is drooping.
-Let's go back.
Mama is dead.
Come.
-Yes.
-Hurry.
Help me push.
-Push!
-Harder!
You guys
are lucky to push the monk's car.
Yes.
The monk first. Please get in.
Okay. Thank you.
You only sleep and eat all day.
If you have time,
drink something soothing.
Yes.
HERMITAGE FOR MERIT
-Let's go.
-Okay, Song.
It's not what you think.
The locals don't know
that there's a new monk.
Where are they going then?
They go to the place
they believe in more than temples.
Please come.
In five minutes,
the medium will start a ritual.
Who brought a sacrificial offering?
Put it here.
Who hasn't brought one?
Please offer some token.
On the right side are garlands.
On the left are eels.
Set birds and fish separately on the left.
Who hasn't made an offering?
The medium will start soon.
Welcome... What?
Buy a sacrificial offering.
Buy eels and you will
find things easy.
What? Father.
Wow! You are lucky.
Master Phoem welcomes you in person.
Master Phoem!
Phoem is here!
He's going to meet his people himself.
Up close and personal.
The market and temple are very close.
Just turn right here and we're there.
Almost there.
Wait up.
We're here.
Let me get the door.
Please.
Weirdo?
Weirdo!
Where is he?
You can look around. I'll park the car.
Sure.
Weirdo!
Shit!
I ran over the monk.
I'm going to hell!
He must have shit himself. I ran over him!
Does this happen often, Song?
Lucky that it's my robe.
If it was the lower robe,
it would bring rain.
Weirdo!
He must be sleeping.
Weirdo.
Is there someone weirder than Song?
What are you doing, Weirdo?
Come on out. Weirdo!
-Hey!
-Ouch!
Is this Weirdo?
No, sir.
Liang is happy that you come here
so I can make a merit.
Liang, why didn't you go home?
What are you doing at the temple?
Stupid!
I came here to welcome him.
Have you seen Weirdo?
Today, there's
a ceremony at the hermitage.
A big one. How can he miss that?
Stupid!
Right?
Above limits. Live your full life.
Do not drink more than two.
A true man...
does not drink more than two.
A great warrior...
Thai with folk-song hearts...
do not drink more than two.
The shark!
Boy, are you going to eat it all?
Do not drink more than two bottles.
These are just...
one bottle each.
Welcome, everyone.
Make some merit.
Superman!
HERMITAGE
It's time for the medium.
Come. Welcome.
Get back.
The spirit is here.
Pay respects to him.
The spirit goes to the wrong medium.
Change it now.
The spirit is in you, Kradong.
The spirit is here now.
What? Why wake me up? You bastard.
She’s a woman but has the voice of a man.
It's really sacred.
Pray!
I know everything.
But can you let me have some rest?
So many people.
How can I answer you all?
Just pick four or five people
that are in big trouble.
Bua Klee, what's your problem?
Stop! Don't tell me. Same old thing.
Your husband.
My husband
hasn't come home for weeks.
He's with someone.
Don't worry.
Just buy seductive oil and
sprinkle it around to bring him back.
Seductive oil.
MAKBOON SUPERMARKET
Make your lover crazy about you.
Sixty-nine Baht per bottle.
Buy ten, get one free.
Yoy. Can't you eat or shit?
Speak! Yoy.
I want a wife, sir.
Whoa!
How hard can it be? She just died.
Hey!
Died?
-Get out!
-So,
-I don't need one.
-Get out!
Get out! Get the hell out!
Get out!
Why so angry?
Why drive me away like this?
I didn't drive you away.
How hard is it to have a wife?
How about Bau Klee?
Her husband's about to leave her.
No! I don't want to be his wife.
Don't say something like that.
Why so picky?
Shit.
She's angry.
Get out!
The spirit is gone.
What about the rain, Master Phoem?
You postpone it for months.
-Right!
-Yes.
What's wrong with you, Muek?
No, father.
How can you do that to a crazy man?
He's trouble.
Just hit him.
-Send him away.
-Yes, father.
This is the place.
We can take advantage
of people's beliefs.
Clear!
We have some business to offer.
Interested?
I wonder if the business
involves money?
A lot of money.
You bastard. You asshole. Weirdo.
Curse you. You lazy man.
Go to hell, Weirdo.
Stupid!
It will get back to you,
I warn you.
None of your business!
Do it together. Don't go on about it.
A temple is like a house.
If the house is dirty,
who would want to stay in it?
So is the temple.
If you look around and it’s not pleasant,
who would want to come?
I got a match.
-I want this one.
-Don't worry. I brought a lot.
-So many.
-I'm here.
Hey!
Don't fight over it.
Hey. What are you doing?
Stop! Where are you going?
Come back, fatty.
-A ghost!
-A ghost is coming.
How's that?
It proves that children are more
afraid of a ghost than a monk.
Weirdo.
Don't ask.
What happened to me?
I won't tell you. I'm used to it.
Is he Weirdo?
That's him.
Hello, sir.
Weirdo.
Mana. I want you to accept me.
And I give all my heart to you.
Please love me a little
but love me for a long time.
Love me, sir.
-Love me.
-Song, catch him.
Not me, him!
-Love me.
-Stop shaking me.
We have a new monk.
We need to celebrate.
This is good, father.
Bring me here again, please.
-Cool.
-I'm your father.
My ears are sore. So noisy.
Don't they have someplace else?
-There's grandfather over there.
-So lame.
Where's Tui? Help me look for him.
I looked everywhere, no sign of him.
I told you to find Tui,
I'm not playing around.
Father. Did they come with Tui?
Don't call him Tui. Call him Pattana.
When did you come, Master?
Right, we didn't see you.
It's dark but you wear sunglasses.
What can you see?
-Our boss is waiting there, Master.
-To boost the negotiation.
Welcome, Master.
Give him a seat.
These girls will help in our negotiation.
-Nice.
-Please.
Come.
-Let me join.
-The fun is over there.
-Here.
-I can't see any bread.
Just boobs.
What business are we talking about?
I'm applying for the
Subdistrict Administration Organization.
To be honest.
You have the people’s hearts
and I have these things.
You want me to be a canvasser.
Attracting the locals, right?
Good that you understand things easily.
It's not that easy, because money...
cannot buy me.
I didn't mean that, Master.
You said the right thing.
Money can’t buy me
If it's not enough.
I'd give you an amulet
but your boobs will weaken its power.
You're saying that
the reason that people
don't come to the temple
is because they believe in
silly things, right?
Something like that.
Many monks cannot stay here.
You move.
Hey.
It's hard to change old people.
I understand.
But we have to persuade people
towards the right direction.
I think you'll have to
use a lot of effort.
Or...
Or what?
-Wait for a miracle.
-Miracle!
Go to sleep before miracles happen.
Hey.
Tell the parents tomorrow.
They have to come to study.
And be in our care.
-Yes.
-Hey.
Wake him up so he can sleep properly.
I'm going to bed.
Weirdo. Go to bed.
He's going to sleep.
Hurry.
He's been here for a while.
Hasn't he got some sleep?
So funny. Just go.
Have fun with me downstairs.
Take a shit with me. I need to shit.
-Do you think I can be a president?
-If you can, so what?
You have to try to choose me.
I don't have an ID card.
No ID card.
Weirdo. Come in with me.
No.
-Please.
-No.
Please.
I'll choose you to be president.
-Fine.
-Close it.
It's not stinky.
You're just not used to it.
-Go!
-Don't drive me off.
Go to hell.
Liang!
What?
What is it?
Pong cursed me to death.
Why curse him, Prompong?
And he's selling me a coffin.
Liang. I'll give you a coffin for free.
Good. Give it to me too.
I like free stuff.
Go to hell. I'll punish you.
Brother.
I don't think you should
ask for alms yet.
Yes. No one offers food to a monk.
People don't know
there's a new monk yet.
To ask for alms
is a monk's duty.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Mana.
Very good.
Honey, did you prepare the food?
I'll offer food to a monk.
Today is Saturday.
Get the rice in the bag.
Get everything in the bag.
It takes you so long to get home.
You are very drunk.
If you didn't have ears,
you would be an eel.
-Did the monk come?
-No.
How did I love him?
-Did he come?
-No.
Are you all right? Need anything else?
If you said no,
then what's standing right here?
Please, sir.
I want to do a good deed.
Aren't you Thai?
Why don't you offer food to a monk?
You act like this in this life,
what will your next life be like?
You don't do good deeds.
I'll kick my wife to show you.
Do you want to see?
-Invite the monk for me.
-You don't make a merit.
It's not good.
Making merit is not good?
I'll take one.
Sure.
May you be blessed.
Please, sir.
Weirdo.
Mana.
May you be blessed.
Paniang. Let's go home.
Brother!
-Brother!
-What is it?
-Good morning.
Brother, they are
gathering here again.
Do you want to study?
-Yes!
Where's Song?
Get Song here, Weirdo.
Ah, Mana.
Don't yell like crazy.
Yes. I'll go.
Song! Song!
-Hey!
What are you doing here?
-Why are you here?
-Why are you there?
I'm thinking.
Do you know who I am?
Uncle!
I don't understand.
You must look like a clown.
So he doesn't remember.
He may not know where his house is.
You...
find a place to teach the children.
Help me with this.
No problem. Right, Liang?
Stupid!
What problem?
Where did you get all this?
I helped the children's parents.
And...
-What?
-Nothing.
They are very happy
that their children are here with you.
They are very generous.
We helped
-and got all of this.
-What is it?
They don't offer food to a monk.
But very generous
to give all this stuff to the children.
-Yes, Brother.
-It's good.
Yes.
Thank you very much...
-My pleasure.
-...for helping me.
Excuse me.
You...
pack it up.
Mana.
My pleasure, Brother.
You walk strangely.
What is it?
Lying is bad.
What are you saying?
I know lying is bad.
But I do this with good intentions.
Where will you take all this?
To offer food to a monk.
To a monk?
-What's wrong with my ears?
-There's a new monk. Will you go?
I raised you since you were a baby.
You never made me a meal.
Don't you want to be a good daughter?
We did many bad things.
Better make a merit.
I don't want to go to heaven now.
I'm afraid of heights.
We should test our new monk.
It's a good thing.
Sacrificing your time to help society.
How can I help you with applying?
I want to get number nine.
I don't want number 13. It's bad luck.
How is 13 worse than nine?
I don't understand. Can you prove it?
Many hotels don't have room number 13
or a 13th floor.
It cannot be proved.
If it cannot be proved,
why do you believe it?
Do not believe it at all.
What if someone gives you money?
One gives you nine million.
The other gives you 13 million.
-Which do you choose?
-Thirteen million.
Aren't you afraid of bad luck?
-Go.
-Clear!
Didn't you preach to him?
I'm done.
Done? It's not the same as on TV.
-How's that?
-When they finish singing,
“More, more! One more song!”
There's no "More preaching!"
More. Again!
-What do you want me to do?
-Easy.
You get long hair like
those famous singers.
Brother, more! Give me your right hand.
Weirdo.
You should be...
Kicked.
He asked for a right hand.
So I gave him a right foot.
You're crazy.
Asking a monk to have long hair.
Help! They're fighting.
Hey.
What do we do?
Stupid! Go on with it.
The police are here!
Come on! The police are coming.
Let's talk.
Only one scene and you are here.
-I'm broke.
-Yeah?
They broke your nose.
-Are they gone?
-Yes.
-I'm okay.
-Enough.
What are you doing? Help.
Don't do it.
You committed a sin. You lied.
It would be more of a sin
-if you let them beat him.
-What's that?
-What?
-What's more,
this is a monk, not a municipality.
-Don't jump.
-Do not jump.
-Dad, don't jump.
What's wrong?
My husband is about to kill himself.
Please stop him.
Please help my dad.
When there's a good thing,
never tell me.
Always tell me when things are bad.
Let me help.
Because I can always help you.
Hey!
The monk is here.
Do you hear me? The monk is here.
Why do you want to jump?
Do you see him as orange juice?
No? You must see him as a banana.
-Get down. Why do you want to jump?
-I won't.
I'm broke.
They say Liverpool is the best.
But it's not. I have nothing left.
I want to die.
Are you sure that you have nothing left?
Yes, I'm broke.
All gone. Nothing left. I want to die.
I want to die!
What did you have when you were born?
-Nothing.
-What about now?
You have a house.
Your mom, daughter, and wife.
And you say you have nothing.
Liverpool did this to me.
-I want to die.
-Fine!
If you want to die, just jump.
Good.
Your wife is still young.
She can find a new husband
who's better than you.
Think wisely.
You earn some money
and put it on Liverpool.
Everything is Liverpool.
Why don't you think about Arsenal?
Your daughter is growing up.
Think about her. How can she live?
Dad's dead.
Mom has a new boyfriend.
Hey!
Shit.
And if you don't die?
Handicapped for sure.
Maybe paralyzed.
Enough! Stop.
You don't have to say more.
I won't jump.
You two!
You two
are having bad luck.
You have to exorcise.
Hey. We're having bad luck.
How can it be?
I just won a lottery.
-Right.
-Nonsense. Let's go back.
-Let's go.
-How can I have bad luck?
-I can't have bad luck.
Crazy.
There are few people these days.
These two just stir it up.
Wanting to have bad luck?
Please.
Pattana is here.
Clear!
Come apologize tomorrow.
-Yes.
-I'll help you first.
-Just go.
Let's go.
If you want anyone to have bad luck,
I'll arrange it.
What are you laughing at?
Let me join you.
Go!
It's not good, Weirdo.
Hello.
We need to talk.
I want you to control him.
Stop the trouble at the hermitage.
I didn't think I would see you here.
I didn't expect
to find Tuam and Prik's son
in the yellow robe.
You too.
You still have the job of lying to people.
This is not a threat.
Do you want to die?
To die is an eternal truth.
Die first to be a senior ghost.
Die later to be a junior ghost.
I'll see you at the welcoming ceremony.
It'll be fun.
Well said.
If this wasn't a temple,
I'd have him shoot you.
People here would like to know
this man before he became a monk.
What has this monk
ever done?
Do you want a kick?
Hey!
Here!
We're in trouble.
My amulet.
I got it!
A frog! I thought I had it.
What will happen to
the people who believe him?
Will the spirit be angry?
Absolutely.
These poor people
have bad luck without knowing.
Yes.
Everyone here
will have bad luck.
How can you come up
with the junior ghost?
Let's go.
We will have bad luck.
Let's go home.
Go back home.
It's not true.
Why do you make that up?
To turn crisis into opportunity.
They're frustrating father.
-I'm not in the mood.
-Hey!
Don't overthink it.
Look at the people
who respect the spirit.
They come here with hope.
But I won't say
anything about the monk.
Up to you.
Do as you think proper.
Chess!
It's okay. You stay in the car.
Do you want to study at the temple?
Do you want to go with me?
Or are you busy?
Or free?
Mr. Liang, where are you going?
Do you want to go to
the hermitage to exorcise?
Let me see.
Your face looks dark
like a burned coconut.
Isn't it?
-See?
-Som.
Look at yourself.
You almost have no shadow.
I'm dead!
Not yet.
But you will be
if you don't stop talking.
It's annoying! Go.
I just try to be good.
Annoying!
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Stupid!
People who don't believe in bad luck
are like a dog with no fear of hot water.
Oh, shit!
Seng! How's my table?
Why don't you worry about me,
not the table?
Fix it for me. It's falling.
-You...
-Wait.
Let me ask you something.
They say that our homes
have bad luck. Do you believe that?
Stupid! Sorry, Seng.
I don't know about others.
All I know is
when Liang is back,
he will have bad luck.
But I don't believe in bad luck.
Bad luck is caused by action.
Do good deeds and you get good deeds.
I believe that.
It's like if we plant Durian trees,
we'll get Durian in return.
If we grow jackfruit, we'll get jackfruit.
Brother.
We grow green beans,
why do we get sprouts?
-Hey!
-I'm watching drama.
I'm watching football.
-Muay Lek.
You have to go school. Go to bed.
No!
-Go to bed.
-No.
It's not clear. Boring.
-I'm bored too.
-Go to bed.
-Muay, take the milk.
-No.
Look at her.
Just like her mother.
It's a draw for Liverpool.
Are you addicted to it?
What are you saying? I'm not.
I've watched it for 20 years.
Never miss a single match.
Twenty years.
So do you know
why the football field
isn't a circle?
If it's circle,
how can they do corner kicks?
Do you want to be kicked?
It's blurred again.
You see for me.
I'll adjust the wire up there.
Let me know.
How is it?
Slowly.
They're taking the penalty kick.
Who's shooting?
I don't know.
Who?
Seng!
Seng, what's wrong?
Hong.
Hong. Wake up.
-What?
-Hong.
Wake up.
-Who's daring to wake me up?
-It's me.
Muek.
I have good news for you.
I think you are good. So I will tell you.
-Do you know?
-Tell me.
The spirit
said that anyone
who has "s" in their name
will have bad luck. A big one.
Do you believe it?
I do.
-Yes.
I have "s" in my name. I believe it.
I do too.
I do.
Seng Saraphee.
I have "s" in my name.
Shit!
Why "s"?
Simple.
Hang a banana in front of your house.
And put a sign saying
"There's no "s" here".
How many bananas, sir?
Just one.
I think the more the better.
Who is she?
My wife.
She will have bad luck
because of her mouth.
Tell your wife.
Do you want to die
because of your mouth?
Do you believe? Just one banana
can repel bad luck.
Are you whispering?
If you don't believe it,
then get out.
Who dares not to believe me?
Where are you going?
The spirit will be mad.
You stay.
You!
You stay here.
Old man!
You disrespect me!
The spirit is gone.
Who believes his word?
You can buy bananas
at the supermarket downstairs.
How much?
Buy ten, get one free. Only 69 Baht.
Only here. Come in.
THERE’S NO “S” HERE
SOM
What's this, Som?
Don't take it off.
The spirit told me to do it.
Are you trying to repel bad luck
or calling for it?
There's no "s" here.
And you write "Som".
Why are you writing your name?
You foolish wife. I need a drink.
You bastard!
If I'm smart, you still drink.
Boring! I'll play some cards.
Not good.
What?
I can fight.
Som!
Open the door for me.
I'll go to bed.
Som!
Open the door.
-Me again?
-Just go.
May you be blessed.
Do you have something on your mind?
Do you know about your friend?
Your two drinking friends
have been beaten up.
Saraphee and Sornrapong.
Two of them got beaten up.
It doesn't end well.
-Beaten up?
-Yes.
Who did that to my friend?
Nothing is impossible.
People are believing that
anyone with "s" will have bad luck.
Look at those two drunk guys last night.
What will happen
if the people in the temple
and Song get it too?
Master.
Yes. What?
My mother had to die when grandmother...
Hey!
-Who are you?
-Thieves.
-We are robbing you.
-Robbing? Come on then.
I'm a ghost.
Are you afraid?
A ghost. I'm scared. Stay away.
Hey!
You said he was alone.
A good man is protected by a ghost.
A ghost!
Go.
Why are they running?
Shit!
It can't get in.
It can.
But it's upside down.
Stupid!
Walk by yourself.
I won't carry you.
Stop arguing.
We can get in right there.
What's that?
Let's go.
Shit!
Wait for me.
It's too small. Who can get in?
What?
Where are my shoes?
Where are you going?
Hey!
-Wow.
-A lot of them.
It's like a shop.
-I go first.
-What?
What's this? Hey!
Hurry.
Hurry!
Get down.
How are you doing, sister?
Do you like it? I'm a responsible man,
but I have to work.
Help! Brother, help me.
Brother! Brother!
Brother! Are you sleeping?
Brother!
-You scared me.
-Open the door please.
What's happened?
You seem afraid. What did you do?
Hey!
What is it, Song?
Close the door. Hurry.
Tell me, what are you running from?
Ghost. A ghost.
Song.
You are old.
You shouldn't fall for silly things.
Ghosts don't exist.
If it does, it can't beat you.
Because you have muscle.
Ghosts don't have muscle.
You can eat, they can't.
They can't beat you.
-You should sleep in Weirdo's room.
-No, Brother.
He's scarier than a ghost.
Can I sleep here?
This is my place.
You sleep here.
-Yes.
-You tear off my net.
Close the window.
-It's windy.
-Close the window.
What are you so afraid of?
You are crazy.
Shit!
Many people here
were at the market
the day the monk
persuaded Seng to jump off.
PLEASE VOTE FOR
PATTANA RAENGSONGTHAM (TUI)
Right! He had an "s" in his name.
But he didn't believe the spirit.
Seng had to die.
Everybody,
do we respect the spirit?
-Yes.
-Believe in him.
We love the spirit. We trust him.
We love him.
I love and respect him too.
No less than anybody else.
Beside the spirit,
I also respect Master Phoem.
A thing like this
is called,
Claw me
and I'll claw thee.
Why do you have to frame the monk?
Frame? It's called
a scapegoat.
Isn't it working?
I'll talk to them.
You!
Who would believe you?
Do you forget that I'm a medium?
The spirit's agent.
If you want to destroy
everything I've built
then get out!
But I want you to know one thing.
Everything I did,
I did it for you.
I'm Pattana.
I'll serve all of you.
-Snack.
-Snack, here.
Mana, I'm hungry.
Want me to help?
With regret--
With pleasure.
Why are you in a hurry?
Where are you going?
To the temple.
Will you make a merit?
You will not get one.
Muek told me
Paniang is at the temple.
Temple? Why?
She's not going to be a nun.
Want to know?
-Come with me.
-Easy.
A smart person should use his brain,
not his force.
Let me help.
I guarantee that your daughter
won't go there ever again.
T for tiger.
B for box.
K for Kite.
B for Bowl.
-O for own.
-O for owl.
Okay. That's it for today.
Will you be back tomorrow?
Of course. She'll come.
Is that right, teacher?
-Of course.
-Attention!
-Thank you.
-Thank you, teacher.
Thank you.
Slowly.
Since you've been teaching the children,
they are having a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
She's no beauty pageant
but she loves children.
I feel at least
it can ease what I have done.
Brother.
I would like to ask
if I can dismiss her?
-Sure.
-Really?
-Thank you, Brother.
-Easy, Weirdo. Ah, Mana.
I'm not milk. Do not shake me.
Send her home.
Yes, sir.
Hello.
-Hello.
-I'm Sayan's parent.
Thank you for taking care of him.
So he will not study here anymore?
I ate already, sir.
Talk properly.
So he will not study here anymore?
No. He has to go to
hospital in Bangkok.
You should too.
Good luck then.
I'll get the car.
You don't have to dismiss us.
Sayan. Let's go.
Good luck.
Nothing.
Let's go.
I feel relaxed with the children.
Mana is not a beauty pageant.
I don't like children.
But if you like them, I'll like them too.
It seems like you don't want to go back.
Do you want to sit?
Why do you go to the hermitage?
When you're there, you get hurt.
Because...
I love someone there.
I don't care if I'm hurt. But...
she doesn't know.
Love her more.
If she knows, she'll love you back.
Really?
Really.
Do you travel a lot?
I've been everywhere.
North. I've been there.
South. I've been there. East.
I've been there. Everywhere.
I've been there.
You have to do a lot of good deeds
so you can go to heaven.
We should go back.
Let's go!
How can it be this bad?
Hey!
I'm broke.
-Only three Baht left.
-Want to do it again?
Mr. Pattana will arrange it.
But you will give something in return.
Okay?
Liar goes to hell.
You scared me.
It's Mana.
Hey.
Song. Do you know
why mosquitos like to
fly around the ears?
-Ears have holes.
-Wrong.
Actually, it flies all over our bodies.
But you cannot hear.
Hey.
But I can hear everything,
know and see everything.
But I say nothing.
-I don't want them to fly around my ears.
-You asshole!
Hey.
I'm not stupid.
I'm crazy but not stupid.
Right, Tick?
Where are you rushing to, Song?
Driving so fast.
To do some business.
Wow. You must have a lot to do.
I told Weirdo to help you.
Huh!
How can he help me?
There's only Paniang who can teach.
I haven't seen him yet.
-Just go.
-I will hurry back.
-Hello.
I want you to repel all the bad things.
Please. Help me.
Please.
Please, Brother.
Let's see with our own eyes.
Let's see.
Are you here for your daughter?
I come here for my hermitage girl.
-Muek.
-Yes?
She said she's here.
Father.
She's in the monk's house.
-I told you.
-Why's she in there?
You act like this.
You should be a monk in Pattani.
Don't worry. We cannot hide.
Finally, everybody knows.
Disgusting!
-I won't come here anymore.
-I won't respect him.
I won't offer food.
I'll take all the money to the hermitage.
He never gave us numbers
for the lottery.
Really bad.
Anybody who knows would be afraid to come.
-Get out of here.
-You don't regret it.
I can explain this.
-Look at him.
-Making excuses.
-Pervert.
-We see with our eyes.
Everyone sees it.
Do you want to make an excuse?
Get out of the temple.
Get out of here.
-It'd be better.
-You should be...
Clear!
-Get out!
Paniang.
Quiet. He's not a monk anymore.
He should leave.
Take off the yellow robe.
-Get out!
-Leave.
-Go!
-Get out!
-Get out of here.
-Right!
What's going on?
Why?
Did he shit in your cupboard?
Your brother took her in his house.
How could it be, father?
-Everybody saw.
-With our own eyes.
Get out of here.
Maybe the rain will fall.
-Go!
-Get out!
-Leave.
Okay. If it make everyone happy,
I'll leave.
It should be like that.
Ashamed, aren't you?
You lied.
-Go.
-Get out.
Get out. Go!
Go!
Get the hell out.
-Go.
-Go now.
-Who did you drive away?
-Stupid!
-Your brother.
-Stop making merit.
I feel ashamed.
-He was with a woman.
-I gave him a lot of money.
All of you believe the spirit.
Ask him!
Ask him the truth.
I know. I believe the spirit.
I asked where he was,
he said, "At the club".
Go!
Right.
He knows the truth.
The spirit will tell the truth.
Let's meet at the hermitage.
Of course. We'll see.
Why are you keep drinking?
-Drunk like a dog.
-So you admit to having dog as a husband.
-Give me your money.
-I won't.
I haven't paid for Teng's tuition fee.
-He might not get to study.
-I didn't study, I can survive.
You want him to be stupid as you!
What are you yapping about, Mom?
Yapping till father died.
Your father died because of alcohol.
You will too.
Good. Just die. I'll be fine.
Where are you going?
To drink with my friends.
Don't get into a fight.
I know. You say that every day.
You still do it every day!
Get a haircut. It's too long.
It will be short then.
This son...
-Teng.
-Mom.
Are you hungry? Here, fried rice.
Have some.
You don't have to.
How are you?
I'm fine seeing you in jail.
I was going to bring you alcohol.
But I respect the police.
Be good in there.
Don't let them kick you out.
You're being sarcastic.
I talked to the village leader.
He promised to bail you out.
But I think
you have to stay in jail.
Remember.
A gangster's life
only ends with death,
or jail, like you have now.
I was in the wrong direction
but I improved myself.
I have a lot of money for you.
Just do not stay
in the temple, will you?
Hell is waiting for you.
Why do you say that?
You never make merit.
All you did is sin.
You expel a good monk.
Everybody saw
that monk with a woman.
Yes. I saw that too.
With my own eyes.
That's right.
You saw it.
I saw it.
The monk is with my woman.
Why do you say confusing things?
The monk was being framed.
Bullshit! There's no spirit.
They lied to us.
Shit.
They're escaping.
Hurry.
HERMITAGE
Everyone!
Listen!
If you choose me,
there won't be bad people like this.
We'll punish them.
-Yes.
-Hey!
-Hurry. Let's go.
-Good that I wore shorts today.
Hurry. They're following us.
There!
-Hurry. Paniang
-Why are you following me?
Hurry.
Hey!
What a mess! It's a mess.
What happened?
It's gone.
Help!
What happened?
Brother.
Phoem and Paniang are in trouble.
Where are they?
Do not run.
Don't run.
You won't get away.
What should we do, father?
Just call the police.
Why police?
They didn't get fooled.
We are being lied to.
-I bought so many bananas.
-Right.
-Do it now!
-Hey! Stop.
-We have laws.
-Yes.
You fooled us.
It's against the law.
-Right!
-Hey!
Prison is not for dogs.
He called us a dog.
Father!
Father.
Paniang!
Weirdo!
He can't swim.
Neither can I.
Weirdo!
Brother. Help.
-Brother.
-He's gone.
Where is he?
Where?
Hey.
They're there!
Make way.
Make way for me.
Weirdo. Hey, Weirdo.
Weirdo. Where's the Brother?
He's not waking up.
What should we do?
CPR!
Mouth to mouth.
Hey! With this Weirdo...
I'll do it.
-He woke up.
-He survived.
-Father.
-Hooray! He's not dead.
Phoem. Give me a hand.
-Give me your hands.
-Grab here.
Where's Brother?
-Brother!
-He's pushing me up.
-Get up here. Brother.
-He's here.
-Brother!
-Dive and see, Weirdo.
Dive!
-Where's Brother?
-Brother.
Is he dead?
I can't see him.
Brother.
Hey! That's his robe.
-His robe, there!
-Let's see it.
Is that Brother?
Somebody dive in and get it.
He's dead.
Don't curse him.
Song.
-Song.
-A ghost!
-Hey!
I'm here.
Brother.
He's in the water.
He's still alive.
I'm not a fish.
Why don't you come over?
-I can't.
-Why not?
The lower robe is gone.
Someone get a robe. Get it to him.
Brother. Be careful of the fish.
-It's cold.
-Hurry.
Get the monk and all the liars!
This place will be better,
and the rain will fall.
-Right.
-Why do you say that?
-Catch him.
-What?
It will rain this evening.
Rain? What?
What are you saying?
You will see this evening.
-Trust me.
-Fine.
How can it rain?
Last chance.
We'll see this evening.
He's in church.
How is it?
-It's cloudy.
-No, it's not.
It's dark.
-Do you want to bet?
-How much?
Brother. What if it doesn’t rain?
Right. It doesn’t look like rain.
If I say it will rain, then it will.
Monks cannot lie.
Yes, you two
are too old.
Just trust the monk.
Who can we trust?
One is a fraud.
The other is an expelled monk.
-You're right.
-Yes.
Trust me. Choose me.
And I will give you everything.
-Even--
-An asshole like you
cannot do what you promise.
It's him. He paid me to get to the monk.
Liar!
-He's lying.
-Don't trust her.
Don't trust them.
-Hey!
-She's lying.
This Pattana paid
the medium to lie to people.
That's right.
You, curly hair. You paid me
to go out of the temple when she came.
-Get out!
-You too.
-Clear!
Brother.
How did you know it would rain?
I listened to the weather forecast.
Weather forecast.
I thought you could make it rain!
Listened to the weather forecast!
You look happier
since you start making merit.
The rice is hot. Be careful.
Thank you.
Wait for me.
Why don't you help?
It spilled. How can we eat now?
It's wet. Will it work?
It's okay. If it doesn't work,
throw it away. If it works, keep it.
-No harm.
-Okay.
It doesn't work.
It's all wet. How can it work?
You have to try.
See? It works. Keep it.
This is a director's joke.
We play it for him.
Actually, I don't want to.
Same old joke. Let me try--
Subtitle translation by Amiga Jenkansuk