YEAR 2004
I want to loan ten million baht.
Kid, you can deposit or withdraw
money at the front counters.
I want to open a factory.
Kid, I have lots of
loan applications to review.
Let's do this, then.
In one sentence,
tell me something
that will get my attention.
ITTHIPAT KULAPONGVANICH
You don't have to care about
who I am or how old I am.
Just listen to me.
My name is...
TOP, GIVE ME THE FIRE BLADE
I WANT TEN MILLION IN EXCHANGE
I made you guys set the paper margins
to 1.5 inches at the top and on the sides.
Once the margins are set,
type the information you have
into MS Word.
Make sure you typed your name correctly.
Fix it now if it's wrong.
Once you are done,
press "enter" or move down a row
and type your biography.
SHIT, MAKE IT CHEAPER
I NEED IT TO KILL THE DRAGON
Make sure the information is correct.
FIND ME THE MONEY
OR GET THE SWORD YOURSELF
DAMN IT, YOU TOOK ALL THE ITEMS
ON THE MAP, HOW CAN I GET ANY?
JACK, I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER
BIGTOE WANTS TO BUY SOMETHING
SHIT, REALLY?
...to let the computer know
that this file on MS Word
has a name.
Next...
Put it on MS Word.
Okay? Once you have a photo,
set its frame to any color you want.
Check out the picture and the information.
JACK, WHAT IS "SGD"?
It means "Singapore Dollar."
That's right.
It's 12,000 baht.
Weren't you worried about giving
your bank account to a stranger?
Not at all.
I've got the balls.
Crinum Lily
Is blossoming in the field
Grow me
Tuang.
May I borrow your bankbook?
BOONTUANG MAKMEESUK
Why do you want to borrow my bankbook?
Just let me borrow it.
I have 50,000 in my bank account.
You only have 1,500.
Let's see what will happen.
Sweet!
Here you go.
Oh, my god.
I still have eight more dragon boots,
forty-three more shields,
forty more swords,
and seventeen more armors.
This is...
awesome.
Mister.
What comes with the best model?
Mostly first class insurance.
Is that all?
If it's a down payment, then that's it.
Where did you get so much cash?
I sell weapons.
ISSUE A VISITOR BADGE BEFORE ENTRY
You can't get in
without a parking sticker.
Here is your sticker.
RESERVED FOR THE SCHOOL DIRECTOR
Song, no more excuses.
You can go now.
Itthipat, give me your parents' numbers.
Come on, sir.
Please don't call them.
How about you deduct 40 merit points
and call it a day?
Please don't call them.
You don't have any points left.
How about this?
May I donate money
for the new neon sign for the school?
Are you trying to bribe me?
No, sir.
I just want to help our school
as much as I can.
This is what they call a bribe.
Why can't you be like your siblings?
They graduated
and found great jobs in China.
How will you earn a living, Itthipat?
ADMINISTRATION
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
The whole school knows.
But only you get to sit in the car.
As if.
We can't park here. Let's just go.
Here's a parking spot.
You want noodles with extra crab, right?
Wait, Top!
To go, please.
Sure.
-How much?
-It's 280 baht.
Fuck you.
Top!
I got your favorite chestnuts too.
Okay, let's just go.
Tuang.
Is Dad home already?
-He came back this evening.
-Is he sleeping?
Yes. Is this your car?
Yes.
Tuang.
Move Dad's car back.
That should be enough room for mine.
Okay.
Top.
Press the top button. Press it. Hurry!
If you spend money like this,
you will go broke one day.
Return your car tomorrow.
Be honest with me.
Are you betting on soccer games?
No.
I already told you,
I make money from online games.
Stop lying.
I already explained it,
but you just don't understand.
Top.
If you don't graduate,
you will be really sorry!
I'm warning you now.
All I want is for you
to study.
Can you not make us worry?
UNIVERSITY ADMISSION RESULTS OF 2003
EXAMINATION ID NUMBER
WE ARE SORRY TO SAY
THAT YOU ARE NOT ACCEPTED
Wow.
This is a whole new world.
The image is so clear.
There are
many new games.
You can watch movies too.
-Really?
-Yes.
But for movie lovers,
this one is better.
It's made in China.
It's only 800 baht.
It will get the job done.
Get a new one if it breaks.
I see.
And
how much is
the PlayStation 2?
I can sell it to you
for 25,000.
How about 24,000?
Give me a discount.
Please don't haggle,
I barely marked it up.
Come on.
I haven't even looked around yet.
Fine.
I'll give you a 500-baht discount.
So it will be 24,500.
Are you okay with that?
What about this?
Don't give me a discount.
I'll buy it for 25,000,
but give me the DVD player.
No, I can't do that.
Eight hundred baht is too much.
I'll look around, then.
Wait. Fine, it's a deal.
Kid!
Top.
Mom.
Do you want to play games with me?
Wait.
How did the admission go?
I got accepted...
to a private university.
Private universities are good these days.
The tuition fee is around
50,000 to 60,000.
It's not that expensive.
Please look after this client for me.
No problem, sir. I'll get going, then.
All right. Thanks.
Go to a community college.
Mom.
-A private--
-You didn't study hard.
So why are you complaining?
I will take care of it.
I have the money. I don't need yours.
Honey, what are we going to do about Top?
Let him go to a community college.
How can he go to a community college?
How can he compete with others?
He might not graduate.
If he's going to work hard,
I wouldn't mind the cost.
You should understand how our son is.
You always spoil him.
No wonder he's a brat.
I won't allow it.
He'll go to a private university.
Does he know how bad the economy is now?
But his future is important too.
What?
You can't stop me now.
Hey, what's up?
Can you sell the DVD player
to me for 300 baht?
I want to buy them together.
Come on, don't do that to me.
I got it for 800 baht.
Mister.
You were willing to sell the PlayStation 2
to me for 24,500, right?
I said I would pay 25,000 baht,
but you have to give me the DVD player.
You agreed to that deal.
That means you'll still make a profit
by selling the DVD player
for 500 baht.
Therefore, the cost of your DVD player
must be lower than 500 baht.
Wow.
You're a true businessman.
How many
are you planning to buy?
Fifty.
I thought you were going to buy
a thousand players.
All right.
The cheapest I can give you
is 500 baht each. Are you okay with that?
I see. So you're opening
a DVD player factory.
No.
This is just the beginning.
What? Just the beginning?
How much longer?
Can you please pay attention?
Are you done?
I haven't sent it yet.
All right. Make it short. Go on.
Okay.
So Mom scolded me.
Why didn't you spend the money
on school supplies?
The image is clear.
It comes with a remote.
Now you will enjoy
watching your favorite movie even more.
Watch this.
What the hell?
My life went downhill.
The DVD player broke.
How could you buy
a DVD player made in China?
Don't you know
that it only lasts for a few days?
It broke before I even sold any.
Give me new ones.
No exchanges. They have no warranty.
How come?
It's only 500 baht.
Just throw it away.
Why didn't you tell me before?
Only stupid people don't know it.
I can sue you, you know?
Go back to your mommy and daddy.
Take your shitty DVD players back!
Shit.
This won't even cover half
of the money you ripped me off.
Dad.
I'm going home.
Do you want a ride?
Doing business
isn't as fun as playing online games.
I just think you should know.
I could have sold them all
if I wasn't conned.
Welcome to the real world.
When you lose, it can cost you everything.
Even adults can barely survive.
Kids are no exception to this reality.
I'm giving this to you
so you can study anywhere you want.
I am not one of your employees.
Let's start. All right.
The idea of our generation,
that we will study,
includes the product...
That was it.
I went back to school.
Hang on.
-Your dad gave you money. You declined.
-Yes.
How did you get the money for school?
Did you really go back to school?
Of course, I did.
How did you pay for your tuition?
You took your dad's money, right?
No, I really didn't take his money.
-Right? It came off.
-No.
-It came off.
Do you have an amulet to sell?
Mister.
I want to pawn an amulet.
Let me see it.
Here.
How much do you want?
I'll take...
a hundred thousand. That's it.
A hundred thousand?
Please, sir. Help me out.
It's for my tuition.
Fine.
A hundred thousand, it is.
I like to support people's education.
-The money is really for school, right?
-Of course.
All right.
Here.
That was the first time I was in debt.
If you think you will be rich,
you will be rich.
If you think you will succeed,
you will succeed.
The company
used the Urban Forest Strategy plan
to become as successful
as they are today.
The Urban Forest Strategy plan
-consists of
-Fuck, Jack.
-creating relationships
-I can't do this. Let's leave.
-with our rural customers.
-No.
I'm a good student now.
Oh, please.
You're reading a soccer magazine.
But I'm listening to him.
I don't hear people
say "Bao Zheng" anymore.
Now, they only say "Bao." Our generation
pays attention to...
Top.
You know we are paying for
every second of class, right?
Here. Just hit the record button
for me, then.
I won't attend this class anymore.
I went back to school,
but I kept thinking about
what I could do
to get my dad's amulet back.
It's your turn.
Aod.
Those who can't follow the rules
will be punished.
Therefore,
all of you will do
public service
by picking up the trash
in front of this building
for the next three days.
You start today.
Now.
Right now.
Okay.
Please proceed.
Make it slower. That was a bit too fast.
Okay.
And your voices were not balanced.
Oh, we forgot to warm up our voices.
Hey.
How did you get here?
Why would you say that?
No, that's not what I meant.
Don't you have class today?
I have class, but you're not there.
I'd rather have you.
Well, you can't have me
because I have class.
Come on. Let's get some crab noodles.
I'm starving.
I can't. I have rehearsal tonight.
What?
We hardly ever get to meet.
Are you busy now too?
It's not that I'm busy,
you're just too free.
MUANG THONG THANI
You only need to invest 800,000 baht.
The admission fee of 400,000
will be waived. Today, you can...
Can I try them?
Yes, you can.
It's good.
-It's good.
-Is it good?
You can't miss this price.
You don't need to try it any longer.
We have a special promotion
for this event.
Three for a hundred.
Feel free to try it.
Please try our chestnuts.
-It's free.
-Can I try two?
Of course. Take some.
It's free.
Go ahead.
Hello, mister.
These chestnut baking machines
are on promotion. This way, please.
This machine
can control the temperature.
It can go from 150 to 180 degrees Celsius.
This way, the chestnuts will not explode.
And this mixing paddle
will mix the chestnuts
so that they are heated evenly.
We're the first company
to import it from Japan.
So if I buy this,
I'll be the first one, right?
Yes, you will.
How much is it?
It's very expensive.
I didn't ask if it was expensive.
I asked how much it costs.
What is this?
I'm going to sell chestnuts.
This machine automates the baking process
so I won't break my back.
How much did you pay for this?
They sold it for 500,000.
But I rented it for 50,000 baht.
You can buy one for 30,000
at the weekend market.
It's okay, honey.
What's done is done.
I dreamed about Guan Yin last night.
She carried something black in her hand.
It must be a good sign.
Everything on the whiteboard
will be on the exam.
If you have any questions
or if there's something
you don't understand,
please ask me now.
Are there any questions?
Mister.
Why must you soak the chestnuts?
So I can tell which ones are spoiled
and which are not.
Really?
How can you tell?
The floating ones are spoiled.
The sinking ones are still good.
Then what will you do?
I'll roast them.
And then what?
Pay up.
When trying to gather economic data
to analyze a business,
you should gather information
from various sources.
What would you like?
Wow.
Your chestnuts have the best smell
around here.
What type of coffee do you use?
Try it yourself.
There will be a ten-point quiz
at the end of class.
The questions require a lot of details.
In my opinion,
you must understand this thoroughly
before you can graduate from this faculty.
Sweet chestnuts!
Hello.
-Get them here.
-How much is one box?
Only 280 baht.
-I'll take one.
-Wait a second.
Shit.
Am I going to die?
Tuang.
Please try my chestnuts.
What does that face mean?
Mom, try it.
I think it's delicious.
Everything is ready.
Everyone has already signed it.
Here, read it.
Okay.
I'll head back now.
The chestnuts are good.
Did you buy them in Chinatown?
No, Top is roasting them here.
He wants to sell chestnuts.
Your son works very hard.
He wants to be a Tao Kae Noi.
SHOP'S NAME: TAO KAE NOI CHESTNUT
Here, it's the last spot.
Do you want it?
-Right here?
-Yes.
What would you like?
One spicy salad.
-How spicy?
-A little spicy.
-Do you want sauce on the side?
-Make it a large.
A lot of veggies?
One second.
Thirty baht.
TAO KAE NOI CHESTNUT
Come on, Top. We're almost there.
Shit.
I'm not cut out for this work.
What's that for?
Your mom told me to put it here.
Come on.
The chestnuts will sell themselves.
We don't need any superstitions.
Did we sell 600 grams?
Did you fall asleep?
No, I didn't, Top.
Thank you.
Four sticks? Please line up.
-Please line up.
-Did you do that?
Dancing meatballs. Four sticks?
-I did. I yelled too.
-The meatballs are hot and yummy.
But I can't beat her voice.
Her voice is so loud and sweet.
Tuang, this is not American Idol.
We're here to sell.
We need to be repetitive
and loud.
Is that so?
Yes. Let's do it.
All right, then.
-Here we go.
-Yes.
Line up, please.
Hang on, Pretty Face.
Chestnuts!
Get your chestnuts here.
-Tuang.
-Chestnuts.
-Hot chestnuts.
-Hot chestnuts!
-Yes.
They taste good.
-That's good.
-Tasty chestnuts.
-Good.
-This way! Chestnuts!
Chestnuts!
-Get your chestnuts here.
-Tell them it's from Chinatown.
These chestnuts
taste just like the ones in Chinatown.
They're the same.
Call them over with your hands too.
-Chestnuts! This way.
-Yes.
-Get your chestnuts here.
-That's good.
Tasty chestnuts over here.
They taste like the ones in Chinatown.
Chestnuts.
Very delicious chestnuts.
Hello. Everyone, gather round.
Today's special deal is for shorts.
Buy three and get one for free.
Buy five and get two for free.
Buy more and get more free stuff.
Come on. Gather round.
This way.
The promotion is only for today.
You won't get it tomorrow.
-Shirts for 69 and 96 baht.
-Come on.
Short sleeves for 69
and long sleeves for 96.
Come on, everyone.
This way, please.
Sixty baht for every item.
It's the cheapest price on the planet.
Choose your shirts here.
Our shirts are unisex.
-We have all sizes.
-Top.
-Please stop by.
-Do you want a shirt?
No.
It's perfect for the beach.
If you don't buy one today,
it won't be on sale tomorrow.
I don't get it.
You're the actress.
Why must you do the shopping?
I'm just helping out.
Are you getting paid?
Of course not. It's for the drama club.
How much are the tickets?
Why are you asking all these questions?
It doesn't seem worth it.
I don't care if it's worth it or not.
I want to do it.
For what?
I like it.
Is that all?
I don't know. I think
it's weird to not get paid
for your hard work.
I'm not tired. If you are, just go home.
Hang on, Lin.
Top.
Business isn't good today.
What? Speak louder. I can't hear you.
Other shops are packed.
But I don't know why no one visits ours.
Did you yell the way I told you to?
I did. I yelled the whole time.
I need your help here.
So what do you want me to do?
I don't know what else to do.
I'll call you back, Tuang.
Next time,
if you need to talk on the phone,
don't bother coming.
Don't be like that.
It was important.
I was talking to Tuang. See?
Call back the number.
I can't. It was from a public phone.
That's a convenient excuse.
Don't let me find out.
It's the truth.
How can I make you believe me?
Let's go home.
I'm going to the restroom.
Please hold these for me.
Bubbles, anyone? Bubbles.
I'm sorry.
Please donate your spare change
to help rural children.
Help rural children.
-Help the children.
Please donate.
-Thank you.
Help rural children.
Please donate your spare change
to help rural children.
Thank you.
We volunteer to help those in need.
1. FREE GIFTS 2. DISCOUNTS 3. CHARITY
-Thank you.
Goodwill fundraising
looks like an easy way to raise money.
You've never done it
so don't talk that way.
Hey, I'm genuinely impressed.
It's so damn smart to wait
in front of the restroom for change.
It's a great location.
The location...
LOCATION
Sir.
I would like to move my store here.
The area is all taken.
I'll close the shop, then.
It's useless to sell in the parking lot.
If you close before your contract is up,
we won't refund your deposit.
You can't be serious, right?
Yes. Didn't you read the contract?
Hold on.
Hey, can you check
if there's any booth moving out
from A Zone?
All right. One booth will move out
at the end of the month.
Are you interested?
But you must sign the contract today.
I think
you should ask your parents first.
If you were me, would you take it?
This is a prime location. Trust me.
I'm all for it.
The rental fee is 24,000 baht, right?
You'll earn that back in no time.
280 BAHT PER KILOGRAM
This place is haunted.
It's still too early to tell.
Whose phone is ringing?
Please turn it off.
Professor, may I pick up the phone?
No, you may not.
If you do, I will have to report
that you cheated.
Turn off your mobile phone now.
Top, come back here.
This is a mandatory subject.
What did you say?
Make it hot.
One kilo of hot chestnuts, please.
Okay. All good things take time.
All delicious things take time.
Hang on. Please wait.
It will heat up soon.
Here.
Hang on.
This machine heats up fast.
Don't go anywhere.
All right.
Okay.
-Three hundred baht.
-Three hundred baht,
-so here's 20 back.
-Yes.
-Tuang.
-Hang on. It's ready.
Let's open more branches.
Hey.
Slow down, Top. This is our first day.
Listen.
We are selling like crazy
on our first day.
If we sell two sacks a day,
we'll have 4,000 baht.
That's 120,000 a month.
And if we have ten branches,
wow,
we'll get 1.2 million each month.
Shall we do it? What do you think?
I don't think we should.
Can we handle them all?
-I think we should do it.
-What?
Why did you ask me, then?
Mister.
Put it next to that one.
Okay. Move it a bit, just a little.
All right. That's good.
Please sign here.
Mister, I'll meet you at the other branch.
All right.
-Set the temperature at 120 Celsius.
-At 120 Celsius.
Roast two kilograms each time.
Don't put too many pebbles
-because it won't mix well.
-I see.
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
Okay. You can start now.
Keep these chestnuts in place.
Are we still dating?
Who told you?
Why did I have to hear it
from someone else?
Have I ever hidden anything from you?
If you knew that I was selling chestnuts,
what would you have said?
Are you ashamed?
What kind of person do you think I am?
I'm worried about you.
Don't put your future at risk.
Go back to school.
Fuck you, Jack. Why did you tell Lin?
Shithead, it wasn't me.
You disappeared.
Lin called me.
She thought you were cheating on her.
So I said I had no idea.
Then she called your mom.
Will you come back to school?
Your booth is causing damage.
Can you see that?
The smoke is turning the ceiling yellow.
Please get it fixed.
Of course, there would be smoke
from roasting chestnuts.
It is a violation of your rental contract.
If you can't fix this,
we'll have to cancel your contract.
Cancel my contract?
I'm sorry.
You can't do that.
Do you have a way to fix it?
Yes, I do.
Hey.
You can't paint it now.
It's bothering customers.
Paint it after the mall closes.
Mom.
Hold it well. It's shaking.
I am. I thought it was steady.
It's almost midnight.
If you weren't here,
I would have finished already.
Are you tired? Can I do it for you?
Mom, you're not helping.
Mister, time's up. You have to leave now.
Sir.
Please give me a bit more time.
It's not done yet.
But your request form
only allows you to stay until midnight.
Sir.
Please give me more time.
I can't. Your time is up.
If my boss sees you,
I'll get in trouble.
Here.
Are you his mother?
Yes.
Please discipline your son.
Take all your things
and exit that way, please.
Please stop, Top. That's enough.
No, I will finish it tomorrow.
-There's time.
-No, there isn't.
Go get your passport tomorrow.
We'll move to China
at the end of the month
to stay with your brother and sister.
We are in debt, aren't we?
Why doesn't anyone tell me anything?
You don't need to know.
It's not your concern.
How much debt are we in?
Mom, tell me, how much?
Don't worry.
My chestnut business is going well.
I only need
to finish painting the ceiling.
Come with us.
At least we can be together.
Please.
Excuse me, please look at the camera.
Get ready.
Hey.
Mom.
I am not going.
-I will stay here and study.
-Go back and take your photo.
You wanted to pay me to study, right?
I'm ready to be your employee now, Dad.
Fine.
Stay if you want.
I'll wait for you inside.
You should stop
with the chestnuts.
Go back to school.
Top.
I'm sorry that...
I need you to move out your booths.
Every branch?
All of them.
My boss really can't allow it.
I'm truly sorry.
Mister.
The paint is dripping
on my store's lucky charm.
You ruined my spiritual altar.
My glasses have stains too.
Please take responsibility.
Look.
Yes. How can I sell them like this?
CENTRAL BANKRUPTCY COURT
WE WILL HAVE TO SEIZE YOUR HOUSE AND LAND
I really like the backdrop.
-Yes, it's gorgeous.
-I agree.
They made it so well.
When you take pictures...
I really want to see it.
I'm scared that our year will...
And other people will...
What's wrong with you?
Why didn't you pick up my calls?
Hey, Top.
Top, what's wrong?
Top.
Forget about the chestnuts.
Go back to school.
Your high school diploma
won't get you anywhere.
Please, Top.
Please.
I will help you.
Fine.
Do you promise?
Yes.
Let's go to Chinatown, then.
It's been a while.
I miss the crab noodles.
The traffic is bad
and there is no parking.
No problem.
I can wait. I just came back
from a trip with my family.
Look. I brought back some fried seaweed.
It must be really good.
You even brought it back.
You're crazy.
Just drive. I'll feed you some.
If you tell me
you tried frying the seaweed,
I'll go to lunch right now.
Yes. Here are my scars from the oil.
Damn.
At first, I bought some seaweed
from another province.
But I was unlucky,
it all went stale within a week.
Wow. You are indeed unlucky.
It got worse.
When I asked
if they could do something about it,
they said they didn't know how.
I begged them for three days.
But they didn't care.
We ended up arguing.
What happened next?
Don't tell me
you got your butt kicked again.
I did the butt kicking this time.
-Yes, they deserved it.
-Right?
-Right.
-Yes!
In the end, I had to fry it myself.
So how did you solve the problem?
Even they couldn't do it.
Kasetsart University could.
HEAD OF FOOD PROCESSING
AND MANUFACTURING DEPARTMENT
You're not a student here.
How did you get her to help?
You don't have to care about
who I am or how old I am.
Just listen to me first.
My name is
Itthipat
Kulapongvanich.
So I told the professor
the same story I told you.
Here's some tissue, Professor.
There's oil in your fried seaweed,
just like this rice crackers.
It will oxidize and cause it to go stale.
The solution is vacuum packaging.
Look.
The vacuum keeps oxygen out of the bag.
So, your seaweed is crispy, right?
-Yes.
-So, it can break.
We must put nitrogen in there instead.
It will prolong the shelf-life by far.
I see.
There.
See? That's it.
So I just need to buy this machine, right?
Yes, that's right.
Now it is up to you to find a way
to make it delicious.
Go.
Is this all we got for those machines?
Each box costs 10,000 baht.
Wow.
Why is it bitter?
I guess it's burnt.
Yes, that's enough.
Why is it so soggy?
Maybe it has too much oil.
Damn it.
Tuang.
Let's eat.
What should we do?
We're running out.
We can get more.
We can probably get
five or six more boxes.
-Top.
-Yes?
I don't want to do this anymore.
I wasted 100,000 baht worth of seaweed.
I don't want to waste any more money.
Just because you've wasted 100,000 baht,
doesn't mean you should give up now.
Please don't make me waste anymore.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Waste some more.
A lot more.
I believe
that you can get it back for me.
Hello, are you here yet?
What are you talking about?
The university admission.
Oh, my god. Wait for me there.
UNIVERSITY ADMISSION
You already forgot everything?
DOCUMENTS VERIFICATION
I have to check...
Come on, Tuang. It's all or nothing.
Let's fry some more seaweed.
Tuang!
You've reached the voicemail system.
Please leave a message...
How are you?
I'm okay.
I can go home in a few days.
I guess you can eat now, right?
Yes. I already ate the congee
the nurse gave me. I ate it all up.
Oh, you asked
because you want me
to taste your seaweed, right?
That's right.
I wonder what I've ever done to you.
Please taste it.
Is it that delicious?
No.
My tongue is still numb.
Can you taste it now?
How did you do it?
-Two bags, please.
-Two bags?
Can you give me a discount?
No, I really can't.
It's very difficult for the divers
to get the seaweed.
They had to fight off sharks
and giant octopuses.
-See?
-You're funny.
They're selling well.
Selling is fun when you do it.
-One of these.
-Yes, of course.
Hang on.
Two bags, please.
Here.
It's guaranteed to be delicious.
-I'm sure you'll come back.
-Is this your son?
Oh, he's my nephew.
Two bags, please.
Two bags will be 160 baht.
-I'll get one bag.
-All right. Hang on.
-That'll be 160 baht. No change needed.
-Yes.
Thank you.
-I don't need a bag.
-Wait for the change.
-No bag.
-No bag?
-Your change.
-Stop global warming.
ONE MILLION A YEAR
Here's your 20 baht.
-No bag.
-It shouldn't be too hard.
Here. It's guaranteed.
One bag? There are two of you, though.
MOM
Here. I'm sure you'll fight for it.
Hello.
Hello, Top. How are you?
I'm good.
Are you in class?
Well...
I'm not.
I don't have class today.
I can talk.
There's nothing much.
I just want to wish you a happy birthday.
That's right.
It's my birthday.
Are you that forgetful now?
Happy birthday again.
Study hard.
You win some,
you lose some.
But remember
to take care of yourself.
Make sure you get enough sleep.
Thank you, Mom.
Hang on.
Dad wants to talk to you.
ONE MILLION A YEAR
Hello, Dad.
Top.
Listen to me.
Study hard this semester.
Next semester,
you can transfer here.
I checked out a university for you.
I'll send you
the plane ticket.
Dad.
Can you tell me the truth about the debt?
Be honest with me.
How much is it?
It's 40 million.
Have you ever felt so small?
FOR SALE, PROPERTY OF THE BANK
If you think you will be rich,
you will be rich.
If you think you will succeed,
you will succeed
because you'll be
thinking without the box.
Thinking without the box
is more powerful
than thinking outside the box
because each person
has a different kind of box.
Today,
the Urban Forest Strategy plan
consists of creating relationships
-with our rural customers.
-No.
-I'm a good student now.
-We use it
with many products.
Oh, please.
You're reading a soccer magazine.
But I'm listening to him.
I don't hear people
say "Bao Zheng" anymore.
Now, they only say "Bao."
Our generation pays attention to
rural customers...
Would you like dumplings
or buns with that?
One Cheese Bite, please.
We ran out. Do you want something else?
Never mind, then.
One Cheese Bite, please.
If you think you will be rich,
you will be rich.
If you think you will succeed,
-you will succeed.
-It's been years.
Rich, my ass. It's all bullshit.
...Urban Forest Strategy plan
to become as successful...
Thank you.
The Urban Forest Strategy plan
consists of
creating relationships
-with our rural customers.
-No.
-I'm a good student now.
-We use it with many products.
Oh, please.
You're reading a soccer magazine.
But I'm listening to him.
I don't hear people
say "Bao Zheng" anymore.
Now, they only say "Bao."
Our generation pays attention to
-rural customers.
-Top.
You know we are paying for
every second of class, right?
Here. Just hit the record button
for me, then.
In order to use the Urban Forest Strategy
with true knowledge and understanding,
-The Urban Forest Strategy.
-it would be very good
if you understand
-All over the country.
-the strategy first.
It would be useful.
Hello.
I would like to sell my product
in 7-Eleven. What should I do?
From where?
Magnum Banana Sticky Rice
proudly presents
the perfect balance
of Western and Eastern culture.
Just think of it as a Thai-fusion snack.
It's easy to eat.
Let's try again.
Magnum Banana Sticky Rice
proudly presents
the perfect balance
of Western and Eastern culture.
It's easy to eat.
Your hands won't get messy.
Just think of it as a Thai-fusion snack.
I'd like to use the Urban Forest Strategy
that 7-Eleven uses now.
Since 7-Eleven has branches
all over the country,
lots of people will see my product.
The strategy that 7-Eleven uses
suits my product well.
And if my company and your company
work together,
I believe we will have
a good future together.
I believe
we'll have a good future together.
All done. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Excuse me,
didn't you come with your father?
He wasn't my father.
I have an appointment with Pu at 9 a.m.
But I haven't been called yet.
Have you given your name
to the front desk?
What?
Was I supposed to do that?
Of course. Otherwise,
how would I know that you arrived?
Then,
my name is Itthipat.
Let me check. Please wait.
Young man, Pu's in a meeting.
Would you like to leave a note?
No, thank you.
It was my fault. I'll wait for her.
Hello, this is CP Company.
Who is this?
All right. Please hold on.
Hello.
Hello, this is CP Company.
How may I help you?
Pu, this is Itthipat.
Did he send his assistant here?
No, this is Itthipat himself.
Hello, Itthipat. I'm Pu.
-Hello.
I have another meeting at 5:10 p.m.
So please leave your product with me
and I will take a look later.
May I have ten minutes of your time?
I'd like to present the product myself.
Okay, go ahead.
So let me tell you about my product.
My product is fried seaweed.
Itthipat, can I see your product?
Sure.
Here you go.
I'd like to use the Urban Forest Strategy
that 7-Eleven uses now.
Since 7-Eleven has branches
all over the country,
lots of people will see my product.
I believe that this strategy--
Your product isn't ready.
How come?
The packaging design won't make it.
The size is also too big for our shelves.
What is your retail price?
It's not that expensive. Only 80 baht.
That's expensive.
We are a convenience store.
Eighty baht won't be convenient anymore.
I am sorry.
-Pu.
-Yes?
Don't you want to try some first?
That's all right. It would be a waste.
Okay, we're done here.
By the way,
the Urban Forest Strategy
is when you start from the countryside,
then make your way into a big city.
I think you misunderstood the strategy.
Top.
Why don't you tell me what's going on?
I'm breaking my promise.
I won't go to university anymore.
Still, you should talk to me.
Why did you turn off your phone?
If I told you I quit school,
what would you do?
I know you want to help your parents,
but what you can do
is to graduate.
You don't think I can do this, do you?
That's why you want me back in school.
I don't want you to struggle
or risk losing everything.
If you actually believed in me,
you wouldn't be saying this.
If it's about money,
I can ask my parents for help.
I haven't hit rock bottom yet.
I don't need your help.
That's not what I meant, Top.
Top, that's not
-what I meant.
-I can make it work.
It will work, do you hear me?
Top, come back and talk to me.
Don't go, Top.
Top.
Top!
Top, am I so wrong for worrying about you?
You should go home.
Come back and talk to me.
Top!
Top, come back.
Tuang.
Can I sleep with you tonight?
Sure.
Tuang.
What the fuck is wrong with me?
She loves me.
She's worried about me.
But I chased her away.
Don't cry, Top.
Mister.
Can you design a package
that looks like these?
What is the concept of your product?
I want it to be for youngsters,
Korean Pop style.
The brand's name is
Jay Chou.
Jay Chou is a Taiwanese singer.
Really?
Isn't he Korean?
No.
I think "Tao Kae Noi"
is already a good name.
Doesn't it sound old
because of the meaning?
Listen.
It's up to the designer to decide that.
I'm Itthipat.
I'd like to make an appointment with Pu.
I have a product to present to her.
Did you make an appointment?
The thing is,
I just finished re-designing
the packaging this morning.
I want Pu to see it right away.
Pu has appointments all day.
That's okay. I can wait.
Hello.
Okay. Do you want to send a fax?
Excuse me.
I'm leaving.
I understand now.
Pu didn't really
have appointments, did she?
TAO KAE NOI
Mister.
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet.
Here.
-Wait.
-No.
Hello. You guys are here.
Where's Itthipat?
He went home.
I see.
Hello, Mom.
What's up?
What are you doing?
Can I talk to you?
Yes, you can.
Is something wrong?
No.
I just felt like talking to you.
How's school?
Your grades from last semester
must be out now.
How are they?
What is this?
A boy gave them to me.
Hey.
It's seaweed.
Can I take some?
Go ahead.
-See you later.
-Okay.
-Oh, no.
I stepped on it.
My grades are not so good.
That's all right.
I'm just happy
that you're in school.
My beautiful Oum,
I...
bought you some seaweed
since you might be tired from work.
I studied hard for it.
I was too confident in myself.
Maybe I'm just stupid.
-Take it.
-What is it?
-Eat the rest too. It's good.
-All right.
-I can eat it, right?
-Yes.
The board concluded
not to accept any more products.
It's like every door has been shut.
Top.
Don't give up.
Your grades
are a small problem.
You will face
bigger problems in life.
Oum, I have a meeting outside.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello, Dang. Isn't your shift over yet?
-It will be soon.
-I see.
So...
my product passed, right?
Yes.
Congratulations.
You're the youngest business owner
that I've ever met.
Are you working with your family?
Yes.
I am working at home.
Next, you will have to deliver
your product to our 3,000 branches.
Altogether, that will be 72,000 bags.
How many again?
Seventy-two thousand bags.
And one month from now,
we will have the GMP inspection
at your factory.
I see.
The GMP...
All right.
After your factory is GMP-certified,
after two weeks, it will be delivery time.
If your total stock's shelf-life
is less than 80 days
from the manufacture date,
we won't let you pass.
I see.
Okay.
GMP stands for
Good Manufacturing Practices.
Seventy-two thousand bags.
Tuang,
how can a 19-year-old kid like me
get the money to open a factory?
Are you 19?
Yes.
LAND DEED
DATE OF BIRTH: 24 NOV 1984
Top.
I really respect you.
I like
that you're a fighter.
But you're only 19.
I can't loan you money.
You're not old enough.
You only graduated from high school.
Your family has 40 million baht in debt.
Your buildings are ready
to be auctioned off for sale.
Your parents aren't here.
I am sorry.
But everything you've done,
I think it's amazing.
You're still young.
Go get your degree.
Are you ready?
All done.
BUY AND SELL ALL TYPES OF CARS
-Count it.
-Okay.
TO ITTHIPAT KULAPONGVANICH
The head is slightly tiled.
-He must be muscular
-Okay.
-and has three bases.
The amulet must not be bent or crooked.
-All right.
-Okay.
On the back,
it could be a flat back
or a pattern of betel nuts.
It's made from shell cement.
-Shell cement?
-Yes, it's mixed with other powders.
Hey, kid. Long time no see.
Have you got a new amulet to sell?
No, I want to buy it back.
Which one?
That one.
Hey.
This one is now worth a few million baht.
Do you have that kind of money?
I pawned it for only 100,000 baht.
How did the price go up?
This amulet has always been traded
for millions of baht.
Give me my dad's amulet back!
Talk nicely.
It's mine. It's on my neck, can't you see?
-I said it's my dad's!
-Hey.
-What the hell?
-I said it's my dad's!
This fucking kid.
I'll shoot you right now.
Get out of my sight.
Go.
You were stupid to sell it to me
for 100,000 baht.
Did I scam you?
Get out.
Asshole!
FOR SALE, PROPERTY OF THE BANK
This is our factory.
That's right.
I forgot we had this building.
I remembered it
when that banker mentioned it.
Including the labor cost,
it would be around 1 million baht.
Can I pay for some of it now?
Normally, we need 50 percent upfront,
and then we start working.
If you don't pay up,
I'll throw you in jail.
TAO KAE NOI
-What time?
-Three p.m., right?
Tua.
Tuang.
What should we do
if this doesn't work out as well?
Don't worry about it too much.
Nobody knows.
Sometimes,
I feel like I don't think hard enough.
That's good.
You wouldn't be here
if you thought too much.
TAO KAE NOI FACTORY
TO PU, FROM ITTHIPAT
TAO KAE NOI
TAO KAE NOI FACTORY
Hello, Pu.
Hello.
This is Ton from the QA department.
He will check your factory today.
This is just the front
of your factory, right?
No.
This is the whole factory. This way.
Just bribe them.
We won't make it.
No, Tuang.
I don't want anyone
to blame my parents again.
You must believe me this time.
I've seen it before.
Even when things look ready,
without the money, it's no good.
I'm sorry.
I forgot to tell you
the paint's still wet.
I see.
To be honest,
your factory
isn't up to standard, Itthipat.
What are some examples?
Look at that.
The lights have no cover.
Dust can fall into your food.
We take hygiene
during production very seriously.
Pu.
I'll get it fixed right away.
-Chart.
-Yes.
Please get someone to cover the lights.
All right.
-You can use this tissue.
-That's okay.
I'll cover the lights right away.
So...
will we know the result today?
Itthipat,
there are many things
that are below standard.
The lights aren't covered,
the sewage pipe isn't covered,
the sink must be turned on
by pressing a lever with your foot.
Otherwise,
you will re-infect
your hands with germs.
You're also using the wrong alcohol.
This is for cleaning wounds,
which is dangerous.
You should use ethyl alcohol only.
We will go back and make our decision.
I will let you know again by fax.
We have to go.
Goodbye.
It's okay.
You did your best.
We must prepare for packing and delivery.
We don't even know the result yet.
If we wait,
we won't make it in time for delivery.
I see.
THE RESULT OF THE INSPECTION IS
Shit! The ink just had to run out now!
I can't read it, Tuang. What should I do?
Go look in the sunlight.
PASSED
We passed!
Top.
Top, wake up.
Hurry. We're almost done
loading the boxes.
Hurry.
Be careful.
Speed it up.
Line them up nicely.
You can go when you're done.
Hurry. Time's up.
Come on. Bring more. Hurry.
Thank you, Tuang.
Everything I have is on the line.
If this doesn't work out,
we will really have nothing left.
And I will quit.
I'll stop being stubborn.
I promise.
Excuse me.
I'm Itthipat from Tao Kae Noi.
Mister.
Why are you here now?
Your scheduled time was an hour ago.
Sir,
please.
We're just a bit late.
Listen.
Everyone always says that.
If I let you go,
I'll have to let everyone else go.
And your time is up.
I'm begging you, please.
This is really important to me.
I just finished packing
at 5 a.m. in the morning.
Fine.
Just hurry up.
You're next. Get ready.
-All right.
-Okay.
Thank you so much.
Kid.
Yes?
Do you want to wipe your nose?
Thank you so much.
You can go in. He let us in.
Okay. Back up the car.
Do you want to speak to Mom?
No.
Dad.
You and Mom can come home now.
Top.
Are you tired?
TWO YEARS AFTER SUPPLYING
TAO KAE NOI TO 7-ELEVEN,
TOP PAID OFF
HIS FAMILY'S DEBT OF 40 MILLION BAHT
HE STILL LIVES IN THE SAME HOUSE
WITH HIS PARENTS
How's it going, Top?
-I'd like to loan 400 million baht.
-No problem.
Are you expanding your factory?
TOP'S FACTORY HAS 2,500 EMPLOYEES TODAY
SUPPLYING PRODUCTS
TO 6,000 7-ELEVEN BRANCHES
AND 27 COUNTRIES WORLDWIDE
NOW, TOP HAS A SEAWEED FARM IN SOUTH KOREA
HIS SALES REVENUE IN 2010
WAS 1,500 MILLION BAHT
TOP IS NOW 26 YEARS OLD
"DO NOT GIVE UP WHEN YOU FACE ANY PROBLEMS
BECAUSE IF YOU GIVE UP, IT'S GAME OVER"
TOP
Subtitle translation by Joey Vajrabukka