OVER 500,000 THAIS
HAVE FALLEN ILL DUE TO UNKNOWN CAUSES.
OVER 100,000 PEOPLE BELIEVE THAT
THE UNKNOWN CAUSES ARE...
WANDERING SPIRITS
What are you doing to me?
Get rid of it!
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED
GHOST DOCTOR TV FOLLOWS THE GHOST-BUSTING
STORIES OF A SHAMAN CALLED "MASTER PLA."
MASTER PLA HELPS HEAL "ILL PEOPLE"
FROM ALL CONDITIONS BEYOND EXPLANATION.
THIS FILM WAS INSPIRED BY TRUE EVENTS.
GHOST DOCTOR: THE LOST CASE
Do you really have to film this?
Yes, I do.
Are you trying to catch something from me?
Everything you two did.
You could take me down, too. You know?
So I need to record this as evidence.
I simply went to work like you'd ordered.
Do you have any idea
what I've been through?
How the heck would I know?
I'm just seeing you now
since you've returned.
And where the hell is Itt?
So where's the work I asked you to film?
It's here.
And what happened to your eyebrow?
Nothing.
I have a bit of a problem with Itt.
What problem?
How many times have I told you two
to talk it out when you have problems?
I get that.
You should ask Itt yourself
what the hell is wrong with him.
I've been waiting for him.
He hasn't been in the office since
he returned, and he won't answer my calls.
After we got back,
I went to pick him up the following day.
But look at this.
I shouldn't have let you two
go on the field alone.
You can fire me if you want.
I don't want this job anymore.
Let's try this.
Calm down and tell me what happened.
Okay. I filmed everything on this.
You can check it out yourself.
Have you already edited
what you're showing me?
TWO WEEKS EARLIER
Which button do I push?
Let me see.
This one here. That's the menu.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Wait. Which one again?
This. Here.
Right.
How's the new camera?
It's okay. Pretty light.
Won't the camera keep shaking?
Hell, no. Even people with Parkinson's
can film with this one.
Wow, too good to be true. Let me try.
Yeah, check it out.
Do something.
Want me to do K-Pop moves?
You can? Go ahead!
Fuck you! I'm not gonna do that!
You're not being very helpful, man.
Can't you see I'm working here?
You only try to look hard-working
on camera.
Whatever!
This is Itt,
a fake-ass crew member of the show
called Ghost Doctor TV.
On this show, we travel
to help people who are disturbed
by mysterious things,
ghosts and supernatural powers.
Let's get to know
this fine young gentleman.
Mr. Itt, what are your roles on this show?
I'm the creative producer.
Wow, creative producer? Sounds awesome!
What is the role of a creative producer?
Well, to stay creative.
Sounds real tough.
How long have you worked here?
Around three months.
Tomorrow will be the first case
we film on our own.
After three months of being a slave?
Yeah, you can say that.
Okay, do you think
we'll pull through probation together?
Good question. We'll find out soon enough.
But I've heard,
whether we pull through or not,
we'll have to give it our all tomorrow.
We'll be in trouble
if we come back empty-handed.
So you have to be focused
and not get me into trouble.
You're the one always fucking up!
Don't say that. Don't get me involved.
Let me try the camera.
Let me try working with it.
Here you go.
Let's see.
Hello, Mr. Por.
Hello!
What is your role on this show?
I'm the show's main cameraman.
Have you prepared everything for tomorrow?
Not yet.
Why don't you fucking do it?
Because I'm testing the new camera here.
You don't deserve to be
the creative producer.
Are you done testing?
Yeah, I am.
Good, now get everything
ready for tomorrow.
Okay.
What will you be filming?
Why do you need this much stuff?
Just in case, you know.
When will you be back?
Don't know.
Tell me when you'll be back.
I don't know.
-We had a deal. When are you coming back?
-Come here.
So when are you coming back?
In a couple of days, maybe.
We already have plans.
I know. I won't be gone
longer than three days, babe. Babe...
Don't. I'm not in the mood.
I'll be away for many days.
Don't you wanna give me some love?
Nah.
Please.
Turn off the camera first.
Turn off the camera.
Por, turn off the camera!
Whose girlfriend is this? She's so pretty.
What are you doing, Por?
I'm testing the camera.
We're here. Hurry up and get Itt.
You'll be late for work, so hurry.
Do the sexy face.
Hurry, or I'll leave you here,
and you'll have to get a cab to work.
First do the sexy face.
Por, get out!
Okay.
My friend is a very loving
and grateful son.
I really want him
to be nominated for Son of the Year.
Plus, his younger sister is super cute.
Por, hurry up!
Okay.
Give her these two antibiotics
before breakfast.
This is paracetamol.
Give her one or two tablets
after each meal. Okay?
Don't forget to give her these,
and easy with the cellphone,
so you can hear Mom when she calls.
I know. Just hurry back.
I will.
Hi, Por.
Hi, Oil.
What the hell are you filming?
Son of the Year nomination video.
-Is your mom dropping you off?
-Burn! No, that's my driver.
Let's roll!
-I'm leaving now.
-Okay. Take care.
Call me when you can.
-Sure.
-Bye.
Does she want to come too?
Fuck you.
Come on. Let's go.
Itt, I'm serious, man.
Why didn't you book first class
or at least something air-conditioned?
It's fucking hot.
Come on. Don't be so picky!
These were the only seats available.
Itt. Itt.
What?
Film me too so I have evidence
to show Jay that I'm working.
Fucking bastard!
It's 2,500.
Okay, thank you.
You sure it's this way?
I'm sure. It's this way.
From the atmosphere around here,
it seems like we're considerably
far away from any civilization.
This case will be a tough one for sure.
We're close to the scene.
But looking around,
I feel like all the houses are haunted.
Hey, Por. We're almost there.
Can you be serious for once?
Put your work mode on!
Why so serious?
We have to be, or else we'll get told off.
Yo allowed us to work
by ourselves unsupervised.
More like nobody wanted to do this,
especially not Yo.
Always throwing the tough ones at us.
You're so fucking picky.
How did they hire you?
Because they saw potential in me.
Whatever you say.
Do you know which house is his?
He said to keep walking straight,
and we'll find it.
I think it's this one.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Is anyone living here?
When we arrived here,
I could feel the presence
of wandering spirits in the house.
Shit, what the hell is she doing there?
You!
Are you Chai?
Yeah.
I'm from the TV show you contacted.
Yeah? Where's Master Pla?
Well, Master Pla can't make it here today,
so we arrived here first.
I see.
Well, come in.
This is where people have seen the ghost.
Oh, is it here?
So I put up a spirit house.
My neighbors told me that
they'd seen somebody walking around
and heard some sounds, like a girl crying.
Have you seen it yourself?
Well, never.
But it does feel kind of strange.
No idea why that is.
It feels so suffocating that
I can't sleep inside this house.
What did you do?
Did you collect any weird stuff
or swear to anything?
Well, no.
But my daughter passed away last year.
I'm not sure if it's her.
How did she die?
She hanged herself in the storage here.
Do you know why she did that?
Check out what I've brought.
Two brand-new cameras.
This is one.
And that is the other one.
Let's try on this one. What's good?
Sure.
Por, did you bring the camera light?
Fuck! I forgot.
Fuck, you just talk so much!
How are we gonna shoot in the dark?
It's all right.
This camera can shoot at night.
I tried before coming here.
The picture will be pixelated.
Trust me. If I say it will work, it will.
I can use the flashlight
on my phone and attach it on.
What else have you brought?
Here, I've brought a bunch of GoPros.
We can attach them
where people say they saw the ghost
and hope we get some freaky stuff.
Good. At least we have those.
When they pay me ten,
I'll perform a hundred.
A little mistake can be fixed.
Don't you get it?
A smart man can always fix problems.
Haven't you heard?
Nope.
Because you've never known shit.
Successful people aren't flawless.
They're judged by how they solve problems.
And that's me.
Hey, Por. Good news for us.
What?
Master Pla still can't make it.
Fucking shit.
Fuck! Four days?
Fuck me.
This is where we're staying.
And this is where
the daughter hanged herself.
Right next to us. Perfect location.
Guess they wanted to put on a show for us.
And look around.
There's fucking nothing.
Complete darkness.
If something happens to me,
I've no idea what to do.
See anything, Por?
Nothing.
But I know now
why the girl killed herself.
Why?
Look around, man.
There's nothing but banana trees.
I would kill myself too.
Wow, you've got a big mouth.
Be careful what you say.
Let me take that back.
Por! Look!
What?
Who the fuck is that?
I don't know.
Who would take a walk this late?
Do you think it's someone drunk?
Which direction is she coming from?
I'm not sure. Let's follow her.
Are you nuts?
Duh, idiot. We're here to work.
They didn't hire you
to film your own vlog.
It's so fucking dark.
Why the fuck are we following her?
Just come with me. Stop bitching.
Be careful.
Itt.
Where did she go?
Over there. Can't you see? Hurry!
Shit, is this place dangerous?
There's nothing here. Come on.
Hurry up. We'll lose her.
How far are we going to follow her?
Let's go back, Itt.
No, let's keep following.
Fuck, it's so fucking dark.
Itt, take me back.
Where'd she go?
Shit. We lost her.
We should go back then.
Did Itt tell you
we had to stay there for four days?
Yeah, he called me.
I don't know if he was lying
about Master Pla or not.
But I guess he wanted to stay there
as long as possible.
I understand that
he's under a lot of pressure
because he has to take care of
his whole family after his father died.
This job decides his future.
It's getting worse
as it's nearing assessment time.
He wants to do his best on this job.
This is where
the woman disappeared yesterday.
Where could she possibly have gone?
Hey, Por!
What the hell are you doing there?
Nothing. Just checking
on the person we saw last night.
She's over there, dude.
What?
She's at Chai's place.
The lady from yesterday?
Yeah, I guess.
How did she end up there?
How would I know?
What is she doing?
Hanging the laundry, I guess.
Come with me if you want to find out.
Yeah, I think it's the same person.
Itt, I think you should ask Chai first,
then casually ask about his wife.
But don't ask him out of the blue,
or else he might not answer.
Fine.
Hello?
Is Chai here?
He's inside the house.
We're here to film a TV show.
Did Chai tell you about us?
No, he didn't.
So can we go up to see him?
Of course.
This way.
Shit, isn't their daughter dead?
Are these your daughter's?
Yes.
This one is when she scored 100% in math.
These were what she drew
when she was younger.
And this,
she said when she'd improved at drawing,
she would draw me.
So Mommy can look pretty.
She loves English the most.
There's a lot of her writing here.
She's started to speak English now.
How many children do you have?
Just one.
She's not back from school yet.
Since today is Friday,
the kids are still playing at school.
They come home late.
I'll get Chai for you.
Thank you.
Is she hallucinating?
I think she's been through a lot.
I think she got messed up badly.
Guess so.
My wife thinks
our daughter is still alive.
But she saw her when she...
She did, but she passed out.
When she woke up,
she didn't remember anything.
Have you talked to her about this?
Yes, but she wouldn't listen.
She still does things
as if our daughter is here.
Have you taken her for help?
I took her to the hospital,
but the doctor said she's fine.
I took her to see famous shamans.
We got all these things from them.
They told us to pray to them
every Buddhist holiday.
I followed all their advice.
But Aueng remains the same.
Do you have more questions?
If not, I have to excuse myself
and work on the farm.
No more questions.
Thank you very much, Chai.
Are you done?
Just a second.
Here, all done.
Have a look. Is it working?
Yes, put them there
in case something freaky happens.
There will be something for sure.
Don't you worry.
We'd better interview people around here.
Maybe they'll know something.
Ever experienced strange incidents
near Chai's house?
Yes, I have.
What did you see?
I saw it when I was walking at night.
I saw a tall, dark silhouette
standing face down under his house.
When I walked past the house
late at night,
I heard weird noises from under the house.
But when I turned to look,
nobody was there.
What kind of weird noises, would you say?
Like a door loudly slamming open and shut
and something smashing
from under the house.
What do you think
of Aueng's behavior after that day?
I think Aueng sees her daughter's ghost.
What do you think is wrong with her?
She's gone mad.
I guess when her daughter killed herself,
she was so traumatized
that she lost her mind.
You're here for a TV show?
Yes.
At what time will it air?
I want to catch it.
Sure, I'll give you a call
about when it airs.
Will I be in it?
Yes, yes. Thank you.
How is it? Is it okay?
Okay, I guess.
What else do you want to film?
I think that's enough.
There's nobody here.
You sure?
Yeah.
After interviewing the villagers here,
I know now that
I'm not only facing a ghost,
but I need to prepare myself
to handle a mad person too.
But aren't ghosts and mad people
a match made in hell?
Isn't that right, Itt?
Right, my ass. They say only people
with good karma can see ghosts.
Is that so?
Yeah, you're not one of them,
so you can't see them.
So that means mad people have good karma?
I guess so.
I'm lucky that I don't have
good karma, then.
Dickhead, mad people are always happy
because they don't care about shit.
They're stress-free. The ones with stress
have to take care of them.
Really?
-Yeah.
-And how's Aueng these days?
Don't you see her condition?
You think she's happy?
And how do you know she's mad?
What? Every day of her life,
she still thinks her daughter is alive.
Isn't that called madness?
Fuck that!
Nobody really knows the truth.
Just do what you came here to do.
Why? I just wanted
to share my opinion. That's all.
If you want to share your opinion,
come up with a good name for this episode.
Well, as far as I know,
people who can see ghosts
have brain wave frequencies
that match those of ghosts.
That means...
I suppose that works similarly
to radio frequencies.
So the name for this episode is
"Ghost Frequencies."
What do you think?
Do you think the name will work?
I don't think it will.
Why not? It's such a cool name.
You really think
Aueng sees the ghost of her daughter?
She doesn't see shit.
You can't just say that.
Did you talk to someone?
Dude, I'm serious.
Why? Are you scared?
Hell, yeah, I'm scared.
Come on. Don't overthink it.
There's really nothing.
Easy for you to say.
Have you had enough? It's almost 11:00.
There's nothing to film now.
Okay. Let me check out
the inside of the house.
If there's nothing, we'll call it a day.
Por, come here and see this.
What?
Did you see a person's shadow
inside the house?
That's probably Chai.
I don't think so. Chai's not here.
-Should we go in and get it on camera?
-Is that a good idea?
Let me get the camera.
Wait, Itt.
We should wait for Chai to come back.
It's fine.
I'll go film upstairs. You go downstairs.
Itt!
Fucking Itt!
For fuck's sake!
Where'd she go?
Fuck!
Shit!
That's my daughter.
Por, you bastard,
you didn't fucking wait for me!
Did you see something?
See what? What's wrong with you?
Look here.
What?
There's something right there.
It's their daughter's ghost.
The spirits of people
who die unnaturally go adrift.
They don't have a reincarnation.
Did you know Chai's daughter?
My daughter was Nhoonee's classmate.
I think they were friends.
But when I asked her,
she said she didn't know anything
and she didn't want to talk about it.
Were you there at the scene
when they found her body?
Yes, but I had a bad feeling
since the night before.
Suddenly, there was
a barn owl flying near their roof.
It wouldn't stop hooting.
The next day, she hanged herself.
When I saw her, her neck came right off.
Today is day three.
The situation here is
starting to get unusual.
I think the daughter really is here.
And today is Saturday,
she's probably playing
and running around here.
Por, I have something to tell you.
Last night, I went into her room.
I got this from there.
What is it?
I guess it's her diary.
Shit, Itt!
You've gone too far.
Why?
If you don't respect our hosts,
at least respect the ghost.
What's the big deal?
She's already dead. She won't use this.
How can you be so sure?
Be careful. You'll get screwed.
You know what will really get us screwed?
What?
If we go back empty-handed.
That's the real trouble.
You should be thanking me.
I'm helping you out here.
What did she write in that?
Not sure.
I think
she liked drawing.
Have a look.
Can we make any use of it?
Don't know. I have to see inside.
If she hadn't killed herself,
she would have been a great cartoonist.
Look, there's a photo.
Fuck! The face is completely ripped up.
Must have been her ex-boyfriend.
Should we ask this guy in the picture?
Maybe we'll get some details about her.
But his ex-girlfriend killed herself.
Dude, don't assume things on your own.
Let's try asking the guy first.
If he doesn't talk,
we'll find something else.
And do you know where he is?
We can ask the daughter
of that lady we interviewed yesterday.
She's her friend.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. Don't you remember?
No, dude, it's not my job.
Excuse me.
Were you friends with Nhoonee?
Yeah, why?
Can I ask you something about Nhoonee?
Did Nhoonee ever ask you for any advice?
No.
Have you seen this guy?
Where did you get this picture?
They used to date.
I introduced them myself,
hoping that their lives
would be better, but...
nope.
Do you know where this guy is?
He helps his father
sell noodles near here.
Where?
Just a short walk from here.
There's only one noodle shop.
Is this the guy?
I think so.
But I think we shouldn't mess with him.
Come on. It shouldn't be a problem.
Hi, bro!
We're here to film a TV show.
We want to ask you about Chai's house.
-What do you think you're filming?
-Bro!
-What are you filming?
-Wait!
What the fuck are you filming?
Bro, calm down a sec.
Fuck you, I'm not your bro!
What are you filming?
Calm down.
-Fuck you! What are you filming?
-Calm down, brother.
-Don't--
-Fuck off.
-I asked why the fuck you're filming me!
-Calm down.
You're here to film a TV show?
Yes.
Why are you messing with that guy?
We wanted to ask him about Chai's house.
About what?
About his daughter.
That ended a long time ago.
They concluded that it was a suicide.
Nobody knows why she did it.
You two, why are you messing with him?
Hello, Yo.
-Look at the chaos you created.
-Well, we've got a bit of a problem.
-Nothing to see here.
-I'll have Itt call you back.
Okay, thank you.
Go.
How is it? Is the camera intact?
It's flickering.
You tell Yo what happened.
Okay, I'll talk to him.
It's no big deal to him.
Yeah, he won't yell at you,
but he'll yell at me.
Plus, it's a new camera.
What happens in the end?
I have to work for free.
Screw that. It was an accident.
Don't be such a little bitch!
I told you! Didn't I tell you
nobody wants to talk about it?
Yeah,
but I think he's guilty of something.
He couldn't answer a simple question.
Probably knocked the girl up
and didn't want to take responsibility.
You have to be careful.
This is not a place we're familiar with.
If anything happens, no one will help us.
Yeah.
Fuck. There's a bunch
of missed calls from Yo.
Shit. Let's head back
before I call him back.
Did Itt tell you
we almost got into trouble?
Yes,
but, after that,
I told you guys to leave that place.
Did you?
Itt didn't tell me that.
I told him to come back
if it's too dangerous.
But Itt said you two
wanted to stay and finish the job.
Wait. I didn't say anything of the sort.
Really? That's what Itt told me.
Yes, boss. Well, we...
Yes.
What did Yo say?
Nothing.
He said we've filmed
sufficient material in Chai's house.
I told you so.
How's that? He told you off, didn't he?
What the hell are you looking at?
Let me see.
Can't you see I'm using this right now?
What are you so upset about?
Mind your own fucking business.
Have you checked
the cameras inside the house?
What's the purpose
of putting them up if you haven't?
Every time you get told off,
you always take it out on me.
What the fuck?
Hey, Itt!
Itt, where are you going? Wait up!
Hey, Itt.
Are you really going up there?
Fuck, whose footprints are these?
Itt, there are so many footprints here!
We should go back, Itt.
Itt!
Fuck!
Itt, let's go, please.
Itt!
Itt, I can't take this anymore.
Itt, let's go!
Itt, did you see that?
Itt, let's leave!
Itt!
Itt, I really can't do this!
Itt, let's go.
Don't fuck with my mother!
Fuck!
-I will take my mom with me!
-Itt.
Get out!
Fuck!
Fuck! You see? I told you not to go up.
We're screwed.
Are you okay, Itt?
Don't you fuck with me.
I'm already scared shitless.
What the fuck is wrong with you, Itt?
The time now is 2:00.
Itt has disappeared out of the blue.
He's not at Chai's.
Why did you leave me
all alone, fucking Itt?
I'm scared as fuck.
Where the fuck did Itt go?
Why don't you pick up the phone, Itt?
Itt!
What the hell are you doing there?
Are you okay?
Itt.
Itt, what the fuck are you filming here?
Itt. Stop shooting, man.
Shit, are you okay?
Let's see what Itt shot.
Itt!
Itt, what the fuck are you filming here?
Itt. Stop shooting, man.
Shit, are you okay?
Itt started to change from that moment.
I don't know what had gotten into him.
How was he?
He'd get mood swings.
He was like a roller-coaster.
Sometimes, I couldn't tell
what his mood was.
After that night, he became very quiet.
Like he was mad at me or something.
He wouldn't talk to me at all.
Itt, I think that's enough.
Let's go home.
We can't leave yet.
Or we can go stay somewhere else.
We can come back here
when Master Pla comes.
If we stay somewhere else,
how are we going to film?
Then give me the camera.
I'll go outside
and shoot some footage myself.
And don't forget
to return that book to her.
There's definitely
something about that house.
We're going through this together,
but instead of helping...
Something is fucking wrong with Itt.
I guess he's in his work mode.
I really want
to ask you guys at the office
if you hate me or anything.
Why did you send me to this place?
I have to go back and check on Itt.
I wonder how Itt is doing.
Fuck, you're still sitting
in the same spot?
Itt, you haven't returned that yet?
Do you hear me?
Have you had enough?
Where are you going?
Itt!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
What are you looking at?
Itt! Where are you going?
Not again!
Itt!
Can you hear me?
When are you gonna stop following her?
It's our last night.
But you've already got enough footage.
Our boss will be so pleased.
Trust me.
He'll definitely let us pass probation.
How would you know?
I'm the one who filmed all this footage.
Why wouldn't I?
If the footage is not enough,
you'll be responsible.
You ass! I'm not going with you.
Itt, how will you film without a camera?
For fuck's sake. What the fuck?
What is she doing at the school?
Itt, don't follow her.
Do you hear me?
Shit.
What is Aueng doing up there?
Who is Aueng coming to see?
Who is Aueng talking to?
Why aren't you home?
I've already told you...
Don't you argue with me.
I told you to come home.
Why aren't you coming?
Come home!
Goddammit!
Where are you going?
I'm fucking leaving.
And you? Are you leaving or staying?
If you're staying,
there are the cameras,
and you help yourself.
At that moment,
I couldn't take it anymore.
All I could think was,
I had to get out of there ASAP.
I didn't care
if I was pissing anybody off.
And so you just ditched your friend?
I guess so.
If he wanted to shoot so much,
he could stay and do that himself.
But in the end, I couldn't.
I tried to drag him out.
But when I went back
inside the room, he was gone.
Itt!
Itt, what's wrong with you?
Shit, Aueng!
Aueng!
Aueng! Aueng!
Itt, give me a hand!
Itt!
Hey, Itt,
what the fuck is going on?
Why is Aueng trying to kill herself?
Answer me!
Itt!
Itt,
talk to me!
Why are you back?
Why are you saying that?
Why the fuck do I have to be
in a situation like this?
I don't know.
I don't know how she got in there.
Damn it!
When Aueng gained consciousness,
I asked her about hanging herself. She
said she didn't know what was going on.
Next thing she knew, she was up there.
She's lucky that we found her.
Otherwise, she would be much worse.
And Master Pla?
The next morning,
Master Pla performed the ceremony.
Put your hands together.
Get a grip on yourself.
Keep your hands together.
Aueng.
Okay, untie this.
Why did you accept all these child dolls?
They said they would help.
For Christ's sake,
how can these dolls help you?
All these sodas you get for them,
they can't even get it themselves.
All this stuff, it's not just
for the rich. It's for the dumb too.
Get it? I'm not trying to insult you,
but be more logical next time.
You wouldn't have kept them otherwise.
These are devilish, not auspicious at all.
There's too many.
What fell didn't jump out by itself.
Someone broke them.
You think some kind of miracle happened,
but there's no miracle.
Tell me why.
My neighbors say
they see a ghost around here.
Do they know who the ghost is?
I don't know.
Has it been here long?
About a year now.
Your daughter hanged herself a year ago?
Yes.
And what is this little spirit house?
A shaman told me to build it.
For what?
For my daughter to live in.
So you let your daughter live in here
instead of letting her go?
Why keep her here?
Building a spirit house isn't the way out.
Your daughter's ghost can't reincarnate
because she has to stay here.
She has nowhere to go
because she's attached to this house.
I see all these termite hills
around the house.
Why are you worshipping them?
The shaman said they're holy.
What's the name of this holy being?
Grandpa Jomthong.
Yeah, right. Some holy grandpa wouldn't
want to live in this stupid termite hill.
What did Master Pla say?
He said the house was haunted
by wandering spirits.
And he did his ceremony.
And were Chai and his wife better?
It seems like it.
And your friend?
Finally, we can go home.
I've never been this happy before.
Look at Itt.
We're going home, and he isn't happy.
Guess he wanted to stay on a bit longer.
I was the one who helped him,
and I don't even get a thank you.
Don't you have to return all this stuff?
No rush. I can do it tomorrow.
Anyway, I have to pick up Itt.
He can help me carry all this.
How was work? Did you have fun?
Yeah.
Tell me, what did you see?
No, I don't feel like it.
Are you going to tell me or...
Do you really want to know what I saw?
I saw a horny ghost!
You freak. Stop teasing me.
What is Itt doing? Is he coming out here?
I'm always late because of him.
Probably up missing Aueng all night.
Guess I should get out.
See what he's up to.
Itt.
Are you coming to work? We're late.
Hi, Por.
Itt is inside, feeding Mom.
Is he coming to work?
I don't know. Something's up with him.
Can you check on him?
Hi, Mom.
Hey, Itt, you're making a mess!
Itt, enough.
I'll take care of it.
What the heck is wrong with you?
See?
What's wrong with him? He isn't talking.
Let me go talk to him.
Itt.
Itt,
what's up with you?
Are you okay?
Shit, why do you still have her stuff?
I'm going to throw it out.
That's what happened.
Do you get it now?
I don't know what's wrong with him.
Try calling him.
Let me speak to him.
Good idea.
You can talk some sense into him.
Hello?
Is that you, Oil? Where's Itt?
In his room, I guess.
He left his phone here.
How is he? Still going insane?
He's still bummed out.
Do you want to talk to him?
Yeah, let me talk to him.
Okay. I'll get him for you.
Itt, it's Por on the phone.
How's it going, Oil?
Itt!
Shit!
Oil, what's wrong?
The power went out.
Is Itt there?
Nope.
I have to go check on Mom.
-Okay. Okay.
-Okay.
Watch your step.
Mom, the power is out.
I'll go check the cutout switch.
What's wrong, Mom?
I think we should go to his house!
Something's not right.
You go. If something's up, just call me.
What? Don't you think you should
take care of your crew?
I'm busy. I've got work to do.
You're such a dick.
Watch your mouth. I'm your boss, prick!
Fine, I'll go by myself.
And don't forget to show
your boss this tape. I quit!
I really don't want to go in.
But he's still my friend.
Guess I have to go check on him.
If something happens to me,
please check this tape.
Itt!
Itt, where are you?
Fuck!
What's happened, Itt?
Itt!
Oil!
Where are you?
This is not funny.
Itt!
Oil!
Itt! Are you upstairs?
Itt!
Stop messing around. I don't like this!
Itt! Itt!
Itt!
Itt! Where the hell are you?
Itt! Itt!
Itt!
Can we conclude that
there was a ghost there, Master Pla?
We can't conclude
whether there was a ghost or not
because we don't have
any evidence to prove it.
People can argue all day about this.
For those who believe there was,
there was.
For those who don't
or who didn't see it, there wasn't.
My job was to help this family
be free from the thing
that couldn't be seen but existed,
to bring their lives back to normal.
That's the mission I had to complete.
But it can't be proven
if there really was a ghost in that house.