YIN YANG MASTERS
USE THE DOCTRINE OF FIVE ELEMENTS
TO DISTINGUISH MEN FROM MONSTERS.
RIGHTEOUS MEN GATHER
IN THE YIN YANG BUREAU
TO TRAIN AND CAPTURE EVIL SPIRITS.
Qingming.
What have you done?
Brother Cimu…
was killed.
Cimu.
What did you do to him?
Nothing.
A demon escaped the Sealing Chamber.
And tried to steal the Scale Stone.
There are dismembered bodies.
So tell me, how was it
that you escaped untouched?
I didn't do it.
-Please, I swear.
-One cannot change one nature.
The only true demon here is you.
It wasn't me!
Baini.
What happened here?
Qingming killed Cimu
and tried to take the Scale Stone.
But that's…
-impossible.
-He has already fled out of guilt.
If you can't tell right from wrong,
how will you expect to be chief?
The bellflower bracelet.
SEVEN YEARS LATER
PINGJING CITY
When Pangu separated heaven and Earth,
humans and demons
initially live together in harmony.
But then an evil demon named Xiangliu,
proclaimed himself
to be the Demon Emperor.
The nine-headed serpent
seduced the demons
into wreaking havoc upon the mortal world.
Fortunately, a group
of Yin Yang Masters fought back.
They forged a sacred weapon,
the Tushan Sword.
With it, they slay Xiangliu
and banished all demons.
Humans and demons were forever separated.
Humans inhabited cities,
while demons strolled
in the Monster Realm.
Both sides kept to themselves.
Whenever a demon crosses the border,
a Yin Yang master is treated as a part
of the Demon Emperor's army.
It's captured and imprisoned
in the Sealing Chamber.
Move aside. Move aside.
The Capital Guards are on a mission
to escort the imperial tribute
out of the city.
Move aside.
The Capital Guards are on a mission
to escort the imperial tribute
out of the city.
MONSTER REALM IS DANGEROUS
LEAVE AT YOUR OWN RISK
It is the time for ghost festival,
yet the Captain volunteered us
to escort the offerings out of the city.
This is just asking for trouble.
Agreed.
Why they send us to do this?
This is supposed to be the Bureau's job.
Something in the woods.
Oh?
Who's out there?
Go!
Whoever…
is foolish enough to challenge us,
this is what will happen to you.
Oh…
Sword!
Give me the sword!
Stealing the imperial tribute? Outrageous.
You.
Huh?
I was just passing through.
Figured I'd help you.
Good sir.
You're welcome.
-Ah…
-Hey!
Stop that.
I said stop!
I'm helping you exorcise demons
but don't worry,
no need for a thank you gift.
-I'll just help myself.
-Who said anything about a thank you gift?
Huh?
Well?
-Good sir.
-Huh?
You're in the wrong here.
When people barely survived
the demon attack,
they'd happily show their gratitude.
But I make the effort to help you…
and you don't appreciate it.
It's our duty to escort
the imperial tribute.
So hand it over.
It's obvious that those three demons
knew you.
My guess…
is you're a demon in human guise too.
Sir.
Your suspicion is so small-minded.
Hmm.
Small-minded?
You're coming with me.
If you intend to keep this up,
you will fall.
I assure you.
You're actually with the Bureau.
-How dare you knowingly break the law?
-Purity from within and without.
Hmm.
Thieving pig.
Oh. Oh…
What's your rank in the Bureau?
I dare you to tell me your name.
Okay.
Qingming.
Qingming?
I'll remember you.
I can't watch you fall anymore.
So for now…
I think we're done here.
What happened to all the Capital Guards?
YIN YANG BUREAU
SCALE STONE WARD
Something is wrong in the Sealing Chamber.
SUBDUING CELL
Move.
Return to purity, seal.
-Demons have broken in.
-Chief.
Who's guarding the Scale Stone?
Sunless day, moonless night.
Return to purity from within and without.
This seal must be…
The northeastern road, seven miles away.
The Scale Stone.
Don't touch the Scale Stone.
You're not going anywhere.
Rat demon.
Put it down.
Stop!
My failure must be punished.
We took the Scale Stone from the Bureau,
but then we ran into three rat demons.
I don't know who gave them the order,
but someone must have told them
to intercept the Scale Stone.
You said three rat demons?
They must be Qingming's ferrets.
What were they doing there?
Your job was very easy.
How did you ruin it?
The Raven Hound twins.
Monster Realm's greatest warriors.
They said you could never fail.
Turns out…
they were wrong.
But then again,
the Scale Stone has been removed.
I suppose the Raven Hounds
have at least achieved something.
You can die in peace now.
If you think
that you can make up for things
just because you got back in tribute,
Master took you in
because he expects great things from you
but if you slack off,
you will be punished.
Practicing military maneuvers
in martial arts
to prepare you from whatever is upon.
High.
Forward thrust.
Side thrust.
Side swipe.
Lift your arms.
Harder. What are you aiming at?
Remember,
Master has graciously taken you in
to be the Spirit Guardians.
If not for him, you will all be out now
wandering alone, bullied.
-Shh.
-Don't take this lightly.
Work hard.
What are you doing?
What's the matter?
Stop.
Fell down. Who fell down?
He swallowed something.
And he got into a fight.
We meet again, Qingming.
The Scale Stone has finally been removed
from the control of the Bureau.
You will help me return
to the mortal world.
That is your destiny.
Do you understand, Qingming?
I summon the light of Purple Star
for protection.
Has something happened here?
Look after the ferret.
Something might have happened to
Scale Stone. I'm going to Monster Realm.
Removing the Scale Stone from the Bureau
has wreaked havoc on the Sealing Chamber.
The Defenders have tried to contain it
with sigils all night to no avail.
I refuse to believe
it was merely a coincidence,
that those who stole the Scale Stone
were all Qingming's cohorts.
It is obvious
that he came back to finish
what he failed to do seven years ago.
Losing the Scale Stone is disastrous
for the Bureau.
It's hard to fend off a thief
who lives among us.
If Qingming didn't betray the Bureau,
how did the Raven Hounds
access the restricted area?
How could they have known the spells
to destroy the golden pagoda?
As soon as the Scale Stone was stolen,
the three rat demons were there.
The Bureau should have apprehended
that traitor long ago,
had the Chief been able
to make a decision…
Xican.
…that demon would be roaming
wherever he pleases.
Elder, you don't need to worry
about my past with Qingming.
-I didn't want you to forget.
-Elder Xican.
Choose your words carefully.
I have my own thoughts
on the Scale Stone issue.
A hundred years ago,
helpless elders at the Bureau
took it upon themselves
and sacrificed their lives
to finally slay the demon, Xiangliu.
But the evil serpent had nine heads
and its power was immense.
And although its body was destroyed,
its spirit could never be eradicated.
They could only reduce it
into the Scale Stone
which was then sealed inside this pagoda.
And so…
defending the golden pagoda
and safeguarding the Scale Stone
are the two greatest duties
of the Yin Yang Bureau.
One day, it will be your turn.
And you can never relax in your duties.
Cimu.
Lead the chant
to ward off the evil spirits.
Yes, Elder.
Black Tortoise protects the north,
Vermilion Bird guards the south.
Black Tortoise protects the north
Return to the unity,
purity from within and without.
Qingming.
Don't chant with them.
You're a demon.
You and I are connected by blood.
Release me
and join me.
No!
Qingming.
-Qingming.
-Are you out of your mind?
This is a Scale Stone Ward.
He's half-man, half-demon.
Demonic blood flows to his genes.
Xiangliu has been calling out to you.
Don't say that.
Qingming will be a Yin Yang Master.
He was abandoned as a baby,
we barely know anything about him.
The Bureau only took him in
-to contain his equal--
-Shut up. That's an order.
You're not chief yet, Baini.
-We're not listening--
-Shut up.
And sit down.
Yes, Brother Cimu.
Qingming.
All of this…
stays between us.
Yes, Brother Cimu.
Man or demon,
you must learn to gain control.
Otherwise,
you'll destroy yourself.
TOMB OF CIMU
Brother Cimu,
I will not let your death be for nothing.
Qingming has left us no choice
by doing this.
We brought shame on the Bureau
by failing to apprehend that traitor
for the past seven years.
Even if we have to scour
the entire Monster Realm,
we will bring him to justice.
COURT OF THE GUARDS
Order?
What order?
I must go to the Yin Yang Bureau,
to arrest Qingming
and reclaim the tribute.
Something serious happened
at the Bureau last night.
They can barely deal with it.
Why would they care about
the imperial tribute?
I hereby pronounce
Seventh-Rank secondary captain Yuan Boya
is suspended effective immediately.
He has three days
to repay the lost tribute
or face imprisonment
and confiscation of family assets.
You spend every day thinking about
nothing but your ambition.
But in the end, you're just a nobody
who doesn't know his limits.
I'm going to capture that demon now.
And then you'll see who's the nobody.
Sir, I'll tell you the truth.
I used to get my demonic goods
from Yanyan Le.
Yan what? Come again?
He's a mystical master,
-specializes in demons.
-in demons?
His shop is over there.
If you wanna know about Qingming, ask him.
Quit wasting your breath.
Tell me now.
There is no path
to the Monster Realm.
Are you going to tell me or not?
Shh.
Whoever is in there,
this is Captain Yuan Boya.
I'm here to investigate a crime.
Where are your manners?
The incense outside is still burning,
it means he's with a client.
You can't just barge in.
Are you the expert Yan Lele?
I'm looking for somebody.
Name is Qingming.
Do you know where he lives?
You're asking about
the Yin Yang Master, Qingming.
That's him. I fought him yesterday.
But he fled in defeat.
-I'm bringing him into justice.
-You're full of shit.
Who's hiding back there?
Get out here and talk--
How dare you assault an imperial officer!
I'm going to charge you for this!
You can't even capture me,
why would Qingming run from you?
Are you Yan Lele?
I'm the only one who gets to talk here.
-I'm looking for Yan Lele. You better--
-Get in with the talking.
And his name is Yanyan Le, moron.
What?
Isn't that exactly
what I just said to you?
You're not very smart as a Capital Guard.
Yes, I still need your help then.
So talking or beating?
-No. No.
-I have my umbrella.
It's right behind me,
inside that pile of hides.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
It would have saved us a lot of trouble.
Not just anyone can get in
to the Monster Realm.
-A map won't be much help for--
-Then how does Qingming go back and forth?
Qingming is half-demon.
-He is?
-He also has the sigils from the Bureau.
Sigils?
I have a sigil.
You do?
Where is it?
Untie me.
My young captain,
I can tell you're someone special
and not just some ordinary nobody.
Get back.
This it?
Sir.
I swear on my name, Shenle,
I will help you get into the Monster Realm
and arrest Qingming.
If we go to the Monster Realm…
we'll find Qingming?
Uh-huh.
I could tell Qingming
wasn't a decent person.
But half-man, half-demon?
You know nothing.
A man of Qingming's power comes along
once in a century.
-He's the only one who can control demons.
-Fine.
If he won't be a human,
let him be a demon.
Either way, I'm taking him down.
Hey, check your map.
How far away are we?
How will I check when I'm all tied up?
You're tied up for your own protection.
The map says to go about
35 miles after passing the Temple of Earth
then we'll see the stone statue
at the entrance to the Monster Realm.
CRUMBLING CLIFF
And voilà, here we are.
Well…
we definitely found the entrance.
Only problem is…
How are we supposed to go through it?
Hey.
Give me the sigil.
Give it. Come on.
A halo of golden light engulfs my body.
I fly like a cloud
through the three realms world.
I traveled thousands of miles
like the shadow that follows me.
A halo of golden light engulfs my body.
I fly like a cloud
through the three realms world.
I traveled thousands of miles
like the shadow that follows me.
W-what'd you do?
What… You destroyed the sigil. You…
-You're a swindler. You're under arrest.
-You're the swindler.
Where's your badge?
Can you prove you're a Guard?
Behave yourself.
Let go of me.
Huh?
There's the path. You see?
It takes time for the spell to work.
If you're going to be stupid,
just keep your mouth shut.
What are you doing?
We have to go now or we won't make it.
What?
You were just as surprised as I was!
What's that?
Plum-infused water.
To mask our human scent.
Why didn't you do that before?
-I was so excited, I forgot about it.
-Come on, focus.
This is the place.
The Red Tower.
The Port Master handles all the affairs
in the Monster Realm. He lives here.
Qingming has been doing business with him.
Fish-eye earrings.
How much?
Can you focus on the job, please?
-How does it look?
-It's horrendous.
Qingming won't show up
until the time is right.
If you're worried,
you can stick out by the bridge.
Yuan Boya.
Try this.
Mmm.
It's not bad.
What is it?
Hey.
Are you okay?
Go away.
Come on.
Try on this belt.
-What is this?
-It's a gift.
It looks good on you.
I like it.
We're here on a dangerous mission
and you're acting like--
-Master.
-Oh…
Master!
Demon thief?
Master.
Master, I've finally found you.
Uh, here's a gift to introduce myself.
Please accept it.
I finally caught up with you, you coward.
-Ow. Ah…
-Back off.
Leave him alone.
Master, this guardsman wants to hurt you.
I came to warn you. So don't forget it.
I know what you are, freak.
And I, Yuan Boya, am taking you in.
Whoa.
What was your name again?
Yuan Boya.
Seventh-Rank secondary captain
of the Capital Guards.
-Is this how you write?
-Let go of me.
Oh… Oh.
Oh, using evil magic…
-Spirit Guardian sigil.
-What sigil?
Spirit Guardian.
What is that?
Oh, hey…
Cast the Spirit Guardian sigil on me too.
-Cast it on me too, Master.
-Why can't I control my arms and legs?
-I'm willing to give my life to you.
-Remove the spell now.
Whoa.
Oh.
Hey. What are you doing?
-Hey, master.
-Demon thief!
Master! Master!
-Get back here, freak.
-Let go, Yuan Boya!
Hey, that was so fun.
Mm.
What an honored guest.
Welcome. Welcome.
It hasn't been long
but feels like forever.
Your familiars sent me two carts
of offering yesterday.
Today, you're here in person.
I wonder
if you brought me even more treasure.
Actually…
I need something from you.
Giving and taking brings opportunities.
-So, what do you want?
-The Tushan Sword.
That name is taboo in the Monster Realm.
Why would I have it?
-Think carefully before you answer.
-My precious gems!
After you pledged your allegiance
to the Bureau,
you borrowed the sword to dominate
the Monster Realm
but you never returned it.
Still wanna play dumb?
Such a trivial matter.
Not sure why you'd even remember it.
The Tushan Sword slayed the Demon Emperor
Xiangliu a hundred years ago
and the Monster Realm
still hasn't recovered.
Once the Demon Emperor was gone,
nobody cared much about the sword anymore.
So, what do you want with it now?
The Emperor's body perished
but its spirit lives on.
It never hurts to be prepared
for the worst.
But I can't afford to offend the Bureau.
Hey. Stop.
You can't bully me.
You're in the Monster Realm,
this is my turf.
I am the boss here and what I say…
No!
Be reasonable.
Fine, let's negotiate
but you have to make me a decent offer.
How about two live humans?
Oh.
"Live humans"?
So does this offer sound better now?
Kill that human, don't stand there!
Master!
-Master!
-Yeah!
Master, look here!
Master!
Hey.
Yuan Boya, watch out!
Let her go! Right now!
Don't worry about me!
My dear demons and thieves,
prepare to witness a fight that lights up
which you've never seen.
Man versus demon in a battle to the death!
Place your bets now
for this once-in-a-lifetime showdown!
Hey, captain or whatever.
You better give it your best.
Otherwise, your little pal dies.
May I present to you the Red Ghost Demon.
Born and raised in this very arena,
he has never lost a fight.
Two of you enter
but only one of you will live!
Yes!
Get up!
Stop!
This is it!
The more you hurt
the Red Ghost, the stronger he gets.
This is what he's truly capable of.
This is why he's remained
unbeaten in the ring.
The Tushan Sword's manna is too great.
You have to go alone.
You got here fast.
Who knew the Bureau was so capable?
The light shines a thousand miles.
Connect.
Master's sigil?
Three thousand spears
between Heaven and Earth. Break.
How have you been?
I'm not here to talk about the past.
You have something that isn't yours.
Give it back.
So, the Chief wants this sword too, huh?
Don't be coy. Give me the Scale Stone.
What?
So it really was stolen?
You're either pretending
or you need to talk to your ferrets.
"Ferrets"?
They might cause trouble
but would never steal the Scale Stone.
Awfully trusting of you.
Of course.
That's why I've made them
my Spirit Guardians.
They're not evil by nature.
Spirit Guardians live and die
with their masters
and never betray them.
That is what you taught me.
The nose! Hit his nose!
Yeah!
Nice hit!
Kill the freaking loser.
-That's the rule of the fight.
-Yeah!
Only one gets to be alive.
Let's go!
Stop them!
Don't let them get away!
Be careful! This human can fight!
Where are you going?
-Huh? Watch out.
-Huh?
Huh? Oh…
The Tushan Sword!
What is the Tushan Sword doing here?
-There they are!
-Surround them. Get them!
-The ghost is helping you!
-I don't want that thing to help.
Whoever returns the sword
will get a hefty reward.
Demon thief decided to surrender, huh?
Captain…
That thing you're holding
is worth more than your life.
Give it.
-Is it yours?
-Of course.
Now you lost something,
so it's your turn to be worried.
Give it now.
Come back to headquarters,
prove my innocence.
Fine.
The Yin Yang Bureau's people! Run, run!
Chief!
Baini!
Baini.
Go, go, go.
Ouch.
What's he doing here?
Well… where are we now?
Huh?
This is Master's home.
That bandit lives here?
So this is where he hides his loot.
Wait, stop. Stop it.
We're on the same side.
Did you think that following Master
would make you one of us?
Who wants to be one of you?
You think I don't recognize you?
You're the filthy little thieves
who stole the imperial tribute.
Who are you calling a thief?
I'll rip out your tongue.
Quiet.
Sister.
Please, forgive this stupid human.
They are guests.
Bring them inside.
Thank you so much.
We'll just have a look around.
Don't mind us. We're not even here.
Thanks.
Baini.
Is there really no place for me
at the Bureau?
-What's that?
-It's a token.
That's for girls. I don't want it.
This bracelet will let me cast
a Spirit Guardian sigil on you.
The sigil's only for demons.
I'm a human.
You're also half-demon so that counts.
I'm not a demon.
And I'll never be one.
Qingming, it's okay if you are.
Be my Spirit Guardian,
and I'll be your master.
Don't you know about that?
Once a demon has a master,
it knows it has a home,
and they will never become evil.
Well…
I…
Qingming…
from this day forward,
am Baini's guardian.
We now live and die as one
and we shall never betray each other.
Never betray each other.
Careful with those wounds.
I promise…
-I'll help you find the truth.
-Your promise…
is worthless.
If that's true…
why would you take this one for me then?
I've been looking for the Scale Stone.
Your demons have been a nuisance
for years. Everyone knows that.
You're definitely involved in this.
All the demons here
have the same fate I do.
We're not allowed in the capital city
and don't belong in the Monster Realm.
We're outsiders,
living as thieves.
Trying to survive
-the only way we know how--
-So now it means you and the demons?
You promised
that we would always be you and me.
But you chose to leave the path
and ruined everything.
I left the Bureau
because I had no other choice.
That night, seven years ago,
it was my turn to guard
the Scale Stone ward.
I bumped in to Brother Cimu.
Qingming.
He was concerned
about my well-being as always.
Brother Cimu.
Are you still being troubled
by Xiangliu's spirit?
During the ghost festival,
it's especially bad.
Thankfully, you taught me
that protection spell.
I've been chanting it a lot lately.
You can't afford to cause
any more trouble.
If you truly lose control someday…
reverse the incantation
and destroy yourself.
So Xiangliu doesn't possess you.
"Reverse the protection spell"?
I'll guard the Ward for you tonight.
Return to the unity,
purity from within and without.
Little did I realize
that the evil spirit
would be especially violent that night.
I knew…
that something serious must have happened.
…purity from within and without.
The Golden Pagoda?
Inside the ward,
there were bodies everywhere.
I tried to find Brother Cimu,
but the Golden Pagoda had melted.
The evil spirit inside the Scale Stone
was driving me insane.
Qingming, you're pathetic.
You're seen as nothing more than a freak
in the human world.
but little did you know
that you belong to the rarest
and most precious bloodline.
Purity from within and without.
This order shall break the seal!
Don't bother
with that useless incantation.
You are a demon.
You and I are connected with my blood.
Another one has gone for the Scale Stone.
-Hmm.
-It was the Snow Queen.
She was supposed to be locked
in the Sealing Chamber.
How did she get inside the Ward?
-Brother. Brother!
-Qingming, get out.
That was the last time I saw Brother Cimu.
I had no choice but to defend myself,
then I saw that Brother Cimu had been
torn to pieces by my counterattack.
And the Snow Queen had disappeared.
No one has wanted to find her
more than I have these past seven years.
"The Snow Queen"?
There's nobody else besides you
who could send demons into the Ward.
Seven years ago,
Brother Cimu died because of you.
Seven years later, people at the Bureau
died because of you again.
You're not innocent in this.
If you're so sure it's me…
why do you still have our token?
Give it back.
Huh?
There it is again.
-Something's in there.
-Wait.
You can't touch anything in the courtyard.
Wanna bet I can?
-Hey.
-Maybe that's the beheaded tribute.
Wait your turn.
Qingming.
The Tushan Sword.
The Ferret has mutated.
Kill it.
What do you have to say now?
If the Bureau had done its job
and protected the Scale Stone,
the Ferret would still be alive.
I won't bother with you all tonight.
You and your demon friends
can have a few more days of peace.
But when I return,
I'm going to destroy this place.
The life of a demon, it needs a master.
So it has a home,
it doesn't become evil.
But back then…
my demon sisters…
didn't even get to be buried.
Your demon sisters?
I was born an orphan.
I had to beg for food. One time…
I was chased by a ferocious dog.
Ended up passing out
in front of a big house.
There was an amazing smell
coming out of it.
I felt energized all of a sudden.
The pain from my wounds was gone.
You were dreaming, weren't you?
It was even better than a dream.
It was called the Courtyard.
"The Courtyard"?
Wait, are you talking about
the famous brothel?
Why were you so happy to end up there?
It was wonderful.
The sisters treated me so well.
And when I was seven…
the Bureau came.
They told me that my sisters
were all demons hiding in the city.
They weren't allowed
to stay there anymore.
Those who cooperated were sealed away.
Those who resisted
were slaughtered on the spot.
But that time…
there was a young man with them.
He was shivering.
He was a Yin Yang Master,
but he didn't harm any of my sisters.
Instead, he just held me in his arms
and gave me one of my sisters' umbrellas.
That was the day
I decided he would be my master.
Wherever master went…
that's what I'd call home.
I am no one's master.
You really have an urge to say that?
You're the problem.
If you're a demon,
why would you become a Yin Yang Master?
If you're a human,
why do you keep those demons around?
-It's ridiculous.
-We were both abandoned.
No need to insult each other.
-You're comparing yourself to me?
-Aren't we both…
oddballs who got fired?
Hmm?
Come here.
-Drink with me.
-Hmph.
What's wrong?
Afraid I'd poisoned the wine?
-Do you think I'm afraid of you?
-Yuan Boya.
Stop it.
You want a drink? Let's drink.
-We'll see who's afraid.
-Don't make a fuss.
The chief left Qingming's garden
with her injuries unhealed.
They've cast a spell
to keep her from going back.
The Scale Stone must not be returned
to the Bureau.
Last round then I'm bringing you in
and putting this case to rest.
Even my closest ally
has called me a traitor.
Yet you still believe
that I will keep my promise.
Then why…
would I not believe you?
If you have any sense of gratitude,
-you should make a toast to master.
-Hmm?
Did you think you beat him
all by yourself?
It was my master's sigil
that helped you win.
Just hurry up and remove the spell, okay?
A grown man wearing a red bow
is so embarrassing.
Stop being such an ingrate.
-Hmm?
-Master, can I have it too?
That's not a Spirit Guardian sigil.
The red bow in his palm…
is just a prank master's playing on him.
Huh?
-It's not a real sigil?
-Humans can't be guardians.
Only demons can.
-Fine with me.
-So just because we're human,
we're not allowed to be a Spirit Guardian?
The human heart is fickle by nature.
Promising to be faithful
till death do you part?
No human is capable of that.
Hey, don't look down on humans.
If you think humans are so bad,
that means half of your master is bad too.
If I think demons are stupid,
then half of your master is stupid.
In other words,
he's a bad and stupid
freak.
Hey.
Very well said.
I am absolutely a freak.
From one freak to another.
Well, I'm a freak too.
So I also get a drink.
Hmm. Stupid demon.
Stop it. He is not.
-Whatever. I'm so drunk.
-Hey, pass it over here.
Come on.
Why have I ended up here?
Chief.
-Chief.
We came as soon as we got your location.
Are you all right?
This place is dangerous.
We can't stay here.
Keep this safe.
The Scale Stone.
Return it to the Bureau
as fast as you can.
Hmm.
Watch out.
Behind you.
The Scale Stone.
Take it and go, Chief.
Baini!
It's you.
It's unfortunate we had to meet this way.
Then again, if you kill her,
get back the Stone for Master,
you're sure to be rewarded.
You started this seven years ago.
Today…
I'm finishing it.
If you want me, come and get me.
It's my fault for not trusting you.
We have the Stone. We can still win.
The Snow Queen mentioned her master.
-I'll find him.
-Qingming.
When this is finally over…
the bellflower bracelet…
will be yours again.
With or without the bracelet,
you are my master.
We live and die as one,
and shall never betray each other.
I won't be long.
Was your master too afraid to show up?
Patience.
You will kneel before him shortly.
The whole world will kneel before him.
Who's there?
The Scale Stone doesn't belong
to the human world.
It's been away from its rightful place
for too long.
If that's true, then where does it belong?
In the hands of the world's
most powerful demon, of course.
It doesn't matter who your master is.
Today, you'll finally pay your debt.
You really are a fool.
The master looked after you at the Bureau.
Weren't you always very grateful to him?
Cimu.
I joined the Bureau at the age of nine.
At 30,
I became the youngest Defender ever.
But for what?
At that point, the Bureau
had nothing more to offer me.
Travelling to the mortal world…
in my eyes, you were nothing
but distractions.
I understand your obsession with Qingming,
but I have my own obsession.
The freak who'd been abandoned
by everyone existed for only one reason.
To show me the true strength
in demonic power.
If little Qingming could possess it…
then with Xiangliu's aid…
what could possibly be out of my reach?
What I want…
is the power of the Scale Stone.
Master Cimu…
is the savior
for both of us.
Do you hear the master's call?
You're lying.
I know what I saw that night.
I watched Broher Cimu die
right in front of me.
Just a simple illusion.
Master.
SNOW QUEEN
I, the Snow Queen, hereby vow
that I shall serve
Master Cimu forever.
Greatness will be yours.
I…
I wish I could be there
to see you…
achieve it.
Show me the road.
Mommy!
Mommy, I'm scared. Mommy…
I want to go home.
Mommy…
I wish I'd been alive
till the Demon Emperor's reign,
but I was born too late
and I had to become the Bureau's lapdog.
But if the Demon Emperor were to return,
I would gladly sacrifice my life for him.
Where is my wine?
More wine for me. More wine.
Why are you still lying there?
Unless you wanna become a barbecue,
we have to move now.
Barbecue? Where is the barbecue?
Let's go.
Huh?
What the heck is that?
Oh, what happened here?
What is going on?
Cover your nose and mouth with the sigil
to protect you from mutating.
-Give me one too.
-Humans don't need it.
What?
Why is that?
An evil demon has acquired the Scale Stone
and opened the gateway
to the Monster Realm.
Hordes of demons will soon be invading.
Invading?
-Why?
-For years,
Master has trained you for war
because he never forgot his duties
as a Yin Yang Master.
And now…
we'll honor him
-and protect the Capital City.
-Capital?
-Who's invading the Capital?
-Today is the day.
-Guard the Border Bridge with your lives.
-What?
Spirit Guardians…
fight until your last breath.
We've burned our garden.
There's no retreat for us.
Hey… Wait!
Shenle, where are you going?
Uh…
You're using this as a cover to escape.
You are not one of us.
Go back to the Capital Guards.
Not one of us?
She says it like it's a bad thing.
What?
What does that mean?
Keep an eye on them?
You know what? I think I'll do that.
Catch up.
Brother Cimu,
I have a question for you.
We're not at the Bureau.
So…
no need for brother.
Seven years ago,
you were the Bureau's Defender
yet you conspire with the Snow Queen.
to slaughter your brothers
and steal the Scale Stone.
Purity from within and without,
this order shall break the seal!
Master. A human body
can't handle the Stone's power.
Only a demon's can.
Stay back.
Master, let it go. Let it go.
Or it will kill you.
Master.
Master. The alarm bells are ringing.
We need to go now.
Live to fight another day.
Another one has come for the Scale Stone.
Mm-hmm.
Mm!
Sure, I lost an arm,
but its replacement was far superior.
So it was worth it.
You were the one
who showed me the true power of demons.
Yet you did not know how to follow
your true nature.
That's why you're in this pathetic
predicament now.
Actually, I think you,
Brother Cimu,
are far more pathetic.
You've become a monster
with nowhere to go.
Maybe my guard…
can take you in.
Take me in?
I answered Xiangliu's call.
I tortured myself
to create this demonic form,
and now I have the power
of the Scale Stone.
Which makes you…
lower than the mud underneath my feet.
Xiangliu called to you?
Yes, and he told me
that it was my destiny.
To be the strongest being on Earth.
And if anyone in the human world
or Monster Realm ever dared to defy me,
they'd be destroyed.
Innovation.
I never would have thought
I would kill you with this sword.
The Scale Stone
has been growing stronger
for over a hundred years.
Did you honestly think…
this rusty old sword could beat me?
Also, you should know
you're never gonna see Sister Baini again.
Your beloved,
your master,
is gone.
It's the most important moment
and that freak is nowhere to be found?
Let me through. Let me through.
Well, I guess I just have to take care
of everything…
myself.
That…
That… that might work too, I guess.
Assuming it doesn't take a year.
-Uh…
-Chew harder!
Don't let them cross the bridge!
What's happening?
It's awful.
It's demonic…
Where? Is it poisonous?
Are demons attacking?
Shenle!
I'm coming.
Shenle. If we get out of this alive,
I'll take that belt you picked up.
What bell?
What bell are you talking about?
Oh, yeah. Well, Red hit so hard that…
he'd be great at ringing bells.
Why'd they stop?
Careful, it could be a trick.
What is that?
Master?
Huh?
Master!
Master told me that if one day…
he should die,
all of you
were free to go your separate ways.
There's no need to die with him.
It won't make any difference
if we go back now.
So let's stay and die fighting.
There are more Capital Guards
protecting the city besides me.
I do so enjoy
watching pointless struggles.
It's so amusing.
The bridge is breaking. Everyone, run!
Shenle.
I'll remember you.
And I hope you'll remember me too.
Yuan Boya!
Destroy the bridge!
Even if it takes us with it.
We can't let them pass!
Qingming.
Wake up.
Baini?
What is this place?
Thankfully…
you kept your promise.
I've been waiting for you for a while.
Forget your demon friends.
Forget the Bureau and Pingjing City.
There's only you and me.
We'll be together forever.
Isn't this
what we always wanted?
You are not Baini.
Baini would never turn her back
on the mortal world.
Are you sure about that?
Demon.
Qingming.
You must replace Cimu
and join with me.
"Replace Cimu"?
You were the one controlling him,
driving him insane.
You wouldn't embrace your true nature
and kept refusing my call.
Now that Cimu has pierced your heart,
you and I are finally connected.
This is the perfect time for us
to become one.
Why does it have to be me?
Cimu does not share my bloodline.
You are the only one
who can truly bring about my resurrection.
No.
I'd rather reverse the protection spell
and destroy myself
than become your puppet.
But what about them?
Do you want them to be destroyed as well?
I once made a pact with Baini
that I would never become an evil demon.
Baini.
You also hold Baini's life in your hand.
No.
No! Stop it!
Cimu has the power of the Scale Stone.
I am no match for him.
Join with me
and fully embrace your demonic nature.
Recognize me as your master.
You can still achieve greatness.
Recognize you as my master?
Would you rather be a weak human
or a demon capable of saving the world?
Which do you choose?
Yuan Boya!
Red!
The bridge is broken.
We'll guard the city.
If it's the last thing we do.
Do you really think this will stop me?
I'm Seventh-Rank secondary captain
Yuan Boya,
I'm honored to fight alongside you
and die without regret!
Hmm?
Huh?
Nice trick…
freak.
How did you…
I was supposed to control both realms
and rule over all.
Vanity fills your heart.
You have no respect for the world
and no attachments to anyone or anything.
And you think you deserve to rule?
The Scale Stone
is not yours to use.
Chief,
we defended the Border Bridge
and saved the capital,
all thanks to Master.
Take the Scale Stone
and come to the Yin Yang Bureau.
Master.
Qingming.
You once promised me
we'd live and die as one
and never betray each other.
Did you forget?
Freak!
You know that stupid sigil of yours?
I believe in it. And look at them.
They were willing to die
because of their loyalty to you.
Which do you choose?
So you used…
Cimu to force my hand.
You made him wreak havoc for both realms
to coerce me into joining you.
Yes.
Return to the unity,
purity from within and without.
You're actually reversing
the protection spell?
You will destroy yourself!
Both my body and soul
will be destroyed.
And you will be trapped
forever
inside Cimu's body.
You can't do this to me!
If you want me to free you,
call me Master
and obey.
-It's not possible! Stop it! No!
-Will you obey?
Say it!
Qingming!
If you take me as your Spirit Guardian,
you will continue my work,
you will abandon everyone
and everything you love
and you will forever
be an enemy to humanity.
I'll ask again.
Will you obey or not?
I swear on my name, Xiangliu,
that I shall become Qingming's
Spirit Guardian from this day forward.
We will live and die as one
and never betray each other.
You're all released…
from my guardian spell.
Master!
From now on,
we are no longer connected.
In the seventh month
of the 47th year,
disaster struck Pingjing City.
Hurricanes, tornadoes
and pestilence ravished the land.
At least,
that's what the historians wrote down.
My report, however,
told a different story.
The battle at the Border Bridge
decided the fate of the world.
And it was Qingming
and his Spirit Guardians
who won this impossible battle.
I was there purely by chance
but somehow emerged as a hero.
Qingming.
What happened to you?
I fear I may never know for sure.
But what I do know
is that you look so determined
when you released your Spirit Guardians.
And you clearly didn't have a choice.
Your sacrifice brought peace
and prosperity to people,
but it also scattered your guardians
to the winds.
I, too, no longer have a home.
Qingming.
I don't care who's the master
and who's the spirit guardian,
we are all hoping
to see you again someday.
And we'll gladly follow you
wherever you wanna lead us.
In the end, isn't that what it truly means
to be a Spirit Guardian?
Sharing all sorrows and joys,
living and dying as one,
and never betraying each other.