Brother, there is a lot of stuff.
Should I sell what's left?
Song, that's inappropriate.
The townsfolk offer them to us for merit.
We shall donate the surplus
for good deeds.
In the next life
-your lips might be thinner.
-What?
I'd rather not be born again
just to listen to your nagging.
Brother!
Please come.
We can't take any more.
Should I row past him?
Nonsense, Song. I want to make merit.
-We can't, Song.
-Yes?
-Preventing merit-making is a sin.
-Is that so?
Okay, we'll stop here.
Help catch the boat.
Wow, Liang.
Are you drunk? You look dewy
like a ripe pineapple
that can't be carried by its stem.
You have to hold the whole thing.
-The current is strong, Brother.
-Are you drunk?
I was asleep last night.
Woke up and got drunk again.
Are you laughing or crying?
Brother is doing well?
I'm fine.
No.
I mean Brother Theng. Is he doing fine?
-Brother Theng went to Tibet.
-Tibet?
So far away!
And didn't even say goodbye.
Can the long-tail boat reach there?
Hey.
Liang.
Are you offering food
to the monk or the fish?
I miss Brother Theng.
That's enough.
I don't need much.
That's right.
-Many people gave alms to you.
-What?
All my life...
Doing good has given me nothing.
-What now?
-Even my own wife.
She never appreciated me.
Isn't that right, Brother?
That's enough, Liang.
Brother, let's go.
-Wait.
-What?
Girl, bring the fruits to offer the monk.
Yes, daddy.
-Like father, like daughter.
-Namhom coconuts are coming.
-Put them down, girl.
-Daughter taking after father is lucky.
Want some fruits, Brother?
To drink after your meal.
May you be blessed.
-Sadhu.
Let's go, girl.
Giving coconuts as alms,
we'll be as beautiful in the next life
as we are now.
Yes, daddy.
Song!
Tangkwa.
How good is your English now?
Good enough to go
to England, Teacher.
-Very good.
-Thank you.
Brother Theng went on a pilgrimage.
Will you go as well, Brother?
I can't stay long.
There's temptation by evil.
I'm going to study religion.
Tangkwa, you study the secular world.
-Understand?
-Understood.
Wait a moment.
Anyong haseyo.
Dongbangsin-gi.
What's up, man?
I've told you many times,
this is not Wat Samian.
Wait, where are you going?
Joking. We're not going back.
Talk to a monk with respect.
-Good morning, Venerable Uncle.
-Venerable Brother!
Sorry.
Hey, hey.
You see, today we...
have something to say to you.
Are you leaving the monkhood or not?
Said you'd be ordained for nine days.
But now it's been a year and nine months.
Is Brother getting senile?
A year and nine months or just nine days?
Are you leaving?
-Are you leaving?
-Enough.
This is a temple.
-What are you doing here?
-Our songs are finished.
I've prepared your clothes.
-The studio is booked.
-Songs are finished.
I took a shower and waited for you.
Brother Smart is calling too.
-Smart who?
-Smart-ass.
What's up, man?
Song is waiting for me.
Song, please start the car.
I'll give a sermon to my mother.
Yes, Brother.
Bro, what's up with the car?
Full-on.
Acting like a kid.
You've been naughty
since you were a little boy.
Now you're a monk.
I taught you but you never listened.
Visiting your own mother,
why put on such dark makeup?
Mother.
I...
I who have nothing
You see?
Coughing again.
I... I will always love you
You're making fun of me.
I'm not. Don't you know that
back in the day
I sang with those...
old-school singers.
The Elvis of Thailand. Don't you know?
They didn't sing like you do now. Just...
Whatever.
They sang starting in a low voice
up to soprano, a very high note.
With one scream, the glass broke.
Think about that. Like me, for example.
I'll sing for you, okay?
Do re mi fa sol la si do
Mother.
Her voice is like a nightingale.
Why didn't Brother give a sermon?
I told you, mother.
Don't sing such high notes.
I apologize.
The former singer in me took control.
Do you want to hear some more?
It's all right, mother.
That's quite enough.
Oh, you.
You're a monk.
You can't touch a woman.
It's forbidden.
It's okay, mother.
A mother is like the saint
of a household.
I'm your son. I can wash or wipe you.
I think it's okay.
Sin or virtue,
it depends on intention.
Moreover, I came here today
because I don't know when will be
the next chance to take care of you.
Where are you going?
I'm going on a pilgrimage to find Dharma.
I rejoice in your merit.
I have something to give
for you to take with you
on your pilgrimage.
-Yes, mother.
-Wait a minute.
-This is a photo of you as a child.
-No matter what
I still love...
you
The woman is me.
And the man is your father.
Goodbye, madam.
I'll give Brother a ride.
Let's go, Brother.
I can't help but feel sad.
You're going too.
Makes me miss Brother Theng even more.
What's the point talking about him?
He went to a nice place.
-Brother Theng is dead?
-Not yet!
He went on a pilgrimage in Tibet
to find wisdom.
To find wisdom?
What for?
How far are you going to go
for your pilgrimage?
When you run out of gas,
I'll get out of the car.
So you can go home.
How am I supposed to?
Let bygones be bygones.
It doesn't matter when everything happens.
The sun rises
and falls in a cycle.
It's a lesson of life.
-Enjoy yourself, but look at the road.
-Yes.
You, you.
Song.
Hey, you!
Did you buy your license,
son of a bitch?
Brother, what are you doing there?
What are you afraid of?
We have a bunch of amulets.
I was just alarmed.
If I didn't hit the brake in time,
we'd be goners.
Brother, end of the road. We can't go on.
Let's go back.
I can't. I've made up my mind.
When we decide to do good,
the road will open up.
So you can stay here.
Then I'll say goodbye.
But Song...
Hey!
Song!
We're supposed to go back together.
You!
That's not appropriate for a monk.
It's okay to ask for alms,
but not okay to fly like a bird.
That is even worse.
Because I am a monk.
This is how a monk does it.
Good thing it was just an idea.
Didn't really happen.
My alms bowl.
Hey.
My bag.
My umbrella!
I'm a monk.
I've practiced Dharma.
This wind...
cannot stop me.
Earth, water,
wind and fire.
Go...
My alms bowl is gone,
my bag is gone.
My last...
umbrella.
Where the umbrella goes, I go with it.
The highest point is non-self.
Ouch.
It burns.
This must be a test
from the Lord Buddha.
You.
Brother.
-I--
-There's a wedding.
The groom's procession
is going to another village.
-No, I mean I--
-A westerner has a wife here.
They're already married.
They brought some friends over to marry.
-I...
-They're Americans.
But we're Thai.
They get married. Many women here
-have married a westerner.
-Okay.
Wow, Brother.
Your robe is all torn.
It's not, it's in one piece.
Brother, you look so beaten up.
From the looks of it,
you're the final stage of monk.
You misunderstood something.
I'm a monk.
Not cancer.
Yes.
Why are you limping?
I got pricked by some thorns.
Usually the thorns here
don't prick anyone.
You must have stepped on it.
I have to go.
I'll see them get married to westerners.
Don't want to miss the beginning.
This must be a test
once again.
I'm going to have a foreign husband,
but I can't speak foreign yet.
What do you want to say?
I'm going to meet the groom, right?
I'm going to say to him,
Honey,
I'm so happy.
-How do I say that?
-It's not hard, Kamlah.
We have a great deal of experience.
Seriously, why do you want
to have a Thai wife?
-Thai women are... beautiful!
-Beautiful!
KOKSA-ARD TEMPLE
KOKSA-ARD KLIANG VILLAGE
What are you looking for?
If we both take one step back,
would it be embarrassing?
Not at all.
Hello, abbot.
Not abbot. I'm Somkiat.
You can call me Jiew.
-And who are you?
-A monk.
So you've been a monk for a long time.
You look so old.
I'm joking. You're looking for the abbot?
I came to get married today.
I'm very happy.
John, what does "I'm happy." mean?
Tell me about it.
Happy means delighted.
Delighted.
And what does "Oh, yes" mean?
-I want to know.
-"Oh, yes"
is used when climaxing.
My goodness.
What about the things we taught Kamlah?
May you be happy.
Oh, yes.
That's not it.
Calm down.
Just wait for the guests to leave.
Ouch.
Did that hurt?
It's all right. I hit that all the time.
The days I don't hit it, I can't sleep.
And the days you hit it?
Can't sleep even more.
It will hurt all over this side.
Screwdriver...
I've found it.
This is the taste of Dharma.
Please finish soon.
So I don't have to walk.
I'm asking you this seriously.
Are you really a monk?
Yes, sir. Here are my credentials.
I see.
How did you end up here?
I intended to go on a pilgrimage
to find the taste of Dharma.
But I found monks fixing a car.
Good. Usually...
we don't see young monks like you.
Not to mention, walking on a pilgrimage.
Scram!
I'll take this.
You step on me!
-Okay.
-Still stepping on me!
You said to step on you.
Which is it? Step on you or not?
I'll go to another jar.
This is the usual.
This is totally normal.
Don't be afraid. Just chill.
People offered them,
so we have to use them.
It's safer.
FLY TO FIND LOVE
KAMLA - TOM
Venerable Grandfather.
How are you? They're bombing again.
Man, where have you been?
I went to see a foreigner get married.
You know what's wrong with the monks?
I went away for a moment,
is there something wrong already?
-Who are you?
-In the temple, in the dead of the night,
it must be...
-a temple boy.
-You!
You don't have to shave.
Why do you have to shave?
It won't be sacred
if you don't shave, huh, Dom?
Will it clear your mind?
What if someone robs or kills anyone,
they'll be innocent if they shave?
A monk with long hair.
That's not a monk, that's Add Carabao.
This woman!
-Why?
I'm just curious.
Why are you mad?
Shaven, why not wearing earrings?
This is a monk, not Nong Chachacha.
Not Nong Chachacha?
Nong is not a monk,
why did he shave?
I'm talking about monks,
why do you talk about Nong?
But you mentioned him first.
I said if you let a monk wear earrings,
he will be Ling Nong.
Nong is not a monk,
why did he shave?
-To look funny.
-Funny?
I should be laughing
at all the monks then.
Why laughing? They don't tell jokes.
Monks shave their heads.
-You don't know my father.
-Why?
If Venerable Father was a layman,
he would sky-kick you.
-You think I'm scared?
-You see?
Having a wife is a nuisance.
Venerable Brother, Father.
I shouldn't have married.
You're lucky to be monks. No wives.
Or do you have one?
-No.
-See?
-Monks don't have wives.
-Dom, are you crazy?
-Shut up and give alms.
-I won't until you answer me.
Are you making monks wait all day?
Their meal time will be up.
Monks from other temples
would have gone long ago.
But monks from this temple wait.
Huh...
Come on.
-Give alms
-I'm pissed off. I won't.
Whoever wants to give, give! I don't.
You prepare food and have the monks wait.
Now you won't give alms?
Do you want to win?
She's trying to win against me.
You don't give alms? Then I won't either.
I won't give alms now.
See if you still win.
Good luck.
Who's going to eat all this food?
-Seriously...
-We both eat it.
-I'm quiet now.
-What are we going to eat?
Wow, what a big fish.
Dokkaew, your father didn't come with you?
He's busy with work.
He told me to bring food to you.
Business is going well.
Lucky us, this meal.
What if the monks eat it all?
What's left for us to eat?
You little runt. How can you say that?
You say "If the monks eat it all,
will we be able to eat?"
Don't worry. Traditionally they will eat
just one side.
The other side must be ours.
Please don't flip.
Don't flip, don't flip.
It's flipped!
Your father's business.
It's such a breakthrough.
Breaking through.
Stone mill business.
Yes, Joey.
Once it explodes,
the people are in trouble.
Our temple is also affected.
Look at the ceiling full of holes.
Almost no space for new holes.
It wasn't like this before.
The temple was beautiful and pleasant.
People liked to come here
and listen to Grandfather sing.
We've stopped but why don't you stop?
Angulimala said
That I made mistakes,
so I want to go back to virtue
And Dharma like the Lord Buddha taught.
Sadhu.
The reason Grandfather is not well
and coughing all day
is because of
the dust from the stone mill.
Nobody stood up to this?
Of course there were some.
The first disciple of his.
He had tattoos all over,
but was shot dead.
Praya Chatrathan
Doesn't bully
He breaks the ant nest
And give it to the red ants
The red ants bit him
He twists and falls down
Then rolls over
My voice is horrible now.
New monk, you try.
-When Praya red ant--
-Hey.
Red ants aren't here yet.
-Chatrathan.
-Again.
Praya Chatrathan doesn't bully
He breaks the ant nest
No, the coughing is mine alone.
Take a look...
Jiew, you try.
Praya Chatrathan
doesn't bully
-Oh.
-Sounds like steam from a rice cooker.
Like a car going up a high bridge.
Oh, the...
Dove
Bares its fangs
Shows its teeth
-What's so funny?
-What kind of dove
-shows its teeth?
-Birds have to coo.
-Right, cats show their teeth.
-Yes.
Oh, the kitty cat
Being a father, being a mother
Is so difficult
Have to pay karma
because of the poor babies
Take care all day
When baby cries, it breaks mother's heart
Oh, dear child
My dearest one
The baby cries
The mother soothes
Nipples have scars
The mother feeds milk
The baby plays with her nipples
The mother is suffering
The chest hurts so much
What the baby desires
The mother provides
Tears in the eyes
With blood in the bosom
Mother takes care of many children
No matter how poor, she's always near
No matter how difficult,
she never asks for anything
The benevolence of mother
that raises us
If it's a boy, the mother
wants him to be ordained
Study religion
Be grateful
To wear monk's robe as payment
If it's a girl
The mother will take care
so she can marry and have a nice family
Teach her female traditional values
The mother teaches with care
But the child usually doesn't care
They always forget their mom and dad
The mother can raise many children
But children get married
and don't take care of mother
Some sons have a former life's luck
With a rich wife and beautiful daughter
Bring the mother in to the home
to be bullied by daughter-in-law
Some girls have a former life's luck
With a rich husband
Use mother until she's exhausted
Bad children swear at the mother
Listen to the song about father and mother
If you like it, please praise us
Don't be arrogant
Just listen and chill
We don't criticize anyone
Sadhu.
Joey, try some.
Go for it. I'll be cheering for you.
Kliang, do you know why
the seat that monks sit on
is called the pulpit?
-I don't.
-You will.
He walked up to it normally.
Now he sits on it,
he tries to look elegant.
Listen.
It's a condition
Not thuggery or instinct
Not annoyed, invaded, or come across
Haven't seen you for long
No organization or bureau
Whether young or old
Everyone can have flaky skin.
What does Dharma look like?
Are its parents Chinese or Thai?
Or Lao? Light or dark skin?
Hair short or long?
Short, tall, fat, slim
Some are barren, some are missing teeth
Some are a couple, but everyone
can listen to a sermon every day
Those who hit parents become hungry ghosts
If you like my sermon, put your hands up
I thought I was performing in a concert.
-Sorry about that.
-Sadhu.
Hey!
Not again.
What the hell? Again?
When is it going to be over?
Destroyed.
I'll be damned.
The new monk's singing was so cool.
That's right. He's very on-trend.
-What does "on-trend" mean?
-It means "on the trend," idiot.
Are you sure?
The last time,
you made me embarrass myself.
When the water poured down my hands,
I said, "Oh, yes".
In front of the whole village.
This time is no mistake.
My husband, John, bought
a book for me to translate.
Then can I ask for your help?
When I'm with my husband and...
I'm about to cum, what do I say?
That's easy. Let me check the book.
I got it.
Cumming is potato.
Potato.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
-Let's play this.
-Play what?
Close your eyes and count to ten.
One, two, three, four, five, ten.
Where are you, sweetie?
Don't let me catch you.
Where are you?
Whose behind is this?
Don't know, don't care.
Are you taken?
-Don't know, don't care.
-Not taken then.
That means it's public.
I'll take it then.
Come in, hurry.
Follow Kamlah in.
Kamlah will let you eat the dog's bowl.
Come in.
From this moment,
Tom, you'll see my dog's bowl
fully with your own two eyes.
Where the hell is he?
Looking for him until dark.
My husband is gone
All I have is a lighter
I'm here.
You baldie. What are you doing here?
I was looking for you until now, you ass.
-Potato.
-Potato!
I don't know what to do.
I'm afraid to tell my dad.
When I see the villagers
trying to adapt, it hurts me.
It's partly my fault
that the village has to suffer this fate.
Don't think about it.
This is not your fault. Don't worry.
And what you do together
with the villagers
makes them see
-that you're different from your father.
-A different person.
Thank you so much.
I feel much more relieved.
Before I felt so guilty.
Brother, I brought guava for you.
We already ate.
Not the fruit, but the one with limbs.
I've never had one before.
Should be delicious.
Brother.
You're a monk. Please don't be so funny.
He's here.
He said he wanted to be
your disciple.
He's a foreigner. Is he a Buddhist?
No, Brother. I worship God.
But I saw what you did.
It made me want to study the system
of thought of Buddhism.
So I want to be your disciple.
Foreigner from which province?
Weird accent.
You can try. What's your name?
-Donny.
-Yes
-What about nicknames?
Debt.
He probably doesn't have
the money to go home.
Your name sounds so poor.
Is that so, Brother Ey?
Brother Joey.
Brother Ey.
Don't be so cheap with words.
-Call him Brother Joey.
-Bring him up.
Go up there.
Our stone mill never causes
problems for the people around.
People here are happy and chirpy.
Yes, because this place
is just like a town in a fog.
People used to go to
Rong Khun Temple.
I'm sure they'll come here
because this is
even whiter than Rong Khun Temple.
What's that?
I'm still using the same number.
Yes. 081-002-0227.
Okay.
I'm hanging up. Bye.
Goodbye.
Dokkaew.
Where have you been?
Temple, daddy.
That's good. People should go to temple.
Give to the needy.
Our family is full of kind people.
Daddy...
What is it, honey?
-Tell me, honey.
-It's nothing.
Dokkaew is being weird.
What's with those get-ups?
Who do you think you are?
Jack Sparrow? Rambo? Che Lives?
Che Lives, but you won't!
Dressed up so much
but you never get any work done.
You bastards.
I want to know
where you learned that kind of behavior.
Don't be so courteous.
Honey, your favorite is coming.
Chim, Tao's sweetheart.
Put it down gently.
Let me kiss your cheek.
How are you looking so good today?
Did you have botox?
You look so young and fresh.
Let me kiss your ears.
Tonight we will have so much fun.
I'm embarrassed.
Chim is a sadist.
She's my mom's friend.
My mom said to take care of her
before she dies. So I can't leave her.
Hey, Tao.
Everyone knows that your wife
-is the millionaire of this village.
-Sure.
In a few days, your wife will die.
And when the time comes,
this ragged Tao
will become Papa Tao.
Sure thing.
I'm going to be Papa Tao.
She'll die in a few days.
Forget dead, she never coughs once.
-It's true.
-Don't lie to me.
-I don't lie.
-Seriously?
-She never catches cold.
-Yes?
From the first moment
I lived with her,
she sneezed like three times.
The first time though,
she sneezed and I woke up.
I thought it was White Cricket.
Her hair was so white.
And the second time...
-Dead for sure.
-Dead.
And the third time...
Just "ha", not a complete sneeze.
-What the hell?
-And strong to this day.
But in the nighttime, my Chim
is so sexy. She likes to make
her mouth like this.
Chim, don't be sad.
You're still young and beautiful.
I'll find you a new hubby.
-How about ten of them?
-Don't be stupid, Pancake.
I don't even have the energy to fart.
Grandfather.
You stepped on my foot.
I'm going to kick you good.
This is not the time to play.
Put it on correctly.
Are you gonna walk backwards?
-My feet are not in harmony.
-You runt.
-My head.
-Move.
Vengeful. S.S. shot dead
in a car full of holes.
-Senator
-Not S.S.?
People nowadays are so ruthless.
Killing each other like this.
That's right.
They can talk but they won't.
They kill instead.
They don't have moral values.
They should be ashamed.
Worse than animals.
I saw a mother dog
letting baby monkeys feed from her.
Humans should be ashamed.
Have you ever seen a baby lion?
-No.
-Me neither.
Hey.
Venerable Father!
What are you doing? The dust fell on us.
Monk's duty.
What are you doing?
Reading newspaper.
The same car.
Different one.
This one doesn't have holes.
Red plates too.
Which one is Venerable Father?
It is I. What business do you have here?
Hello, Father.
-Bless you.
-I just got a new car.
Red plates, second-hand.
Only 700-something miles.
Cash. Too lazy to do the installments.
I want you to anoint it,
for good luck.
Is this the principal Buddha image
that people build together
and put in the temple?
You must be anointed.
Because you're the driver.
Not that the car drives you.
And don't wash it off now.
Keep it for a week.
I won't sleep on my side again.
I'll lie on my back for seven days.
People are so gullible.
Everyone has their car anointed.
I will shower up to the shoulders only.
Bless you.
By the way,
don't forget the five goods.
Think good, do good, speak good,
have good friends,
and be in good places. Remember that.
Bless you.
What the hell?
So many cousins.
Full-on.
What?
I'll bring Brother to meet Father.
He's lived in this village
since the end of last year.
Always helps with development.
He teaches kids to study.
If you guys put the effort in together,
you could make a great thing.
Many great things.
Father.
I'd like you to meet Brother Joey.
-Hello
-What's up?
Brother, welcome to the village.
-Bless you.
-I hope we can work together
and teach the people
of this good village
good values and
from the book of the God.
Should be very good experience
for us together.
Yeah, very good.
Every religion teaches people to be good.
Mom, help!
Mommy, help!
Mommy, help me.
Come this way.
-Go in.
Let's go in. Hurry!
Everyone go inside!
Hurry up.
Just go inside.
This rock destroyed my house.
You promised that
you'd activate the signal.
Where is the signal, you son of a bitch?
I'll throw this rock
at your father's head.
Bastard!
Bastard.
You'll pay!
I can't stand it anymore.
Wait, Brother Joey.
Trust me, don't do this.
Grandfather wouldn't allow it.
Grandfather wouldn't allow us
to stand up against the stone mill
because he was afraid of loss.
But for us to just do nothing,
I really can't stand it.
I have to at least teach the people
how to cope
-with a life full of dust.
-What are you talking about?
Grandfather.
Anyone who wants to do anything,
don't do it disgracefully
or hastily, understand?
Or else you'll be like my disciple.
The first one.
If he were still alive
he would be the same age as you, Joey.
And from now on,
I don't want
the same thing happen to anyone again.
-Do you understand?
-Don't worry.
I have people who are ready to help.
Brother, how will you do this?
I've prepared the plan.
To live here, you have to adapt.
If dust is the problem,
the solution is
to be able to live with it.
I can't stand it.
What about this rock?
Our skulls will crack open one day.
Don't worry about this rock.
We'll see the authority
that's responsible.
-Dad, you have to be careful.
-I'm always careful.
Bless everyone. Today...
Father and Venerable Grandfather
and Imam invited you here
to study the use of natural water filters.
Start with rocks
that you can see everywhere.
Put them in here and...
Hello.
Mister Nankij? Yes, it's me.
Mississippi. Yes, the same one.
I'd like gunmen.
Very skillful, like one-shot kill.
Not like those three dumb shits.
They can't finish any job.
Please dress like people in the village,
so that they fit in.
Help!
What happened?
Put in a bunch of dynamite in.
Make everything gone in one bang,
so we don't have to do it many times.
It's done. One-shot kill.
There was a flash and then he fell.
Excellent! This is how I like it.
But the way you dress
is as bad as those three dumb shits.
What a miracle.
There's a hole in the alms bowl,
but Brother Joey is fine.
This is the same story
as with Grandfather's first disciple.
I told you many times
but nobody listened.
I said don't bother with them.
But why? You misheard me?
Why didn't you do as I said?
Let's go.
How did you end up here?
Is it not difficult?
As long as we have Dharma
in our hearts,
it's not difficult anywhere.
Dharma is nature
that clears our minds.
And some people
who live in civilized places,
their minds are not as civilized.
That's not good.
Did you have a family before?
Yes, I did.
But then...
when we saw things
we used to dream of,
it became a light
that made me decide to give something up
and come live here.
Brother!
Brother.
Brother! Grandfather's coughing blood.
Prepare the car.
-Hurry.
-Hurry up.
-Let's go.
-Hurry.
Hurry up!
Wait up!
Hey!
Wait!
Stay strong, Grandfather.
We're almost there.
Stay strong.
Wait.
Just a little bit further.
What's with all this, Lord Buddha?
What's wrong with the monks
in this temple?
Grandfather.
Just a bit further.
-Let's go heal at the temple.
-Let's go forward.
Just a bit.
Let go with your hand.
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER
-Hurry!
-Hurry up!
-Quick, quick.
-Grandfather.
-Hurry!
-Quick.
-Why didn't you help?
Letting Brother carry Grandfather alone.
Why did you open the back?
Grandfather is already on the ground.
-Close it up.
-Help, hurry!
Hurry up!
Come inside.
Please go to the room.
Brother, please wait outside.
You can't be inside.
A little later
and Grandfather wouldn't make it.
A little faster and I wouldn't make it.
You can't be here.
Is it full?
You let Grandfather cough
until his throat is sore?
They won't let us in.
Good thing we had the car.
If not, we would have had to carry him.
Good thing I fixed it.
Doctor.
Mr. Jumlong passed away.
Jumlong!
-Miss Woranuch.
-Yes?
-Take the deceased to the morgue.
-We're about to get engaged.
Don't be so sad.
-We're the same.
-Jumlong!
Don't be sad.
Jumlong, don't leave me.
-We're to be engaged in a few days.
-Make way.
-Jumlong!
-Jumlong.
Why did you leave me?
-Jumlong is dead?
-Jumlong is dead.
Ever since he was born, he just died
-for the first time.
-Brother.
Grandfather needs the respirator.
-Move him to that bed.
-Okay.
Let's go.
Doc, but the guy just died.
-It's okay, they always die on this bed.
-Hey.
-Is it a good idea?
-Birth, old age, sickness, and death.
It's normal.
-What are you talking about?
-Brother, I can't hold on.
Brother, hold him.
Put him in position.
Please open your mouth.
You need the respirator.
Let me check the machine for a bit.
Please let go of it.
Grandfather, please let it go.
Please let go.
Sorry, my hand slipped.
It's okay now. Please breathe.
-Dust from the explosion...
-Do you have Grandfather's
credentials or documents?
Wait until everyone dies?
Brother, Grandfather's credentials.
When will there be a brave man
who goes against that stone mill?
Brother.
I'm a nice man.
I like to help good people.
If I have to be a bad man,
it's to fight bad people.
Put more dynamite in,
make it a big bang.
Make the whole mountain go up
so we don't have to do it many times.
Let's go.
What is it?
Do it again. I won't pay you for this.
Boss, I want to ask for alms.
Can you please stop bombing?
I have instructions.
I'd have to ask Luang.
The dynamite's almost expired.
And I cannot
move the mountain to
be exploded elsewhere.
I think you all
should move away from here.
It's easier.
I say this not out of my selfishness,
but because the temple and village
were here a long time
before my stone mill opened.
And just like that,
now you should move.
It's a good thing I was ordained
in a Thai temple.
Saying it like that,
-you'd blow me up as well.
-You said it yourself.
Fine. Encountering an immoral being,
I'm prepared to die.
Everyone was born to die one day.
Live here any longer, you'll die anyway.
Let's die today.
Let's get it over with.
You said it yourself.
If you don't leave,
I'll blow it up now.
Father, please stop.
We have a lot of money.
Stop causing people problems.
How could you say that?
The money we have today
is because we blow up the stones.
Without it, how will we live?
If you're going to blow it up,
you blow me up too.
My goodness!
Dokkaew, you're acting
as if you're my mother.
Like mother, like daughter.
Where are you going?
Brother.
What are we standing here for?
I don't want to live anymore.
Hey.
Don't go in.
It's dangerous. Come out.
Dokkaew, why are you there with them?
Come out now!
I said come out. It's dangerous.
If it blows,
your head and limbs will be everywhere.
You'll be in many pieces.
It's not pretty. Please come out.
If you don't believe me,
I'll order them to push the button.
I'll really tell them to push the button!
Are you challenging me?
If you don't come out,
I will order them to push the button!
Did you hear? He said to push the button.
How?
This is how.
Why did you do that?
He said five!
I don't know. I already pushed it.
-Please come.
-Don't have to. I'm free.
Dokkaew, where are you?
Buddha, help me!
-You.
-Help!
Completely fine.
Such a big rock.
He's fine.
Hey.
-Brother is fine.
-How come?
Brother is totally fine.
He must have good amulets.
Brother.
Just as I shouted, Buddha, help me!
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Brother is really almighty.
-That's right.
-He can break rocks.
That's right, he's fine.
I didn't do anything.
I was shocked so I froze.
If the rock didn't break,
I'd be dead meat.
No, it must be a miracle.
That's superb. Totally amazing.
Arrest them, they're the culprits.
Arrest them.
There they are.
-Police!
-This is the police. Freeze!
Wait.
Boss.
You're an offender in a contracted
murder case. Take him to the station.
You're evil.
The fishes are super fresh.
BEAUTIFUL VILLAGE BECAUSE
OF OUR UNITED PROJECT
I think it'd be good
if we have a big school.
-I think so.
-Our children don't have to travel far.
They can study here.
-Different religions studying together?
-Of course, no problem.
Everybody, today is a ceremony
at our temple.
Please come together
for the prosperity of the temple.
Please help.
The women help check things.
Our village has so many stories...
Take all the shells off.
Do well and I'll teach you English.
Tan, I speak English fluently now.
Pig is pig.
You know?
Hey. Monk is called monk
MOBILE DHARMA
Thanks to Yong's chili paste
which didn't help at all.
Bought it to eat.
Mobile Dharma.
it became Red-Eye chili paste.
Where to stick "Dharma Car"?
In front, so people know
it's a monk's car.
Come together...
This is "Dharma Car," not monk's car
You talk too much.
Come here...
I invite everyone.
Please come.
Who wants to help our temple?
They say the temple will be good.
Good morning, Father.
Full of faith.
Ever since I met you,
I became so rich.
Yasothon Rocket Festival.
I was the only provider.
If you light my rockets,
three days and they will
still be up there!
I don't know if they interrupt the angels.
I also bring my wife and kid.
Please anoint my wife all over.
-Bless you.
-Trust me.
-I'll light it for you.
-You don't have to.
Count them out, Grandfather.
Brother, believe me.
My rockets are top-notch.
I'll take some with me to light.
When it goes up, three days,
it will still be in the sky.
Make it like a big festival.
I'll take my wife and kid
for Grandfather to anoint.
So happy. Grandfather is so fast.
Grandfather.
After this ceremony,
may I visit my mother?
Father,
do you want to come with me?
You see...
From now on, for 120 minutes,
you'll see a fantastic spectacle.
Your village and temple
will prosper forever.
Isn't that high?
Will it come down in three days?
Scram!
Full-on.
-Brother.
-Grandfather.
Grandfather.
Are my eyes okay?
Grandfather can cough now.
May your life be full of laughter.
May everyone be rich.
What's under the turtle?
-Do you want to know?
-Yes.
Flip it to see.
Please flip it back to prank the next one.
Song, we have a problem.
Song, is that turtle
going to be all right?
We shouldn't be worried about the turtle.
Worry who's going to be next!
What's under the turtle?
If you want to know, then find out.
Okay, Ma.
Brother Somkiat.
What's wrong with the jar?
It broke.
The car broke down, no brake.
I'll check.
You said no brake.
I see the brake here.
I guess it came back.
But it likes to go away.
Brother, if this pole had some basil,
it'd be so delicious.
The pole is not food!
Mother...
That's enough.
Your mother won't come here again.
Praya Chatrathan
It's like a plane taking off.
Praya... is that right?
Praya Chatrathan doesn't bully
Break the ant nest to give...
Like the plane landing, right?
-Sure, go ahead
-No, no.
-Okay.
-Yes.
-Teach him some.
-Have...
-Patience.
-Say it.
-Patience Have.
If you want to take a stab at lottery,
why don't you start with yourself?
With myself. Brother.
Kamlah doesn't dare.
-Then try with your husband.
-Is that so?
-Hey.
What?
Take a stab at the lottery with
your husband, not stab your husband!
-Help him.
-I'll be damned.
-A foreigner was stabbed.
-Oh.
Translated by: Narisara Sirimongkol