Tell me more about
your family's situation.
Is this your mother?
Yes, she was in good health back then.
And now, she's your burden?
Life is hard here.
You're always burdened by something.
I'm used to it.
However…
I'm afraid the illness is still there.
It won't go away.
I'm worried for my child.
Why do you think
it will affect your child?
Sleep paralysis makes
your mother a dangerous person?
Come here.
Sleep paralysis affects
millions of people.
There is a state of wakefulness
that has not been explained.
This happens when our mind is awake
but our body is still in deep sleep.
In many cases, one may not distinguish
between reality and nightmares.
THE ANCESTRAL
This will be a long trip.
I don't know when we will be back.
Do they have bubble tea there?
Yen, why don't you close the blinds?
It's too bright.
I'm afraid of the dark.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Are you okay?
She's at it again?
Probably another nightmare.
Remember what I said?
Take a deep breath in.
Breathe out slowly.
Do it slowly.
Help your sister.
Such a long drive.
I'm tired. You girls would be too.
Wake up! It's our ancestral home.
Here you go.
Hey! Are you abandoning me?
Dad!
Let me take care of it.
That's okay.
Go stand in the shade, Princess. I got it.
Sis!
-Sis?
-What?
When do you think
we'll be out of this place?
No clue.
But we'll have friends at the new school.
That sucks.
Let's go see the rooms.
You can pick whichever room you want.
Your choice.
But the biggest one is mine. Okay?
Smartass!
Smartass?
Don't they say,
"You gotta be the smartest
to be a princess?"
-Whatever!
-Go to your room and sleep.
Sis! Let's check this one out.
Yen! Join me.
-Okay.
-Go!
Eat your food!
Bubble tea?
Whatever.
It's so dry.
-Sis!
-Be careful!
Let me see.
Is it a doll house?
Yeah. Isn't it pretty?
So ugly!
Don't be annoying! Do you want a spanking?
How can you do it in this darkness?
You ask too many questions.
We'll probably get power tomorrow.
-I'll do the chimney.
-No. Let me show you.
Cut little pieces like this
to make the windows.
Listen.
Tomorrow you can pay me
with a bubble tea, okay?
-Sure, if they have that here.
-Yeah.
Don't forget.
Is this okay?
Yen!
I'm sorry.
It's because your house is weak.
Just like this house.
You're so annoying.
Hey, girls!
Guess what I found.
Attack!
Tickle!
I'll get you.
-Your back is hurting, isn't it?
-No. Not at all.
Why are you hiding things from me?
I'm not.
Let me give you a massage.
What? Do you know how?
You're so skinny.
How are you gonna massage me?
I'm not skinny. These arms are strong.
This is strong?
I'm a pro.
She's lying. How would she know?
I agree with your sister.
Good things come in small packages.
Okay, since you're begging,
I'll give you a chance.
-Show me what you got.
-When did I beg you?
You've been begging.
Okay, do your best.
Wait.
-Come on, Dad.
-Okay.
I'm ready.
-Here I come!
-Okay.
What is this?
This is torture, not a massage!
Are you kidding me?
Is that you, Yen?
It's the boogeyman.
Go to sleep!
Damn you! So stubborn!
Yen!
Wake up! Wake up!
Wake up! Dad!
Yen!
-Are you okay?
-Get off me!
Yen!
-It's me!
-Let me go!
Yen! It's me.
Dad!
What happened?
-Is she sleepwalking again?
-Yes.
It's okay. I'm here, it's all right.
Inhale, exhale.
That's right! Good!
Okay, let's go.
It's okay.
It's okay. I'll take her inside.
She'll be okay.
I'm here, it's all right.
Her heart…
is beating so fast.
That's the reason why we have to
take care of her.
But why does she sleepwalk?
She has nightmares
due to prolonged stress.
She wasn't like this before.
I don't know
how to explain this to you girls.
But I think
if we'd stayed in our old house,
she'd have gotten worse.
I think being there won't do her any good.
I know.
Honestly,
I feel bad dragging you two through this.
You girls should be going to school,
making friends…
Rather than coming here with me.
But that's life.
There's just the three of us now.
We have to take care of each other.
You're the big sister,
you have to be strong for her.
I was also thinking
that we shouldn't live there anymore.
I couldn't forget about Mom.
I know.
I know you miss her.
Let's go to bed.
Yen!
You were sleepwalking last night.
Did you know where you were standing?
Where?
In the altar room.
Hey.
Last night I dreamt of Mom again.
Of her dying?
It's just a dream. It's not real.
Don't be scared.
But it feels so real to me.
Dreams are like that.
Besides, she died at the hospital.
Sis.
When I dream about her dying,
I think there was
someone else in the room.
Was it dad?
We weren't there
when she died in the hospital.
No, not dad.
Who was it then?
I don't know.
But it looked like…
a ghost.
We got power. Feels good?
You girls stay home and help me tidy up.
There's still lots to do.
I'm going into town.
I'll be back in the afternoon.
Remember to be home for dinner.
Got it.
It's iPad time!
Hey! Help your sister. Don't be lazy.
Yes, sir.
It's so dusty, isn't it?
You're asking for trouble.
Keep watching zombie stuff,
and I bet you'll dream about them.
Is that you, Yen?
Yen?
Yen!
Yen! Stop messing around!
Come and get me.
Damn you!
Peekaboo!
This way!
I'm over here.
-Come and get me!
-Teasing me?
Over here.
Yen!
Come here!
-How dare you!
-You're a mess!
-Who were you running from?
-You.
Did you see her too?
Just you.
Quit joking around. I meant the old lady.
Yeah. I saw her.
But, who was she?
Where did she go?
She ran that way.
Disappeared.
-Let's go!
-Where?
What about the clothes?
Hey!
-Hello!
-Hi!
-Please come in.
-Yes.
Hey.
Did you find her?
See…
It's not just my imagination.
You saw her too, right?
I'm pretty, not crazy.
Carry on.
Hi, girls.
Kids. This is Ms. Hanh.
She will be your tutor.
Your dad has told me a lot about you.
Let me guess.
The taller one with the oval face is Yen.
And Linh has dimples when she smiles?
No, I'm Linh.
And I'm Yen.
Say hello, girls.
-Hello.
-Okay.
Study with your tutor.
I got somewhere to be.
-Let's do it!
-Okay.
Did you girls sleep well last night?
We're not familiar with the place yet.
I heard Yen has trouble sleeping?
Well…
Yen has nightmares.
Hello.
My name is Bubble Tea.
Let's be friends.
This is for you.
Thank you.
-Her name is Bubble Tea?
-Yeah.
It's so cute.
Is this your daughter's?
I'm not a mom yet.
This was a gift from my mother to me.
Whenever I held her, I slept well.
I rarely got nightmares.
Thank you.
How's everyone doing?
Studying well?
Of course.
You know what? You're so blessed
to have such sweet girls.
We were just talking
about Yen's nightmares.
Actually, your dad has told
me about Yen's situation.
But first of all,
I have a surprise for you both.
By the way,
I studied psychology at a university.
So you can talk to me
about anything you want.
Ms. Hanh has helped our family.
Especially with settling here.
Okay.
After you.
Here?
We are in our first room.
Can you guess whose room this is?
It's mine, isn't it?
That's correct.
It's so cute.
-Bubble Tea will have a friend now.
-Dad, you did all this yourself?
Look at the decorations.
There has to be a woman's touch.
Look.
I can barely iron my own shirt.
To be honest,
there is another surprise.
Let's open door number two.
Dad!
-When did you do all this for us?
-I wanted the best for you two.
Have you seen my room?
It looks like a pig pen.
I also prepared some craft materials.
I hope you like them.
Thank you. Thank you, Dad.
Let's talk more tomorrow.
I'll get going.
Goodbye.
This comes with a photo.
Girls, I'll go out for a bit.
I might be home late.
When you're done cleaning up,
take care of her.
Because you're bad.
There's a crazy girl!
Yen!
It's me, Yen!
-Wait.
-Stand back.
Don't wake her.
We have to let her wake up by herself.
If we wake her too suddenly,
she might have a panic attack.
It could even be fatal.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm right here. It's okay.
Calm down. I'm here.
Listen to me.
Breathe in deeply and breathe out.
Breathe in deeply, that's right.
Deep breath in. Breathe out.
I'm here. It's okay.
Linh.
I love you girls very much.
I can't always be here for you.
You're the big sister.
You know how hard it is, right?
Being a woman
is not as easy as it seems.
Aside from being a wife
and a mother,
you have to be a good cook,
and a responsible and dutiful person.
But that's not all.
Linh.
When you grow up...
if you love anything...
want anything,
you have to pursue it.
Don't wait.
Life is short.
Let's just keep it up for now.
Yen still remembers those terrible things.
And Yen keeps making up horror stories.
That smells so good.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
Sit down, honey.
This looks so good. You're so talented.
Everything you have remembered
about your mother are all just nightmares.
They are not real.
You should forget it all.
Your mother's sudden death
has traumatized you into bad memories.
Your present life is what's real.
Dad!
What's wrong?
Last night…
I saw something…
I mean...
I felt like there was
someone in our house.
Are you okay?
Why do you look so tense?
I saw someone in Yen's room.
Are you sure?
You have to believe me. I saw a shadow…
or someone sitting on top of Yen.
Listen to me.
What if your sister hears you
talking nonsense like this?
It will scare her.
You are her big sister, right?
Maybe I was tired.
But, Dad,
what is Ms. Hanh doing here?
What do you mean by asking me that?
Because…
she seems to know a lot about Yen.
Like she's a professional.
Of course. She studied psychology.
Okay.
Hey.
You couldn't sleep last night?
Yeah.
I must have been tired and seeing things.
Let me watch something else, please.
I'm so bored.
Sis…
Hello! Check!
One. Two. Three. Four. Check.
Wanna sing with me?
Times are tough.
I gotta have a second career.
What?
Are you any good to challenge me?
Are you kidding?
I used to be a singer back then.
So?
Come on.
I'm a pretty good singer. Watch me!
SONG: "TIEN DUA" - MALE TONE
Dad!
-This song is boring. Pick another one.
-I think it's good.
-I'm good, right?
-Let me pick.
Okay, your choice.
What? This song?
-I can't do this song.
-Yes, you can.
Just look at the lyrics.
Sing!
What? Okay.
Dance too.
Yen…
Yen.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I couldn't move.
It was just a bad dream.
I'm here. It's okay.
I…
saw…
the devil…
And…
It was Miss Hanh.
I think your situation is getting worse.
You're too stressed out
and imagining things.
I'm afraid it can be dangerous.
But don't worry.
I can treat you with a new approach.
We will succeed this time.
This is due to your bad past memories.
It's not real.
Listen to her.
Clearly I…
I saw…
the devil.
Calm down. Look at me.
Listen to me.
There are no such things as ghosts.
If you think of them all day,
you will dream
about them at night, understand?
Why does she keep getting worse?
I think, for now,
Yen has to practice replacing bad memories
with good ones from the present.
This will work for sure.
But it hurts me.
It was strong.
Are you hurt anywhere else?
Did you fall down somewhere?
I don't know.
There are cases
where people can hurt themselves
in an attempt to wake up.
I'll take her outside.
Wait…
Watch her.
Hurry up.
-Sis!
-What?
Do you think Hanh will soon be our mother?
What are you talking about?
Don't you think she's suspicious?
Her and dad.
What is suspicious?
She's smart.
Very smart.
You're such a gossip!
What did you hear earlier?
-You're annoying.
-Linh!
Yes?
If there's anything I can do,
I'm here for you.
I'm here to help you girls.
Okay.
I know this is a difficult time
for you both.
Don't misunderstand us.
Your dad always wants
what is best for the both of you.
Let's all try our best.
Yeah!
I understand. We need to go.
I gotta go.
It's so beautiful here.
This is far enough.
Can't see our house from here. Get down.
What are we going to do here?
Let's go home.
Are you kidding me?
-Fine, stay if you want.
-Let me get on.
Why aren't we staying?
-You're weird.
-I haven't been out in a long time.
Get down.
Hurry up.
I don't know what they're doing in there.
No clue.
Can you see anything?
Yes.
Not a thing.
Probably just playing house.
No big deal.
Why would adults play house?
Then what do adults play?
Get up here.
Where?
Be careful.
Hurry up.
No, it's scary.
-Come on, you have to try.
-No. I'm too weak.
You always call me skinny.
Don't you remember?
Listen to me, Yen.
You have to trust me.
You have to believe you can do it.
I got you.
Come here.
Are you sure?
Protect me.
-Slowly.
-Okay.
Help me!
Almost.
Be careful!
I know.
Landed safely.
See?
I told you.
There's something going on.
Can he see us?
-Cover up.
-Shut up.
Is dad crying?
Yeah, he is crying.
Yen! Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
Yen!
Yen! Yen!
What happened?
-Yen fell down.
-What?
Yen!
-Yen!
Are you hurt?
Why don't you answer me?
What were you girls doing?
What did you do to make her fall?
-Are you okay?
-I trusted you.
You have to protect her.
Why did you let her fall?
Why aren't you answering me?
Did I kill her?
What did you just say?
I killed her.
What did you say?
-What kind of sister are you?
-Thanh!
You're scaring her.
It's not your fault. Listen to me.
Yen will be okay.
It's not your fault.
Let's go find someone to help her.
Let's go. She'll be okay.
It's not your fault.
Yen! Can you hear me?
It's too deep.
Come to this side.
It's not your fault.
We will find her.
She'll be okay.
Okay?
Sis!
Where am I?
It stinks down here!
Who's there?
Let me go!
Let go of me!
You'll fall asleep if you close your eyes.
I want to stay awake.
I don't want to sleep.
I can't sleep.
They'll get you!
Hey, what are you doing here?
Your children cannot know about this.
We have to find a way to protect them.
I think you and I have to stay calm.
We will find a way to hide this
without them ever knowing.
Yen!
Yen, come here.
Come here.
Come to me.
This is only a nightmare.
You are dreaming.
This is not real.
It's only a dream.
This is a nightmare.
You're dreaming.
I think she's still conscious.
Yen.
She's okay.
She'll feel better after a nap.
I'm sorry.
Dad, what is this place anyway?
Linh,
I want to show you something.
The truth is this is a facility
specializing in mental illness.
And my specialty
is studying sleep paralysis
and its effects on the human psyche.
So this is a nut house?
No, it's not.
It's a research center.
So our house is not our home?
It's part of a section
in this research center.
Hanh has been helping me all this time.
I'm sorry I couldn't spend
more time with you and Yen.
I asked her to help you two
overcome the pain of losing your mother.
Your family has a history
of sleep paralysis.
You mother had it,
so both of you would have it too.
Your father is a special case.
And I think Yen's is worse
because of your father.
We had to erase Yen's negative memories.
If a person cannot overcome
their traumatic memories,
their dreams will become nightmares
and turn into hallucinations.
A sleep paralysis patient
will feel like a demon's
pressing on their chest,
holding them down,
stopping them from moving.
It gets stronger,
heavier, making the person feel paralyzed.
Their whole body will tense up.
It can lead to suffocation and even…
sudden death.
Who are the strangers in our house?
I'm sorry.
They are patients here,
who got lost and ended up in the yard.
A long time ago, this was a local port.
After years of renovating, it became
the research center as you see now.
Underground are the remains of this port,
creating a tunnel
between the hospital and your house.
Those patients ended up in the house
through an opening
in the hospital's warehouse.
But don't worry.
They are harmless. They need our sympathy.
-You're awake?
-How do you feel?
How are you?
I saw Ms. Hanh.
When mom died.
Linh! Linh!
Listen to me.
Why did you lie to me?
Your mom was very ill.
You said she died of cancer.
I don't trust you anymore.
Why did you have to treat her?
Listen to me.
She was depressed,
and anxiety attacks kept her up at night.
It took over her mind,
making her lock herself up all day.
It was a hard time for us.
Don't you understand?
Of course I do.
You didn't think I felt the sadness?
That's why
I needed a doctor.
She was getting worse.
With nightmares and sleep paralysis.
I didn't know what to do.
I was terrified.
She couldn't control herself.
She didn't know who she was.
-And then she…
-Committed suicide.
Yen saw everything.
Why am I only hearing about it now?
Linh. I'm sorry. I couldn't save your mom.
But now, I've promised myself
that I'll do whatever it takes
to not let Yen hurt again.
You have to understand that
when she died, you weren't there.
I didn't know how to explain.
I needed time.
I needed time to face the truth
and to find a good time to let you know.
Is that all?
That's why you put us in this nut house?
For what?
So Hanh can brainwash Yen?
It's not like that.
It's the only way to save her.
You have to listen to me.
How dare you?
And you.
You ruined our family.
Linh! Linh!
Thanh.
Give her space.
Don't worry! I can take care of it.
I can take care of it.
I can't find it.
Babe, you look beautiful in that dress.
We don't take photos together often.
I don't see our stuff.
Hurry up.
Are you not wearing your ring?
Where's your ring?
We will stay here…
This…
is our family.
We won't go anywhere.
Your mom wants us to be here.
Our family will stay here.
Are you okay?
You saw it too, didn't you?
It's okay.
I'm here.
I'll always be with you.
I won't leave you.
Yen!
I think I saw it…
It's the devil himself.
But it was dad…
Dad!
What are you doing here?
We won't stay here anymore.
Let's get out of here.
What's wrong? Tell me.
There are demons in this house.
I'm scared.
Let's go back to where we were.
Go inside.
I really hate this place.
I don't want Yen to stay here.
We must go back to the city.
I don't care what you think.
Where did you learn to talk like that?
You have no respect for me?
Whatever it is, it takes time.
You think moving here was easy?
You have to be patient.
What about you?
You are the big sister,
you have to set an example.
Instead you're scaring her
with your nonsense.
Do you think that's right?
Even I get nightmares.
Terrible things have happened
and you don't trust me.
And it's all your fault.
After everything I've done,
everything I've sacrificed,
you say it's my fault?
Because of me?
What did I do wrong?
You are always forcing us with Ms. Hanh.
She's replacing mom, isn't she?
Did you forget mom?
It's your fault mom died.
Dad! Let her go.
Let her go, please!
Dad!
She's my sister. Let go of her!
She's my sister.
Dad!
Please.
Let go of her.
She's my sister.
Sis! What do you think dad's
been doing up there all day?
Yen, come here.
Listen.
If anything happens, you have to run.
What about you?
I'll be right beside you.
We're really doing this?
Something's wrong with dad.
He's not the same anymore.
I'm not staying here.
But…
I'm scared.
What are you scared of?
I don't know.
Sometimes, dad really scares me.
You look gangster.
Yen.
You have to toughen up.
I need you.
We're a team.
Okay?
Sis?
Ms. Hanh is probably up there with dad.
Let's go back.
-Let's go to our room.
-No one's here.
Take this.
Back off.
Wait here.
Sis!
Dad, what are you doing?
I'm so happy today.
Why are you happy?
Your mom…
What about her?
I miss your mother.
But she died.
Don't say that.
I've spoken to her.
Hanh helped me talk to her.
We will be together again.
We will be happy.
I want us all to live here.
We will be here with mom.
Always beside her.
Wake up, Dad.
There.
That's your mother.
Can't you see?
-Dad.
-Babe.
Answer your daughter.
Dad!
Look at me!
Dad, wake up!
Mom is not here.
She died a year ago.
There's only Yen and I.
We shouldn't stay here.
Let's go back to the city.
Stop it.
Your mom is not dead.
You have to trust me.
Babe!
Why don't you tell her?
Tell her.
Talk to her.
I miss her.
Dad!
Sis!
Yen!
Where are you, Yen?
-Ms. Hanh!
-Linh!
What happened?
Dad and Yen disappeared.
It's okay. I'm here.
Tell me. What happened?
Dad took Yen away.
I'm so scared. He's different.
What do we do now? I can't find them.
Follow me.
Where are you?
Thanh.
-Thanh!
-No way.
Thanh. It's me. Where is Yen?
Thanh!
What did you do to her? Tell me.
Did you hurt her?
-Where is Yen? Is she okay?
-Babe.
-Tell me. Did you hurt her?
-I'm up here.
-You hurt her, didn't you?
-I heard you.
I can hear you.
-Thanh!
-I'm coming!
Thanh!
Do you see me now?
I can see you well.
-Listen to me.
-I'm here.
-I know you're here.
-Thanh!
Don't you see me?
Thanh! Don't let it take over you!
-Thanh!
-I know you're here.
-It's not real. Don't be like that.
-I can feel you.
-Don't let it take over you, Thanh!
I'm here.
I know you're here.
I'm close to you.
I can feel you.
Thanh!
Look at me.
Are you looking for your wife?
I can feel you.
I'm here.
I'm right here.
Are you looking for me?
I'm here with you, honey.
I need you to focus here.
I'll count from one to five.
You'll go to sleep.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Thanh!
I came for you.
I knew you were here.
I miss you so much.
Are you tired?
I am.
I'm exhausted.
I'm not a good husband
or a good father.
I failed.
It's my fault.
I need you now.
I only need you.
From now on,
you don't have to worry anymore.
I'm their mother.
Can you bring them to me?
Can you?
I knew you were here.
Yen!
Dad!
Wake up!
You have to fight it.
Don't hurt Yen.
Back off.
Don't do what it wants.
It's not real.
Yen has to be with mom.
No.
She needs you and me.
There's only one way.
This is the only way.
Dad.
I know you can do it. Fight it.
You don't have to do this.
Give her to me.
I have to save my child.
Dad! You already saved us.
We're a family.
You're my father.
Mom died.
We can't lose you too.
We need you.
I need you.
-Give Yen to me.
-I'll kill her if you come near.
I was wrong.
I couldn't keep your mother.
Fix it then.
Give her to me.
Our family will be one again.
It's the truth.
Mom?
We'll be together again.
Dad! Mom died.
She's not here.
She killed herself
because she wasn't happy.
It wasn't your fault that she was sick.
It's not anyone's fault.
Let her rest in peace.
Let me take her.
What's wrong?
What do you want?
Your child.
Leave my child alone.
If you want to take a life, take mine.
Take my soul.
Don't hurt them.
They're innocent.
Dad, look at me.
Where are you?
Come and face me!
Don't hurt my children.
I want her life.
Dad!
I have to save you two.
Come and face me!
Come here!
Dad!
Are you ready, Yen?
Are you okay?
I'm okay. Let's go.
Yeah, we're late.
Hurry up!
Dad's cooking.
Just a moment. Food is almost ready.
You are actually cooking?
Of course.
Just a moment.
It's my favorite. Not sure if it's edible.
Why wouldn't it be?
When it's too delicious,
don't come crawling back
asking me to cook for you everyday.
Looks nice. But will it be
as good as mom's cooking?
I promise, I'll make her proud.
It's almost ready.
Just a bit more.
Great! Okay, go sit over there.
-Thank you, Dad.
-Okay.
They'll get you when you're asleep.
Why does it still hurt?
It strangles me!
I can't sleep.
Can you help me, please?