…The person I thought would take my side
and protect me
turn against me like that.
I'm so sorry.
Mutual understanding
requires an open mind.
When did you get so smart?
Do you like it?
I like it.
What happened to you in the past
made you lose faith in love,
but I'm going to show you
how serious I am about you.
-Mom!
-Mrs. Na.
-Dress up tomorrow.
-Yes?
We are going shopping tomorrow.
Nut.
This is Mr. Nobu.
He wants to buy your show
and broadcast it in Japan.
Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you, too.
I am from Tokyo. My name is Nobu.
Please be kind to me.
This is Mr. Yoshi.
He is an entertainment reporter.
He's here to interview you.
Nice to meet you.
-Mr. Nobu.
-Yes?
We will go and sign
the contract in my office.
And leave Nut and Mr. Yoshi here
for the interview.
-Mr. Nobu.
-Yes?
Want some Japanese sake?
I love sake.
-Rice whiskey?
-Whiskey.
Mrs. Na,
Nut has not read it yet.
He is probably busy.
That’s all right.
We can go by ourselves.
How about these?
They're a bit bright.
People can see them from miles away.
How about some plain ones?
-Excuse me.
-Yes.
Do you have other colors?
We do. Please wait a moment.
Do they fit well?
They are a little tight.
-Miss.
-Yes?
Do you have a bigger size?
Of course. One moment please.
I will take a look over there.
Okay.
Are they comfy?
Try walking in them.
Anything you like?
They are all pretty. I can't pick one.
Why don't we let Nut pick one for you?
Shall we?
Nut.
Can you pick something for your mom?
I told him
that your phone is broken.
What about this one?
Would it suit Mom?
It looks good.
We should get the right color.
I think she would like a pink one.
Thank you, son.
Let's go.
What color would you like?
The one that best suits my mom.
Then I recommend this shade.
It should suit you.
Do you like it?
How much is it?
It is 599 baht.
I stay home most of the time,
so I don't wear much makeup.
You can look pretty at home too.
Are they both your sons?
They're so handsome.
Yes.
He is my son.
He is also my son.
The three of us are a family.
What about those two? Are they yours too?
They've been looking over here.
Song.
Why are you following me?
Who followed you?
I was passing by and got a little curious.
All this time, I have never seen you
go out with your mother.
So I was wondering
what has gotten into you today.
Nothing much.
I just brought my mom to the mall.
I am glad you are happy.
I've been waiting for this day.
What about you?
Why is he with you?
You and he…
Well, I…
What about us?
Well?
So?
This kid…
is not with me.
It's me…
who is here with him.
So, are you two together?
Yes, as you can see.
You said you didn't like younger guys.
Did I?
When was that? I can't recall.
Well done.
I will reward you with something later.
You are the sweetest.
Why aren’t we ordering something?
I'm hungry.
Go for it, Tofu. Tell me what you want.
Today, I am so happy
that I will treat you.
-You said it.
-Of course.
I'll order, then.
Alright. Go ahead.
-I want this one.
-This one?
-And this.
-And this?
-This one and this one.
-Those two?
This one and this one. I want all of them.
-Good job.
-All… all of them?
Yes.
You want all of them?
Are you sure?
-You said it was a treat.
-Really?
-You said you would pay.
-I will.
Eat what you like and I'll swipe my card.
Hurry up and grow.
There is a kid waiting to eat you.
You're in a good mood today.
You went on a date, right?
I saw Song earlier.
I'm in a good mood because of Nut.
I saw Nut. He took
his mom and Tofu shopping.
Nut made up with his mom.
Really?
A lot of time was wasted though.
What I mean is…
had they reconciled earlier,
they would have spent
much more time together, right?
You too, Gen.
Don’t make love difficult.
You never know what is going to happen.
Be good to each other,
so you don’t regret it later.
You know me.
You are my son after all.
Of course, I know you.
Thank you so much.
I had a great time today, son.
This has made becoming human worthwhile.
At the very least,
I get to help in healing the rift
between Nut and his mom.
It made me realize
that whether you are a mother or a child,
everyone makes mistakes.
I’m going, Mom.
What about…
my lunchbox?
I'm going.
All right.
By accepting each other’s flaws
with love and understanding,
only then can the void be filled.
Seeing this
has been worth it,
even if
I might be gone forever one day.
You're here early, Gen.
You are late.
Hey, Gen. Let go.
You're suddenly so possessive.
-Won't you share anymore?
-No.
It's a good thing Prib isn't here.
Or else she would ask you for some.
You are right.
Where is my niece?
Kuenchai.
Why are you barking?
Prib?
I need to talk to you.
Do you know Tatarn?
Do you know him too?
Did Nut tell you about him?
Nut told me about his ex.
He never told me the name.
I found out his name is Tatarn.
You are friends with him on Facebook.
Can you take me to see him?
I have to ask him something.
I would like to,
but Tarn is in a coma and has not been
responsive for months now.
I really shouldn’t tell you this
as it might be hard for you.
But this is a really important matter.
I want Nut to visit Tarn.
A miracle could happen.
Even if it doesn't,
at least,
Tarn gets to see Nut one last time.
Can you help me just this once?
I've heard people say
that happiness often doesn’t last.
It is actually my secret,
but I will tell you about it.
Before I was into Nut,
I used to like Tarn.
It's a small world sometimes, Tofu.
Two people I liked used to be in love.
And that’s also why I want to help Tarn.
That's why Tarn asked you
to draw him with Nut.
He never mentioned Nut
in that page or on Facebook,
but I can tell
from all those photos and messages
that he wanted Nut to know.
Tarn still loves Nut, doesn't he?
I don’t know about that.
All I know is that
Tarn never wanted to trouble Nut.
Tarn told me
that he wanted Nut to be happy.
He wants him to do the job he loves
and be surrounded by good people.
And what happened between them
should just be left as a happy memory.
Isn’t that obvious?
If he is still in love with Nut,
why didn’t he come back for him?
I know why.
What did you just say?
Well,
you were wondering
why they didn’t get back together.
I think the guy is not sure
if the girl wants him back.
Though they used to love each other
and they broke up out of necessity,
no one stays the same forever.
Now that the girl has feelings
for that other guy,
the guy who has been waiting
is now afraid to act.
Well…
How do you think it will end?
Just wait and see.
TATARN KLAIANANT
TATARN KLAIANANT, AN ARTIST WHOSE ART
VOICES CONCERNS TO THE SOCIETY
UNCOVER TATARN KLAIANANT,
A YOUNGBLOOD ARTIST AND ENVIRONMENTALIST
SPECIAL INTERVIEW WITH TATARN KLAIANANT
AN AWARD-WINNING ADVERTISER AND ACTIVIST
TATARN KLAIANANT AND HIS FAMOUS WORKS
ENTHUSIASTIC ADVERTISER, TATARN KLAIANANT
The world is not fair.
Why is he so good at everything?
He is skillful,
cool,
and probably rich.
If only he were here
instead of a useless amnesiac like me…
What do you think?
Does it still smell good?
-It smells so good, Tarn.
-Of course.
Try some.
-How is it?
-Amazing.
How sweet. Now, get back to work.
If Nut had stayed with him,
he might have been happier
than he is with me.
Tofu.
Can you smell something burning?
Tofu!
You're miles away. It's burnt.
Oh, gosh.
Hey.
Jeez!
How am I supposed to eat that?
Don't eat it if you don’t want to.
I thought you wanted fried pork,
so I made some.
If it's that bad,
then get someone else to cook for you.
I will give this to Kuenchai.
Kuenchai, come here.
Here.
Eat it.
What is it, boys?
It's nothing, Mrs. Na.
I burnt the fried pork.
I’m heading to the market.
I get Nut now, Kuenchai.
I didn’t mean to be unreasonable.
I couldn't help it.
I lost, Kuenchai.
I couldn't compete with him.
Maybe…
I should just tell him.
Tell me what?
I thought you went to the market.
I didn't make it that far.
What did you want to tell me?
I was going to say…
I’m sorry.
I don’t know what's up with me.
I know.
How did you know?
Because I’m the best.
I’m your boyfriend,
so I know what you are thinking.
Don’t make that face.
People will say I'm picking on a kid.
Stop overthinking.
I don’t know if I did something that made
you feel insecure.
I will tell you this one more time.
You are you,
and I love that about you.
I didn’t want to feel this way.
I just can’t help it.
Let me stay like this a bit longer.
What’s the matter with you, Tofu?
If I’m unreasonable like this again,
will you still love me?
I’m like that all the time,
and you still love me.
What if…
you meet someone better than me,
someone you are happier with,
and isn't a burden like me?
Will you leave me for him?
All right.
Even if you always burn the pork,
I won’t leave you.
Are you satisfied?
I promise
that I won’t give you cancer.
I will fry the pork beautifully next time.
I'll make it like
how you used to have it.
When did I ever tell you
that the fried pork I used to eat
was so good?
Where did you get this from?
Why do you ask? Do you want some?
I only asked where you got it,
so that I won’t eat there.
I made it myself.
It might not look great,
but it tastes amazing.
Want to try it?
Yuck.
Try it. I put a lot of effort into it.
Here.
How is it?
Delicious, right?
Hey,
it's great.
If you want more,
then eat with me every day.
I live alone.
How about I make you Thai barbecue
over at my condo?
It looked…
It looked just like the stuff you made.
It was all in your head
and you blamed me for it.
Don’t get all upset
about me remembering it.
It was just one of the first times
we ate together. That's all.
Do you remember
the first time we ate together?
Are you looking for something
to argue about, Tofu?
Stop comparing yourself with someone else.
Be confident in yourself.
And trust me.
You said you wanted me
to be patient with you.
You should be patient with me too.
I promise
that I won’t be like this…
too often.
Tofu.
THE LITTLE PRINCE
Where have you been?
Did you get the pork?
I’m sorry I made you worry.
Also, I didn’t get any pork.
That’s fine.
Never mind. Nhong brought
some stir-fried rice noodles he made.
I'll set the table.
Let me help you.
I'll pour the water.
THE LITTLE PRINCE
Is your work done?
You're checking holiday spots.
Do you want me to only work
and ignore Mom and you?
Would you like that?
No.
Don’t tell me
that you're taking us on holiday.
Yes.
I saw Mom reading The Little Prince
over and over.
She might want to travel like he did.
You guys will go out of your minds
just staying at home.
Let's take a trip and relax.
This time,
we'll go as a family.
We can go as a couple next time.
Deal.
Help me pick a place.
Where should I take Mom?
We haven't been anywhere together
for ages.
Well…
How about we ask your mom?
-Do you think so?
-Yes.
I don't mind. You decide.
See? I told you.
You are her son.
Of course, you know what she thinks.
If Mom won’t choose,
then I'll let you choose.
Where shall we go?
I can choose?
I want to go to Chiang Mai.
What is it, Kuenchai?
Don't give me that look.
You don’t get to go.
Stay home.
TOFU: NUT, MRS. NA AND I
ARE GOING TO CHIANG MAI.
PRIBPREE: SORRY I GAVE YOU A HARD TIME,
TOFU. I WAS BEING SELFISH, WASN'T I?
TOFU: EVERYONE CAN BE SELFISH,
ME INCLUDED.
I didn't promise Prib anything.
Maybe not,
but you're dragging Nut to Chiang Mai.
I want to see if you can stand
not telling Nut about it.
I know this is important.
It is a matter of life and death,
but I don’t want to tell him about it.
I’m afraid.
Humans need to be
a little selfish sometimes
in order to avoid getting hurt too badly.
I don’t want to be that kind of human.
They are so fearful, dishonest,
envious,
and even jealous.
That is because you are in love.
You'll learn more about life as you grow.
I know Nut
will always be there to help you.
Tofu.
Why aren't you packing?
We’re leaving tomorrow.
Here.
What’s wrong?
I'm tired.
Well…
This trip is kind of sudden.
Are you sure Juea won't mind?
Why would he mind?
I worked day and night
to finish the script.
He has a lot to work on.
What about Gen?
Can you go pack now?
I can’t. I’m exhausted.
Do you feel better now?
Nut is going to Chiang Mai.
Right.
He said he is taking his family on a trip.
-I see.
-So what?
I’m envious.
I haven’t taken a vacation in ages.
Then take the vacation now.
And I'm going with you.
Hey.
Here to deliver food?
No.
I’m here to see my boyfriend.
I'm just kidding.
I’m here to pick up my check.
What are you talking about?
Well, Nut is going to Chiang Mai.
Gen wants to go too,
so I’m going to take him there.
We can go and see my dad too.
Who said I’m going?
I’m going.
Who's that?
Hello?
Tofu.
What's taking you so long?
You seem more excited than me.
You talk too much.
Go pack your suitcase.
Go.
Is anyone there?
Keep an eye on the house for us.
-Okay.
-Don't worry. We'll tend to your house.
If something happens, give me a call.
Thank you so much.
No problem. Have a good trip.
I hope you all have a great time.
Okay.
Where is Kuenchai?
Is he going too?
-Hey.
He's in the car.
Kuenchai.
He probably wants to go.
-There he is.
-You can't go. Come here.
There he is.
-Kuenchai.
Hey.
Kuenchai. Come here, boy.
Sit.
Be a good boy, all right?
I’ll be back soon. Okay?
Be good.
Don't be a bad boy.
-Let's go.
-Kuenchai.
-Nhong.
-Sorry to bother you.
-Come here.
-Kuenchai, sit.
Here, turn that way.
I’m sorry we can’t take you with us.
I'll buy you some treats, okay?
Have fun.
Shall we go?
Let’s go.
Thanks for your help. Take care.
-Goodbye.
-Have a safe trip.
-Thank you.
-Bye, Kuenchai.
-Bye.
-Bye. Be good.
-Wave goodbye.
-Bye.
It’s beautiful.
Oh, wow.
Nut.
What's up, bro?
-Hello.
How was the drive? Are you tired?
Why are you so hyper?
Are you tired, Mrs. Na?
Just a little.
Well, well…
You don’t look like someone
who has just traveled for ten hours.
I’m envious.
I want to take a road trip too.
-I'm going to check in.
-All right.
Mom, Tofu, let’s go.
-Do you need me?
-Of course. We need your ID card.
Coming by plane is better.
Your food delivery motorbike
is not a big bike.
Even if it were, I wouldn't ride with you.
You might get weird and take orders
along the way.
I could drive your car here.
Why trouble yourself driving?
Just enjoy the trip, all right?
We get it. You care about Song.
Are we done?
I’m sick of this lovey-dovey vibe.
That's harsh.
You could've told me so.
-I'm so touched.
-What are you doing?
There are people here.
Will you spend the night
at my dad's place with me?
So Prib can relax by herself. All right?
Your dad might have a heart attack.
He doesn’t know about us.
All done.
I’m too tired to go anywhere today.
Let’s split up.
See you tomorrow.
Let's go.
Please let me be with Nut.
I wish that he will love me forever.
-I'll take a picture for you.
-Nut.
That's a great picture.
Can we go inside?
Song. Come here.
Your mom looks so happy.
She's a history teacher after all.
When I was little,
she used to read me stories.
When we had finished them all,
she then told me stories
about Thai history and foreign history.
How nice.
I want to hear them too.
Can you tell me some stories at bedtime?
Go ask my mother.
I don’t like history like she does.
Why not?
History depends on who's writing it.
It's what you choose to believe.
We like to believe in what we agree with.
A lot of people use belief as a weapon
to hurt those who think differently.
Some use it as a tool hiding the truth
to serve their purpose.
The same way my parents used to tell me
that being who I am is a sin.
When I grew up,
I realized
that there are other beliefs
that no one else had told me…
except…
Tatarn, right?
Yes.
He was the one who made me understand
that being gay isn't a disease.
It's not down to bad karma,
or an emotional disorder.
And it's not a joke.
Being gay
doesn't mean we love every one
of the same gender.
We can love someone
as sincerely as anyone else.
That’s why I became a writer.
I want to use my stories as a weapon
and erase those wrong beliefs.
You really are your mother’s son.
She likes to tell stories.
You also have something to tell.
Perhaps
her history lessons
motivated you to become a writer.
I’m sorry, Nut.
I got carried away walking around.
Where are we going next?
Where do you want to go?
It's up to you.
You want me to decide?
Oh, wow.
You wanted to come here?
I never thought I would get to come here.
I never knew you would like
something so extreme.
I've always wanted to give it a try.
Smile!
Nut!
That was fun.
Are you all right, Tofu?
I'm fine.
Can we go somewhere less exciting next?
I knew it.
Nut has finally fulfilled his mom's dream.
If you want to go somewhere, just tell me.
I will take you there.
I’m glad I got
to take a trip with you before…
while I still can.
You are still healthy, Mrs. Na.
You still have enough time to travel
the world with Nut.
It’s just that he's probably too busy
to take you.
Wrong. I can't afford it.
Being a writer doesn't make you rich.
But actors like me are quite rich.
I can take you to travel the world
many times.
You are rich, are you? So rich?
I think,
for the next place,
let's go somewhere Tofu will like.
All right.
I know the perfect place.
How is this a place for Tofu?
Why? You don't think it suits him?
She probably wondered why it suits Tofu
better than her.
Gen, I was just curious.
Flowers don't have to be for girls only.
They can also go well with men.
Right, Mrs. Na?
That's right.
I remember wondering
why people associated flowers
with one gender.
When we give someone flowers,
no one tells us the gender of each flower
or who are they suitable for.
We give someone flowers because we know
their meaning
and the reason we give them to someone.
-Right?
-That's right.
Let's go.
I'm sick of the people around here.
Let's go over there.
-Did she mean me?
-Yes.
Nut.
Did you bring me here
for a particular reason?
Look there.
They are the same kind of orchid,
and yet they are different.
Each flower is different.
So are we.
We all have value.
There's no need to compare.
Each of us is a unique flower.
You are a special flower
that belongs to me.
Let's take some photos.
I'll take lots of it.
Okay.
One, two, three.
-Gen.
-What?
Do you want some flowers?
I will buy whatever you like.
Which one do you like?
Black-eyed Susan?
Black-eyed Song sounds better.
Let's just take more photos.
What are you doing, Tofu?
I'm choosing a photo.
Which one do you like better?
I'll post it on my Facebook.
Save it as a good memory.
Which ones?
This one and this one too.
I like this one.
This?
Yes.
I want to post it too.
Can you send me that photo?
Of course.
In that case,
I'll create a family group chat
and post the photos in there.
So you can save photos from there.
Yes, Juea.
Nut, I'm sorry.
I need you to revise the script.
I sent my comments to your email.
I need it by tonight.
Tonight?
Yes. I was kind enough to let you go.
I want it by tonight.
All right.
Juea is probably upset
that he has to shoot alone.
Maybe.
Well then, that's it for today.
We should head back now.
Nut can also get some work done.
Gen and I have to excuse ourselves.
We are going to have dinner with my dad.
I'm going to visit some more places.
I want to find a good spot to sketch.
I'll go with Prib then.
You have to work.
I won't be much help here.
Hey.
So you would rather go somewhere
than be with me?
Nut, a little time alone won't kill you.
All right, all right.
You can go.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Look after Prib as well.
I'm sure she'll be okay, though.
You didn't just want
to hang out with me, did you?
Tofu.
Are you okay?
I was a little overwhelmed.
I just feel a bit dizzy.
What happened to him?
He was attacked.
The police are investigating the case.
I think he was involved
in some conflict of interest.
He was a protest leader
in the Hollow Forest project.
Tofu.
I know you are confused right now.
I didn't come here to pressure you
for an answer.
I was just worried.
I turned your trip
that should be filled with joy into this.
It would be nice
if I could help you with something.
I understand.
I get it all,
but it still hurts.
Before this,
I had always wanted to meet Tatarn.
At the same time,
I didn't want to see him,
for fear that he might separate
Nut and me.
Now, I want him to wake up,
as he might hold the answer to my miracle.
But if he doesn't wake up,
I might be able to prolong my happiness.
I still don't know
what will happen to me though.
Tofu.
Do you still want to hang out?
I used to come here with Tarn.
We both like art.
It was around the time
he got back from Japan.
He was getting involved
in political activities.
He joined a workshop here.
The way I saw it, Tarn was a warm person.
But his paintings
were bursting with emotion.
His paintings showed two men
with satirical scenes about social
and political issues, the environment,
religion, faith, and even love.
He just took it all.
I asked about the inspiration
behind these paintings.
When something can't be said,
then let art speak for you.
Art is the most peaceful form
of expression.
Its voice is subtle
and you need to interpret it.
Yet it is a powerful way of communication.
Too bad.
Who would care about art
when their stomachs are empty?
That sounds depressing.
Right?
That's why Tarn and I studied art abroad.
But you guys came back to do art here.
That's because we're hopeful.
Especially, Tarn.
He wasn't just hopeful for art.
He was hopeful for everything.
He hoped for things
that are normal in other countries.
He didn't want to see our country
destroyed and held back anymore.
So he started the Hollow Forest,
something personal.
I just want to live a normal life
in a society where everything is normal.
Everyone is equal.
No matter your sexuality,
no one is seen as different.
I used to wonder
why he was so bold and true to himself.
Why was that?
It's because of his family, Tofu.
He told me that before.
He must have told Nut the same thing.
Can I ask you something?
How do you accept it so easily?
That I like boys?
Weren't you ever confused?
Everyone is.
I just knew myself early.
When I told my parents about it,
they even told me
that I didn't have to come out.
Even though I'm their child,
we are all human.
My mother also said
that gay
also means joyful.
Being gay is not wrong.
We can have fun in our lives like others.
Your parents are nice.
Yes.
My mother grew up abroad.
My father, though he worked
for his Chinese family,
later decided to start his own company.
So I had some freedom.
Unlike me.
In my household…
My parents would never understand.
You don't need people to understand you.
If telling them
means being uncomfortable
or causing problems,
then don't tell them.
If telling them about it makes you happy,
then tell them when you are ready.
If I can prove myself to them,
so that they accept me,
-then--
-Why?
Why should you struggle to be accepted
just because you are gay?
Do gay men have to be good-looking,
capable, and respectable
to be accepted?
Why can't they just accept us
as human beings?
You have nothing to prove.
You should just be yourself.
Live the life you want to live.
Got it?
You didn't say you would bring a friend.
He is not my friend.
I see. You're one of the film crew, right?
He looks older.
I guess he's not your age.
He is actually older than me.
But…
-Gen and I--
-Excuse me.
We're still waiting for our food.
Actually, Gen and I…
We are…
Oops!
How clumsy of me.
Excuse me. I spilled some water.
Dad.
So, Gen and I…
We…
are…
How are you, Suwat? I'm good.
Long time no see.
What? Your kid got married?
When?
I can't believe your daughter
is old enough to even get married.
My son is in his freshman year.
There's no hurry.
Kids these days grow up fast.
They are one thing today,
but tomorrow, they may change.
I'm not that old. I can wait.
I'll get a grandchild one day.
You never gave him a hint?
I wanted to tell him in one go.
More like you plan to kill me
along with it.
This is not how I thought it would go.
My dad seems quite open-minded.
Some parents are open-minded
about other people's kids.
When it comes to their own child,
they may be disappointed.
Don't give up just yet.
Let me talk to my dad first.
Let's make him accept us.
I won't give up.
You won't give up either, right?
How can I give up?
You flirted with me first.
And I'm confident
that I'm good enough.
What right does he have
to disapprove of me?
If you think he really is open-minded,
then we might have
just caught him off guard.
So we should just take it
one step at a time
until he gets used to it.
Just like what you said to your fans.
I'm glad I get to love you.
There, there.
You crybaby.
Come here.
I will console you.
You want to console me?
You got it.
What are you doing?
Song.
No. Don't!
No, Song!
Come here.
Here. Get this.
-Here.
-Song, what's wrong with you?
Stay in there.
Hey.
I'll get a new room and send you the bill.
Don't!
Don't.
I was just
fooling around with Song.
You can leave now.
See you tomorrow.
Don't worry about it.
We will get through this.
I'll call you when I get to my room.
All right. Go carefully.
Go.
Leave already.
Do you want some too?
When did you get back?
You love your work more than me.
I got back ages ago.
You didn't even notice me.
You chose going sightseeing over me.
Now, we are even.
Isn't it boring
having to work while on a vacation?
I'm used to it.
But I'm not.
You keep checking your phone.
You don't have enough time
to eat or sleep.
You don't get any exercise.
And not to mention the benefits,
there's none.
When the show was on-air,
you still took all the criticism.
I know how much you love your work.
What's up with you?
You're being weird lately.
I'm worried about you.
I know
how much you love this job.
Are you really okay with it?
Of course, I am.
I knew doing this job
in a country like this wouldn't be easy.
At first,
I just liked writing
as my dad didn't let me do much.
Once I got to do it as a job though,
I found out
that writing can heal me.
It enables me to express
what I can't say directly.
Whenever I'm exhausted
or I feel like giving up,
I look back to the day
that I chose this path.
Can you guess
which scene I liked the most?
The CGI one?
You know me well.
The CGI scene is so seamless
and beautiful. I love it.
Now, I will try to guess
which scene you like?
Which one do you think I liked?
The ending.
How did you know?
Because I know you.
I wanted to know
at the end,
if the character has to choose one way,
what is it going to be like?
If you really want to know,
why don't you write your own ending?
Do you really think I could do it?
If you like it, then give it a try.
My parents wouldn't like it.
If you're doing what you love,
why wouldn't they like it?
I believe in you.
I'm looking forward to seeing it.
I still remember that feeling.
It's like falling in love.
It's like you finally found someone.
I'm lucky to have found what I like early.
Though along the way,
it wasn't easy at all.
Nut.
What's wrong?
I didn't get in the short story contest.
I didn't get a prize.
Were you confident that you would win?
Of course, I was.
I put a lot of effort into it.
I thought I might win something, at least.
Writing is like art.
There's no right and wrong.
When you turn it in,
it's a matter of what the judges like.
Don't forget
that art serves no one
and it is a slave to none.
Therefore,
I don't want you to pressure yourself
just to win.
It is okay to lose.
Whether you make it or not is fine.
Along the way,
I hope you are happy with it.
But happiness won't feed you.
I wanted the prize money
to pay for my tuition,
in case I have to support myself
when I go to college.
You can try again.
Gain more experience by trial and error.
I believe that
one day, someone will like your work.
You've got this. I'm here for you.
Juea really likes your work.
So…
did you work with Juea from the beginning?
Juea and I get along.
So working together is easy.
Still, I can't say that I'm successful.
But if I keep going,
I can still write what I want to say.
What do you want to tell people
from the story you are working on?
I want to tell them
that the country that exports shows
about boys' love,
has the prettiest transgender people,
and has gay couples as net idols,
doesn't support the rights
for those people,
as they aren't truly accepted there.
I also want to tell him
that even though it has been a decade,
I still want to apologize,
and express my gratitude.
He is a good memory,
an inspiration that made me who I am,
and the one who made me love myself.
Then…
your show should have
a happy ending, right?
Hey. Are you jealous of my work now?
I'm just curious.
Don't forget that I'm a fan of your work,
and a fan of yours.
It will have a bad ending like my life.
I don't want to turn back time.
I want to move forward.
And don't make me tell you
who…
keeps me going.
Nut and Tatarn
reminded me of a quote
from a book that I read.
It said,
"Good love makes us want to grow
into a better person,
and makes us love ourselves more
as we love that person."
Nut is who he is today
as a result of Tatarn's love.
Therefore,
at such a critical time for Tatarn,
if Nut can help him,
then I should be glad.
Right?
Didn't you get any sleep?
Are you all right?
A lot of strange things
have been happening lately.
I'm beginning to see some images.
There was a place.
There was a person.
Are you regaining your memory?
I'm not sure about it.
Let's go to the doctor.
I don't want to remember it.
I'm afraid,
but also curious.
Tofu.
It's okay.
I will be here for you.
Nut.
The real reason
I brought you to Chiang Mai
is that I saw an image of a man
here.
So, did you used to live here?
I don't know.
Can we go somewhere?
Being there,
I might find out the truth.
Tofu.
Are you scared?
I don't know…
what will happen to me
if I take you to see him.
We will finally get to know who you are.
You're afraid
that we can't be together, right?
That's right.
If he's really someone in your family,
we can talk to him
and ask if you can stay with us.
My mother and I don't look like
bad people, do we?
Why did you bring us to the hospital?
Tofu's cousin may be a doctor,
like your mom.
Am I right?
Is he sick?
Why is the person you saw in the hospital?
Who is he?
Tarn.
Is that Tarn, Neung's friend?
The person you remembered is Tarn?
I was scared that if I brought you to him,
I would lose you.
Na must be really happy that her son…
Everybody has a gender.
You can be any gender you wish to be.
And every gender is equal.
I'm glad you can be yourself
whenever you are with me.
If something is troubling you,
I'll be the one to ease your mind.
Subtitle translation by:
Supichaya Ketwongwiriya