What do you want?
You should be careful.
With some matters,
the more you know,
the more danger you are in.
Was hurting the kid not enough?
You sent someone to shoot the cop.
I was only going to handle that young man.
But you had him transferred here
and alerted the police.
I had to nip it in the bud.
I know about your argument,
about him knowing
that you killed Mr. Sibmeun,
That secret should have stayed
between the two of you,
but now it has spread.
Do you mean Tatarn?
THE END
Is it really the end?
I'm really going to miss it.
So many things have happened
while writing this screenplay.
The best thing, though,
was you helping me reconcile with my mom.
Thank you, Tofu.
I'm so pleased.
I couldn't have done it alone.
That's not true.
Even if I wasn't here,
you two would still have made up,
because you love your mom.
I also love you.
I love you too.
Very much.
I was born out of Tatarn's love
and Nut's memories.
But I think
my identity is also
linked to Nut's desire.
The desire he had to resolve things
with Tatarn
and his mom.
He just never had the courage.
Aren't you sleeping?
I can't sleep.
Humans have it rough.
Objects like us never struggle to sleep.
The bear is not the same anymore.
He has evolved
from a simpleminded teddy bear
into a fully-fledged human.
Human lives are never simple.
It's hard
and tiring.
I'm happy, though.
I got the chance to live as a human
and to love Nut.
When I was a teddy bear,
I could only comfort him
when he hugged me.
As a human,
I helped him reconcile with his mom
and move on from his painful past.
I gave him the courage
to write a screenplay about Tatarn.
I think that's more than enough.
If I really have to leave now,
I won't be sorry.
Come on, Kuenchai.
We have to take Mrs. Na
to the hospital later.
Let's go.
Kuenchai.
May I help you?
Are you free?
I'm donating some belongings.
Can you give me a hand?
What do you say?
Are you so afraid of me
that you won't come?
Let me tell Nut first.
I won't let you go.
Are you her servant?
She can do it herself.
Calm down, Nut.
Jan lives alone.
It's probably hard for her.
It would be nice
if Tofu could lend a hand.
We can go alone. Okay?
She asked me for a favor.
Why don't you go with your mom?
Of course. Why not?
Right?
Nut.
What is it?
Drive safely.
Okay.
I'll come straight home after.
You should
wait for me here, okay?
You should get going.
When you come back…
I might not be here anymore.
Goodbye, Nut.
Kuenchai.
You don't want me to go either, do you?
I've made up my mind, though.
All right.
Before I go,
let's play together one last time.
Let's play your favorite game.
Goodbye, Kuenchai.
I'm here.
CASHIER - PRESCRIPTIONS
Do you have an appointment?
Yes.
Where's Tofu?
He's not here.
He's helping Jan with her stuff at home.
I have to go. Please excuse me.
Thanks for helping me.
I barely did anything.
There wasn't much stuff.
It's better to have a helping hand.
Drink this to feel refreshed.
TOFU
TOFU - NHONG
NHONG
-Hello.
-Kuenchai is barking nonstop.
Tofu is not here
and he won't pick up his phone.
Well…
I don't know what to do,
so I'm letting you know.
-Excuse me, nurse.
-Nut.
Take care of Mom for me, Gen.
I'll be right back.
Nut!
Aren't you drinking, Tofu?
Do you really want me to drink this?
Yes.
Why?
Don't you like soft drinks?
Your first name is Sajjaree.
It means truth.
What are you trying to say?
You're not telling the truth.
You lied about needing a favor.
You knew,
but you came anyway.
I wanted to know
what you plan to do to me.
Are you doing all this
because you love Mr. Saen?
What do you mean?
Everything you've done…
has been for Mr. Saen…
Right?
People will do anything
to protect their loved ones.
You have someone you love.
You should understand
that it hurts even more
to see your loved ones in pain.
For me,
nothing is more important
than their happiness.
If you were me,
you would have done the same.
I understand.
We all do things for the ones we love.
But you and I are different.
My love is based on truth
and righteousness.
Nut.
Wish me luck.
I must finish this.
I'm the only one…
who can do this.
It's sweet,
but it's not healthy.
You knew that, but you drank it anyway.
What an idiot.
I've been waiting for a miracle,
just like the others are waiting
for one for Tatarn.
Jan finally handed it to me.
Thank you
for making everything easier.
Forgive me.
I didn't want to do this.
It's too painful.
But this is the easiest way.
It's your fault
for being stubborn and asking for trouble.
If you hadn't tried to force Saen's hand,
I wouldn't have been bothered.
I know that Saen
is running out of patience.
That's why I had to step in.
Even if all I can do
is get rid of a puny pawn,
it's still better than doing nothing.
I understand.
I knew this day would eventually come.
I shouldn't be alive.
It's not fair on Tatarn.
Me, Mrs. Na,
you, and Mr. Saen,
Our lives have jeopardized Tatarn's.
I can't continue living like this.
Nut once told me,
Some use belief as a tool hiding the truth
to serve their purpose.
I don't want to be that kind of person.
The thing that Nut and I have…
came from Tatarn.
If I were to stay with Nut
and write our own story
while ignoring Tatarn…
I won't leave you alone.
I'll stay with you
until you slip away.
I'm not afraid of being arrested.
I know TRD can help me
since it would benefit them.
That is how this country works.
People with power and authority
are above the law.
-What the hell did you do?
-Stop!
What did you do?
I did the same thing you did for Na.
You killed your own brother
for someone you love.
I just did the same thing.
I poisoned his drink.
I killed Sib because he deserved it.
-Tofu is--
-He deserves it too
if he's keeping you from happiness.
Are you crazy?
You were crazy too.
You and I aren't so different.
We would do anything for those we love,
even when they don't love us back.
Stop.
Gosh.
What are you doing? Don't!
If he survives, you'll be arrested.
Then so be it!
I'm willing to go to jail!
I can't live like this anymore.
You can't do this.
I've done everything for you.
You can't get arrested.
-Let go!
-No!
-Don't.
-Tofu!
Tofu.
Get up, Tofu.
Tofu!
Tofu, what happened?
Tofu.
Tofu!
My life as a human was a miracle.
I learned a lot.
I got to know the people
and the world around me
little by little.
Just as Nut once said,
"History depends on who's writing it."
Now, I know
that a teddy bear like me,
even as a human,
could never love Nut deeply enough
to bring about a miracle
like Tatarn's love did.
I just hope
that what I have done
has made some sort of difference.
Doing that has made my life worthwhile.
Before I go,
I remember a quote I once read.
"When someone passes on,
people recognize them
for who they really are,
as the best version of themselves."
I hope that the best version of me
remains
in everyone's memories.
Neung.
Is that you?
I'm Tofu.
Have we met before?
It doesn't matter.
What matters
is that you brought me to Nut.
Do you know Nut?
Thank you
for turning me into who I am
and giving me the chance
to spend time with Nut.
I don't know if I'll get another chance
to be that happy.
But that one chance
was amazing.
Hey.
Time of death, 5:13 p.m.
Nut,
I'm sorry that we won't grow old together.
I'm sorry
that I won't get to hold you
when you're upset
or when you need someone by your side.
I know that you're strong enough.
Your strength
is what taught me to be strong.
I don't regret my decision.
Even though I'm alone now,
and no one else knows
or even understands why I did it,
as long as I understand,
isn't that enough?
Thank you
for teaching me to stand up
for truth and righteousness.
If we stand up for what's right,
there's nothing to fear.
-Are you a relative of Tofu?
-Yes.
How is he?
He suffered a cardiac arrest.
We tried our best to save his life.
I'm very sorry.
Please excuse me.
Tofu!
What happened?
What did you do to him?
What did you do?
Tell me!
I did it.
I'm sorry.
Tofu knew too many of my secrets.
Tofu.
Hold on.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Tofu. Stay with me.
Tofu.
Tofu!
I never thought someone like Mr. Saen
could hurt anyone,
especially his own family.
I hope you're right.
You love Mr. Saen a lot, don't you?
Maybe because I've always wished
he was my dad.
You have to tell them what I said.
Tell the police that I planned everything.
I was here because I planned to kill Tofu.
I saw the chance
when you asked him to help you,
and I poisoned his drink.
You didn't know anything about it, okay?
You just got caught in the middle.
You tried to stop me when you found out,
but it was too late.
Do you understand?
No. You didn't do it.
None of this
was your fault.
I'm solely responsible
for everything. Okay?
I'll take the rap.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
It's about Saen.
I know you can't forgive him.
I just want you to know that what he did
was meant to protect us.
By murdering people?
What he did
was partially my fault.
I wasn't strong enough.
I let your dad hurt you.
I let him hurt me.
Saen!
I told you not to come here again.
I wouldn't have to come
if you didn't hurt your family.
Saen.
What?
What did she tell you now?
She didn't have to.
I've seen with my own eyes
the terrible things you've done.
So what?
They're my family.
They're not yours. Why do you care?
Have you forgotten?
Before she became your family,
she almost became mine.
You have her.
Why can't you take care of her?
How dare you call yourself
a husband and a father.
Do you think
a loser like you could take care of her?
Don't do it, Saen.
You should leave.
I won't stand idly by
if I ever find out you hurt them again.
It wasn't just him hurting me.
I hurt him too.
Why?
I love Na too.
I'm no less devoted to her.
What's so bad about me?
Why does Na love a loser like you so much?
She never even tells me she loves me.
Why?
Not getting to be with the one you love
is no worse
than being with someone you love,
but who doesn't love you back.
THE LITTLE PRINCE
That one is old,
so I bought you a new one.
THE LITTLE PRINCE
They say
if you read The Little Prince
at different stages of life,
your interpretation changes.
I hope we get another chance
to read this together.
It was the turning point
that made me realize.
I decided to tell him I love him.
I've never loved Sib
the way a wife should love her husband.
From now on,
I've decided to be a good wife
and mother to my family.
Don't worry about me anymore.
I'll become stronger
for my family's sake.
I'm glad
that you're stronger.
I hope you're happy.
If you ever need a friend,
you can always let me know.
Thank you.
Saen!
What's the matter with you?
I should ask you why you keep
coming over to see my wife!
It's not what you think.
So what is it?
Do you dress up,
clean the house, and cook for me?
How can you do this?
Your husband is lying sick upstairs,
and you're having an affair in our house.
How could you do it?
What are you saying?
You--
Oh, no.
Honey, don't.
Don't--
Na!
How dare you hurt her in front of me!
Honey.
Let go.
Don't. Please don't fight.
He's very sick.
You should calm down and leave.
Okay? Sit down over there.
I'll get your medicine.
Don't.
I'll get it.
You should talk to him.
I'll get the medicine.
Where is it?
It's in the bedroom, by the bed.
Honey.
What happened?
Did he take the medicine?
This isn't his medicine.
Honey.
Please stay strong.
How could you do this?
You can see he hasn't changed.
He even hurt you in front of me.
Without him,
you and Nut can be happy.
I can't let him die like this.
No, please stay with me.
Stay with me.
It was too late.
We took Dad to the hospital,
but it was too late.
I didn't know what to do.
I couldn't tell anyone.
I was afraid.
The truth…
might upset you,
but I want to tell you everything…
while I still can.
I'm sorry.
I know you're lonely.
I won't let you be.
I wake up to see the happy face
Of the person in my heart
Why can't I forget this person's face?
Why is he so memorable?
It's strange
To think
Of those lost memories
Of beautiful
Days and nights
However much I cry
I think about you
And the days
When you were with me
In the end
We still have to part ways
This…
This place means so much to me
And I have so many
Memories
Please stay here with me
There will be another day for us
A day when we will be together
Again
Tofu.
I don't know if I can be strong
like you wanted me to.
After everything that has happened
with my family,
I don't know if I can get through it
without you.
I don't know what will happen to me.
I really want you here with me.
But I know…
that's not possible.
It's like I'm cursed.
The good things in my life
are short-lived.
In the end, they all leave.
My mom's memories,
my trusted uncle,
and you.
I was afraid
that you wouldn't stick around,
and it turned out to be true.
I can't believe
that you're really gone.
I guess that's what life is like.
We all die in the end.
We may stop breathing when we die,
but memories never disappear.
No matter how hard it is to say goodbye,
we still have to move on.
The memories
will always stay in our hearts.
Memories also make us realize
that we're not alone in this world.
There are many people waiting for us.
They're waiting for us
to be a family again.
About Gen and me,
you may not agree with it,
but we won't just give up.
I want you to know
that we are serious about each other.
We'll love each other whatever happens.
I'm sorry if I upset you.
I've actually known for a while.
Since the day I visited you on set.
-You knew?
-Yes.
I didn't know what to do then.
I didn't know how to handle it.
I never thought my son would like men.
It doesn't mean
that I can't accept it, though.
I was just worried.
Now, I know that I don't have to be.
I can see you're happy
that you've found each other.
I can tell that you two
can take care of each other.
If it makes you happy, then be together.
Thank you.
I know that I'm not such a great dad.
My words might have hurt you in the past.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
We're both sorry.
Because we love each other, right?
Now, Song and Gen are a family.
It might not be a regular family,
but it's a very big one.
So big that when you see them,
you would be happy for them too.
As for Tarn and me,
we got to meet again.
Tarn.
-I--
-I missed you.
I really missed you, you know?
You were right.
I did miss him.
But that doesn't mean I didn't love you.
I miss you.
I miss your voice.
I miss your hugs
and your kisses.
Don't be afraid that I'll stop loving you.
I know it hurt
that you couldn't compete with Tarn,
that you couldn't help financially,
that you weren't popular like him.
But those things don't mean anything,
because who you are
is what made me love you.
Tarn showed me the reality of this world,
while you showed me the beauty in it.
I really wonder
where you came from.
If you really fell from the sky
like Mom said,
which galaxy are you from?
It's probably really far from my universe.
Your mothership must have taken you back
to your place of happiness.
I'm sorry for what happened to you.
You had to live
with my dysfunctional family.
If it were possible,
I would forsake having ever met you,
if it meant you would have a better life,
so you didn't have to meet me
and end the way it did.
My first boys' love series was released.
How is it?
I think you know.
I'm still my crazy self
writing love stories,
but with political issues snuck in
and complicated storylines.
The reviews weren't as good
as Juea expected.
People still talk about it, though.
A lot of people preferred
my complicated story
to the usual lovey-dovey romance.
Song has so many fans now.
Gen had to step in as his manager.
It didn't turn out as well as you wished,
but I'm happy that I wrote it.
Most importantly,
the person I wanted to show it to
got to see it.
I love you, Tofu.
I have no doubt that anyone
who got to know you
would love you too.
Thank you for always holding my hand
and not thinking I was weird.
You will always be a gift to me.
I wish you were here,
so you could live these stories
along with me.
I miss you.
Love from me.
I do know, though.
I know everything
because I'm back.
You're probably wondering how I came back.
It happened that day.
It wasn't just Tatarn
who received a miracle.
I did too.
I returned to my body…
just before I was…
cremated.
I don't know
how the miracle happened again.
I don't know if my waking up
affected Tatarn in any way.
All I knew at that moment
was I had to escape.
I wanted to go back to Nut.
When will these dogs
stop targeting bears like me.
Let's go.
Gosh.
Why is he so fast?
When will you stop?
Wait a minute.
What?
Ms. Left Slipper.
Why are you here?
Wait. It's coming back.
Let's go, Ms. Left Slipper.
Can you tell me
how you ended up here?
After you lost me that day,
I was brought here.
I thought nobody would find me,
so I came to terms with it.
It must have been hard out here.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
It was no one's fault.
It's not easy to survive out here,
but I learned a lot.
It made me prouder of myself
than when I was home.
I know.
At home,
you barely got to be yourself.
Mr. Right Slipper really misses you.
We all do.
I miss him too.
But look at me now.
Nobody will want me, even if I go back.
Hasn't Mrs. Na
thrown him away?
Not yet.
I saved him for you.
He was really sad that you disappeared,
so he went to sleep.
Maybe he'll wake up if you go home.
Let's go home together.
Were there really no remains?
Yes.
I was surprised too.
Right.
I found this by the crematorium door.
Does it belong to the deceased?
Yes.
Is this all that's left?
It's like a dream.
Tofu wasn't just a dream.
He didn't go anywhere.
He'll always be with us.
That's right. I didn't go anywhere.
I knew Nut would return,
so I'll find a way to follow him home.
But that dog is back again.
Gosh!
Let's go.
Come on.
Tofu, this way!
Ms. Left Slipper!
Ouch.
Go on, Tofu.
No, we have to go home together.
Kuenchai!
Stop, Kuenchai!
Nut.
Where are you going, Nut?
Tofu.
Isn't this my slipper?
That's your teddy bear. Tofu.
The missing teddy bear
and Mrs. Na's slipper
that Tofu was searching for.
They both ended up here.
That's right.
I'm back, Nut.
Tofu is back!
You're back, Tofu.
Hey, Tofu!
Tofu. Good gracious.
You're really back.
-How are you?
-I knew you would come back.
Nothing is better than
when the people you love
love you back and wait for you to return
to them.
Kuenchai.
Tofu is gone.
From now on, I'll play with you more.
Is your name Tofu?
I don't remember.
But that's what your mother calls me.
I'm Tofu, your teddy bear.
I guess…
I really missed you.
Even though Nut doesn't know
that I'm back,
I'm just glad
that a teddy bear like me
can make him feel a little less sad.
This is what love is.
I get to love him,
and I get to watch him.
I get to stay--
That's right. I'm always by his side,
or sometimes by the bed.
Mrs. Na's memory worsens every day.
The pain of a person losing their memory,
and the pain of the person
who still remembers
are just as real.
Mrs. Na isn't the only one who needs help.
Nut is seeing a doctor too.
The doctor said
that Mrs. Na does what she does
because of Alzheimer's disease.
While Nut's accidental fits
are due to cumulative fatigue.
Nut should take care of his mom with love.
But he must also remember to take care
of his own heart.
But I think
Nut has found someone
to take care of his heart.
I heard that your protest
against Hollow Forest
finally succeeded.
Right.
They halted the construction.
It's a shame
that the law can't touch TRD.
They didn't get the real culprit.
What I did
might seem crazy,
but sometimes,
miracles do happen.
You're still the same.
Yes.
I am.
Kuenchai. There you go again.
Come on, Kuenchai.
I was watching quietly.
But now,
I have to witness their love up close.
I didn't think
that you would keep this.
It has always been with me.
It suddenly disappeared
when Tofu came, though.
They have the same name.
He had lost his memory
and Mom called him by that name.
She said he looked like this teddy bear.
When the teddy bear disappeared,
I even thought that he stole it.
He even told me
that he was the bear.
I was furious at him.
So,
how did you get it back?
I found it at the temple.
It's funny.
When he showed up,
the teddy bear disappeared.
Then, when he left,
the teddy bear came back.
So,
what are your plans for the future?
I think I'll still be
an artist and an activist.
I'm thinking of opening a new studio.
In Chiang Mai?
Somewhere around here.
I'll get going.
I think I have an idea
where his studio will be.
Hey, Nut.
Congratulations on the studio.
I once went to your house in Chiang Mai.
I thought you might like it,
so I got it for you.
You can have one here too.
Did you ever think
that we would see each other again?
I didn't dare to.
I'm sorry
for hurting you
and letting go of your hand.
I was never hurt.
You don't have to be sorry.
I know you chose the right path.
Let's go.
All right.
Come on, Song.
Everyone, give me a hand.
-It's quite a lot.
-Take this.
-It's heavy.
-Here.
Take this.
This one is quite heavy.
All right.
-Are you okay?
-Kind of.
What does "kind of" mean?
-It means I'm fine
-It means he's fine.
Okay?
-Are you okay?
-It's a little heavy.
-Hello.
Hello.
Put it here.
What did you guys bring?
I posted drawings of teddy bears
on my page.
They turned out to be really popular.
People wanted them,
so I made some sample products.
Prib. Why does it have to be a teddy bear?
I once asked Tofu about teddy bears.
He didn't say anything,
but when we went to retrieve Tofu's ashes,
Nut got his teddy bear back.
Isn't that strange?
When I think of Tofu,
I think of a teddy bear.
Right.
What should I be
when you think of me?
A dog, since you're like a puppy.
Then you have to be a tick
and stick with me forever.
-You're a tick. A tick. My tick.
-A tick?
Hey, stop it.
I'm getting emotional.
Prib.
I guess
Tofu must have been a great guy.
Everyone seems to love him so much.
I love who Tofu was.
I believe that everyone
wants their own Tofu.
That's why I made these.
But actually,
I think
we should be our own Tofus,
and be a Tofu for other people.
Here.
Nut.
Right. I don't have my own Tofu.
Come on.
Then I wish
that you find your own Tofu soon.
Hello.
Which one do you like?
Well,
I saw on the Once Upon Our Time page
that you were selling stuff here.
Right.
I posted that just five minutes ago.
Do you live around here?
No.
I just wanted to take a Tofu Bear home.
Your post caught my eye right away.
Just the way I like it.
"Just the way I like it."
That's right.
You're "Mittraphap Is A Road Name."
Yes, that's me.
Thank you for always engaging
with my posts.
You've been doing it since I started.
I like your artwork.
I wanted to support you,
so you can continue drawing.
Thank you.
Right.
Which one are you interested in?
This one is really cute.
Finally, Prib found her own Tofu.
You didn't have to walk me home.
We're neighbors.
I wanted to.
It's the first time
I came all the way to your house.
Thank you.
Do you still miss Tofu?
Would you be mad
if I missed him?
No.
I should thank him
for getting your mother to open up
and to get over what other people think.
It's not strange for men to fall in love.
If society says it is,
I think that's what's strange.
I should thank you too.
You gave me strength
and the courage to choose my happiness.
You helped make me who I am today.
Didn't I tell you?
I'm happy
to see you happy.
Whether you agree to marry--
I do.
Even though we can't do it legally,
my heart
married you a long time ago.
Nut once told me,
a good screenplay should leave a trace
in the audience's hearts.
They should never forget it.
No matter how many years later,
they will still think of those stories
and dig up that trace to remember.
I guess that's what Tatarn is to Nut.
I also hope
that I'm like that too.
Are you done with the plot?
Tofu
Are you jealous of Tarn again?
Are you trying to make me think of you?
Even if you're jealous,
I know you won't get mad
if I get back together with him.
No matter what,
you'll always be in my heart.
I told you before,
miracle is just
another way of saying hard work.
Maybe the miracle that occurred
was a result of someone's hard work,
or even many.
Nut.
Tofu.
Is it not enough to stay in my heart?
Is that why you're here?
I told you to wait for me,
but you didn't.
You shouldn't have gone to Jan's.
Everything was already decided.
I'm sorry
that I couldn't wait to see you.
That's why I came back today.
You came on a rainy day, just like Mio.
I'll disappear like Mio too.
Before I go,
I want to tell you something.
Don't worry.
Don't feel bad.
I'll be so happy
if Tatarn is the one by your side.
I'm also glad
that you're no longer stuck in the past.
I am the way I am
because of you.
I'll continue living my life for you.
I'll be happy in your stead.
I love you, Tofu.
I love you too.
I'm happy
to see you smile.
Please be very happy.
Yes, Juea.
It has been approved, Nut!
What?
The plot you submitted this morning
was approved.
Are you serious?
Of course!
You can start writing the script now.
Sure thing.
Tofu! It was approved!
THE MIRACLE… THAT MORNING
I kept my promise.
Your story is being made into a series.
I'm going to celebrate with Tarn and Mom.
Don't be jealous, my boy.
I'll enjoy the food for you.
I know Nut will always think of me.
Whatever he faces from now on,
he'll be fine,
because I'm cheering him on from here.
I hope Nut is happy in the real world
without the need for any more miracles.
Subtitle translation by:
Pattranun Bunyanund