Ask your mom
why your dad used to call you
a bastard.
Do you and Uncle Saen
still love each other?
Am I really a bastard like Dad said?
Don't say that.
Is anyone inside the house?
Come out this instant.
Did you see the way
they were looking at us?
Do you really think
they came here to get Tofu's memory back?
You should live in the present.
You should use the time to worry
about your loved ones' feelings.
You are confusing Tofu
by expressing countless concerns
toward your ex-boyfriend.
She said…
I'm showing symptoms of Alzheimer's.
Since your mom is already sick,
why don't we find a way to help her?
I suspect there is still some evidence
remaining in the house.
Our forensics team even found the blood
that was wiped clean.
Do you think
they could've missed something?
A bit of broken tile.
How did it get there?
And how did you know?
I found a bit of broken tile
in a cactus at Tatarn's house.
Could it be related to the case?
Do you mind checking it for me?
Lieutenant Kong.
Can you find an old picture of the house,
so we can compare?
Yes, sir.
Hey.
Why did you come here?
I told you not to come here.
My employee said
the police went to Tatarn's house.
See? Those kids
are really causing us trouble.
You should've discussed with me
before letting them in.
You're too careless.
You're the careless one.
If you hadn't stepped in,
it would've been much easier.
I stepped in
because I was worried about you.
If you hadn't attacked him,
I wouldn't have to put myself in danger.
Are you threatening me?
I'm just trying to warn you.
Stop trying.
I won't back down.
What do you hope to gain?
You know full well
that you don't have enough influence.
It's not going to bring about any change.
Things might not change today,
but they will in the future.
Time is on our side.
We have time to win, to fight, to lose.
Winning might take time,
but that day will come.
But power is on their side.
We have to get that power on our side.
The people should have the power,
so that problems can be solved.
Am I supposed to give up
and be a coward like you?
Should I give in to power,
abandon my principles,
and behave immorally like you?
I can't do it.
Mr. Saen…
hit your nephew's head.
Secretly keep an eye on him
and keep me posted.
I'm heading there now.
I stayed put like you told me to,
but trouble still found us.
Are you sure
that nobody was in the house
other than you and your men?
Why? Who do you suspect?
Tofu.
He might actually know Tarn.
He could have been in the house that day
and has seen the whole thing.
That's why he moved
to the house next door,
and lied about his amnesia
in order to keep an eye on us.
Did you see the way he looked at us?
It's as if he knows something.
Think about it.
He went to the house yesterday.
Today, the police went
there for something.
How did this happen?
We don't know for sure what the cause is.
According to studies,
there are multiple factors that can be
the cause of Alzheimer's disease.
It may be due to age,
genetics,
brain trauma,
or brain infections.
These can cause changes in brain cells.
As brain cells deteriorate,
the patients start losing memories.
This affects thinking
and decision-making.
They will be forgetful,
and won't be able to learn new things.
To be honest,
the chance of Alzheimer's disease
for someone
in their fifties like you is slim.
Especially for someone
who has had a mental illness,
the chance is incredibly slim.
But looking at your symptoms,
it's most likely
that it is Alzheimer's disease.
But we should still monitor the symptoms.
Why didn't you tell me about it last time?
I was afraid you would worry.
I thought I would tell you about it
after your trip.
I didn't expect that incident
in Chiang Mai.
It doesn't matter.
Now that we know about it,
let's do our best
to look after her from now on.
Exactly.
We can't cure Alzheimer's disease,
but if we find out and treat it early,
and take good care of ourselves,
it will slow down the disease progression.
We can also prevent the danger
of other complications.
To treat Alzheimer's disease,
you can use drugs and other methods.
These are the drugs I'm prescribing.
One is for temporarily reducing symptoms,
and the other is for suppressing
brain deteriorating chemicals.
The patient can lead
a relatively normal life.
You will feel bright,
which will be easier on the caretaker.
Where's Tofu?
Let's go, Mrs. Na.
Shoot.
But what's more important than drugs
is taking care of the brain,
along with caring
for your physical and mental health.
Research has found
that regular exercise
freshens up the brain
and extends the disease progression.
It is also important
for the patient to socialize
and meet up with people
apart from household members.
I noticed that your lights were still on.
I realized I hadn't unpacked.
Do you need a hand?
I can put the suitcase away
for you tomorrow.
Thanks.
Is Nut asleep?
Not yet.
He's rather enthusiastic.
He's reading Gen's book.
I have to thank you for taking care of us.
You don't have to thank me.
Both of you take good care of me too.
It's not the same.
I may be…
a little forgetful,
but… I know my son well.
Nut is a handful,
especially when he's upset.
I'm really thankful to you
for accepting who he is and not giving up.
From now on, my condition…
will keep getting worse.
I won't be the same and…
I'll cause a lot more problems for him.
I would like to ask you
to stay calm
and…
forever remain so nice to our family.
Don't leave Nut.
I don't want him to lose another person
who he loves and loves him back.
I promise.
I'll stay and take care of you
and take care of Nut.
I'll never leave.
I'll take care of Nut forever.
It's not just my job,
but it's my life's vocation.
Thank you.
You're as focused
as when you were studying for exams.
Have you seen me studying for exams?
Who knows?
I might have seen you.
You just didn't care about me.
Come here, then.
So…
Read it to me.
Your voice might make me less sad.
"Your mother behaves
and speaks differently.
After a checkup,
Alzheimer's disease was diagnosed.
The patient can still speak normally.
Her memories remain.
This means
she's still in the early stages."
It says that…
Mom will keep losing her memory
and her ability to help herself.
She'll forget how to chew.
She'll even forget how to breathe.
Don't be afraid.
No matter what happens,
we'll keep fighting.
Let's make the rest of your mom's memories
good memories.
Thank you.
UNCLE SAEN
-Yes, Uncle Saen.
-Where are you?
I just got off work.
We barely talked yesterday.
I'll swing by to see you.
I'm already home.
Why so fast?
My mom is sick.
I took her to the hospital.
What happened?
She has Alzheimer's.
You don't have to worry.
I'll take care of her.
Be careful.
Kuenchai.
Gosh.
So noisy.
Who's that?
It's me.
It feels so nice to have a wash.
It was so stuffy in there.
Was it your voice I heard the other day?
I was the only one
who would wake up in that room.
Wait a minute.
Actually…
Does this mean
you've woken up before?
When was that?
I'm not sure.
I remember that there were
Mr. Sibmeun and Mrs. Na in the house.
Mrs. Na was still pregnant with Nut.
One day, they brought baby Nut home.
He kept crying
that Mr. Sibmeun and Mrs. Na
had to cradle him all night long.
What's next?
This house was filled
with happiness back then.
Both of them loved Nut so much.
Mrs. Na would tell him stories
even when he was so young.
Mr. Sib would buy him toys.
But as Nut grew up,
the two of them started to fight.
Nut is a normal boy like anyone else.
Can't you see how girly he is?
After that, they didn't use me as much.
It's probably because…
you're a keepsake from Mr. Saen,
so Mr. Sibmeun didn't want to see you.
Mrs. Na put me in the closet.
I would fall asleep from time to time.
I remember a time
when I woke up because it was so hot.
Do you love him?
I almost died because of Mr. Sib.
Thank goodness Mrs. Na saved me.
After that day,
I was moved to the storage room,
and I've been sleeping since.
I'm sorry.
I saw it in the storage room,
so I washed it for you.
I'll put it back
once it's dry.
That's okay.
I don't use it anymore.
I'll take a look.
Hello, Uncle Saen.
Go ahead. Mom is inside.
Come here, Kuenchai.
What do you think Mr. Saen is like
when he's angry?
Why are you asking that?
I'm just wondering.
From what I know about him,
he always seems kind and considerate.
I can't imagine what it's like
when someone like him gets mad.
I don't see him that often,
but he usually takes care of Mom and me.
He really loves his family.
He even stepped back for Dad
when they fought over Mom.
He didn't get mad when Dad made trouble.
He's very calm.
I've never seen him mad
except when it comes to Jan.
I assume family members…
wouldn't hurt each other.
Are you worried about Jan?
I don't know about his family,
but I believe that…
he's not the same as my dad.
You seem livelier than I expected.
I have no reason to be sad.
Nut gets worried when I'm sad.
This disease has made me realize
that I don't have much time left
to live a life with memories.
So I would rather use
the rest of my memories
for good things
and happy things.
I'm sorry
for being one of the reasons
that you ended up this way.
Don't be.
I know you've done a lot of things for me
and helped relieve my sadness.
I'm sick from my own doings.
I blamed myself that my family suffered
because I chose the wrong husband.
I felt sorry for myself,
for Sibmeun,
for Nut,
and for you.
Those feelings didn't just…
weaken my heart,
they destroyed my body.
It's a shame
that I realized this too late.
Had I fixed it earlier,
I wouldn't have suffered
and I wouldn't have been sick
all this time.
I'll forget it soon enough.
You'll probably suffer more
since you remember all of it.
If you don't want
a twisted, tormented life like mine,
you'll have to live mindfully.
Correct your mistakes while you still can.
Don't neglect them
and drown in regret like I did.
I don't want you to end up like me.
Thank you for visiting Mom.
I don't know if I can come again.
It will be even harder on you from now on,
having to take care of two sick people.
You can call me whenever you need to.
One person lost his memory.
Another person is losing hers.
Who knows?
I might remember something soon.
Actually,
I'm starting to see more things.
I can't piece them together just yet,
but I think
I might remember everything soon.
When that time comes,
I might find out
what happened to Tatarn.
That would be great.
Tarn's case will finally progress.
I don't know
why Tatarn was attacked,
but nobody
should be harmed, should they?
Not everyone
is blessed with humanity.
People can hurt each other
over simple disagreements.
Conflicts of interest
can lead to murder.
When we disagree,
shouldn't we talk about it reasonably?
Shouldn't we try to understand
rather than fight?
-A fractured skull and a hemorrhage?
-Excuse me, sir.
We found no fingerprints
on the vase or the broken pieces.
Here's the report.
They probably thought
that it was well planned.
They must have thought
that they destroyed all the evidence.
Unfortunately,
they dropped some evidence
in the cactus pot.
It doesn't weigh much.
Why was his injury so severe?
Or, is the weapon not the vase?
According to the report,
if the weapon is really
a blunt, hard object like you said,
and if it's the vase in this photo,
could it really cause
a fractured skull and a hemorrhage?
That's right.
The vase would break after one hit.
The injuries suggest multiple hits.
I confirm that I diagnosed
according to his symptoms.
A combination of things
could have caused the injuries,
not just the weapon's weight or shape,
It also depends on force
and other factors.
Unless
the weapon is not just this vase,
but another as well.
You'll have to live mindfully.
Correct your mistakes while you still can.
Don't neglect them
and drown in regret like I did.
Not everyone
is blessed with humanity.
People can hurt each other
over simple disagreements.
Conflicts of interest
can lead to murder.
Shouldn't we try to understand
rather than fight?
Yes.
I just got back. I'm at the parking lot.
I just found out
that you let people into that house.
The police called. I couldn't refuse.
The issue was dying down.
People were forgetting about it,
but you dug it back up.
You can't blame it all on me.
This whole thing happened
all because of you.
Get out! No more deforestation.
Get out! We don't want it. Is that right?
We don't want it. Get out!
Yes, Dad.
Don't worry.
I'll handle it as soon as possible.
Is the leader your wife's nephew?
-Yes. I warned him--
-Tell him to stop.
The board is getting upset.
You know how much we paid him
to settle this deal.
It cannot fail from these stupid ideals.
I'm not sure if he'll listen.
He's pretty stubborn.
I don't care what he is.
All I care about
is that we continue this project.
If he doesn't stop,
you'll have to.
You…
Your future at TRD depends on yourself.
You ordered me to do it.
I did, but you didn't succeed.
I had to clean up for you.
I kept him alive for your sake.
That's why this is all messed up.
Right now, my father, the board,
and the investors are all pressuring me.
And the police are snooping around.
I have to do something
before we're all ruined.
What will you do?
If your wife's nephew is such a nuisance,
I'll end it myself.
The book that Nut
was reading yesterday said that
this seemingly harmless disease
can eat up the patient
and spit out the empty shell
without the person's identity inside.
The movie Nut watched the other day
also said
that cancer is better than this.
It sounds terrifying,
but seeing her now…
You're awake.
Yes.
Nut went to bed late, so he isn't up yet.
What are you doing
so early in the morning?
I wake up early every day.
You and Nut are the only ones
who always wake up late.
-I was meaning to ask.
-Yes?
Do you like wood sorrels?
Well…
It's a flower that sticks in my memory.
I used to live in Soi Butterfly,
and that alley was lined
with wood sorrels.
That was what they called the alley.
When I first moved here,
I felt a little out of place,
so I planted these here.
These flowers made this place feel
warm and familiar like the old house.
I'm used to this house now, though.
And I…
love this house as much as the old one.
A house that is a home.
I like this house too.
I also like that you're cheerful.
I know Nut and you are worried about me.
But since my disease can't be cured,
don't worry about curing it.
The drugs are just slowing it down,
but my body worsens every day.
I think…
From now on, let's live.
Through both joy and sorrow…
until my memories fade away.
I read somewhere
that the thing that Alzheimer's
can't take away from us…
is love.
Sometimes, the sooner we accept the truth,
the sooner our wound heals.
THIS WAY TO THE BEDROOM
What's this?
I registered your information
at The Mirror Foundation,
and they gave us this wristband.
It's filled with all of your information.
In case you get lost
and someone finds you,
they'll know where to drop you off.
So…
you must wear it at all times.
Don't take it off.
Next.
-What's it?
-The number is…
-Sixty-two.
-I have it.
-You do.
-I have it, too.
-I don't.
This one.
What's the number?
-Forty-six.
-I have it.
-What?
Why don't I have it?
Wait a minute.
-Kuenchai got bingo.
-What?
-Oh, wow. Great job.
-That's awesome.
Great job.
Give me your hand.
-Great job.
-Another one.
Since it can't be avoided,
we'll hold onto it.
We'll use this pain as an opportunity
to bring us even closer.
It smells so good.
What are you making today?
Tofu with tamarind sauce.
What?
-Mom.
-What?
You got Tofu all confused.
I only heard of eggs with tamarind sauce.
Well,
they're similar.
I changed the eggs to tofu.
I like the name of this dish.
So…
what are the ingredients?
There is
hard tofu.
There are also red onions,
dried chili,
and…
Here, Mom.
There's cilantro, tamarind,
and palm sugar.
Some recipes also add garlic and sesame.
-Mom.
-What?
Should we try new recipes someday?
There is a lot here.
Sounds good.
-Should I help?
-Sure.
What are there?
Here.
The bread looks delicious.
The sweets look good.
What sweet?
What does it say?
Can we order it?
-Let's just bake it. It's much cheaper.
-Fine.
Here.
-I'll take a look.
-Okay.
-Hi, Prib.
-Hi.
Long time no see. You're still handsome.
You, too.
I'm still pretty, right?
Do you want to come in?
I haven't seen Nut in weeks.
He barely goes to the office.
Even Uncle Juea is missing him.
He asked me to bring Nut the new project.
Is there a new project?
He hasn't finished the old one.
I can handle it.
It's better to have money.
In case we need it.
I won't get overworked.
You're taking care of me.
It must be harder on you,
having to take care of two people.
It's all right.
I'm happy to do it.
I better find Mrs. Na.
I feel invisible here.
-Hello.
You are…
It's Prib,
my coworker.
-Right. Prib.
-Yes.
I'm sorry. I couldn't remember your name.
Don't mind me.
Don't worry.
I can introduce myself
every time you forget.
I'm a great talker.
Stay for dinner.
Definitely.
Please excuse me.
I have to fill Kuenchai's bowl.
Kuenchai already ate.
He won't be able to walk if he eats more.
Wait.
It smells like…
-It smells like--
-Hey!
Be careful, Nut.
Move aside.
Why didn't you turn it off?
I told you to be careful.
What would you do if you were alone?
I forgot.
I'm sorry.
It's all right, Mrs. Na.
How's it going, Nut? How's the script?
Nut.
You've been doing a great job.
Don't blame yourself.
You did great.
Thank you.
What for?
Everything.
Thank you for staying beside me
when I feel alone.
And I'm sorry
for bringing you into this
when you're suffering from memory loss.
I have to thank you too,
for letting me stay here
and always missing me,
even when you have a lot to think about.
And I'm sorry
that I can't help much.
This is more than enough.
With you hugging me like this,
I have enough strength to go on.
You can recharge anytime.
I'll be right here.
Eat this, Mrs. Na.
Eat up.
Thanks.
-Mom.
-What is it?
I want to host a party.
What party?
Is it for a birthday?
I don't recall anyone's birthday
around this time.
That's not it.
I want to host a party just because.
Just because?
Then please do.
I don't even know some of their faces.
Then we should just invite close friends.
I saw this album in the storage room.
Do you want to take a look?
We might find photos of your friends.
"All grown-ups
were children first,
but few of them remember it."
That's from The Little Prince.
Right.
I suddenly remembered it.
When I was a teacher,
I would stop the children when I see them
doing something strange.
But I had actually done
the same things when I was their age.
Being a grown-up
makes me forget the child in me.
I live in a world of benefits,
filled with numbers and competitions.
Just like how Dad used to ask me
where I was ranked
and how my grades were.
He never asked me
how my classes went, if I enjoyed it,
or if I liked it.
Dad and I are sorry.
We lost our childhoods along the way.
Our childhood memories
shape who we are today.
But as we grow up,
we tend to forget those times.
We lose our own Little Prince
along with our imagination and dreams.
I just noticed
that we have no family photo.
I never thought it was a real family.
And I don't know who to show it to.
We don't really have visitors.
Also,
we rarely take photos together.
As I remember, the last time…
was probably on a trip.
I was around eight years old.
Shall we take a family photo?
We're about to host a party.
We can show it to them.
The party will be at the garden.
We can place it at the garden.
I think we should just frame
the ones we have.
Those photos were for fun.
I want a serious photo.
Whatever you say.
I'll take Mom to a photo studio.
No.
I want to take it in the house.
What?
The house…
Well,
this house is our memory.
Your mom said she likes this place.
I do too.
Let's take the photo here.
Here it is.
But…
we need some assistance.
Get closer.
Okay. Ready?
Oh, wow.
The models look so great.
You can blame me
if the photos don't turn out well.
All right.
One, two, three.
What's with you?
I want a photo shoot too.
What type of photo shoot?
Like this one.
A family photo shoot.
You better ask your dad.
If Dad agrees,
we have to dress up nicer than this.
Fine. Give me that.
Why the rush?
I have to go. I still have work to do.
Thank you, Prib.
-Let me know when you get there.
-Okay.
I'll get going, then.
Thank you, Gen.
You, too, Song.
Sure thing. I'll see you.
-I'm leaving.
-Bye.
UNCLE JUEA
What is it, Uncle Juea?
How was Nut's photo shoot?
All good.
I'm heading back now.
I'll show you the photos.
Once you see them,
you'll want them as film references.
Oh, wow. Are they that good?
They were like wedding photos.
Gen did an amazing job.
I see.
A boys' love fan like you
must be over the moon.
I would be if it was actually possible.
I wish they would legalize
same-sex marriage.
Shouldn't we all benefit from the law
when it's created for everyone?
Tofu.
It will take all night at this rate.
You look good today.
I want to see more of you in this outfit.
You look good too.
Just like in my dreams.
Have you dreamed of me?
A long time ago.
Well,
if you like it,
should we sleep in these outfits tonight
without showering?
What?
So you can take a good look.
Thank you
for letting me into your family.
Ouch. Nut!
Don't get too emotional.
Get in the shower.
I want to sleep.
All right.
Then…
can we keep the outfits
and wear them to the party?
It's a simple event.
We don't need to dress up.
Everyone there will be Mom's guests.
We're all friends.
I don't want you to look too good.
Mom's friends will faint.
Fine.
I'll only look good for you, then.
Nut.
Good boy.
I'll go take a shower.
Nut.
What's a party like?
Is it something with flashing lights,
people dancing,
and falling confetti?
Is it going to be fun like that?
-How are you?
-I'm good.
You're still so pretty.
-You look the same.
-Thanks.
-Su and Na are here.
-They are?
-It has been so long.
Let's head in.
-Hey, host.
-Pritr!
They're dancing.
How's this?
Aren't they having fun?
Just seeing your mom happy
makes me happy.
Oh…
be careful.
Hello.
-Hello.
-I'm sorry.
-Thank you for coming.
-Of course.
How could we miss it?
It's a rare occasion for this house
to host a party.
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Tofu. Set the table for Chu and Nhong.
Okay.
I never thought I would see this house
with such atmosphere.
-Me neither.
-Right.
Is it Tofu's doing?
Yes.
I got to this point, thanks to Tofu.
-I should help Tofu.
-Go ahead.
You can grab the water.
I can't help but envy them.
We can't host such a party. We live alone.
We have no friends or family.
It's just the two of us.
Don't envy them.
It's nice to have a happy family.
We don't need a big family,
children,
or a marriage license.
It doesn't matter what people think.
It's up to the two of us, okay?
We are a family.
Like how Tofu is Nut's family, right?
Right.
He's more than family.
-Make yourself at home.
-Okay.
-Mom made this.
-Did she?
-Hello
-Hello.
-Thank you.
-It's great.
You haven't eaten yet.
Please excuse me.
Are you tired, Tofu?
Thank you for helping me with the guests.
No problem.
I've never done anything like this.
It's quite fun.
Na.
Saen.
I'm happy to see you happy and healthy.
How can she be healthy?
Alzheimer's destroys health.
Lucky you have a son.
Nut is behaving better.
He probably won't let you get sick
and burden people again.
It's probably hard on you,
suffering from two diseases back to back.
What kind of karma is this?
Jan.
If you can't speak nice, then don't.
I'm sorry.
Jan tends to say hurtful things.
Hurtful is different
from disrespectful.
As I recall,
I only invited Uncle Saen.
You came here uninvited.
If you can't behave,
then you should leave.
This event is for my mom.
I want her to be surrounded
by good people.
Calm down, Nut.
As long as she's here,
let's welcome her.
I don't mind it.
I understand that this is who you are.
Well,
you may think that…
I'm selfish
and I'm being a burden to my son
because of my sickness.
Since we can't choose what disease we get,
all I can do is to accept it
and live the best I can.
It's good that you realize that,
so you can find peace.
Excuse me.
Sorry for interrupting.
It's time for the highlight.
Should we get ready?
Nut.
Take your mom.
Song is waiting.
Let's go, Mom.
Please enjoy.
Mrs. Na.
What song will you choose?
If you're staying,
I'll find you a table.
Follow me.
If you can't behave,
don't sit with me.
I'm embarrassed.
What is it?
Do I look more handsome?
You keep staring at me.
I guess.
I saw the photo of you in a suit.
You looked different.
Are you surprised?
There may be more surprises
coming your way.
Get ready for them.
I mean,
get ready for my handsomeness.
I'll look better every day.
We're starting soon.
Please excuse me.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
You might wonder
why I suddenly invited you all here today
when I rarely ever did anything like this
the whole time we've known each other.
To tell you the truth,
I have Alzheimer's.
What?
I'm sorry if I've dampened the party,
but I've decided that it didn't matter
when I told you.
When I first found out,
my reaction was the same as yours now.
I was confused. I didn't know
what to say or what to do.
When I got a hold of myself,
I started preparing
and researched about the disease.
This disease
will strip me away of memories,
skills,
and my pride,
little by little.
Finally, I know that I'll start
to lose myself.
I'll turn into…
someone else.
All of this got me
to decide to stay in the present
and…
strengthen our family ties.
I know
that it will be harder on them
in the future.
From now on,
your mom may turn into
someone new every day.
I may turn into someone
who can't help myself.
I may be unreasonable,
clumsy,
and I may do things…
foolishly
or in a silly manner.
But I always know
that you'll never leave me.
You've always taken good care of me.
I want you to take care
of your own heart too.
This includes
everyone here.
In the end,
it may hurt
that I won't remember you.
You may be the only one who remembers me.
If that day comes,
I want all of you to know that…
even though you won't be in my memories,
I believe that you'll remain in my heart.
Thank you everyone for coming today.
I also
thank my son
for having the idea for this party.
I just want
to gather all the memories
and the love of everyone once again.
I may be sad, but let's have some fun.
I want my last memory with all of you
to be filled with happiness.
It doesn't matter who you were
You introduced me to a new world
I learned what love and compassion are
-When I someone I love
-Loves me back
You lifted my heart
This worn-out heart finally sees
Some wonderful days ever since
You became a part of my life
You're my breath
I can't live without you
I heard some patients found miracles.
I guess Alzheimer's is different.
Since the world isn't so nice to us,
let's try our best instead.
Nut and I will do our best
to take care of his mom,
rather than give up
and let the disease
erase her identity forever.
I'm sorry.
I never knew how much you suffered
after you got married.
I shouldn't have pushed him on you.
Don't worry about it.
It's all in the past.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I made my own decisions.
I still feel bad about it.
Back then, Sibmeun was perfect
in every way.
I thought you could trust him
with your life.
Who would have known
that one day,
that man would turn your life upside down.
Nobody knows what lies ahead of us.
At that time,
we both tried…
our very best.
We chose what was best for us
at that time.
I'm really sorry.
I lost touch with you.
I never knew you were hurt
both physically and mentally.
Pritr.
You really don't have to apologize.
I'm not suffering as much anymore. Okay?
I chose to stay in the present.
I'm going to live every day
as best as I physically can.
If there's anything I can help with,
you must let me know.
I'm happy to help.
Your visits will be more than enough.
I promise.
-Mom.
-What is it?
They're asking for you.
Okay.
-I'll see you outside.
-Okay.
Peeranut.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
What I did in the past
must have scarred you.
I just want you to understand
that I did everything I did
because your father asked me
to take care of you.
At that time,
I thought it was better for you.
On that day,
I intended to call your mother.
Na was my junior
who I genuinely adored and cared for.
I didn't want it to become an issue.
Unfortunately, your father picked up.
It's too late to say it now,
but I'm really sorry.
Did you also tell Dad…
about the exam?
I did it
because…
You meant well.
You studied sciences in school.
Why would you pursue arts?
Engineering has better advantages
than Communication Arts.
I should have pursued the army
like your son.
That would have been the best.
I might have become a prime minister.
Back then,
that's what I thought.
But now,
I know that it's better
to study what you like.
I can see that you're successful now
because you got to study what you wanted.
Even if I failed,
it's okay.
What kids choose
is what they have to live with.
Adults aren't joining their kids
in school.
They don't experience what the kids have.
Even if they fail,
they'll get to learn
and grow.
That's true.
I'm sorry, Peeranut.
I know
that the world is moving forward,
and people my age may be moving backwards.
I'm trying.
I'm slowly learning new things.
I might not understand everything now…
I might…
not agree with some things.
You don't need to agree with everything.
Just trying to understand
and not hurting anyone
is good enough.
If we understand each other more,
not just you and I,
or in school,
but within families,
maybe we'll all understand each other…
someday.
Do you like this one?
I'm trying.
You should've invited your dad.
I guess he's busy
since he's working on Tatarn's case.
Why are you surprised?
Didn't you know
that Song's father was Mr. Anik?
We weren't all together in Chiang Mai,
so I didn't tell you.
Do you have to tell her who my dad is?
That's silly. Who would want to know?
Maybe someone does.
I just want to show off
that I know someone with a rank.
My dad is just a normal police officer.
If you want to show off some big names,
you should pick Gen's father.
He's a navy admiral.
You know more people than I expected
for an amnesiac who always stays home.
Isn't it beneficial
to have good connections?
They may be able to help
if something happens.
What help did you expect from my dad?
He can't even help you
find your family.
That, he can't help with.
Maybe he can help with something else.
Oh, wow.
Speak of the devil. Right on queue.
Hi, Dad.
Yes. That's great.
You can stay longer this time.
Yes. I'll see you.
What did he say?
Don't tell me.
Is he free to join us now?
No.
He said he'll come to Bangkok.
Mr. Saen moved Tarn to Bangkok,
so Dad will follow him.
I moved Tatarn to Bangkok.
Why is that?
It's because of what you said.
What I said?
You told me
to correct my mistakes while I still can.
Not to neglect them and drown in regret.
I realized that Tatarn's condition
hasn't improved.
And it could be because
I made the wrong decision
to leave him there.
I think that it would be better
to get treated by good doctors in Bangkok.
I'll be able to visit you more from now on
since I have to follow up on Tatarn too.
You can tell me if Nut is busy
when you have doctor's appointments.
I'll take you.
Thank you very much
for always taking care of Nut and me.
We would get to meet a lot more
if you moved next door.
Actually, Jan and I…
split a while ago.
It's not because of work.
We decided not to be together anymore.
We haven't divorced,
but the love is gone.
That's what I thought too.
But since it has nothing to do with me,
I decided not to pry.
I wanted you to know.
I wanted you to know
that we ended up this way
because of Jan and Sib's vicious plan.
The two of them…
I know.
I've known it for a while.
Sib said it when he was drunk.
Aren't you angry?
I'm angrier at myself
for being indecisive.
As I said before,
I'm totally fine with the present.
I know you might not be,
but I believe you can get through it.
We've all
been through painful things.
I want us to let go of the past.
Let's forgive ourselves,
and live the rest of our lives happily.
-Thank you all.
-It was fun.
-Get home safe.
-Bye.
-Goodbye.
-Thank you.
-Your singing was great.
-Happy to hear that.
Enough compliments.
-Thanks for coming.
-You sing a lot too.
-Mom.
-Yes?
-I'll clean up.
-Go ahead.
Thank you for coming.
Take care of yourself.
You too.
Saen.
What are you doing?
Why did you get me in trouble?
What's this about?
About Tatarn.
I know you moved him to Bangkok.
Why did you do that?
You should've left him there.
Your boss will cover for you
even if he dies.
Why the sudden humanity?
I don't want him in a vegetative state.
I may be a bad person,
but he's our nephew.
I have no reason to want him dead.
You're the one
who lacks humanity.
He's your nephew,
but you've never cared for him.
You just leave him there,
waiting for his death.
Everything I did was for you.
You never appreciated me.
You destroyed us to impress Na.
I didn't do it
just because of what she said,
but I'm sick of it!
I'm sick of getting pressured by everyone,
including Sib, Mr. Sakon,
Ms. Ching, and you.
I'm sick of this kind of life!
I want to let go of the past.
I want to be able to forgive myself.
I want to live the rest of my life happily
like what Na said,
but I don't see how it can be possible.
I know all good things
must come to an end,
but it is so sad
to see that what's left
is loneliness.
What we can savor
are happiness
and memories.
For Mrs. Na, though,
the memory of today
will be short-lived.
Alzheimer's
is taking her away from everyone.
She's fading away,
but not dying.
She's fading away
because her memories are perishing away.
When her memories slowly disappear,
her belongings
slowly fall into slumber.
This means
that each item is where the owners
store their memories.
Mr. Rocking Chair.
Ms. Sofa.
Ms. Phone.
Mr. Right Slipper.
All of them
came to life with Mrs. Na's memories.
Since she's slowly losing her memories,
they are starting to fall asleep.
Not just memories,
but tears…
also wake us up
to comfort our sad owner like Nut.
I came to life
because of Tatarn's memories.
Tatarn's love
and his ties with Nut
woke a teddy bear like me up.
Those gave me a conscience,
and let me think,
move,
and communicate.
Tatarn may be unconscious,
but his memories still thrive.
That's why I'm alive.
More than being alive,
there's a miracle that occurred.
It's a miracle that turned a teddy bear
into a human.
When Dad gets back,
I'll tell him about us.
I have many good qualities.
Do I still have to prove them?
When I removed the pus,
I found this splinter.
The doctor suspects that it was likely
from the assault weapon.
I reckon it's a vital piece of evidence
that will help us identify
who the perpetrator is.
Subtitle translation by:
Pattranun Bunyanund