THIS MOVIE WAS CREATED FOR ENTERTAINMENT.
IT IS NOT BASED ON HISTORICAL EVENTS
AND IS NOT INTENDED TO MOCK ANYBODY
OR DEFAME THEM.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
LAST HEROES
KUNG RAGA VILLAGE
Come on, come on.
Hey. Puek. Chote.
-Hey!
-Yes.
Boontueng.
Hi, Fang.
Giving the elephants a bath this early?
Are you going to harvest the rice?
Yes. Before it all falls.
-Let's go, Soi.
-Yes, Auntie Fang.
Be safe.
Yeah! I'm going to the rice field,
not a minefield. Shit.
-Come on.
-The mahouts are so handsome!
Mom. Dad.
The village chief and the monk
are calling us.
See you at the gathering yard.
Fang!
Saeng!
Fang, are you here?
Hey, Duen.
Fang left a while ago.
-Where did she go?
-To the rice paddy.
Saeng, wake up!
They are heading to the gathering yard.
Why are you still sleeping?
Wake up!
Mom.
Whatever reason they are gathering for
has nothing to do with me.
How could you say that?
Get up and hurry. Come along.
Hurry up!
Hey, Saeng. Aren't you coming?
Yeah. But you go ahead.
Hurry. Let's go. Come on.
What's going on?
I have no idea.
I want to turn this way.
-Are you tired?
-Absolutely.
I didn't ask you, old lady.
I asked Kong over there.
Wow. Old lady?
-Fug.
-Fuck Fug. It's Fang.
There's a gathering in the village.
Hurry up.
Gotta be now? Things are heating up,
and I'm about to have fun.
Soi, let's go.
Soi. Fang. Follow me.
Come on, come on. Run, run.
Auntie Fang, hurry up.
-Hold on.
-Wait for us.
Please wait for us.
Wait for me.
Excuse us.
Excuse me.
Today, I've called for a gathering here
because I would like to ask for volunteers
to go spy on the Munramaeng
in Yasotharavadi City.
I would like to volunteer.
If you go, who will protect our village?
What? If it's not him,
who else would it be?
Those who are proper for this job
need to seem harmless,
so nobody suspects them.
This job is very dangerous.
We need those who are smart
and sharp, specifically.
I'm not one of those people, am I?
I guess not.
Why do we need to spy on them?
I don't see that our village
has anything to do with them.
How does it not?
If they want to attack Asoraya City,
they have to come through
our Kung Raga village.
If now we think only of ourselves
or our comfort,
soon when the threat arrives,
our nation could fall.
We are merely simple farmers.
What can we do to spy on them?
-Yeah.
If nobody volunteers today,
I would like you all to consider this.
Would you like to live for yourself
day after day,
or try to live for the nation
at least once,
now, while everybody is still here today?
Those who would like to volunteer,
please stay.
Those who would not, go back home.
Let's go.
Nobody volunteers.
Thank you very much, Horm,
for considering volunteering.
Geez.
Acting like he would like
to help our village...
It would be so nice if he died on the job.
Then there would be no homosexuals
in our village.
Lower your voice.
Gon.
What?
Are you going?
Where?
To Yasotharavadi.
This time,
if we don't go,
our village will be razed to the ground.
But if I go and happen to die,
how could I live with my life?
You're quiet because you're confused,
right?
Yes, ma'am.
As for me...
-Are you going?
-No, I'm not.
What did you say that for, then?
-Let's go inside and sleep.
-Yes, ma'am.
Talking to you is like talking to a dog.
Fang, Fang.
What's going on, Boontueng?
I would like to talk to you.
About what?
About going to Yasotharavadi.
Are you going?
-I'm thinking about it.
-Thinking?
Yes, thinking.
Go and think in your home. Go!
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go, Auntie.
-Wait for me.
-Fang.
What? I don't get to sleep now?
What do you want, Horm?
I want to talk to you.
About going to Yasotharavadi, right?
Wow, yes.
But I didn't do it voluntarily.
So why are you standing there?
I fell sleep.
You go!
Where?
Go to sleep. It's late.
It's late, so you go to sleep, Gon.
-And when will you sleep?
-During the day.
I knew it.
Let's get back home.
Or you'll be in trouble.
-With Fang?
-With me!
Damn! I shouldn't have wasted time
with your matters.
Staying home and shaving myself
is better than this.
So, who can I talk to about this?
Ah, Duen.
Duen, I would like to talk to you.
I'm already in bed.
She's surely asleep since she's snoring.
Duen, Duen. That's twice.
I would like to talk to you.
-Mom. Dad.
-Yeah?
Let's get inside.
Just got out here and now you want us
to get inside.
Please be careful.
Going inside again?
So, who can I talk to now?
I would like to talk to you.
Your logic sounds good.
What? What did you say?
Moo moo?
Ah, moo.
Thank you very much. Gotta go.
Now I understand.
It's all gone.
Saeng.
You're a man. You can't be drunk
all the time like this.
Right now, the nation needs men like you
to protect it from enemies.
Mom.
How can someone like me
fight with anybody?
Of course, you can.
I would like to see you fight
like a brave soldier.
Look at Krai. Take him as an example.
You must fight at least once before I die.
Krai.
You came here to see me. What's going on?
I want to know if you will fight
with somebody else.
I haven't decided.
Because I have a concern.
My wife, Kumlai, is in this state,
as you can see.
How can I leave her here?
Yeah, I understand.
But if you decide to go,
please let me know.
I'll leave you now.
ASORAYA CITY
Commander, you pestered me to come
to this meeting. What's the matter?
I was going to have fun
with my beloved wife Jamjureethevee.
Right now is not the time to work.
Why did you have to make it a big deal,
Commander?
None of your business.
Our spies have notified me
that Yasotharavadi wants to attack us
and has sent some spy
inside the inner city, Your Majesty.
You mean, right now, some enemy has
infiltrated here
and might have learned
what is going on here, right?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I believe that such enemies
are just some lies,
Your Majesties.
Commander, are you sure that
Yasotharavadi is coming to attack us?
They promised they would end the war.
I don't think they are coming.
Why? Why?
Why would Governor Anorathaporamintin
betray us
when Yasotharavadi knows very well
how hard it is to attack our city?
The news I received is not a lie.
If we don't prepare an army to defend
ourselves, it will be too late.
Your Majesties.
If it happens,
there's no need to be afraid.
I would just dress to fight
and hold swords,
and all of our brave soldiers would be
ready to rise up to protect Our Majesty.
But I think
we shouldn't underestimate Yasotharavadi,
My Lord.
You know nothing about war.
No need to share your opinion. Understand?
I agree with my beloved wife
Jamjureethevee.
The nation is divided right now.
Whatever you want to do, do it now.
I hope you know what I mean.
I do.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
What did you get from spying
on the village that I sent you to?
We are going to win for sure.
People are not united.
They fight with each other
every single day.
They are divided into groups.
Some are always drunk.
We can easily defeat these people.
Wow. How easy it is!
I agree with you, Commander.
Fang.
Do we have volunteers
to go to Yasotharavadi yet?
Why? Are you volunteering?
Yes.
Once in a lifetime, I would like
to do something for my homeland.
That's right, Auntie Fang.
Yeah. I want to, also.
I have only one concern.
-What is it?
-Fang.
-Auntie Fang.
Kraeng. I have something to say.
About your love for me...
We are probably not meant for each other.
You should forget all about me.
You must live on without me.
Don't be too sad after I'm gone.
I'm going.
I'm really going.
I'm truly really going.
Remember my face.
Krai, what was Fang talking about?
I have no idea. I think...
she has a crush on you.
No. No! No.
Krai, tell me it's not true.
No, no!
Hey, Fang. We think it's time for us
to volunteer to go spying
in Yasotharavadi. What do you think?
I'm so worried about Kraeng.
It's a critical time
and you're chucking down liquor.
You think that's right?
Gon is probably right.
On one hand, I'm worried about Kraeng.
On the other hand,
I'm worried about Kraeng.
Why would you drink the liquor?
Auntie Fang, if you don't go, I'll go.
If you go, will you remember my face?
-Of course.
-I wasn't talking about you.
I meant Kraeng.
But, Auntie Fang,
please don't punish yourself.
Fang, I'll drink it for you.
-Yeah. Help yourself.
-Of all the battles, none are as big
as the war coming to our village.
Nobody loves you more than me, Auntie.
If you had good judgment,
you wouldn't be drinking like this.
Why don't you love yourself?
When we were young,
I was your best friend, right?
-Auntie Duen!
-No more for me.
Where is our unity?
So you guys are volunteering to spy
on Yasotharavadi with Horm, correct?
We both will go as well.
Yeah.
Krai. Boontueng.
That's good. So...
Good.
So our nation will overcome
the enemies and opponents.
They are not enough.
I'll go with them.
-Auntie Fang!
-Fang!
I knew you would come.
I have thought it through.
Between the nation and men,
I'd choose men.
-Fang!
I'm kidding.
You guys.
I could never leave my homeland
in jeopardy.
I'm very good at prying
into someone's business. Believe me.
Are you okay?
You guzzled down all of my liquor.
I didn't have any.
It's so good
that you guys are making a sacrifice
for our nation.
I am relieved now.
Those who have skills don't volunteer?
If we let everyone go with you,
then there will be no one to fight here.
I have someone with skills
to teach you guys.
This is the alchemist who will teach you
the magic spells.
Learn them carefully
-so you can use them in an emergency.
-Okay.
I will teach you guys some spells
until you are good at it.
Today, I'll teach you the spells to call
for wind, water, rain and everything.
First, the water. Watch and learn.
I was totally startled.
-Fang.
-Yes?
-It's your turn.
-To call for water?
Yes.
There. The water called by Fang.
Fang, look!
Is that the water you called or bubbles
from fish gobbling something?
Yeah. Two bubbles are better than nothing.
It's good enough for now.
Keep practicing
and you'll get better, Fang.
Yes, sir.
Horm! Now it's your turn.
Water.
Are you calling for more water,
Auntie Horm?
Today, I'll teach you 15 poses
of Thai boxing.
I'm lost from the beginning.
So much screaming.
What the heck?
Are you guys really volunteering
to go to Yasotharavadi?
Yuck! You guys overestimate yourselves,
don't you?
Yeah. I bet you will not make it
back here.
Is there a monkey show around here?
No more. Luckily, I knew
he was going to do that.
-Auntie Fang.
-What?
Kraeng is here!
Kraeng is here? See?
I knew it! He surely has a crush on me.
I think he's bringing elephants here
for a bath.
Soi, don't lie to me. He came to see me.
He really is, Auntie.
Shit. I'm so embarrassed.
No. It wasn't me.
-Fang is so talented.
-Yeah.
Men always compliment their wife.
Don't be shy.
Not you, Kraeng! It's you, Fang.
Freaking Duen!
Kraeng!
Kraeng.
I have blessed you guys
with warding spells.
From now on, you all are invincible.
You can't be physically harmed.
Gon, step forward.
Wait right here.
I'll bring you the first aid kit.
Where?
Do you think she'll survive?
She's all right. Don't you worry.
Hey, Duen.
-Yes, Dad?
-How are you doing?
Dad. Mom.
I have decided to go to Yasotharavadi.
Duen.
I didn't volunteer at first
because I was worried about you both.
Though I have a feminine mind...
physically, I'm still a man.
I have nothing to fear from the enemies.
I am so proud of you.
Though you're like this,
I am confident
that you will accomplish this job.
Yeah, Dad.
Take care of yourself.
No need to worry about us.
Your dad and I will pray to the gods
to protect you
until you come back.
I have to leave home
and you for a while.
You're the only one
that I'm worried about.
In this situation,
I can't be thinking of just myself or you.
Because if we can't accomplish this job,
not only our lives
but also everybody's lives here
will come to an end.
If I don't come back,
promise me
that you will take care of Kumlai for me.
Can you do that, Chote?
You have to promise me first
that you'll come back, my brother.
Kumlai.
Kumlai. Kumlai, I'm right here.
You don't need to be afraid, Kumlai.
Don't be afraid.
No need to be afraid, Kumlai.
I'm right here.
Don't worry about me.
If you really must go...
I won't forbid you.
Please show your grace to protect him.
I will hurry and come back to you.
Good luck, be safe, and be victorious.
Amen.
Rise!
Find the monk Thammarong.
He'll help you guys.
Pick up the pace. Hurry.
No more dillydallying.
It will be much harder after dark.
Yeah. For big results, we need to be bold
and take risks.
Next time, whatever happens,
we have to follow it through.
You're right, Duen.
-Chote.
-Yeah?
Please take good care of my mom and dad.
Yes, I will.
For the next meal,
you've gotta find them some food.
Duen. Are you saying your last words?
Freaking Fang! I know,
your dad is dead, your mom is dead.
So you have no one to worry about.
Yes, you're right.
Your dad is dead, your mom is dead,
really?
It's time to go.
-Wait for me!
-Saeng.
I'm here.
Shouldn't you leave the liquor first,
Saeng?
Be careful, Saeng.
Wait for me.
They are camping up that way.
Walk for the time
it takes the rice to cook.
Boontueng. You said the time
The rice would have been burnt by now.
When are we going to get there? Shit.
Real soon. Be patient, Fang.
Yeah, Fang. I agree with him.
Be patient.
Remember this. For big results,
we need to be bold and take risks.
You don't agree?
I am so hungry for it.
Hungry for the fight, Auntie Duen?
Food. I'm hungry for food, Soi.
-Are you not?
-I am.
I agree with Duen.
We have walked for a long time.
No shower, no food at all.
I am so hungry that I could die.
You're right, Gon. Since I have known you,
today is the only day
that you've said something right.
You don't need to agree with me, Horm.
So maybe we should stop and rest.
And I'll find out early in the morning
where their camp is.
Freaking Horm! Watch out!
You almost hit my face.
So, move.
Shit.
Freaking Horm! I said that you almost hit
my face. What are you doing?
Stop fighting.
We should be united.
If we are fighting each other like this,
how can we conquer any enemy?
I think she's right.
Whatever she says is right.
Yeah?
Could you stop doing that?
So, walk away.
Stop, stop!
You didn't listen to what Fang just said?
We need to be united.
That's right, Duen.
You guys went back to fighting
as soon as she'd said it.
So, I think we should drink to make a vow
that we will be in harmony.
I agree.
To live and to die together. Be united.
Okay. Let's drink to make a vow.
Where is Saeng?
Over there.
-You freaking Saeng!
-Let's go.
We can make a vow later
after he finishes peeing.
I have drunk it.
That's your problem. Let's go.
I think their camp is not very far
beyond the cave ahead.
This way. Hurry.
Auntie Fang.
What are you calling her for?
Walk up to her.
Krai. Where are they?
Right there. On the bank of the river.
Should we attack them now?
Well...
You didn't answer us, you just shot them.
Duen, what are you gonna do?
You guys, go!
I dare you!
You guys...
they're all dead. We won!
Hooray!
I feel very disgusted dressing like them.
You know that I despise them.
You think I like this?
Look. It hides all of my beauty.
But I like it. There are lots of men here.
Krai, for big results, we need to be bold
and take risks.
We have to do whatever it takes.
Walk straight. Don't show any red flags.
What red flag?
Fang. Gon.
Do you know where they keep the liquor?
Saeng! Can you not drink
at this moment? Jackass.
Wow, Fang. If you were not this pretty,
I would have slapped your face.
Don't believe him, Auntie Fang.
He's lying to you.
He's not lying. It's probably true.
Soi.
What are you doing here?
Right.
That was a close call.
Shit. Almost got ourselves discovered.
Hurry and bring the woman you caught
to serve me here.
Yes, sir.
Krai, Krai.
For big results, we need to be bold
and take risks.
We have to do whatever it takes.
You don't know any other words?
I'm just reminding him.
You'll surely see me fight.
Krai. You're stepping on my foot.
I'm sorry.
Fang. Slow reaction?
Yes, it is.
I think it's bruised.
Let go! Let go of me!
Let go! I said let go of me!
Sons of bitches!
Help!
No! No!
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Fang.
I feel so sorry for her.
Let go of me!
Don't! Don't!
No!
-Krai!
-Krai. For big results,
-we need to be bold and take risks.
-We need to be bold and take risks.
-We have to do whatever it takes.
-Fang.
-Yeah?
Are you mocking me?
-You said it every time you stopped Krai.
-You bastard.
Look. She's mean to me.
-Stop!
-Krai. I told you to stop.
Auntie Duen!
Don't do it, Krai! Krai.
Stop!
Krai.
-Krai.
Horm. What did you do? He's fainted now.
I said, "Krai, stop!"
-Fang.
-Are you all right, Auntie Fang?
Take a look at her.
What's wrong with him?
-He's drunk, my dear.
-No!
He's drunk, sir.
-Good. Have a good time.
-Yes, sir!
So tomorrow you guys can go home.
Yes, sir!
Duen.
Did I say "Yes, sir" like a man?
Firm and very manly.
Who's manly?
Auntie Duen!
Auntie Fang, you shouldn't have done that.
She said I was very manly.
I couldn't take it.
You guys.
What hit me?
Foot.
Whose foot?
Mine.
Let's call it even.
You guys, hurry up
and enjoy the party, so we won't attract
any attention like Saeng over there.
THREE MONTHS LATER
Krai, you miss Kumlai?
Fang, you know
that Krai has never been away
from his wife.
It's impossible for him not to worry
about her.
I wonder how she's doing.
You don't need to be so worried.
She's in the village.
She won't be harmed
because everybody
will take good care of her
to ease your worries.
You have to promise me
that you will love only me.
I promise you that I will love
and take care of you until the day I die.
Don't say that.
If you die...
I probably can't live my life.
We came here, and we don't know
if we will go back or not.
Don't you guys miss someone
at the village?
Daorueng, I love you.
Give me a hand.
Boontueng.
Auntie Fang, Auntie Fang!
What? What's all this noise?
-Someone is here.
-Who?
Kraeng.
Kraeng! Tell me,
he came here for me, right?
He didn't come here for you.
-Are you sure?
-He didn't come here for you.
-Do not tease me.
-I'm serious.
How are you doing, Tang.
See? He came here for me.
He's calling my name.
He called the elephant. Her name is Tang.
Yours is Fang.
Go. To the bath.
Gone, all gone.
What's all gone?
Your hearing.
Kraeng, Kraeng.
Auntie Fang.
-Kraeng.
-Auntie Fang, come here.
-Auntie Fang, come right here.
-What?
-Look.
Look at yourself in the reflection.
Wow, Soi.
You are such a lovely niece.
I know.
-Turn around.
-Turn around?
-Fang.
-Yeah?
-What?
Turn around and look at what's behind you.
The Munramaeng are naked.
White as pearl.
I'm not gonna look because I'll look only
at my lovely Kraeng.
Wow, so big.
Yeah. You're right, Duen.
So white, so big. Pleasing to the eyes.
Unlike somebody here.
Is that a face or a toad? I think my foot
probably looks better than his face.
You think so, Duen?
-Yeah. Fang.
-What?
Don't jokingly offend him.
-He might understand your words.
-Nah. He doesn't get it.
He could kill you.
No, no way. Right?
You don't understand, right?
I do. I'll kick your ass.
So white and such big butts.
I want to be a little bird
chirping right there.
I'm already there. For quite some time.
Here.
Damn! You're gonna get us exposed.
Horm. That guy is eyeing you.
Really? Don't lie to me.
-You really can't hold it in, huh?
-Jackass!
Krai did this, I'm sure.
Yeah, I think so, too.
Yeah.
Krai, what are you doing?
You're gonna spoil our big plan.
Watch out. We're on the same side.
Finally, you...
Sugorpan. Take him away.
Krai.
Let go.
Let go of me.
I said let go.
Krai shouldn't have been hasty.
I was enjoying naked men. Anyone see that?
Why are you spying on us?
Why?
I'm gonna kill you all.
Take him and chain him up.
Lock him up in a cell.
Don't let him die easily.
Go!
Let go of me! Let go!
Post more guards. I trust no one.
YASOTHARAVADI CITY
Let go of me!
Duen.
Which way?
How would I know?
I'm not from around here.
Hurry up and choose one. Otherwise,
the Munramaeng will come get us.
Fang. Soldiers.
Let's go upstairs to hide from them.
-Which way? Let's go.
-There.
-Hurry up.
-Hurry. Let's go.
Get out of my way.
All right, I think we're safe now.
Duen, whose house is this?
How would I know?
I'm not from around here.
We are women. We should walk carefully.
Look at us.
Fang, someone's coming.
Okay, just go do your stuff.
We have just escaped from the guys,
now we have to face the girls.
-Soi, find some place to hide.
-Okay.
Look around.
See where we can hide.
Follow me.
Hurry. Let's get inside.
-Mig Khin.
-Yes, My Lady?
-Is the house in order?
-Yes, My Lady.
-Fang!
-What a dumbass.
-Mig Khin.
-Yes, My Lady?
-You said the house is in order.
-It is, My Lady.
So, who has just entered that room?
Mue Tor. Tor Pa Yee. Did you see anyone?
-I didn't.
-I did,
but I'm not sure who that was.
-So, you go and look.
-You go first.
Both of you go!
-Yes, My Lady.
-Mig Khin.
-Yes, My Lady?
-Go help those two.
-Yes, My Lady.
Somebody's peeking at me.
Mue Tor. Tor Pa Yee. Did you see anyone?
Nobody.
Go inside and look.
-Yes, My Lady.
There's nobody here.
Good grief!
Somebody must have been here.
You guys are useless.
Daorueng.
What's the matter?
I don't know.
I think you're pregnant.
-Pregnant?
What are you gonna do?
Boontueng is not here.
Daorueng, go get some rest.
I'll do this for you.
Come, Daorueng. Go sit down.
I wonder how Boontueng is doing.
He's fine, I'm sure. He'll come back soon.
Daorueng, you don't need to worry
about him. He can take care of himself.
Fang, look.
These fabrics are so beautiful.
If they were sold in our village,
they would cost a fortune.
This one is beautiful, too, Gon.
It would look very good on you.
I think it's too old-fashioned.
This one here!
So beautiful. How do I look?
The color is very bright. It suits you.
Wow, this one here looks good too.
Yeah. The patterns are delicate.
What's the matter with you?
I fold it and you unfold it.
When is it gonna be done?
You could have told me nicely, bitch.
All my lice must be dead from that slap.
I'll go to sleep now.
I don't want my lice to die.
But how are we going to find the monk
that our chief told us to find?
-Are you asking me?
-Yes.
-How would I know?
-I'm so worried about Horm.
We don't know if she's still alive.
Freaking Horm.
If she wasn't crazy to sleep on the wagon,
it wouldn't have been like this.
You guys don't need to worry. I think,
she can take care of herself.
I agree. Horm is street-smart.
We should worry about Krai.
He's hot-tempered.
Where's Saeng?
He must be drunk around here somewhere.
Hopefully, he will not reveal our secret.
Horm!
You can't resist men, can you?
How is the investigation going
that I requested?
There are conflicts among the noblemen.
They are divided into two groups.
So it's a good time to gather our army
to attack them.
If so, prepare an army and wait
for the right time.
Priests, could you find an auspicious
time for the Prince?
I'll do it right away, Your Majesty.
This time I have prepared a large army
to seize the city as a present
for you, Father.
Mung Tra Bureng, don't underestimate them.
There are people ready to fight you
along the way, aren't there?
Pi Ya Sawe, you think
my son can't secure us the victory?
It's just a small village.
I don't think it'll be hard to crush it.
I can destroy all of them in a wink.
Easy-peasy, just like an elephant
stepping on some grass.
If you think so,
I hope you can deliver
what you just promised.
Don't let this small matter
be a problem for Yasotharavadi.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You guys are looking for me, correct?
No, we are not.
If not, why are you here?
We want to meet a monk
when we come to a temple, of course.
I am a monk.
Yes, we see you as a monk.
Or would you like us to see you
as something else.
What would you like me to be?
I'll be as such.
What is he talking about? I'm so confused.
Fang. Duen.
Or is he the monk that we are looking for?
I don't think so, Gon.
I don't think he's the one
that is going to help us.
Right, Fang?
I am Thammarong. I'm the one
who is going to help you.
See, Fang?
I told you. And you don't believe me. See?
Amen. We're so sorry.
We would like to salute you.
From now on, you have to call me
Ya Sin Visura.
-Ya Sin...
-Visura.
Who is that, Duen?
How would I know?
Me. That's my name in Yasotharavadi.
-I see.
-Don't forget this name.
-Yes, sir.
Be gentle.
Do it gently.
La Ong Inlay.
The monk Ya Sin Visura is here.
Namaste.
You came to visit me here.
What can I do for you?
My relatives came from Mawtamaeng.
Staying with me is inappropriate.
So I'd like you to teach them
to do something
in exchange for a place to sleep.
Could you do that for me?
Yes, sir. Since you know them,
I'll teach them.
So that they can serve
the Royal family like us.
Isn't that right, La Ong Inlay?
I really appreciate it.
And, you guys, work as hard as you can.
-Yes, sir.
So Sew, follow me. I'll try to find a way
to get you into the army again.
Yes, sir.
You asked me to come here.
What can I do for you?
I would like to ask you to enlist him
in the army
under the command of your father,
Po Ong Tin. Can you help me?
Him?
Yes, sir. I'm Boon...
My name is So Sew, sir.
He's not from here, is he, sir?
This man is just a commoner
whose village was affected by the battle.
He came here,
just hoping that his village will survive.
He has nothing else to gain
from this battle.
So I just hope that you could help him
to survive here
until his job is done.
Could you be of help to your mentor?
Father, I don't agree with this battle.
We have promised to end the war.
So, why are we breaking our own word?
We didn't want to end the war
from the beginning.
We can't let Asoraya
be a worrisome loose end
that could attack us at any time.
You are my son. Just do what I say.
I don't agree with everything in this war,
and I'm grateful for your kindness.
I'll take care of you and help
as seems appropriate.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Master, since I'm about to take the army
to attack a city far from here,
I would like to ask you for a talisman.
Could you give me one?
The thing you want
is actually unnecessary.
If you put your mind to it,
you will succeed and win this battle.
Please, Master. Give me a talisman
to make me feel secure.
If you really want it,
I'll give you one.
I have kept it for over 20 years.
-Ivory! You're so lucky.
-Ivory or a knife handle?
Because of this, I've had to lie
on my stomach for 20 years.
I'm giving it to you.
Well, Master...
Come on, help me here.
Master...
It hurts.
It must have been in the bone.
Master...
Master, I think...
that we should leave it like this.
Or you'll bleed to death.
Yeah. Leave it where it is.
Soi, be on the lookout for us.
"Lookout", not look in, right?
I'm going.
Use the spell, Gon. Call him over.
Come here.
Stop.
Where do you keep the battle plans?
With me.
Bring it to me right now.
Your spell is no longer working. Let's go.
Where?
To wash our feet, of course.
They're soaked with pee.
Damn it!
-Fang.
-Yeah?
We're standing here.
Aren't you afraid that they'll wake up?
How could they?
Remember the sleeping spell?
Just put them to sleep. And voila!
I've never seen you being so smart
like you are today.
Go ahead.
I want to know
when they are taking the army there.
Okay, you say the spell.
What are you doing here?
Buatong and Tongkayee asked me to see
if you are asleep.
Isn't that right?
Fang, Fang.
Oh, my God, you two.
Sleeping like a log. How am I gonna move?
How's it going, you two? No more bragging?
-You also failed last night, didn't you?
-What?
-What about you two?
-Yeah, you shouldn't say anything mean.
Stop fighting for a little bit.
Fang, what are we gonna do now?
We've been here for quite some time.
We still haven't got any information.
I've been busy with your quarrel,
so I haven't had time to think.
Think about what? Your plans always fail.
The witch doctor.
Which doctor?
The alchemist gave us some good stuff.
What good stuff, Fang?
What's the good stuff?
I totally forgot. Shit.
-Bitch. Took this long to remember.
-Here.
Here. Hold this.
It's a sedative.
-What?
Pour it here, Duen.
Whoever inhales it,
in the blink of an eye...
Auntie Fang!
Fang, Fang. What's wrong with Fang?
Fang, Fang.
It's very potent.
It's almost time to go to the battle.
Is everything ready?
Yes, sir.
I think we will win this battle.
The weapons and artillery are ready to go.
You don't need to worry.
Don't let anyone in Asoraya know
about this plan.
If anyone gets in our way, kill them.
I won't lose this battle.
Take good care of yourself, Dad.
I'm leaving now.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the room for dancing girls.
-Are you a dancer?
-Yes, sir.
How was it, Horm? Did you succeed?
Horm!
Horm! Horm, Horm, Horm.
Just like me.
Mue Tor. Tor Pa Yee.
Go tell La Ong Inlay
that I thank her for training the girls
to dance so gracefully.
-I will.
Who are these girls?
They are relatives of the monk
Ya Sin Visura.
He asked La Ong Inlay and us to teach them
how to serve the Royal family.
So we both think that they should serve
the Prince and My Ladies.
Great.
You two shall give them proper training.
Let me see your faces.
All of you, please look up
to let the Prince see your faces.
Have them beheaded!
My Lord, calm down.
Wait, My Lord.
Get them out of here.
Hurry up. Get out of here.
You two as well.
Wait.
Not you two.
Them.
Get out.
-Yes, Your Highness.
Such useless staff.
How is it going with the auspicious time
for the army?
-Yes, Your Majesty.
For the most auspicious time
to take the army into battle,
the Prince should leave Yasotharavadi
from dawn to dusk
on the 12th waxing moon day
in the first lunar month.
I don't agree.
The most auspicious time
is not the one the priest Mayatai said.
Rather, it is from dusk to dawn,
on the 12th waning moon day
in the second lunar month.
That is the most auspicious time
for the Prince
to take the army.
So which one is it?
Priest Pawatin,
I'm sure your time is best for my son.
I don't think so.
The priest Mayatai's time
should be best for the Prince.
I'm afraid that if you go
at the priest Pawatin's time,
you won't be victorious.
Enough!
You two'd better talk
and come to a conclusion.
Then let me know.
Don't fight in front of me like this.
I don't need to listen to your argument.
If there is no conclusion
by the next meeting,
I'll have you all beheaded.
You've got all the information, right?
I heard that they'll move the army
in the first and second lunar months.
At dawn and at dusk.
Did you hear the same?
How are they gonna do that?
Both in the first and second lunar months?
Neither of those times.
They all are going to get beheaded.
Me?
Damn. Not you. And not us.
But the two priests. If they can't find
the most auspicious time.
What are we gonna do now?
When can we go back home, then?
I think next time we should get closer
to hear it more clearly.
Yeah, Fang. If you want to hear it
more clearly next time,
you would have to piggyback on the Prince.
Would he let her do that?
Found the battle plan?
It must be here somewhere.
You two hurry up before someone comes in.
Fang, I've found nothing.
Oh, God, someone is coming.
Fang, Fang, run!
-Nothing in there.
-Wonder where they put it.
Somebody's coming.
Hurry up, Auntie.
What about Gon and Horm?
Won't they be caught?
-Soi.
-Duen, Duen.
This way. Soi.
They're right behind us.
What should we do? They found us.
What can we do but run?
They're coming.
Fang.
What should we do now?
Whatever it is, let's do it.
I know what we should do.
On the 11th of the waxing moon, at dawn,
at 7:00 a.m. of the second lunar month,
which is the auspicious time for victory,
so suitable for the Prince
to move the army.
Mung Tra Bureng,
have you got your army ready?
For the auspicious time that the priest
just said, I have the army ready
for the battle, Father.
Great.
To celebrate this auspicious time,
I have prepared dancers
to dance in front of His Majesty
and my son
as entertainment before the war.
Which dancer do you like?
I'll bring her to you.
Commander Po Ong Tin...
Your Highness...
these dancers could be spies.
Duen, we didn't practice this pose.
Stop! Soldiers!
Take these dancers to the prison.
Auntie Fang!
These dancers could be spies
infiltrating us to get information
about the battle.
Let go of me. Let go now!
Duen.
I can walk in there myself.
You guys, what happened?
Duen, you tell him.
It's because of you, isn't it?
You always blame me.
If you guys could dance delicately
like me,
we wouldn't have been caught.
Geez. You danced like a monkey.
Yeah. Anybody could see through that.
-Yeah.
-Enough.
Stop fighting. We'd better figure out
how to get out of here.
How are we gonna get out of here?
What are we gonna do now?
I don't know, either.
Tomorrow is the most auspicious time
for me to take the army into battle.
So I came here to say goodbye.
-Tomorrow?
-But I still lack confidence,
as I'm worried that this battle
is not like anything in the past.
Actually,
the auspicious time is not
what matters the most.
Be confident, be brave.
And you'll win
no matter what the auspicious time is.
Your advice is very helpful.
I'll keep that in mind
and follow it through.
Bless you.
Be safe and sound. Return victorious.
Your Highness...
if you're still worried...
then take this.
This is just the handle.
Where is the rest?
Come to get the blade next time.
Stop the bleeding.
It's all right.
Take care of him. I must go now.
Be safe and sound.
-Master!
Master, master!
Saeng, Boontueng, and Soi...
I wonder how they are doing.
They are moving the army tomorrow.
What are we gonna do?
If we can't get out of here,
everything we have done will be in vain.
The villagers alone can't fight them off.
I'm so worried.
If the village is ruined because of me...
I would rather die.
Don't say that, Duen.
If we must die...
we all should die together.
-Fang!
-I'm serious.
Darling, look at the moon. It's so pretty.
Please, all angels,
please protect my son Duen from any harm.
-Please.
-Please protect my son.
Saeng, my son.
I wonder how you are doing.
I, as the King
and your father, would like to give you
blessings to win this battle.
Thank you, Father.
I will bring you the victory
without doubt.
Bring me the victory.
You two hurry up and go help the others
before it's too late.
Saeng!
How are you doing, Boontueng?
It's time to do it.
We'll go help Krai and the rest.
You should get everything ready.
Don't worry. I'll do it.
Thongdee. Chote.
What's the matter, Puek?
Boontueng has sent a message.
-Hurry up, Soi.
-Auntie Fang.
-Soi.
-I'm here to help.
-Krai.
Come on.
-Go.
-Hurry before they all come.
Hurry up.
Hurry, come on.
Saeng, why are you sitting there?
I'm waiting for you guys.
Guys,
where is Gon?
-Yeah. Gon.
-I'm here.
Gon, hurry up.
Don't drag your feet.
Hurry. I have all the weapons,
clothes, and horses ready over there.
-Let's go.
-Hold on.
I have an idea.
Doksok.
You and I have been friends
for a long time.
I think it's time...
that we all cut ourselves
to make a vow to be friends forever.
Good.
Let heaven and earth be the witness.
Seventeen layers of heaven,
15 layers of earth,
forest, and mountain angels,
please be the witness.
If I or any of you guys face a threat,
I will totally fight by your side.
But if I face a threat, you all will--
-Duen!
-I'm not done.
I'm bleeding to death!
-Give me the knife.
-Here.
Doksok,
I have cut myself.
I'll send a message to my forever friends.
So they come to help us.
Shit. Where are you gonna find a pigeon
right now?
I have one right here.
Gon, we're leaving now.
Wait for me!
Thank you very much, Pi Day Gong.
With fate, we shall see each other again.
So, Kraeng, Klar, Kriang,
go tell everybody to get ready.
Yes, sir.
-All of you as well.
-Yes, sir.
Saeng, don't let them go
through the village.
You can count on me, Boontueng.
They have to face someone like me.
For my nation,
I will never let them go through.
I'll let them know that the people
of Kung Raga
are not afraid to fight to the death.
Let's go.
Go.
Hurry up, everyone, before it's too late.
Horm. Fang. Duen. Hold on! Wait for me!
Let all the good deeds I have done
be the power
to protect everyone of Kung Raga
and help them to survive any threats
in this battle.
-Sher!
-What?
Something terrible is happening!
Oh, Fai. What's wrong?
The chief is calling everyone
to fight a battle.
A battle?
Sher. Shor.
What?
Sher, no need to go.
Why do we need to fight?
We could just move
and escape from the enemy.
Because of people like you two,
our nation has been endlessly
losing our land.
It's just land. You don't need to care.
You are so old.
If you go, I'm sure you'll die.
Bitches! No matter how old or young,
we have to fight
for our Kung Raga village.
I will fight with them.
I despise them.
You two, go get weapons ready.
Meet at the front of the village
in a moment.
Master!
The enemy is coming toward us.
What should we do?
If that is so, this battle is inevitable.
Fight for our nation! Fear no one!
If we do not fight today, we won't have
a nation for our descendants.
Fight for our nation!
Are you okay?
The master's talisman is really powerful.
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
Doctor!
Witch doctor!
Horm. I don't think I can make it.
What? No! You'll be all right.
No! You gotta be all right.
Not me. I didn't do it.
I didn't do it.
Kraeng. My dear Kraeng.
Kraeng, are you all right?
Leave him alone!
You have to go through me.
-Yes!
-Gon.
I have something to tell you. Gon!
Stop calling my name.
Hand me a cannon ball now!
-Which one? This?
-Yeah.
Move aside.
Daorueng!
There are no more.
No more? So we leave!
Kumlai!
Kumlai.
How are you holding up?
Daorueng!
No! Our baby!
You!
Mom!
Mom.
-Saeng.
-Mom.
Saeng, my baby.
You don't need to say anything.
I'm so glad to see you hold a sword
and fight.
Mom!
Mom.
Duen.
No dad, no mom...
Take care of yourself, okay?
No, Mom.
It can't be like this. Mom. Mom!
I can rest in peace now, my baby.
Don't cry. You are a man.
You have to defend our nation.
Hold a sword to fight...
for our descendants.
Mom!
No!
You mean, we couldn't defend our city
and men?
Yes, Your Majesty.
If our city had great leaders,
not those noblemen,
who are treacherous, ignorant cowards
that let the enemy in to ruin our nation.
It doesn't matter if we had ten times
more people and soldiers than the enemy,
we couldn't have won this battle.
That's because we are divided, isn't it?
You die!
Duen! We are here for you.
Doksok, Doksok. Oh, God, you came
to help me. I'll survive!
Duen!
Not long after that, in 2112 B.C.E.,
Yasotharavadi returned to attack Asoraya
once more
because Asoraya was still divided and weak
from the previous battle.
So, Yasotharavadi
was able to easily seize Asoraya.
The villagers at Kung Raga
were the last group
that fought to the death.
Translation by:
Sudaporn Pluempitiwiriyawej