Do you want to be gay?
Don't you want to be a man?
Are you and Nut in love?
Yes.
You can hate me all you want.
But I will never be who you want me to be.
Did your ex-boyfriend traumatize you
from dating a younger man?
Not all younger men are the same.
Don't generalize us.
Don't you have confidence in me
when I'm with you at all?
Didn't you say you had lots of homework?
You better go.
I want to drop you off at home.
I want to keep seeing your smile.
But my freedom
ended once I was at home.
Get home safely.
I'm going then.
Who was that?
Just a friend.
I know now
why you were angry with me.
I said the same thing as Tatarn, didn't I?
When I was at home,
I felt suffocated.
Tarn seemed to realize
that home didn't feel like home to me.
He tried to give me
a bit more time to smile
by the gate.
That's why you chose
to keep it to yourself
and didn't even tell your mom.
Yes.
We were secretly dating for about a year.
It was risky
but exhilarating.
The more you were oppressed,
the more you wanted to rebel.
Am I right?
I was so happy to beat them,
even though it was behind their backs.
But one day,
I almost got caught.
That scene really impressed me.
-Which scene?
-Take a guess.
-The book opening scene?
-Yes.
When the book was opened
and the music started,
I almost cried.
-Were you sucked in?
-Of course.
That person had a crush
on the other person for a long time
but they had to say goodbye.
Nut!
Dad.
Hello.
-Let's go home.
-Please calm down, Uncle.
I'm not your uncle!
-Come on. We're going home.
-But Dad…
We're going home.
Come on.
-But--
-Stop.
I said to stop.
I got away with it that time,
but luck didn't stay with me for long.
-What are we doing here?
-Just follow me.
Come. Sit down.
Gosh.
I was expecting a bigger surprise.
Nut.
In two months,
I'm leaving for Chiang Mai.
I'm going to miss this.
Miss school?
School
and someone at school.
If you miss me,
you have this as a keepsake.
Seeing you in the flesh is better though.
How about
I go and study there too?
There's no need for that.
I don't want that to be your reason.
I want you to study
at the university of your choice.
But if I'm far from you
and we miss each other,
what would we do then?
We can do something before I leave.
What are you two doing?
It happened at the gym.
I was returning something
to the second floor,
at the gym storeroom.
What I saw was…
Peeranut and Tatarn
kissing each other.
I…
I am sorry.
-Hey!
-Please don't.
Mr. Sib,
I beg you.
Please don't start a fight here.
Go.
If you don't stop seeing him,
don't you dare call me your dad.
Come with me.
Once I broke it off with him,
I stopped feeling happy.
Can I see you one last time?
Tarn.
Nut.
I get it.
Even though this is it for us,
I'll never forget you.
In my heart,
all the space
is occupied by you.
I'm not dead yet.
I won't let you die before I do.
I want you to stay with this
for a long time.
I'm asking you to keep it.
One day,
if you're afraid
and you don't know what to do,
give it a hug
like when we hugged.
I believe that you're strong
and brave enough
to find your own happiness.
Thank you.
But I don't have anything for you.
I just want you to be happy.
Then I'll be happy too.
Can I ask you one thing?
Can I hug you one--
Nut!
Why are you doing this?
Please don't, I'm begging you.
Dad, don't do it.
-Please don't.
-Nut.
Nut.
Don't do it, Dad.
-We're going home. Come with me.
-Nut.
-Come on!
-Come.
-Let go, Dad.
-Come with me.
-I said let go.
You're such a disgrace.
Have you thought of my reputation?
-Will you stay out of this?
-Come.
Come here.
What is going on?
-He sneaked off to see him.
-Mom.
They were hugging in the mall.
I told you to break it off.
But you went behind my back.
Do you want a beating?
Please don't. Stop it.
Nut, don't.
You want to fight?
Do you have no respect for me?
Don't you respect me anymore?
If you want my respect,
you have to earn it.
Nut!
No, don't!
Please don't.
Why are you protecting him?
You damn moron.
Why protect him?
I don't want a fucking
mean dad like you either.
Where are you going?
Did you think you could run away?
Don't.
Nut!
Nut! Open up!
Open up!
Nut, open up!
How dare you raise your voice at me.
How dare you raise your voice
at your own dad.
Nut!
A little pervert like you
will never achieve anything.
You two are never going to last!
You want to see each other?
Over my dead body!
-Open up!
-Please don't.
-Are you not opening up?
Fine.
Since your mom failed to teach you,
I'll do it myself!
What are you going to do?
That's why
on the day I woke up,
Nut was crying.
I should actually thank my parents
for ending my relationship with Tarn.
It gave me the courage
to do something
I never had the courage for.
Nut?
Why don't you come down for dinner?
Your dad wants you
to take a military exam.
Please study hard.
I'm not taking it.
I don't want to be a soldier.
If you won't be a soldier,
what do you want to be?
Anything.
I just don't want to be like Dad.
Will you please
listen to your dad?
He wants the best for you.
He wants the best?
For me or himself?
I've never been allowed
to do anything I wanted.
You wanted me to transfer, so I did.
You told me to end my relationship,
I did.
Now, you want me to stop being myself?
Do I have any say in my own life, Mom?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for making your life like this.
All you do is apologize.
You can be angry with me all you want.
But will you come down for dinner?
Your dad won't be angry for long.
He'll cool down when he sees you behave.
If you want to see a doctor…
I'm gay.
I don't have a disease.
It doesn't go away.
I agreed with no military exam,
yet you took the communications one.
It's what I want to study.
Reject that offer
and take the engineering exam.
If that's what you want, do it yourself.
Nut!
I'm going to study what I want.
I can transfer as many times as you like,
try out however many military services
or see however many doctors,
but I'll still be the same me.
But I forbid it!
If you want to do that,
wait until I'm dead!
Sure!
Since you two won't let me be myself,
I'll live somewhere else.
Since you despise who I am that much,
I'll tell everyone
that we are not related,
that I'm not your son.
Don't you ever say that again.
You are our son.
-Nut.
-Let him go!
If you step out of this house,
don't ever come back!
Your dad said that out of anger.
Don't take it to heart.
Why don't you eat something?
Go ahead and eat if you want.
Mom is good.
Good at making me behave.
Whenever we had a fight,
she would give us food
and apologize.
When in fact,
she simply wanted me to obey Dad
the way she did.
Even when I said I was leaving,
she still wanted me to concede to him.
She never loved me.
She wanted an obedient son
like you.
That's why she agreed to let you stay.
Is that why
you refuse to eat from your lunchbox?
I refuse to eat what she prepared
because whenever I see it,
I'm reminded of that day,
of what she said.
If I could turn back time,
I would rather have Dad beat me to death
than have the person I loved the most,
the person I thought would take my side
and protect me
turn against me like that.
I'm so sorry.
I was going to lock up.
I'll leave that to you.
I get it now.
The reason you blow up at your mom…
is to resist the feeling of love.
You're afraid that if you love someone,
you'll lose them.
What happened at the mall…
You were hesitant to enter
not because of bad memories,
but because it's where you lost
your loved one.
You lost him for good.
I never realized that my backstory
had everyone upset.
This must be why he loved to hug me
when he was sad.
It wasn't because he loved the teddy bear,
but because
I represented someone he loved dearly.
I apologize for my lies.
I am actually hurt
and jealous of Tatarn.
Am I a liar now?
But no matter how jealous I am,
I'll always be here.
Whatever reason he had for hugging me,
his hugs
have always been my safe harbor.
Right now, he's in need
of a safe harbor too,
isn't he?
What can I do to help
Nut and his mom reconcile?
At first, you two fought.
Now, Nut and his mom also have issues.
If you won't help, be quiet.
Nut and his mom
have always been like this.
We've spoken about it.
But…
as you know,
he's a complex character.
He has been through a lot.
Right now,
he has a good person supporting him.
I think things are looking better.
They are a family. They'll talk it out.
Someone once told me,
to help another person understand,
you should be honest.
Talking is not that hard.
I'll give it a try.
That lot is now working things out.
This lot needs to do the same.
What's with that lot and this lot?
I'm not talking to you.
I have something important to discuss.
Tomorrow,
will you meet me?
I have something important to discuss.
Tomorrow,
will you meet me?
Hey.
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
If you want me to do that,
let me in first.
Just say what you have to say,
so I can go back to bed.
Why did you want to see me so early?
Let me ask you this.
Do you not like younger guys,
or do you just not like me?
You seem to like me, though.
Why do you pretend
that you have no feelings?
What's wrong?
I want to know what I have to do
for you to give me a chance.
Could it be
that whatever I do,
you're never going to like me
because you can't forget your damn ex?
Come on.
I'm being serious.
Not every kid is like that.
There are many good kids out there.
You don't have to come.
It's just a scratch. It's not deadly.
Once I get my salary,
I'll treat you to a meal.
It's just tiring
when you try your best to please someone,
but they don't even notice.
Why aren't you saying anything?
You're making me nervous.
Gen?
Is it you, Gen?
Win.
When did you get back from Australia?
A month ago.
May I ask
who you prepared this surprise for?
Your boyfriend?
Yes. We met when we were there.
We came back together.
I wanted to make it official.
You and I haven't spoken for three years.
I'm glad
that we can still talk.
Well,
we parted on good terms.
Even though I was upset,
I understood
that you had to plan for your future.
Back then, I didn't treat you well,
but you always treated me like a king.
Actually,
I did many things for you
without you having to ask.
You were head over heels.
Seriously though,
if I could turn back time,
I would still break up with you.
Good relationships
come at the right time.
-Song…
-By the way.
What is it?
I'm all grown up now.
I eat my vegetables,
but I no longer like cabbage.
Do you still grow it?
No, I don't grow it anymore.
I grow ivy gourd now, got it?
I thought you had left.
I can wait.
I just don't want to watch.
You're too sensitive.
It's because you're the youngest son.
What did cabbage boy want?
His name is Marvin.
I don't care what his name is.
Tell me what you were talking about.
Are you getting back together?
Song, are you blind?
This is for his boyfriend.
Where would I fit in?
You didn't answer my question.
Did you have to drag me here
to tell me your answer?
I want to talk this through.
Here.
Drink this to cool yourself down
and listen to me.
Okay?
Okay.
You've talked with your ex.
Now, you have to talk to the new guy.
Why do you keep resisting me?
Why? Did cabbage boy hurt you that badly?
We were in a relationship three years ago.
He was 18 at the time.
I was 24.
Did he ask you out?
No, I approached him.
He was so cute.
I was generous with my money.
He liked eating cabbage, so I grew some.
I even cooked it for him.
It lasted less than a year.
He went abroad to study.
I told him I was willing to wait,
but he said I shouldn't waste my time.
Also, he might meet someone better.
When I saw him just now,
he stood by what he said before
and he's not sorry he said it.
Maybe he was focusing on his future,
but he obviously didn't love you enough.
That's why he let you go.
He and I are different people, you know?
I know that.
What are you afraid of then?
What happened to you in the past
made you lose faith in love,
but I'm going to show you
how serious I am about you.
People change.
You're young. You have a lot to see.
This is all I have to say.
Hey.
Hey, where are you going?
So what if I'm young?
I'll grow up one day.
You're afraid I'll change,
but what about you?
If you were to die tomorrow,
what would I do?
Are you cursing me?
I'm not cursing you.
I'm serious.
What are you afraid of? It just
complicates everything and wastes time.
We don't know what will happen tomorrow.
Why can't we just get together now?
Where are you going?
Can we talk this through?
Wait.
I'm going home.
I need to water my plant,
so it grows quickly,
like someone I know.
Are you agreeing to our relationship?
Finally!
I can't wait to eat some ivy gourd leaves.
-Hooray.
-Let me down.
We're in a park. Don't make so much noise.
I'll refrain from making noise.
-Let me kiss you instead.
-Don't.
Stop it. Keep your hands to yourself.
Do you hear me?
Look, there are people around.
Okay?
I love you. Let's go home, shall we?
Come on.
-Are you driving me?
-Yes.
Get on my back.
One, two, three.
Let's go home.
Let me help you.
Are you thinking about last night?
Why would I?
You want to make things better, don't you?
You get irritable with your mom,
but you're not really angry.
You just…
hold a grudge.
You've been holding onto it for so long
and you can't seem to let it go, right?
You're such a know-it-all.
Someone once told me
that families should try
to resolve their problems.
If you love someone, you should say so.
If you want to understand,
you should talk to each other.
Mutual understanding
requires an open mind.
When did you get so smart?
Do you like it?
I like it.
I like listening to your voice.
Let me help.
Don't do what you did yesterday.
As long as Mom doesn't start it.
Nut.
All right. I won't.
Are you satisfied now?
I'm satisfied.
You're very cute like this.
If I'm cute, I want a reward.
Let me think about what to give you.
Kuenchai.
Mrs. Na.
Mom.
I'll check upstairs.
Sorry, the number you've dialed
cannot be reached--
She's not upstairs.
Sorry--
Where did she go?
Why is her phone switched off?
I forgot to tell you
that her phone is broken.
I'll go and ask the neighbors.
Ms. Chair, do you know where Mrs. Na went?
Ms. Chair.
Chu and Nhong didn't see anything.
Kuenchai.
I have a doctor's appointment.
I'm going to see the doctor.
She is…
I forgot your mom
had an appointment this month.
I'm sorry for not taking good care of her.
It's not your fault. It's my fault.
You're worried about her too, aren't you?
-Hi, there.
-Hello.
Hi, Nut, Tofu.
I came to pick Mom up.
Really?
I saw her going that way.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
The psychiatrist sent me
the preliminary test results.
You shouldn't worry.
The symptoms you described
could have stemmed from several causes.
It could be a side effect of the medicine.
How about this?
I'm going to run a few more tests
and do an additional blood test.
This way we can identify the real cause.
There she is.
-Mom!
-Mrs. Na.
Mrs. Na.
Are you all right?
Are you hurt, Nut?
Are you?
Are you hurt?
He's bleeding.
Oh, no.
Does it hurt?
Does it hurt a lot?
Not at all.
How could it not hurt?
So long as you're okay, it doesn't hurt.
However, if you're hurt,
I'll feel it even more.
I cast a magic spell.
Your wound is going to heal soon.
Is it? Thank you.
Thank you, my boy.
Excuse me.
I've finished dressing your wound.
Thank you.
Does it hurt?
How could it not hurt?
So long as you're okay, it doesn't hurt.
However, if you're hurt,
I'll feel it even more.
I'll go collect the prescription.
Sit down.
They found you?
Where were you going just now?
You left by the back door.
I was…
just thinking about stuff
without realizing where I was going.
By the time I realized it, there I was.
Next time, you should go with her,
so she doesn't get lost.
You seem to have the meds.
Make sure to remind your mom to take them.
Yes, Juea.
I'm at the hospital.
I have something to do.
Okay. Once I've taken Mom home,
I'll be there.
I better get going.
Sure.
-Thank you.
-It's okay.
Thank you.
Let's go.
NEVER FORGET THE GOOD DAYS
ALWAYS CARE
STILL WAITING, WHEREVER YOU MIGHT BE
I broke up with him.
You two broke up?
It was my decision.
Why?
It's just…
I'm not over my ex.
I can tell that you really like him.
You must have been together a while.
He seems to have left quite an impression.
Only one year.
He was my first love though.
They say people tend to remember
their first love.
They also say first loves
often end badly.
Who was he?
My junior in school.
NEVER FORGET THE GOOD DAYS
SOMEONE SEE… AND VALUES
ALWAYS WAITING, WHEREVER YOU MIGHT BE
Prib.
-Where's Juea?
-Hi, Nut.
Can you check this out?
-I want to know if--
-Watch out, Juea.
What's wrong with your arm?
I had an accident.
Hey, Nut.
I want to discuss the script
with you. Come.
-Ouch. Careful, Juea.
-Sorry.
-Nut, can you first check this out?
-Prib.
We have work to do.
You don't get it, Uncle Juea.
When am I going to finally find out?
The scene where Kawee argues with his dad,
and his mom hits Kawee.
You describe the mom's feelings like this…
His mom is angry
because he disobeys his dad.
Why would you think so?
I'll tell everyone
that we are not related,
that I'm not your son.
Don't you ever say that again.
You are our son.
Because his mom is angry.
This child who's been obedient
all this time
suddenly rebels and threatens
to cut ties with his parents.
As I read your script
and got to know your characters,
it seemed that prior to this
Kawee's mom was too afraid
to stand up for him.
But in this scene,
it seems more like his mom
is trying to protect him.
What do you mean?
If his mom doesn't hit him,
his dad probably won't stop.
She hits him
to avoid any further violence.
His dad might end up beating him to death.
But what she has done
shows that she is affected.
She just locks up the feelings of remorse
and pain inside.
So long as you're okay, it doesn't hurt.
However, if you're hurt,
I'll feel it even more.
Since you despise who I am that much,
I'll tell everyone
that we are not related,
that I'm not your son.
Don't you ever say that again.
You are our son.
If the mother protects her son
by hurting him,
how does she expect him to understand?
That's hard to say.
There's more to what she did
than I can get from the script.
It's not easy to tell
without scratching the surface.
ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE
WHAT IS ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE?
Ms. Chair has fallen asleep.
The house is really quiet.
Mrs. Na has been very quiet too.
Surely, she's still upset
about what happened last night.
I think there's more to it.
Since we came back from the hospital,
she has been silent,
as if she has something on her mind.
Tofu?
Can you do me a favor?
I know that doing this is wrong.
If Nut finds out, he'll be angry with me.
I want to know what he thinks about me.
I want to know
if he says anything bad about me.
Why do you want to find out
all of a sudden?
Is it because of last night?
I made many mistakes in the past.
I want to find a way to correct them.
I want to make things better
before…
it's too late.
Can you read it out for me?
Okay.
Moving house
is such a hassle.
There are so many things to think about.
There's the house itself
and the people in it.
At least, living here is better
than our old place.
I haven't bought everything we need yet.
Fortunately, I brought my desk and chair
from our old house.
They might be old,
but I really like them.
It's my favorite desk.
I've written a lot on it.
I like sitting at this desk while working.
I feel comfortable writing on it.
You used to tell me
that Nut wasn't home a lot.
But it sounds like he loves this house.
He chose everything in the house.
I'm terrible.
I've lived in this house for years,
but I've never thought
about how each item came about.
It's okay.
It's just everyday stuff.
But Nut's everyday thoughts
don't seem to include me.
I'm sure they do.
I haven't reached halfway yet.
Here we go.
Mom's phone is so old.
I'm getting my paycheck today.
I'll buy her a new phone.
I shouldn't have bought it.
She complained it was expensive.
What's the matter?
What else did he write?
He wrote that you complained
it was expensive.
I don't need something
this new and expensive.
You should have saved the money.
I didn't know what to do.
I didn't mean to be insensitive.
I should have told him how good it felt
that he had thought of me.
I should have at least said thank you.
But I didn't say that.
Nut wanted you to have a good phone,
while you wanted him
to keep the money for himself.
You both had different ways
of showing good intentions.
If you had been honest
with each other that day,
Nut wouldn't have been upset.
What else did he write?
There's more.
I've already bought
everything for the house,
but it's still so damn quiet.
Adding a new member to the household
should make it feel more like home.
And this little guy is supposedly smart
and easy to keep and train.
He makes a good companion.
He's just right for Mom.
He can keep Mom company while I'm at work.
Despite having heavy workload
that makes him unable
to stay home with you,
Nut is always trying to take care of you.
I'm very lucky.
He might be stubborn at times,
but he has always been a good son.
I know now
why she didn't want to read it herself.
She would rather not face
the harsh reality.
The reality
that Nut hardly ever writes about her.
When he writes about her,
it's not necessarily in a good light.
You've done your best, Teddy.
Sometimes, humans tell white lies
to make others feel better.
I wasn't intending to lie to her.
I know
that even when he writes about her
that way,
when it comes down to it, he loves her.
If the mother protects her son
by hurting him,
how does she expect him to understand?
That's hard to say.
There's more to what she did
than I can get from the script.
It's not easy to tell
without scratching the surface.
If you don't see us when you get home,
don't panic.
I'm taking your mom out for some exercise
as Dr. Kanya recommended.
Since I moved here,
I've never come out for a walk like this.
As a matter of fact,
I haven't done it since I was a kid.
Back when I was still single,
I was a workaholic.
When I got home, I had to look after
my mom who was old.
After I got married,
I had to take care of the family.
You always put others' needs
before your own.
I grew up with my mom.
My parents separated.
It really affected my mom.
I just wanted to be good
to relieve her burden.
When I got married,
I wanted my children
to have a loving family.
Not like mine.
But Nut wasn't like other boys.
Isn't this pretty?
Nut. That's a girl's dress.
You can't wear that.
Why not?
Can't boys wear it? I like this dress.
Pink is for girls.
You are a boy.
You shouldn't like pastel rainbows.
It's silly.
Being different
isn't the same as being bad.
I admit that I was negligent back then.
I didn't know why Nut was like that.
I was genuinely concerned.
I was concerned about his future.
I wondered if he would be accepted,
if anyone would love him.
His dad couldn't accept it
and blamed me
for not raising him properly.
That's why I took his dad's side
and forbade Nut from being himself.
He's turning gay
because of your negligence.
He's just a nice boy.
Don't talk back to me.
Boys have to be strong.
What kind of mom are you?
I'm not taking it.
I don't want to be a soldier.
If you won't be a soldier,
what do you want to be?
Anything.
I just don't want to be like Dad.
Will you please
listen to your dad?
He wants the best for you.
He wants the best?
For me or himself?
I was weak and selfish.
As a mother,
I should have sided with him
and protected him.
Instead, I trampled on his heart.
I forced him to comply the way I did.
I forbade him from being himself.
I failed to support him.
I know that you feel bad about it.
But now that you've acknowledged
what happened,
you feel better, don't you?
If you want
to get anything off your chest,
you can tell me.
I'm willing to listen.
After that day,
Nut avoided me.
He barely uttered a word to me.
I never had a chance to apologize to him.
After his dad passed away,
we became even more distant.
Nut.
Come for dinner. I'll warm it up.
There's no need. I've eaten.
Mom,
I'm moving to a dorm next week.
I knew that Nut moved here
because of my condition.
He didn't want me to be reminded
of what had happened before.
Despite our move,
the distance between us didn't change.
The longer it went on,
the harder it became to heal the rift.
Then I came to realize
that Nut didn't need me anymore.
I wronged him
because I grew up in an unstable family.
I wished for my own family to be perfect.
But in this world, nothing is perfect.
I used to fear
that Nut was abnormal for being like this.
In fact, being gay is normal.
These days
seeing him all grown up,
capable of supporting himself…
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW
WITH PEERANUT BURARAT
…being accepted by others,
with friends like everyone else…
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW
WITH PEERANUT BURARAT
I've realized that kids
should be themselves.
They should be allowed
to choose their own paths
with the support of their parents,
without being under control.
A child's life is their own,
not their parents'.
You accepted who he was long ago, right?
That's why you could accept me.
I never wanted to kick you out
like Nut always feared.
I'm actually thankful
for your presence in our life.
I no longer care about
what others might say.
The smile on his face
makes me realize what makes him happy
and what makes me happy.
Thank you
for throwing me a birthday party.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Do you like the party
or me?
What a cheap shot.
When you asked me what I wanted
for my birthday
and I said nothing,
that's because
I already have you.
Stay by my side…
and don't go anywhere.
Thank you so much
for making him happy.
You make him laugh and smile
like I haven't seen him do for so long.
Also,
thank you…
for being there for me
and supporting me through all this.
If I hadn't been sick, I would have
been able to talk to him more.
Now that I feel better
and I'm thinking straight,
it seems like it's too late.
It's never too late.
You can always start over.
You can do that right this minute.
Shall we go home?
Let's go.
How about this?
Think about it.
From what you've written,
the mother and her son
don't really show it,
but I can tell for sure
that they still love each other.
Do you think I should revise it?
You should ask yourself that.
You're the one writing it.
How the relationship
between the mom and her son will turn out
is not up to me.
It's up to you.
You came home late today, Nut.
I thought we might go out for a walk.
I took a walk with your mom.
We talked about many things.
She knows about us.
She's not opposed to it.
Perhaps she doesn't say anything,
not because she doesn't care,
but because she accepts who you are.
I know
that you're staying silent
because you're thinking.
Your mom is like this too.
If you listen carefully,
the silence
may hide deep love and concern.
Don't you think you should give yourself
and give your mom a chance?
You're quite the philosopher.
Are you talking now?
Today, your mom had sore feet.
Shall we buy her new shoes tomorrow?
Mrs. Na?
I came to tell you to dress up tomorrow.
Yes?
Why?
Well, we are going shopping tomorrow.
Nut is taking us.
Really?
Is this outfit okay, Tofu?
I don't go out much.
I only have old clothes.
You look great.
Where's Nut?
He…
Are they both your sons?
They're so handsome.
Yes.
He is my son.
He is also my son.
Tarn told me
that he wanted Nut to be happy,
and what happened between them
should just be left as a happy memory.
He was the one who made me understand
that being gay isn't a disease.
It's not down to bad karma,
or an emotional disorder.
And it's not a joke.
NEXT EPISODE
Tarn.
Subtitle translation by:
Supanida Piyayotai