[upbeat music playing]
[engine humming]
[cars honking]
[tires screech]
[woman yelps] Gabriel!
Gabriel, is that you?
[woman exclaiming]
I'm Gabriel, but you can call me Gabbi.
And that's with an "I," not with a "Y,"
because I...
thank you.
Hmm.
[instrumental music playing]
I grew up here.
Scary, isn't it?
Yes, that's me.
Flamboyant, even as a kid.
Moon prism power makeup!
But even though our house was gorgeous...
I hated it.
The people here were crazy.
[crying hysterically]
[exclaiming]
Here they come.
[Nora] Hello? Hello, Doc? Can you hear me?
Doc? This is Nora Panti.
Hello? Yes.
Doc, my eyebrows are uneven.
What happened?
[Gabriel] My mom, the scandalous one.
She'd do anything to stay young-looking.
And of course, my dad,
Don Emilio Montemayor Zobel Ayala y Panti.
He holds himself in such high esteem,
even his own family
calls him Don Emilio.
I'd rather have my factories shut down!
I'm not in the mood to sign that!
Uh, Don Emilio,
is it okay if we miss that event today?
See, my eyebrows are uneven.
What will people say?
Even your eyebrows
are my problem now, too?
Just cover them with bangs!
[clears throat] Mom, Don Emilio...
I have something to tell you.
I hope this doesn't come as a shock.
I'm gay!
What? Really?
Unacceptable. I'm going
to enroll you in a co-ed school.
Your mom made the wrong decision
putting you
in an exclusive school for boys!
Wait, why is this my fault?
You're the one to blame.
You never had time for your son.
He has no father figure,
that's why he became gay!
I'm working so hard
to give you a good life,
yet it's my fault?
Your son became gay
because you always take him
to the shopping mall!
Shopping mall?
He became gay
because you never taught him basketball!
I got him a personal coach, no?
Aren't you part of the varsity team?
Why do you always ask for money
to buy basketball shoes?
Right.
-They were for the coach.
-[groans]
[in cute voice] He's just so cute.
[stammering] My son... dear...
You are possessed!
Don Emilio won't stand for it.
Unacceptable! I'll send him to the PMA!
They will surely make a man out of you!
Mom...
This is all your family's fault!
Blame your ancestors,
or whoever had the
bright idea to make Panti our last name!
Mom, Don Emilio's ancestors
have nothing to do with this.
It's not my school's fault, either.
Nor is it the shopping mall's!
It's the devil's work.
-Fight it, Gabriel.
-[whining] Mom!
Fight it,
or else I'll throw you out of this house,
and I won't ever
want to see your face again.
-Fight it!
-That's harsh of you!
[yelling] Fight it! Fight it!
-Mom!
-My gosh.
[yelling] Fight!
[yelling] I'm leaving this house!
-Don't try to stop me!
-[Nora gasps]
Don Emilio, he's our son. Show some mercy.
-Mom!
-No.
Forget that you have a son named Gabriel.
I'll also forget that you are my parents.
Good... Goodbye?
So, why did you summon me?
Take a seat, Gabriel.
Oh!
Hi, Gabriel! Long time no see!
[funky music playing]
Medusa has been looking for her hair,
you snake.
[hissing]
-Are you still with him?
-Hmm. Yes.
Don't talk to me then.
[Gabriel] Look at you.
K-pop wannabe.
You don't look like an idol.
You look like a member of a hunk group.
Hmm.
You weren't summoned here to fight.
Why are we here then?
We're still waiting for some people.
[techno music playing]
Waiting for us?
[scoffs]
Well, here we are.
That explains the funky smell.
Vilma, Samuel, have a seat.
[scoffs] Hmm.
Let's eat.
What?
[loudly] Let's eat!
-What did he say?
-[shouting] Eat!
-Let's eat.
-Yeah, let's eat.
What are your mistress
and her son doing here?
Do we need more maids?
Can we eat first?
-Say what?
-I can't hear them either, Samuel.
Why did you ask us
to come here, Don Emilio?
[Samuel clears throat]
Excuse me.
Can you speak louder?
We can't hear you over here.
Can't they just sit closer?
-Yeah, let's sit closer.
-Let's go.
You can't come closer! Stay where you are!
[grumbles]
If you don't want them near,
why did you invite them?
I only invited the bastard son,
not the mistress!
-[scoffs]
-Is she talking about me?
Is there any other mistress in this room?
Okay, let me make it clear.
I'm referring to the mistress
who wears fake branded clothes.
Hey, I may be wearing fake brands,
but at least my face is real.
Unlike someone who's had work done. Right?
[laughs] Right!
Want me to beat you with our silicone?
What a reaction. You're so sensitive!
He takes after his mom!
Speak for yourself,
-you take after your mom!
-[Daniel] True!
-And you look like a pug!
-[Nora laughs]
Hey! My child doesn't look like a pug.
She's the prettiest among you!
[all arguing loudly]
[arguing continues]
[yelling] Damn it!
I'm still eating my lechón.
I'm not yet done with my food.
[utensils clatter]
[sighs]
I have testicular cancer.
I am dying.
We've consulted medical experts
from Europe and China.
We've talked
to faith healers from Siquijor.
[sighs] There is nothing that can be done.
I will only live for a year,
or maybe a year and a half.
But while I am still alive,
you may get your inheritance.
[Don Emilio] 300,000,000 pesos
is at stake.
There are three of you,
so you will each get 100,000,000.
[gasps]
But I have a condition.
Oh, I knew it.
You just have to make
everything difficult.
First of all, you and Daniel
have to live here with Samuel.
-Huh?
-What?
Second, if you're all going to live here,
all of you have to act like men.
No dressing up like girls, none of this.
No gay stuff.
-Huh?
-[Gabriel chuckles]
Excuse me, Don Emilio.
Even if you remove the makeup,
take off the wigs, and have none of this,
gays will be gays.
Mmm.
Third,
while I am still alive,
you have to give me a grandchild.
If only one of you fathers a child...
he will get the entire 300,000,000.
[scoffs]
What do you think women are, baby makers?
That shouldn't come as a surprise.
You've seen how he treats Mom.
[Don Emilio] My decision is final.
Take it...
or leave it.
Leave it.
-Uh, Emil! Emil!
-Ouch.
Samuel is a real man.
He looks like this because he came
from a Halloween party,
but he's really just metrosexual.
Stop it, Mom.
No, no, no!
What do you mean, "no"?
Hush, you're not gay!
Shape up! You're a Panti!
I'm a Panti wearing panties.
Enough!
Now that everything's clear,
if you come back,
that means you agree to these conditions.
[sighs]
Why do you want a grandchild, anyway?
You want to spread the name Panti?
It stinks!
No Panti will stink
if you take a bath every day.
-You're such an idiot, Samuel!
-[Samuel mutters]
You should have just played along with me.
That would have gotten us
into your father's good graces.
[groans] Why don't you do it?
You might get a girl pregnant.
If you can't do it,
I'll find a girl for you!
[groans] But, Mom, I don't want a girl!
I don't like tight spaces
and smelly places.
I don't like the dark, I don't like mud!
Do you want a slap in the face?
Support me on this!
I was supportive of you,
so you should return the favor!
When we get a ton of money,
you will become a total woman!
Promise?
[sighs]
[gasps]
Hi, Pepe.
[automated voice] Hi! I'm Pepe,
the prettiest among the Pantis.
-How are you today?
-I don't know.
Pepe, do you think I should stay here?
Growing up,
Pepe has always been my best friend.
Actually, I came out to him first.
[shushes]
[young Daniel] Pepe, I'm going to admit
something to you.
-[whispers] I'm gay.
-[Gabriel] Daniel!
Daniel! Mom is looking for her things!
What foolishness is this?
Why is Pepe wearing makeup?
Don Emilio,
Pepe has something to tell you.
Go ahead, Pepe.
Tell Don Emilio everything.
Tell me what?
It's okay, Pepe.
Don't be scared, I'm here.
-What's wrong with you?
-[Daniel gasps]
[automated voice] Gay.
What is he saying?
Pepe just wants to let you know
that Pepe is gay.
Oh, my God.
-Please, don't!
-Stop it!
It's not his fault!
I was the one who took Mom's things!
Don't lie to me.
Come with me, I'll teach you a lesson!
[Daniel] My brother was
my original best friend.
When he left,
I tried to be an ideal son to Don Emilio.
[Nora stammering] Son...
[Daniel sobbing]
Tell us.
Are you gay or not?
It's a very simple question.
I'm not.
[sighs]
But I'm also not a boy.
Don't tell me you believe you're a girl.
No.
You're not a girl, not a boy,
and not gay. What are you?
Are you a lesbian?
Mom, Don Emilio,
it's so hard to explain.
The truth is,
I am a demigirl.
A girl who's a little masculine.
Huh?
[both] Say what?
In other words,
I'm like a chick with balls.
Do you get it now?
[both] Huh?
I have no son who's a chick with balls!
I don't understand you. Get out!
Leave. I never want to see you again.
Stop! You're hurting my Pepe.
-[Nora] Have mercy.
-[Daniel] That's my Pepe!
You don't have a Pepe anymore!
-[Nora and Daniel crying]
-Nora!
Nora!
-[Daniel crying]
-Emilio!
[Daniel] Last I heard,
they tortured my Pepe.
[MC] Here she is. Ladies and gentlemen...
Vukaka Panti!
-[dance music playing]
-[people applauding]
[dance music continues]
[audience cheers]
[Louie] 300,000,000 pesos?
Gabbi, get a girl pregnant!
Then share your blessings,
so we can all leave that bar.
Why don't you do it?
My best friend is different.
He doesn't get dazzled by money.
-Right, sis?
-Right.
I know of a quick way
to give your father a grandchild.
IVF.
-IVF?
-[Louie] Mmm.
In vitro fertilization.
That way, you don't have
to go to bed with some woman.
-[Louie] Right.
-That's better.
Idiot. I know what IVF means.
Do you know how expensive that is?
And it doesn't always work.
[Kat] You can talk to your mom.
Borrow some cash,
and pay her back when you get your share.
I'm sure she would rather
have a grandchild from you
and not from your half-brother.
My mom doesn't have any money.
Don Emilio never allows her
to handle finances.
Well, then that's too bad.
[scoffs] If you can't pay for it,
then you have to work for it.
[Gabriel] Didn't you hear what I said?
I will never take part
in Don Emilio's mad scheme.
No, no, no!
Gabbi, isn't that where you live?
[gasps] He's right! It's your place.
-[Kat] Haggard!
-[Louie] Oh, my gosh.
I have to get home!
You have no home.
It's being gutted by a fire.
[Samuel] Many have claimed
to be the King of Tondo.
But no one can take pride
in being its queen.
Except for me.
-[crowd screaming]
-[thugs fighting]
Ouch!
Ouch! Hey, it hurts.
I said it hurts!
Ouch! It hurts!
You stink! Bonehead!
Homo! Queer!
Show me what you've got!
You want some? Huh?
-Arrogant fag!
-Here goes.
[Samuel yelps]
[thug] You gay!
[shrieks]
You're ruining my makeup!
-[thug] Let's get out of here!
-Show me what you got.
Get lost!
-[thug] Hey, you fairy!
-Really? You want more?
Not so tough now, huh?
-I'll bust your balls! Cowards!
-[thug coughs]
Those idiots!
-Hey, Samuel.
-And you!
You've got some nerve.
You had to stay behind.
[sensual music playing]
Kid, what's with the bubbles?
Want me to devour you?
-Huh? Scram!
-Go on, go on.
Crazy kids.
-You're so grouchy.
-The other one.
-There.
-[giggles]
You think you're cute?
-What now?
-What?
Estong...
whenever there's a ruckus here,
I see your face.
Hey. That's what you call coincidence.
Coincidence!
-I heard something about you.
-What is it?
-I heard you're moving.
-What?
You're going to leave me?
Come on.
Oh, yeah. To my father's place.
Wow, "father." Big word.
Samuel! Samuel!
[Samuel] Chiqui is my first
and last girlfriend.
Hey! Let him go!
-[clamoring]
-Scram!
Are you okay?
[Samuel] We became a couple
because I thought she was a guy.
She also thought I was a guy.
Because of these false assumptions...
[shudders]
...we got together.
-What are you staring at?
-That's enough.
We still have plenty of time.
-Just rehearse!
-Relax.
Look, your back is drenched in sweat.
You might get sick.
Chiqui, stop it. You're all over me.
It's embarrassing.
So what? They know we're a couple.
Besides, your mom likes me.
She keeps asking, "Have you done it yet?"
Done what?
It! You know.
Of course, I told her that we haven't.
We don't even kiss.
You and your big mouth!
If you're too shy, I'll do it.
-Hey.
-[Chiqui] Ouch!
-Why did you slap Chiqui?
-[Chiqui] I'm okay.
[Chiqui clears throat]
Mom, I have a confession to make.
Gather around, everyone.
Please, I need everyone here.
You there...
even you, with the missing tooth,
come here.
[all murmuring]
I asked you to come here...
because I want to confess something.
There are no miracles!
Miracles are in people's hearts.
They are in every one of us.
We make miracles happen.
Babe, come here.
Mom, I don't have a girlfriend...
but I do have a boyfriend.
Mom...
my boyfriend and I are doing miracles.
Chiqui, sorry.
[Vilma screams]
Quick! Help her. Water!
-[Chiqui] Samuel!
-[Samuel] Chiqui hasn't gotten over me.
-Here comes your girlfriend! Hey!
-Shut up.
Samuel...
-[giggles]
-[clears throat]
Isn't it obvious?
Samuel, I miss you so much.
I've been waiting for you.
Chiqui...
don't you ever get tired?
Just say the word. I can relive the past.
Just let me know.
[door creaks]
-Babe.
-[Daniel groans]
Babe, I have to go to work.
You still don't want to get up?
Are you okay?
I was just thinking about our future.
Think about it. With that much money,
we can have a fabulous wedding.
Nonsense. It's just a ceremony.
You know our marriage
won't be considered legal here.
Well, it's our right.
Even if they won't honor it, let's do it.
Babe, are you sure...
this is going to make you happy?
Babe, as long as you're with me, I'm okay.
[woman] You never mentioned
you used to live in a mansion!
I didn't think I'd ever come back.
I told you, you can stay with us.
But our place is cramped.
I don't want to bother you. This is fine.
Hey. Once you step inside,
there's no turning back.
What else can I do?
Bye, babe.
[Daniel giggles]
Here's your bag.
[scoffs]
-I'll go ahead.
-Bye.
I thought you weren't going to be
dazzled by 300,000,000.
Can't I change my mind?
And you even brought a minion!
-Hi, Kat.
-Hi, traitor.
My God. Move on, guys.
It's been three years.
FYI, INF.
I never forget!
WCEF. Who can ever forget?
I let you live with us, yet...
YSMBYS.
You stole my boyfriend, you snake.
Excuse me.
I'm no snake.
I'm too pretty to be a snake.
[mouthing]
[Samuel] Nanny!
You may be pretty, but your hair is dry!
Oh!
[Nora] Mmm.
One more. There.
-[Nora giggles]
-There!
Okay. Let me take a look.
Finally, we're all
together again in a photo.
Good morning!
-How's everybody?
-Samuel!
You are not welcome here!
Welcome home, Samuel. [chuckles]
Don Emilio.
-This is my girlfriend.
-Chiqui.
My girlfriend.
[Samuel] Yeah, her bangs
really go that way.
Excuse me.
Uh, this is Kat,
the future mother of my child.
Is this a girl?
Yes! She just looks like a gay man.
[all laughing]
[Don Emilio] I knew it.
[Daniel] Really?
Well, you better get ready.
[techno music playing]
[Daniel in cute voice] Yummy!
Daniel... focus.
Sir, you need to slow down.
It looks like a milkshake,
but it can make you drunk.
That's okay. I need the boost.
[Daniel] You can do this.
Go get yourself a girl.
But the bartender's so cute!
Idiot! Focus!
[techno music continues]
[Daniel] You're a winner, girl!
They're buying your act.
Even grandma here is unstoppable.
[woman] Excuse me.
[Daniel] Someone wants the spotlight.
Get lost.
[Daniel] And she's game for anything.
I knew it, alcohol is the key!
-What?
-Nothing.
You wanna come over to my place?
[in deep voice] Sure.
Are you okay?
[gagging]
[Gabriel] Kat, come on.
Kat, please talk to me.
Okay. I'll give you 30 seconds
to tell me what you really want.
What am I, a microwave?
Fine, don't do it.
Find another girl to play the fool.
Okay, just 30 seconds?
[clears throat]
Ready?
Timer starts now.
I'm desperate. I didn't tell you,
but if I do get my inheritance,
I will help not just you,
but your family as well.
Please let me impregnate you.
I don't want to do this
with anyone else but you.
I'm sure when you get pregnant,
no one would dare court you.
Who would want to court a pregnant woman?
But I promise
I'll spoil you when you give birth.
And then superficial people
will be all over you
but when they get to know you,
they'll love you.
Even a gay like me would like you
if I weren't gay.
So please let me impregnate you
so we can have kids--
Stop!
You took it too far.
[inhales deeply]
How much will you get
if you get me pregnant?
100,000,000.
Do this.
Tell me this, make me feel it.
"I can't bear to be away from you, Bella."
[Chiqui] Bell-ya?
Idiot. Bella!
"Bell-ya"? Bella Flores?
[Chiqui] But I don't get it.
Who are you, anyway?
Who am I supposed to be?
Why are we wearing these?
You are Edward Cullen.
You're a vampire.
I am Bella Swan. A goddess.
We need to role-play to get me going.
Know what I mean?
All right.
Twilight is my favorite movie.
-Okay?
-Mmm.
Oh, here.
Shine the light on your face. [gasps]
Edward...
you're turning me on.
I'm getting turned on, Edward.
How can you get turned on? I look dead.
Dead people turn you on?
I think you should see a doctor.
You talk too much. Stop complaining.
Just say your lines.
You can ad-lib if you wish,
as long as in the end,
um, you bite me, okay?
Okay.
Is that clear, Edward?
Tell me, Bella...
Bella, tell me... wait.
Why are they speaking in our language?
Stop ruining the moment. Just go on.
-So what if it's our language?
-Okay, okay.
Go on, continue!
[breathing deeply] Bella...
What am I? What am I?
You are a vampire.
Rawr! Rawr!
Idiot!
It's Twilight, not The Lion King.
-Fine. Okay.
-Again!
Bella, aren't you afraid of me?
I'm not afraid of you, Edward.
You should be scared of me.
I'm not, Edward.
My only fear is
if you are no longer with me.
[moans]
-[growls]
-[laughs]
That hurts!
Ouch! Ouch!
[screams]
-Chiqui, what have you done?
-Samuel, sorry.
But you did tell me to bite you.
I told you to bite me, not kill me!
[Kat] How's it coming along?
Will you be done soon?
I might fall asleep.
Hey! Don't sleep!
I'm really making an effort here.
Do you think this is easy for me?
This isn't easy for me, either.
This gay.
Just make yourself comfortable.
I'll come out right away, okay?
When I'm ready.
Gabbi!
What is it again?
Let's grab a bite!
You know I'm concentrating.
Don't bother me.
Fine.
Hold on.
It's the reception.
They're asking if we will extend our stay.
Isn't it obvious?
So quick-tempered!
Uh, yes, we will extend our stay.
No. Make it two more days.
[Gabriel] Kat!
Kat! Are you ready? Assume the position!
[exclaims] I've been ready.
Gabbi! Shocks!
I don't think I can look at you.
I might throw up.
The feeling is mutual.
Quick! Are you ready?
I'm not going to face you, okay?
Just do your thing.
Yes, I can do it. Quick!
-Go!
-[Gabriel] Game?
Go!
[Gabriel screams]
[laughs nervously]
-[Gabriel giggling]
-[Kat screams]
Success! I'm going to have a baby.
I'm going to become a mother. Success!
Gabbi!
[Kat panting]
You went through the exit,
instead of the entrance!
You didn't check first.
You're driving me crazy!
So, sorry, no baby?
-Don't count on it!
-Sorry.
Haggard!
-[man shouting] Joy!
-[knocking on door]
-[shouting] Joy!
-[door opens]
I've been here for ages!
Out of my way!
[man] Come here. Make me a cup of coffee!
[man shouting] Joy!
[door closes]
Mmm. How did it go?
I tried meeting women in a bar.
And?
Epic fail.
I'm sure you'll come up with a plan.
Whatever that will be,
you have my support.
But keep in mind, Dane.
We don't need a huge amount of money.
-[glass breaking in distance]
-[Joy faintly] Have pity on me!
-[Joy crying] I'm pregnant!
-[man] I don't care!
She's pregnant?
And that jerk continues to hound her?
Babe, women should protect each other.
It's been a long time since I practiced
my tae kwon do skills. Okay?
It's not that... Dane! Dane!
-[Joy crying]
-No, not that, Dane. Dane!
[man] Stay out from this!
-[Daniel] Stop that!
-Dane?
-[man] Don't meddle with us!
-Dane!
Don Emilio, this is Joy.
-Hi, Uncle, may I eat?
-Of course.
Join us. Sit down.
Oh, this, then this, and this...
-This one, and this...
-[clears throat] What a gobbler.
Did you say something?
Mmm. I just said, "Maybe she wants rice."
Rice? There's no rice.
[muffled] Sorry, I'm very hungry.
I'm eating for two.
Joy's pregnant. I'm the father.
[both laughing]
You mean, I'm going to be a grandfather?
Yes, Don Emilio.
[Don Emilio laughing]
Don Emilio... how can you be sure
that he is the father of the child?
How come we just met this girl?
Unlike you guys, I wanted
to be sure before introducing her.
Do you want to see the pregnancy test kit?
A pregnancy test kit?
That's crap.
Who knows where you got that!
[Gabriel] Listen to him,
he has a point, Don Emilio.
Don't tell me you believe
everything Daniel says.
He's a smooth liar.
Take it from me.
He has deceived me in the past.
Well, well, well, why?
Are you scared that I'll get
the 300,000,000 pesos?
-Don't be so sure.
-Why would I be?
[all bickering loudly]
Silence, all of you!
The earliest that DNA testing can be done
is at nine weeks.
How far along is she?
-A little over a month.
-Okay.
After the first trimester,
we will conduct a DNA test.
In the meantime,
let me enjoy my son's good news.
Let's eat.
[Daniel] Eat a lot,
so the baby won't starve.
My birthday is coming up next month.
My brother is throwing me
a surprise party,
along with members of my fraternity.
You call that a surprise?
It's a surprise
because they don't know that I know.
I will bring you all,
so my brothers will meet you.
Bring your girlfriends,
so they'll see
that I don't have gay children.
But... haven't they always known?
It's all speculation. Gossip.
Once a blind item on a gossip website.
But no one has confirmed it.
[both laughing]
Stop it.
-Let's do it here.
-Okay.
-Vampire. Vampire.
-Yes!
[both exclaiming and laughing]
You look like a frog, not a vampire.
Wait. Stay there.
Let me strike a pose.
There.
Hold on.
Hey, don't forget me!
Estong is just an appetizer,
I'm still the main course!
What a pest!
Are you in a rush? Fine.
-Get it over with!
-Fine!
She's so...
You, lie on the bed.
-Come here, come here.
-That's it.
Don't look at me. Cover your face.
-Hurry.
-What?
-[giggling] Go.
-Here it is.
[Chiqui squealing and giggling]
[coughing]
Chiqui,
you sound like a pig being strangled.
I'm just helping you get in the mood.
You can't be the only one
who's enjoying this!
I'll be struggling when I get pregnant!
I also need to be happy.
Well, your happiness is such a turnoff!
-Wait.
-[Chiqui] What, really?
-I can't do this.
-Hey!
-[upbeat music playing]
-[Samuel yelps]
I'm ready now, Chiqui!
[groans]
-Chiqui?
-[growls]
-[Samuel screams]
-[door closes]
I'm so tired.
Chiqui, I'm so tired.
[crying] So, so tired.
Wait.
I'm so tired.
[sobbing incoherently]
[Chiqui murmuring soothingly]
[sobbing continues]
Samuel.
If you can't do it, don't force yourself.
What?
Idiot. These are tears of joy.
I almost threw up, but...
I did it!
[laughs]
-Success.
-Congrats!
Remember, you have to act surprised.
-[all] Happy birthday!
-[guests clapping and cheering]
Wow!
I don't believe you guys.
What a big surprise!
[laughs]
Happy birthday, baby boy!
Here. Blow your candles.
Blow your candles.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-Who are they?
-♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
That's Uncle Arman.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-♪ Happy birthday ♪
-And those are our cousins.
-Your cousins?
No, yours.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-[Gabriel] You're drooling.
-[Kat] What?
-[Arman] Blow!
-[people cheering]
-[Kat] Wow. Like this?
-You have to bend over.
Bend? I don't wanna bend.
The cue? The white ball?
-Uh, excuse me. Excuse me.
-[Kat] Hit the ball like that?
-Like, reach for the white ball?
-Hey, hey, hey.
-What are you doing?
-That hurts.
You're flirting shamelessly.
Aren't we supposed to be a couple?
They invited us
to a private resort tomorrow.
Chiqui and Joy already said yes.
Would you like to come with us?
Gee, thanks,
how thoughtful of you to invite us.
You should have asked us
before saying yes.
Are you jealous? Huh?
No. I just find it rude.
They don't respect us.
-I'm going to tell them off.
-Hey, hey.
-[clears throat]
-Hey...
Um, bro...
I heard you asked our girlfriends
to go swimming tomorrow.
You should have asked us, too,
we're their boyfriends.
What if we don't allow them?
We just want to get some tan.
Suntan?
Yes, because we're so pale. Look...
[Kat] Oh!
[Kat barking]
Ouch!
You should have told us earlier!
We could have bought trunks and swimsuits.
-Guys, we'll go swimming tomorrow.
-Game!
You should have told us right away,
since you're so pale.
-[Kat] You're so pale!
-Excuse me.
[chuckles] Um, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Uh, good night, everyone.
Hmm.
Uh, I just want to give a message...
to Don Emilio.
I'm Samuel, his youngest son.
That's my mom, Vilma.
Let's all give a round of applause
to my mom.
-[crowd applauding]
-Uh...
Most of you probably don't know me...
but...
I just want to tell you,
how happy I am to be here today.
As a gift, I want to tell you...
-I am now a father.
-[all cheering]
[whines]
Chiqui.
[giggles] Hello, hello.
Uh, Chiqui's pregnant.
I'm pregnant!
We did it and I liked it.
Ouch.
[awkward laughter]
Uh, I have an announcement, too.
[Nora gasps]
Uh, I'm also pregnant.
-[gasping]
-[Gabriel stammering]
I mean, she's pregnant.
We're going to give you a grandchild, too.
-Pregnant but playing billiards?
-I want to make a toast!
To my sons.
Finally!
I will be a grandfather of three.
-[Nora gasps]
-And I liked it.
Cheers!
-[all] Cheers!
-[crowd cheering]
Let's cheers. Cheers.
[glasses clink]
[sighs] It's so nice here.
It's good that we came.
-It's a chance for us to relax.
-As if.
Did you really come to relax,
or to look at your cousins' abs?
Abs are relaxing.
They make me happy.
Oh. Happiness, wow.
-I have news for you.
-What's that?
Since back when you made an effort
to look for my cave,
gosh, I haven't gotten my period.
-Really?
-I might be pregnant.
Your wish came true.
-[man 1] Come on, let's swim!
-[man 2] Let's go!
-[man] Let's go!
-[laughing]
[water splashing]
[Kat] Here they come.
-Oh!
-[man 1] The water feels good.
[man 2] Yeah, man, it's so refreshing.
We should come here more often.
They're your cousins.
[chuckles] No. I'm an illegitimate child.
-[man] What about the girls?
-Stupid.
It's the same thing.
Really? You're the one who's stupid.
I was just kidding!
Not funny.
-[Joy] Yes.
-Stop bickering.
I have to tell you something.
I was just found in a parking lot.
[both laughing]
-[Gabriel] Like that!
-[man] Hey, guys.
Do you wanna play volleyball
against us tomorrow?
You three against us?
[clears throat] What do you say?
Uh...
-No, thanks.
-[chuckling]
That was so gay.
-[laughing]
-[man] Yeah, you're right.
Hey, you! What's so gay?
Nothing. I just said, "It's so gay."
It's just an expression.
You know, "So gay."
[Daniel] Ah, "So gay."
You mean weak? Worthless?
Look, Dan, I didn't mean anything bad.
And why do you look offended?
Are you gay?
Let's fight.
I'll show you what gay truly means.
-[all chuckling]
-Okay.
[man] Bro.
We need to beat those guys.
They're so cocky.
I'm fine with it.
Losers have to kneel before the winners.
It's a win-win.
Let's stop fighting for now.
We need to work together to beat them.
Have you seen them play volleyball?
They spike like monsters.
Look at their bodies!
Oh, so yummy.
We should have played hopscotch instead.
[Gabriel] Unless...
they really like women.
They get easily distracted.
And so?
It's time for some glam!
[dance music playing]
[women whooping]
[cheering]
[women whooping and cheering]
[Joy] Go, Daniel!
Go, Daniel!
[Joy] That's a miss.
You're such a flirt!
Why me? She's the one who served.
Game! Let's do this.
-Damn.
-I cannot look at this one.
Sorry!
[cheering]
[women cheering]
-[women exclaim]
-[man] Barry!
Bro. Bro, get up!
-[Barry groaning]
-Bro, are you hurt?
Okay! We give up!
-[Chiqui] Give up?
-[Kat] Give up!
[cheering]
Go, Samuel!
Chiqui! Do you have your period?
Period? She's pregnant.
-Let me see.
-See!
-[Kat gasps]
-[Chiqui] I have?
Look.
Samuel! Samuel! It's Chiqui!
Samuel!
[Kat] Hurry up! Faster!
Here, you should eat.
[sighs]
Oops. Stay in bed.
[groaning] How...
Don't be stubborn or I'll poke your eyes.
[Samuel laughs]
What? I won't get up?
How can I take care of you then?
Take care of yourself and the baby.
Here are your meds. Take them.
They say that's how it is
in the beginning.
Just be patient, babe.
[laughs]
You called me babe. Thanks, baby.
Don't act crazy.
You can't stand, okay? Just stay here.
Where are you going?
Are you going to see Estong?
What, Estong? Stay in bed, okay?
Can't I go to the toilet?
What if I have to pee?
I don't want to smell of pee. Babe!
[Kat shrieking]
Well?
Positive.
Congratulations!
Let's see who can be the godparents!
-[giggling]
-Gabbi.
-What?
-I have something to confess.
You see, that night...
when something happened between us,
I also did it with Zeus.
Zeus?
We've been friends with benefits
for almost a month.
So, what are you saying?
He could be the child's father?
Or it could be you.
Gosh. What is this, multiple choice?
What were you thinking?
You introduced Joy to them right away.
Of course your dad
was going to ask for a DNA test.
I didn't know that you could make
pregnant women undergo a DNA test.
I just wanted to make my siblings panic.
[Joy] If only I could do something.
I owe you two a lot.
If it weren't for you,
I would have been killed
by my boyfriend who beats me up.
Joy, that's nothing.
[Joy] What now, Daniel?
Are we going to Don Emilio tomorrow?
[Daniel] Why not?
[Samuel] Standing in front of you
is a goddess from the heavens.
A young, gay dragon.
The Queen of Tondo.
This is my day of revenge, Pantis.
Are you trembling with fear?
[laughing]
[Daniel] This is my last day on earth.
Don Emilio will kill me
when he finds out
that I have been deceiving him.
Please tell Blackpink
"hello" and "I love you!"
Tell BTS' Jungkook and Exo's DO
that when I become a ghost,
I will visit them
while they are taking a bath.
Seems like dying ain't so bad.
[Gabriel] Lord? Beyoncé?
Please. Please.
Have mercy.
Do me this favor.
I hope Kat is pregnant with my child.
My God, please. [inhales]
This is me, Gabbi...
Gabriel Panti,
leaving you with the saying,
"What is beauty if the panty is dirty?"
[techno music playing]
[Don Emilio] Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Act properly.
The DNA test results are with me.
Daniel...
why can't you look at me?
Did you think you could fool me?
You, too, Gabriel.
I wasn't trying to deceive you.
Then why does this show
that you're not the father of Kat's baby?
-Let me explain--
-You don't have to explain!
[Don Emilio] I can't believe
my legitimate children tried to trick me.
Samuel...
you made me very proud.
There is no doubt
that Chiqui is carrying a Panti.
-[Samuel gasps]
-[Vilma shrieks]
That's my son!
Way to go!
[both laughing]
[Nora sighs]
Let's go, Mom.
Another crazy stunt? Why are you leaving?
I'm leaving, Don Emilio.
I can't stand you anymore.
You're too dramatic, Nora!
Am I throwing you out?
I don't take it personally.
After all, 100,000,000 is 100,000,000.
A person's true colors will
show whenever money is involved.
The game is far from over.
You may still get any woman pregnant.
Don Emilio--
Excuse me, sir.
It's true, we all want the money.
But if you were more sensitive,
you'd know that's not all they want.
[Kat] That's right.
They want your love.
[laughs]
You've got some nerve to answer back.
You are all opportunists.
Yes.
We were blinded by your wealth...
but not anymore.
We have come to our senses.
This is wrong.
[speaking Tagalog]
In English...
"That unhatched offspring
is not a product of love...
but of need!"
[in Tagalog] Did he have to translate?
Want me to translate for you?
I can do it in whale language.
[imitating whale]
Let's go.
Uh, Nora!
You left this in your old room
which is now my room.
This isn't mine.
I don't own anything fake.
Oh, it is mine.
Actually, everything's mine now.
I am now number one.
You are still number two, Vilma.
I was never number one in Emilio's life.
His number one is none other than himself.
I wish the two of you good luck.
[scoffs]
Bitter!
B-T-T-ER.
[Samuel laughing]
[Samuel] Estong!
[Samuel giggling]
[Estong] Bella!
[Samuel] No, Edward, please!
-Come here!
-[laughing]
Bella!
[Samuel moaning]
[Samuel and Estong laughing]
[slurring] I'm not drunk. I want more.
Come on. Please.
-Promise?
-Just one more.
-Are you sure?
-Yes! One more!
-Okay, wait.
-I can handle it.
I can.
[Nora snoring]
Look at her.
And she says she's not drunk.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Uh...
[stutters] Where's Daniel?
Uh, she brought Joy to the bus terminal.
Where is Joy going?
To their province.
[sensual guitar music playing]
Are you seducing me?
-[music stops suddenly]
-What?
No. Nothing.
I think I'm drunk.
Why would I seduce you?
I love your brother.
No need to emphasize. I've accepted that.
You grew tired of me.
It happens.
Wait, wait, wait. I grew tired of you?
What are you talking about?
That's not true.
You had no time for me.
You had gig after gig.
You loved your work
more than you loved me.
I was doing it for us.
Even on my birthday, huh?
When I came home that day,
huh, where were you?
But Daniel was there.
He even made the dish
that I always asked you to cook for me.
Frog stew.
I have to admit...
because of that dish...
I fell for him.
Excuse me!
That's my frog stew.
Before I left for work,
I made sure to catch some frogs
so I could cook your favorite dish.
Hey, Chiqui. What's your problem?
Why are you leaving?
There's no place for drama here!
Samuel, did you get me pregnant
because you needed it?
Or do you need me, so you got me pregnant?
What? I don't get it, babe.
I saw you with Estong last night.
If you wanted it,
why didn't you come to me?
Why did you have to go to him?
Do you like him? Do you love him?
Chiqui, look here.
First of all, I didn't ask for it.
Estong did.
Second, I don't love him.
Not yet.
You ask too many questions.
You're messing with my life.
Why shouldn't I? What are we?
Business partners.
We're partners and it's not just business.
Oh, are you requiring me to love you?
If you want me to see this through,
you have to become a lesbian.
Stop seeing Estong.
I don't want to share you.
Chiqui, you're not sharing me,
because we were never a couple
and we'll never be together.
I hope you know that.
If we're not together,
then there's no reason to push
through with this pregnancy.
What are you saying?
You'll get an abortion?
Where's your conscience?
Did your conscience bother you
when you knocked up someone
you don't love?
It's my body, my decision.
-I will get an abortion.
-Chiqui, Chiqui!
-Hey! I'm leaving!
-Don't leave! Chiqui, please.
-Don't interfere! I'm going!
-You're not leaving.
-Chiqui! I'm sorry.
-[grunts]
-[groans]
-Sorry, sorry, sorry.
-Oh, my God.
Help! Help!
Chiqui, sorry.
What took you so long?
I thought you were just bringing Joy home.
I went to church.
I asked for a sign from God
if I should pursue getting
my inheritance from Don Emilio.
[chuckles] That was some novena,
to last all night!
I hope you asked for forgiveness from God.
Forgiveness?
For stealing Zernan!
Huh?
I thought you had moved on.
I thought we were okay.
I thought so, too.
I really believed that...
Zernan fell for you.
But you're something else.
You were sneaky. You stole him from me.
You even pretended
that you cooked my frog stew.
My God! Why fight about him now?
-Do you still like him?
-No.
Oh, then what's the issue?
The issue is, you lied to me.
And you haven't apologized until now.
Why should I say sorry?
Did you say sorry
when you left me with Don Emilio?
I'll give you what you're asking for, huh?
-What if I do that to your face?
-[both grunting]
[Nora] Hey, hey!
Stop that!
What's the matter with you?
Fighting at such an early hour.
You're acting like children!
Don Emilio called...
asking me to come back.
And you will?
He's all alone there.
No one's taking care of him.
Samuel rushed to the hospital
because Chiqui had a miscarriage.
[sober music playing]
[nurse] Sir, please go back to the room.
We'll just bring her there.
Don't be so sad.
According to the doctor,
Chiqui can get pregnant again
in six weeks.
Are you serious?
She's not yet well, and you're already
thinking of getting her pregnant.
Why were you fighting?
Were you fooling around with a man again?
You know how much Chiqui's into you,
and yet you are still flirting
with other men.
Couldn't you wait
for the child to come out?
We could have had 300,000,000.
-And now it's gone.
-Mom!
Mom, give me a break.
You lost a grandchild.
I lost a child.
If I were a good person,
I wouldn't have dragged her into this.
[sighs]
You can be a good person
while you are waiting to become rich.
Just take a look at some politicians. See?
They hoard the people's money
before they share their blessings.
Who knows?
You might become a senator someday.
We need your inheritance first
so that you can become,
as I promised, a total woman.
Will you trade that for your conscience?
Shouldn't I want to be a good person
rather than be a total woman?
What are you doing here?
[inhales deeply]
We heard...
We're all not getting our inheritance.
Happy?
I told you he'd be mean.
We're just wasting our time. Let's go.
We're just making sure
you're okay, Samuel.
Only a Panti can comfort another Panti.
-[sentimental music playing]
-We may have misunderstandings...
but in the end, we are all Pantis.
Why so big?
It looks stupid.
[all chuckle]
It's her fault.
I told her you're not a typhoon victim,
but she still brought relief goods.
-[chuckles]
-At least it's assorted.
[laughs] There's a lot to try.
[sniffles] Thank you.
Thank you, um... forgive me.
I'm just so confused.
[Don Emilio] Samuel!
Why is nobody telling me
how my grandchild is doing?
-Chiqui had a miscarriage.
-Oh?
So, it's all even again.
I will wait for all of you at home.
[Samuel] Wait.
Is that all you can say, huh?
You're not going to ask how I am?
Or how Chiqui's doing?
[Samuel] What's this to you?
A game?
I'm not a sentimental human.
You're not human, period.
All my life, I've dreamt of seeing you,
being with you.
But you're a very bad person.
[Samuel] You're a worthless person.
I'm not going back to your house.
You should die alone.
[sobs] Me, too.
Neither am I.
And I... thank you!
Hey! Come back.
-Hey. Are you walking out, too?
-I have to pee.
It's better to be sure.
You gays. [sighs]
[Samuel] Look!
Your relief goods come with freebies.
-Oh.
-So glam! [laughs]
-How cute.
-The blue one is for you.
-I like this one.
-Thank you.
Oh, fabulous!
[Samuel chuckles]
-Mmm.
-You know...
I was so envious of you two
because you grew up with him around.
I used to wonder
what it felt like to have
a father at home.
-[scoffs]
-It was hell.
He watched every move we made.
We weren't allowed to be effeminate.
We learned all kinds of martial arts,
but he still wasn't happy.
We experienced all sorts of punishment.
We were made to kneel at the stars,
on broken glass...
on mung beans.
All that kneeling made us gay.
[all laugh]
But...
Samuel, um...
Sorry...
for not immediately accepting
you as our brother.
[sniffles and laughs] No need
to apologize.
It's okay, right?
Fate has a strange sense of humor.
He doesn't like gays?
Well, gay, gay, gay!
[all laugh]
I feel sorry for him!
I feel sorry for him
because he doesn't see
that having gay sons is a blessing.
Correct.
But, of course,
we have our differences, right?
When I first saw him,
I wanted to poke his pretty face.
[laughs] More like punch him, girl.
I knew right away that you're into Korean!
-[exclaims]
-So true!
And I believe that size does not matter!
-Amen!
-Hypocrite!
-Yeah, right.
-[laughs]
What about you? What kind of gay are you?
Grandma. An old gay person.
-Oh!
-Are you teasing me?
-I'm a beauty queen.
-[Daniel] Admit it.
Of the three of us,
you're the most old-fashioned.
Wait a minute.
I can practically smell a fight coming.
Is there an issue here?
-Gabriel. Gabriel.
-Huh?
I'm sorry.
He's crying. So, there is an issue.
It's okay. He chose you.
Are we really okay or are you just drunk?
-Both.
-[all laugh]
[exclaims]
I'm sorry, too.
You know our family.
We're stingy when it comes to giving love.
I'll make it up to you, hmm?
Fine, I'll make it up to you, too.
-You might get envious.
-[all chuckle]
-Thank you.
-Let's have a toast.
-Don't cry.
-Wait.
Look who's here!
[Samuel exclaims]
[man] Hey, jerk.
Fix my hair.
What a snob!
As if they're studs.
I'll teach them a lesson.
I'll join you.
-[both laugh]
-Hey, hey.
Let's not. They're our cousins.
[both] You hypocrite!
-[exclaiming]
-Hey, McDonald's!
Just because he's cute,
you're hot on his heels!
-He's gone now.
-[car beeps]
But he was staring at me. He even winked.
-[man] What's your problem?
-That was a long walk.
[man] Let me go!
[Daniel] Oh, my God!
Our cousins are in trouble.
-What's your problem?
-Going to fight us?
-Aren't you black belters?
-[man] You're weak!
-[Samuel] Let's help.
-[Daniel] Wait.
What are you doing?
-[all clamoring]
-[Gabriel] Hey, stop that.
-Stop it!
-Don't mind them. They're just gays.
"Just gay"? Did they say "just gay"?
Girls, position!
[upbeat music playing]
Uniting our hearts to fight as one
is what makes us sailor guardians!
Mercury, power!
Jupiter, power!
And the last, Uranus, power!
-Moon prism.
-Power.
[all] Makeup!
Are you leaving or not?
[all grunting]
That's it! Go, sisters!
[Samuel] Oh, my gosh! Go, sisters!
Let me know if you need my help.
[Samuel] Kick him hard!
Daniel, watch out!
[upbeat music continues]
[man] Let's go!
So, who's gay now?
You're no match for us!
Not so tough now, huh?
Go home crying to your mothers!
[all laugh]
[all panting]
-What happened to you?
-Are you all right?
-Are you okay?
-What happened?
-[Barry groans]
-Come.
-You're so heavy.
-[grunting]
[Barry coughs]
Samuel, let's go find a ride
to take them to a hospital.
Samuel? Are you okay?
He looks traumatized.
I think blood scares him.
No. I wasn't traumatized.
How can they be this hot
even if they're bloody?
Stop messing around.
Come on, let's find a car
so we can bring them to a hospital.
-Mister, help!
-Daniel!
-Don't forget the biscuit.
-Where?
-Are you okay?
-We need to go to the hospital.
Please help us. Thank you.
[Samuel] Careful, your head!
I can only take five people.
We can't fit more.
-Only five people can fit.
-Go ahead, I'll catch up.
-Make sure to follow.
-This feels good.
-[Gabriel] Stop flirting!
-[Samuel] So good!
I'll book a ride.
Wow, that was fast.
[thug] Hey, faggot.
You again? Aren't you tired of losing yet?
If you're going to insult me,
you have to do better.
Call me a faggot all you want,
but I really am gay.
What about you?
You're dumb men who
don't stand a chance against gays!
[blowing raspberry]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey!
Are you done treating the patient
or are you just flirting?
Excuse me. We are all professionals here.
Your eyebrows look more professional.
Hey. Your eyebrows are on fleek.
Come. We better leave.
-Snobs.
-What a snob.
Is this your house?
Probably.
We're done saving you.
You're old enough
to take care of yourselves.
We can't thank you enough for saving us.
Yeah, um...
how can we make it up to you guys?
Oh, make it up?
Um, just...
[in English] French kiss me,
but don't you dare fall in love with me.
[in Tagalog] Samuel, you crazy girl!
You become good at English when you flirt.
Right?
-[in English] Remember!
-[exclaims]
It's us gays who saved you, okay?
[both laugh]
Okay, we have to go.
-[line ringing]
-[in Tagalog] He's not answering.
Try again.
[gasps]
What happened?
He fainted during the pageant.
He hasn't eaten anything.
I see.
-Doctor? Doctor!
-Samuel!
You're driving me nuts.
What are you doing?
Why are you calling for a doctor?
There's swelling at the bottom.
-Swelling?
-Take a look.
Oh, my God. It's an emergency!
We need to take him home.
Excuse me. We don't know you.
-You're overacting.
-[nurse] Doc, he was shot.
-[doctor] Status? Take him in.
-[nurse] Palpatory.
[eerie music playing]
What happened?
-Daniel.
-What happened to him?
Sorry, you're not allowed here.
-That's our sibling. Daniel!
-[phone ringing]
Hello, Mom.
Sorry, my phone was on silent.
Still no news from the doctor.
Yes, just stay calm.
Okay.
It's okay.
[sobbing]
Doc, how is he?
I'm sorry.
[sobbing]
[sentimental music playing]
I shouldn't have waited
for Daniel's birthday next month.
I was planning to propose to him...
to make it more special.
But...
he didn't get to live that long.
[sniffles]
[sobbing]
Daniel wanted this.
[Zernan] He wanted this.
He told me...
that even though the law
would not recognize our marriage,
it was okay.
What was important was the ceremony.
The ceremony is important
for people to know
that we're here.
He told me...
that we will never stop
until the day comes
when we are accepted.
Babe...
I love you, babe!
[Nora crying]
[sentimental music playing]
-[Gabriel] One at a time!
-[laughs]
You're getting bigger.
How are you and Zeus?
Not well.
What do you mean? You're not together?
He left me.
[exclaims]
Nobody in the bar knows where he is.
Since when? Why didn't you tell me?
Huh?
You already have so much drama
in your life. I don't want to add to it.
Want me to punch you?
Stop acting coy.
I've been inside your vulva.
And the rear end, let's not forget.
Let's forget. Bitter past.
Then...
If Zeus doesn't want the baby,
I'll be the father.
Are you sure?
Do you have any objections?
You're going to be a great dad.
-We'll have a beautiful baby.
-I don't know, but that's life.
It may be a while before we meet again.
I also can't text you. It's not allowed.
-Why? Where are you going?
-I'm entering a convent.
Be serious.
Chiqui, in fairness,
you delivered the joke very well.
Do I look like I'm joking?
Is that for real? It doesn't suit you.
I'm serious.
I thought about this for a long time.
I think I will be happy there.
Is it because of me?
Did I ruin your life?
Is it because of you?
Yes and no.
Maybe I just needed to go through that
so I could find God.
Did you ruin my life?
Not at all. You even made it colorful.
If you're saying...
that I was used as an instrument
for you to see God...
does that mean...
he sees me, too?
Of course. Why not?
Well, according to church teachings...
God only created Adam and Eve.
Where am I there?
Do you believe that God gave you life?
Of course.
That's the only answer you need.
If He gave you life,
then that means He can hear and see you.
In fairness,
you already sound like Sister Stella L.
-Sister Chiqui.
-[both laugh]
You seem like a true nun.
[both laugh]
[Samuel] She did become a nun!
We don't see each other often,
but I always send them eggs.
I wonder what they do with eggs.
[Gabriel] Kat was in labor for 16 hours
before our baby was born.
I'm not the father,
but many say the baby looks like me.
You don't need to be blood relatives
to become a family.
I have proven that with my gay friends
who became my family
after my father kicked me out.
I also proved that with Kat,
and our son, Prince Vladimir Ashley.
[Samuel] That's so gay.
Don't butt in. This is my voice-over.
You know what? I've been thinking...
Why don't I make it real?
What if I marry this girl?
[priest] You may now kiss the bride.
[instrumental music playing]
[Gabriel] Wait, you might be thinking
I suddenly became straight.
There was no magical transformation.
I married Kat
because I could see myself
growing old with her.
She feels the same way about me.
Before you judge us,
look at yourselves in the mirror.
Think of those married politicians
showing off their extra-marital affairs.
If you voted for them,
how can you judge us?
-[Samuel] The gay got married!
-[Nora] Congrats!
I wanted to stop her,
but I wanted to experience
being a maid of honor.
-Congrats.
-Okay, okay.
-Picture.
-Wait a minute.
[Gabriel] I thought if there was someone
who would be happy I got married,
it would be Don Emilio.
But... he didn't come.
Mom says
that he has kept himself busy
visiting Daniel's tomb.
Even now his condition has worsened,
he still visits him every day,
always bringing him flowers,
even though he is already very weak.
[Nora] Don Emilio, your sons are here.
Go ahead.
[sighs]
Don Emilio, you don't need
to come here every day.
You need to get well.
Did I kill your brother?
Maybe if I had accepted him...
things would have been different.
Yes, someone else killed him...
but I was the root of it all.
I was a bigot.
I committed a grave sin...
against everyone.
You may not believe this,
but I've always loved you.
I thought my strictness
would correct your ways.
I thought it would save you...
from peril.
I always worry about you.
I don't want people
to laugh at you. [sniffles]
I don't want...
I don't want them to insult you...
or belittle you.
But I was only thinking
of myself, my own welfare...
my reputation and the Panti name.
I never thought about
what would make him truly happy.
[sobbing]
Please forgive me.
[crying] Forgive me, my children.
[sobbing] Forgive me.
We forgive you, Don Emilio.
But you need to forgive yourself.
If Daniel were here,
I'm sure that's also what he would want.
-[sentimental music playing]
-What's important is you're still here.
We can start over again.
[sobbing] We can still see you
and spend time with you.
We can make up for lost time.
Can you call me "Dad"?
Call me "Dad."
Dad... Dad...
It's music to my ears.
Can you do it? You want me to do it?
-I think I can do it more.
-You have big bodies, yet you...
-[upbeat music playing]
-All you do is flirt.
I'll do it.
-I'll text you later.
-You're shameless.
-Doing it in front of Dad.
-[shushes]
What's your Facebook, handsome?
He's mine.
Dad, did you really donate
our inheritance to charity?
[Daniel] You are so materialistic, Samuel.
Huh?
Aren't you dead?
How come you have a voice-over?
-[Samuel] I was just asking.
-[Gabriel] Daniel, are you in Heaven?
Is there Heaven for gay people like us?
[Daniel] Oh, yes,
you'll love it here, sisters.
Do you wanna see it?
Want to come over? [chuckles]
[Gabriel] We're not yet ready, but Dad is.
[Samuel] You fool.
[Gabriel] Do you want to go instead?
[cast chatting and laughing]
I never thought we'd all get along.
No ruckus, no fights.
[Nora] You're right.
From now on, we're not gonna fight.
There's nothing to argue about.
That's correct. We promised this tramp.
Sorry. Sorry.
I just went to the toilet. Are we ready?
[Don Emilio] Let's do this. Positions.
Okay. I'll get set up.
Excuse me. I'm ready. My room smells nice.
His smells of saliva. Mine smells better.
-The shower is also ready.
-No, his room smells like feet.
No, check his breath.
-Look at his face.
-He's married.
Hey, hey!
Stop it. Behave.
You're not acting like Pantis.
-Go to your positions.
-Yeah.
-Sorry, okay.
-Let's do this, we're ready.
All right!
One, two, three, say "Panti!"
-[all] Panti!
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[photographer] We'll do one more.
-Let's look happier.
-[all laugh]
-[photographer] One, two, three.
[photographer] One big Panti.
[all] Panti!
[camera shutter clicks]
[funky music playing]
Your mom's decision
in enrolling you in a school...
-[bleeping]
-[laughter]
I am working very hard for his work...
-[bleeping]
-What's happening?
I am working very hard for... [stammering]
-[bleeping]
-[muttering]
[man mumbling indistinctly]
-I took him as a special...
-[bleeping]
-[all grunting]
-Girls, position!
Uniting our hearts... [laughs]
[crew speaking indistinctly]
Uniting our hearts to fight as one
is what makes us sailor power!
-Mercury... [laughs]
-[all laugh]
That unhatched offspring
is not a product of love, but of need!
[in Tagalog] Did he have to translate?
Do you want me
to translate it for you in Chinese?
[speaking mock Mandarin]
I can translate it into Japanese.
[speaking mock Japanese]
Let's go.
Chiqui!
Chiqui, come on!
That hurts!
-[shouts]
-[both gasp]
-My mom.
-What happened?
I told my mom that I would buy her lunch.
-Ouch, that hurts.
-It's already evening!
[crew laughing]
-[laughing]
-[director] Cut!
Why did you ask us to come here, Don...
-Don Emilio!
-[laughter]
[crew speaking indistinctly]
You're so sensitive.
You are just like your mother.
Hey, gay MC Hammer.
-You are...
-[all laughing]
-Sorry!
-[laughing]
[crew member laughing]
[dance music playing]
[Samuel] Oh, what's this? A sequel?
-[Gabriel] Don't you like it?
-[Samuel] It could be a prequel.
[Gabriel] You could be
the next one to die. I hope so.