Yes!
I win.
The deal was,
the loser has to pay for the movie.
I won't flake out.
If you're so skilfull,
let's race for one more round.
That's not the deal.
What a wimp.
Come on, Tan, don't be a sore loser.
When did you get here, Ice?
Ice, this is Perth.
This is Ice, my girl.
I remember.
You're the guy Tan tells me
he practices with.
Yeah.
Actually, we aren't here to swim.
We are secret lovers.
Right, darling?
Get off me. Get away.
Get away.
Get out.
I'm okay with seeing you two
at the same time.
Hey!
Don't you think you should ask me?
This pool looks really big.
Why don't we try diving
from that platform?
Wow.
Before you think about diving,
I think you should learn
how to swim first.
I'm not scared.
I have two varsity swimmers here.
Hey, Ice. Ice, wait!
If you don't know how,
you can hurt yourself, Ice.
Ice!
Stop messing around!
Your eyes are about to fall out.
Stop staring at her.
Just keep diving.
Hey!
Don't you dare stare!
Hey, Ice!
Are you for real?
3 MONTHS AFTER ICE'S DEATH
BANGKOK GAMES 2014
NATIONAL YOUTH GAMES
-Perth, hurry.
-Hurry, Perth. Hurry!
-Perth!
-Go, Perth.
Come on. Hurry!
-Hurry!
Yes!
He's amazing, well done.
Seriously,
before my gold medal win,
were you ever interested in me?
How about this? Is this called interested?
Hey.
I don't have a condom.
Perth.
Don't be a spoilsport.
Is this...
what you call a spoilsport?
CONGRATULATIONS TO
MR. PATTHANA SAKDAPICHET
THE GOLD MEDAL WINNER
SATHIT CHONBURI SCHOOL
I AM SO HAPPY FOR YOU PERTH.
GOOD JOB.
CUTE AND TALENTED.
WHAT A PACKAGE.
LIKE
YOU CAN DO EVEN BETTER.
THANK YOU, BUT I STILL NEED MORE TRAINING.
GREAT JOB, PERTH.
YOU WON THIS TIME
BECAUSE TAN WASN'T COMPETING.
JUST NOW.
DELETE
SEARCH FRIENDS.
GO TO SLEEP. 8TH JUNE 2014
THIS SATURDAY DON'T FORGET
ICE'S 100TH DAY MEMORIAL.
8TH JUNE 2014
MESSAGES.
ICE: WHAT CLIP?
PERTH: THE BEACH CLIP.
ICE: WHY DO YOU NEED IT?
PERTH: I WANT IT.
ICE: HERE YOU GO.
Here, they have an example, too.
"In order to",
must be followed by a finite verb.
But...
"In order that",
must be used in conjunction
with a complete sentence.
Understand?
Who are you daydreaming about?
I'm sorry.
-I'll be back.
-Okay.
What the heck, Mint?
I just wanted to check my Facebook.
What is the matter?
Ask me first.
I don't like people messing with my stuff.
I'm sorry, then,
for intruding in your personal space.
I'm leaving.
-Hey, wait!
-Get in!
Let me go! Get off!
-Come on in.
-Wait, I don't want to.
-Come on.
-Hey!
Ice?
I like you, Ice.
How about you?
Do you feel the same?
-Hey! What are you doing?
-Come on, you!
Throw her in!
-Throw her!
-Throw her in!
Where are you going?
-Come on!
-Throw her in!
I like you, Ice.
I think your dad's car
is starting to fall apart.
This morning, the car overheated
and broke down on an overpass.
Luckily, there were no cars behind me.
-Mom.
-Hm?
Last night, did you come in my room?
Last night, I worked the graveyard shift.
Did something happen?
Nothing.
Use your quads!
Faster!
Come on, faster!
Overall, everyone improved
on their average time.
So just cool down by doing ten laps,
and then you can go home.
Perth.
I told you to eat one raw egg a day.
Have you started yet?
Don't you want to qualify
for the university sports quota?
You know, this time,
just one slot is open
and it goes to first place?
If this is your best time,
Tan could do better.
Are we going anywhere after?
-Not after today's grueling practice.
-I'm not going, you?
-How about you?
-Pussy!
-Hey!
-You're not going?
-Oh man. I'm done.
-I'm done, too.
-Drive safe.
-Okay.
Where have you been hiding?
The whole team is worried.
Are you still hung up
about what happened to Ice?
Ice has found peace now.
Just let it go.
"Found peace?"
You think people who commit suicide
find peace?
And how does stressing out do any good?
It won't bring her back, you know.
I must find...
the asshole who caused Ice
to kill herself.
What is that supposed to mean?
Ice killed herself...
because she was pregnant.
-You talk like the both of you never...
-No.
No, we never had sex.
Even if you find out...
what can you do about it?
I'll kill him.
WHERE ARE YOU, TAN?
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOREVER.
Ice, your coochie is showing.
You pervert.
You can't see anything.
I'm wearing shorts.
What time are you guys supposed to meet?
Did you call him?
I called already, but Tan didn't pick up.
You are always training.
Tan never trains this much.
Tan is gifted.
I'm not.
So I need to train harder.
That's not true.
Tan can't swim underwater as long as you.
Yeah, there should be...
an underwater diving competition, huh?
Hello, Tan, where are you?
Stop talking. It's always the same excuse.
So you are ditching me again, right?
And what about teaching me to swim?
If I have to wait for you,
I will never learn to swim.
Ice.
Here.
Hey.
You know today is my birthday?
It's Tan's.
He asked me to give this to you
in case he didn't make it.
It's cute.
Of course.
I was the one who picked it out.
Here.
This is from me.
I made it myself.
Thanks.
I got to go. I will see you later.
Ice?
I can teach you to swim.
What's wrong?
-Do you have a cramp?
-Yeah.
Are you feeling better?
Yeah.
You have a tattoo?
Just for fun.
What does it say?
"Ai."
"Ai"?
What does it mean?
"Ai" means love.
As in...
"Wo Ai Ni", I love you?
Yeah.
Then...
Wo Ai Ni.
I'm okay now.
Let's get back to my lesson.
Wait.
So do you also Ni Ai Wo?
What's wrong?
Don't you feel the same?
But I'm still with Tan.
INTHIRA RATIKANAN
TAN: ARE YOU AT ICE'S FUNERAL?
ARE YOU AT ICE'S FUNERAL?
IS IT ALMOST OVER?
ALMOST DONE.
WHEN THE FUNERAL IS OVER. CALL ME.
WHERE ARE YOU?
I'M AT ICE'S HOUSE.
Let's go home.
The number you have dialed
is not available.
Tan?
Tan!
Her mom is coming back. Come on out.
It's me. Perth.
Tan, can you hear me?
Hey!
Ice?
Don't you love me anymore?
That's why you left me here alone.
I'm so lonely.
I...
lit an incense stick to guide you home.
Please come home.
Let me have a look...
at how pretty you are.
Perth?
I'm pregnant.
Stop freaking out.
Perth, I'm just joking.
Here, look. There is only one line.
You see?
I didn't think you would
stress out this much.
Mint...
I am really busy training now.
I don't think I will have time to see you.
Are you breaking up with me?
What happened that night...
I...
I didn't mean to...
It didn't mean anything to me, too.
You are so full of yourself.
I'm sorry.
If I were really pregnant...
would you still treat me this way?
I'LL BE LATE. PLEASE MAKE YOURSELF DINNER.
Mom?
Mom!
Perth, I told you if I am not home yet,
do not lock the main door.
I was out at the supermarket.
Your teacher saw I had a lot of stuff,
and gave me a lift home.
Oh.
So where is your car?
This morning,
I took the car to the repair shop.
What's with the mess?
I thought we ran out of cooking gas.
I was the one who told Perth
to eat raw eggs,
to boost his energy.
You're supposed to only eat one a day.
He must take after me.
When I was pregnant,
I loved to eat raw eggs.
-Really?
-Yes.
If you eat this many raw eggs,
you will definitely be in shape.
If you were giving birth,
you wouldn't need a doctor.
Nonsense.
Perth!
You must be eating like a pig.
Your six-pack is now just one-pack.
I got it. You're constipated, right?
Hey, Tan.
Are you back to train?
Nope. I just feel like swimming.
-Perth, we're gonna go.
-See you.
Hey.
What were you doing at Ice's house?
So, you know where she lives?
That's how you followed me there?
I took her home once.
When you were at a swim meet.
So what the hell were you doing there?
I went in to get her cell phone.
But the screen was all smashed
and wouldn't turn on.
I'm going to take it
to see if they can fix it.
I'm sure there'll be pictures
of that asshole.
I think you should just drop it
and come back to school.
Okay.
Whatever. It's none of my business anyway.
I got to go.
Excuse me.
The pool will be closing soon.
Put your stuff away and go home,
before I lock the doors.
Okay.
PHARMACY
INCOMING CALL TAN
Hello?
My mom dropped her phone in water.
That shop you used, is it good?
I don't know.
I haven't gotten it back yet.
Where is it?
I will get it fixed there, too.
It's at Robinson.
The shop has a big yellow sign in front.
Excuse me.
Um...
My friend asked me to pick up his BB.
The one you were trying
to recover data from.
I think you got the wrong shop.
Nobody brought in a BB for repair.
No, I'm sure.
Let me see the receipt.
Oh.
Give me a second.
I forgot to bring it.
Sorry.
Without a receipt,
even if it was you who dropped it off,
I couldn't give you the phone.
Perth.
You brought your mom's phone?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
I'm here to pick up the BB that needed
the data recovered.
One second.
Where is your mom's phone anyway?
Why don't you give it to check?
It's okay.
I want to shop around a bit first.
Excuse me.
Your phone is damaged beyond repair.
We couldn't recover any data.
That's okay.
I will see if another shop can help.
I'm going to get wasted tonight.
You want to come?
No, you go ahead.
I gotta meet up with my mom here.
Shit.
Hey.
Let go of me!
You trying to scare me, Ice?
I always see you training late at night.
Scared of ghosts?
Who? Me?
Scared?
Oh, boo-hoo.
Sure you're not scared?
Don't even give me that smirk.
What are you doing here this late?
I broke up with Tan.
Does he know about...
you and me?
No.
I want you to tell Tan yourself.
So, when are you going to talk to him?
After he is done competing.
I'm afraid he will lose focus.
But that's a long time from now.
I don't like sneaking around like this.
But sneaking around...
like this is exciting, isn't it?
You like to be excited, huh?
Perth?
Perth, are you here?
Aren't you over doing it?
What are you...
doing here so late?
Ice broke up with me.
Then let's...
go get wasted together.
But can I catch up in a bit?
You're getting your kicks up there.
You don't have to come.
I don't want to take you from anybody.
Enjoy! I'm out of here!
What we are doing is wrong, isn't it?
Do you still have feelings for Tan?
I just don't want him to get hurt.
I get hurt, too...
when I see you around Tan.
What now?
Come on.
Snap out of it.
Snap out of it!
Stop teasing me.
I'm still mad at you.
Let's get off.
I didn't mean this.
So...
what did you mean?
I love you, Ice.
Perth?
Do you have protection?
Don't worry.
If worst comes to worst...
I will carry our baby for you.
You're silly.
Take care of our baby.
Other than a seahorse's unique
method of reproduction,
its specie's other unique characteristic,
is its loyalty to its mate.
Even after it's mate dies,
the remaining seahorse
will not find another mate.
YOU STUDIED WITH THIS JERK
IN MIDDLE SCHOOL, RIGHT?
Try. Very good.
HE POSTED A LOT ON ICE'S FACEBOOK.
Okay, all of you, I want you
DO YOU THINK ICE DID IT WITH HIM?
to get into groups of three
and do the assignment.
I DOUBT IT.
About the reproduction
of underwater animals.
Or go and look for info at the aquarium.
Have you been there?
It's near your home, right?
In that case...
I KNEW IT!
YOU KNEW WHAT?
I SAW THEM WALKING TOGETHER AT THE MALL.
Reports say that 56 percent
of motorists drive recklessly,
-drive through red lights.
-Drive through red lights?
While 24 percent do not pull over
at designated stops.
Mom!
Shit!
The initial blood test came back normal.
I am going to order an ultrasound.
Perth.
Perth?
Come here.
This will feel a little cold
on your abdomen.
Your pregnancy is in its fourth trimester.
Everything looks normal.
This right here, is the baby's head.
This is the spinal column.
Right here. Can you see it?
It is the arms and legs.
Right here...
is the heart.
I will let you hear the heartbeat.
Ice, just calm down.
These tests are not 100% accurate.
Maybe...
you did it wrong.
I took the test twice already.
Pissing on a piece of plastic,
isn't that difficult.
Have you told Tan yet?
Ice...
I didn't mean it like that.
I will take care of it myself.
Take care of what?
An abortion?
That is murder.
Okay.
I won't have an abortion.
We can tell my mom together
this evening, then.
Then, tomorrow...
we can drop out from school.
Perth?
Do you have some money saved up?
You should start looking for a job soon.
When our baby is born...
we don't want to be penniless.
Also, about...
I'm so sorry.
I will find a way to take care of this.
I have a friend who had one before.
Ice, where did you get this money?
From my aunt.
This will feel a little cold.
Who's there?
Open the door!
Mint?
Mint!
Mint! Mint!
Who the hell is there?
Shit!
-Oh, my God.
-Shit.
What are you doing down here?
Coach sent me to get something.
But I cannot find it.
If you're going to lie,
you have to do better than that.
Keep your nose out of my business.
What do you mean?
You mean you and Ice?
Taking off already?
Yeah.
Hey,
I heard you're in the next qualifier?
Yeah.
What is your best time?
Why don't you race me and see?
I'm curious if the national champ...
can keep up with me yet.
You better find out...
at the swim meet, then.
I don't really care what your time is.
I'm out of here.
Twelve...
thirteen.
Fifteen, sixteen, seventeen.
Forty-four, forty-five, forty-six,
forty-seven, forty-eight, forty-nine,
fifty, fifty-one, fifty-two.
Here.
-Thanks.
-It's nothing.
How did you do
on your first day of training?
I did okay.
Still a little rusty.
CONGRATULATIONS TO KITTHIPHONG PHROMMUL
BRONZE MEDAL WINNER.
No practice today?
Nope.
Qualifiers are soon.
I want to rest my muscles.
Perfect.
I need a wingman.
Hey!
Hey, man, slow down! What's the hurry?
Damn!
Why are we here?
Perth, how many years
have we been friends?
What the hell is going on?
Perth what is so important
that you wanted to meet here?
You are the asshole...
who knocked up Ice, right?
What the hell are you on about?
Don't play stupid.
-Tan, calm down.
-Wait a second!
Let me explain.
I only commented on her Facebook,
but she didn't reply.
Don't lie.
Perth said,
that he saw you two
walking together at the mall.
Perth?
When did you see me with Ice?
It wasn't me!
Perth!
Why don't you just admit it?
When did you see me at the mall with Ice?
-I don't even have her number.
-Asshole!
How dare you still lie?
Asshole!
This guy has no shame at all.
We kicked his ass
and he still didn't fess up.
Perth, are you crazy?
I could have fallen off for real!
Crazy? Look who's talking.
What are you on about?
I saw you...
talking to Tan.
So what if I talk to Tan?
You're afraid I will tell Tan
about the clip?
That clip is so old.
I already forgot about it.
I admit...
that I used to have a crush on Ice.
But Ice was Tan's girlfriend.
Okay?
Right now,
I don't care if Tan finds out.
What I do care about
is you talking with other guys.
I don't believe you.
You know I am bad at lying.
Mint, you've got to work with me on this.
If we both qualify
for the university admission quota...
we can move in together.
That's all for today.
DHARMA FORUM
Don't forget to turn in your work.
Everyone can go now.
MR. D-E-B ARE YOU A MONK?
I AM AN ORDINARY PERSON.
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
GO AHEAD
CAN A SPIRIT POSSESS A PERSON'S BODY?
A SPIRIT CAN POSSESS, YES.
I MEAN, CAN IT REALLY ENTER A HUMAN BODY?
IT DEPENDS WHAT THE SPIRIT WANTS.
THE SPIRIT WANTS TO BE REBORN.
DID YOU HAVE AN ABORTION?
Perth.
What do you think
Ice's Facebook password is?
You know...
when people come up with a password,
they base it on something personal.
Like, their address,
birthday, or phone number.
Even their boyfriend's birthday.
Why do you want to know?
The guy had to chat with Ice
on Facebook for sure.
You will have to keep digging, then.
Perth.
When is your birthday?
ENTER PASSWORD
REENTER YOUR PASSWORD
Hey, turn off that computer now.
We are closing now.
REENTER YOUR PASSWORD
MESSAGES
DOWNLOAD
ICE: WHAT CLIP?
PERTH: THE BEACH CLIP.
ICE: WHY DO YOU NEED IT?
PERTH: I WANT IT.
ICE: HERE YOU GO.
SETTINGS
DELETE MESSAGE
NO MESSAGE SELECTED
I already filled it up.
It's leaking. It's all leaked out.
How is it leaking?
You didn't get it repaired?
I...
Well...
I came to get a book
that Ice borrowed from me.
Well...
I...
I needed it for an exam.
-Over here!
-Quick!
-Hurry!
-Over here!
-Give me the ball!
-Moss!
-Pass it!
-You're gonna lose!
-Quick!
-Quick, over here!
On the Internet, it says...
do not use this
if over nine weeks pregnant.
Moss! Moss!
Moss, quickly!
Come on!
Quick! Run, Moss!
Ice?
Ice, you got stomach cramps?
The next event will be
the women's 200-meter butterfly.
Competitors, please take your places.
PATTHANA SAKDAPICHET
Lane 2, Supakorn Chivathavorn.
Lane 3, Tantai Guntha-in.
Lane 4, Phasu Singusaha.
Lane 5, Patthana Sakdapichet.
Excuse me.
The race is about to start.
You have to take off your jacket first.
You need to step outside.
Where the hell are you?
Come on out!
Come out!
Don't worry.
Perth's going to be fine.
Perth?
Perth!
Open up!
-Perth!
-Perth, open the door!
Perth!
Perth, open the door!
-Perth, please open the door.
-Perth!
Ouch.
Perth, open the door!
Perth!
-Perth!
Perth?
Perth!
Perth is suffering
from excess abdominal fluid build-up.
It is a symptom of having Hepatitis B.
Teens usually contract the disease
through sexual intercourse.
Is there a cure, doctor?
Well, it could take up to...
Perth.
Perth, everything is okay now.
Mom.
I'm pregnant.
Mom!
It's in my tummy.
It's in my tummy, Mom.
-Mom, you have to help me.
-There is nothing wrong with you.
It's just some fluid in your stomach.
Here. Feel it for yourself. See?
But I really saw it with my own eyes.
Where did it go?
-Where is it?
-Perth.
-It's in my tummy.
-Perth, relax.
-It's nothing.
-Perth.
-Really, Mom.
The doctor said it's just fluid.
I already gave him an injection
to relax the muscles.
Tomorrow I will have a psychiatrist
come and examine him.
Perth.
-Perth, trust me.
-Mom, help me.
Tomorrow, I will be here
early in the morning.
Damn it!
You're pathetic, Perth.
How gross.
So this is all it takes for you
to piss your pants.
Tan.
I...
I'm sorry.
Don't shit your pants yet.
You don't even know what I am going to do.
Did you know...
that I give Ice the money
for her abortion?
I didn't even ask her...
who the asshole was.
I just wanted her
to get past that shitty situation.
TOMORROW, I'M COMING OVER
TO YOUR HOUSE, OKAY?
SURE, THE POOL IS CLOSED.
I'LL BE HOME ALL DAY.
THANK YOU.
That day, Ice sent me a message
that she was going to come over.
So I don't believe...
that she would kill herself.
I am getting back with Tan.
No.
I won't let you get back
together with Tan.
I didn't come here
to ask for your permission.
I just want to let you know.
No, you can't!
I beg you.
Let's stay together, please?
-Let go.
-No.
Perth, let go! Perth!
Perth, let me go!
Perth!
Perth, let me go now!
Perth! Perth!
I...
I'm...
I am sorry.
Just a sorry, and you think
I would let you go?
Today at 8:00 am,
the body of Mr. Tantai Gunta-in,
a 17-year-old swimmer was found
at the bottom of the city pool
in Chonburi province.
He was found with weights
tied to his ankles.
There were no signs of any struggle.
Police forensics say it was a suicide.
The reason was supposedly guilt,
for breaking his girlfriend's heart.
The event occurred at the same place
she took her own life earlier this year.
Investigators will keep the case open...
6 MONTHS AFTER TAN'S DEATH
I left a part of me with you
For you to feel my warmth
And tenderness
Because I will always be with you
wherever you are
Until the day that you return
Tomorrow
Our lives may change
But tomorrow can't change our love
Tomorrow
Our lives may change
But tomorrow can't change our love
I left a part of me with you
For you to feel my warmth
And tenderness
Because I will always be with you
Wherever you are
Until the day that you return