They say this world has
a lot of evil things,
yet, it is beautiful at the same time.
I don't know if they are right…
but I'm about to get to know this world
all over again.
Wong Kar Mun,
I'm giving you a local anesthetic now.
The operation will take about two hours.
Are you ready?
Who's that?
Quiet! Do you want to alarm
all the nurses?
I'm in the bed next to yours.
I heard that you've just gone
through an eye operation.
I've had many operations here.
Everyone here is a good friend of mine.
How old are you?
Why did you need so many operations?
Eleven years old.
I should be in junior high by now,
but Mum said,
there's an extra black lump in my brain,
which affects my nervous system.
Which means I can simply pass out
at any given moment.
I need open surgery to remove the lump,
but it cannot be done in one go,
because it's very dangerous.
So, I skipped school last year
and have been here ever since.
You're so young, yet so brave!
Big Sister, once you can see again,
I'll take you out to play.
The world is a truly beautiful place.
Wong Kar Mun,
when I remove the bandages on your eyes,
it might hurt a little.
If it hurts too much, let me know.
We can always
remove the bandages tomorrow.
Okay, give it a try,
open your eyes slowly.
Mun, don't force yourself if it hurts.
It hurts!
Is it too much?
Dr. Lo, she must be in a lot of pain!
She's never cried out in pain
since she was a kid!
Easy, Granny, Dr. Lo knows what to do.
Please don't worry yourself.
In fact, very few patients
see immediate success.
It takes time for the eye and brain
to work together.
Here.
Ying Ying.
Ying Ying!
Big Sister, can you see now?
I'm Ying Ying.
Can you really see me?
It seems I can see now.
Fantastic! Big Sister can see!
Nurse, Big Sister can see!
Nurse, Big Sister's eyes
are able to see now!
She sees me! Come quickly…
Granny! The hospital called,
Mun can see again!
What?
Mun can see!
-Really?
-Go get changed, let's go see her now.
Are you going to discharge me now?
Not so soon.
Every cornea recipient
starts off shortsighted,
by as much as 1,000 degrees.
Only when your shortsightedness
falls to about 200 degrees,
will your eye muscles be able to adapt.
When will she have perfect eyesight then?
No one has perfect eyesight,
most people are shortsighted
by about 100 degrees.
That sounds troublesome.
Will she need glasses?
No need, madam.
All she needs is a pair of sunglasses
for the time being.
Mun, get some rest.
If everything goes well,
you can leave earlier.
You can take off your sunglasses now.
Try to get used to the light gradually.
If you feel pain,
or if your eyes start tearing up,
that means you should close your eyes
and let your eyes rest.
Here, I'll help you onto the bed.
Nurse.
Is there a mirror in every washroom?
I'll take you there.
Here.
Slowly.
Take your time,
call me if you need anything.
Who's that?
Ying Ying, is that you?
Why are you so quiet?
Big Sister,
I'm having another operation tomorrow.
You made a promise
to take me out once I can see again.
So, hurry up with your operation,
then we can go out and have fun.
Did they say you can leave now?
Not yet.
But even when I do,
I can always drop by to visit you.
Sis, let's take a picture together.
-Let's do it outside!
-Okay!
-Let's go…
-Go where?
Here, let's take a picture here!
What's this?
-A camera.
-A camera?
Yes. Now, look this way.
Okay.
Ready? One, two, three!
Madam, are you all right?
Madam…
I'm freezing…
Send this one to Block C.
We have a full house
in the Block B Morgue.
Nurse?
Is the old lady dead?
It has been taken care of.
But last night…
I saw someone drop by to visit her.
They even went out together.
Are you sure?
We don't allow any visitors here at night.
Where's Ying Ying?
She went in for an operation this morning.
Dr. Lo wanted you to stay
for two more days for observation,
but I'll be away on flight duty
for two weeks.
No one will be able to pick you up then.
It's easier to have you discharged now.
This way, you and Granny
can spend more time together.
My! It's already 3:00 p.m.!
I wonder if this place is easy to find.
Should have waited until I'd returned.
It's only a few more days after all.
After meeting the therapist,
I'll put you in a taxi.
Granny will meet you downstairs.
Wonder if we can still make it…
Our appointment was at 3:00 p.m.,
we're only ten minutes late.
I have to leave for work soon.
Excuse me, you've mistaken my words.
Dr. Lo saw that you hadn't arrived,
so he went out to buy something.
Okay.
Dr. Lo's back.
Where's my three o'clock?
That's her.
Mun, let's go.
Let me introduce you
to the nature of my work.
Starting from now,
I am Miss Wong Kar Mun's psychotherapist.
Since Miss Wong
lost her sight at the age of two,
her visual vocabulary
is extremely limited,
and she has probably forgotten
most of even that.
For example,
Miss Wong, please remove your glasses
and let your eyes get used to the light.
Can you tell what's in my hand?
You'll recognize it's a stapler
once you touch it,
because all your previous knowledge
of objects
was based on touch, not on sight.
Yet, you are no longer blind.
My job is to help you re-establish
how to use your eyes
and understand what you see.
Actually, I'm not too worried
about that aspect.
What concerns me
is the patient's psychological state.
After regaining their sight, many patients
end up feeling alienated and fearful.
Dr. Lo, is the other Dr. Lo
a relative of yours?
You mean my uncle?
Yes, he's my father's younger brother.
So, what time do you finish work today?
Miss Wong is my last patient for the day.
Well, you see, I need to catch my flight,
so, can I trouble you to get
Mun home after this?
I see. Of course.
Besides, starting from today,
I need to take Miss Wong outdoors
for her training anyway.
Okay.
Sis, you can go ahead, I'm fine by myself,
I'm used to it.
This is you as a little girl.
Your father shot this a long time ago,
so that
you could look at it
once your eyes healed.
It was seven or eight years ago.
He stopped filming ever since
he divorced your mother.
Granny, is it true when Daddy comes back,
he'll take us to Vancouver?
I know you don't want to go,
but Vancouver's pace of life is slower,
it'll suit you better.
I can't even read Chinese,
how can I learn English?
Granny, I don't want to
rely on others forever.
I want to learn to write
and find a job in Hong Kong.
I want to be independent.
Your father might worry about
you going to work.
I have to do the dishes,
just take your time.
Hey, kid, what's up?
Sis, have you seen my report card?
No, I haven't.
Do you live upstairs?
Mun, who's that?
It's a little kid, Granny.
Did a report card
ever fall into our balcony?
That kid is poking fun at you.
Just ignore him!
VIGIL
Kid, what are you munching on?
I'm very hungry.
What is it? What's your problem?
Bravo!
We have two pieces
of good news today, everyone.
First…
Miss Tone Deaf had a successful operation!
And second,
for our Christmas charity concert,
we'll have the honor to perform
with Miss Vanessa-Mae!
Mr. Ching, why haven't
I received the practice schedule?
Mun, you know, after all,
we're an organization for the blind.
You're always welcome
to come and practice, but perhaps,
you should do something else
for the performance,
such as coordination,
or taking care of our members.
I can even arrange for you
to volunteer at the center.
Mr. Ching, I really want to
take part in this performance.
I've practiced so long for this concert.
I totally understand, however…
Excuse me, Mr. Ching,
Vanessa-Mae's agent wants us
to fax over our practice schedule.
I'll be with you right away.
Mun, Mun?
Let's finish our discussion later.
I need to go now. See you.
-Granny!
-Are you leaving?
Yes, to class.
Come back early for dinner.
I've prepared some special turnip soup.
Bye!
Sis, have you seen my report card?
Report card? Haven't you found it yet?
I really haven't seen it.
Perhaps, you should
ask someone else. Okay?
Ying Ying!
Excuse me, I'd like to talk to her.
Look what I've got you.
Sis, I've just gone through chemotherapy.
I'm not supposed to eat.
I'll throw up if I do.
That's all right,
we'll save it until you get better, okay?
If only we had believed him
just that once,
or given him a chance to explain…
he might still be here,
playing video games.
Who would have expected him
to jump off just like that?
Suicide is a dreadful sin.
The souls of those who commit suicide
are obliged to repeat
their painful deaths everyday.
To help him out
of this vicious cycle of pain,
we need to tackle
the cause of his suicide.
Only then can his soul
leave this world in peace.
Have you ever considered
he might be telling the truth?
Perhaps, he really did lose
his report card.
Sir, have you been teaching here long?
Yes, indeed. Many years.
This is calligraphy.
I'll teach you how to write.
Here, hold the brush and write.
Use your big thumb and index finger,
form a circle just like this.
Like this… and write. Here, try.
Very few want to learn
calligraphy, nowadays.
I used to teach three lessons a week,
now, I have only one lesson a week.
Now, try writing by yourself, okay?
Practice on your own.
Why did you take my seat?
What is this? What is going on?
What are you looking for? Are you okay?
How did this happen?
Are you not feeling well?
Is Dr. Lo here?
Miss Wong, you were here two days ago.
Your next appointment isn't till Friday.
He's out for a meeting,
he'll be back at 5:00 p.m.
Will he definitely be here at 5:00 p.m.?
Is it urgent? I can page him if you want.
I'll be back at 5:00.
SANYANG CAFE
Can you see them, too?
They usually don't want you
to notice them.
Give it some time,
and you'll get used to it.
All the stores nearby have been bought up,
only my boss refuses to sell.
He seems to be expecting
his wife and child to visit.
Actually, he can't see them at all.
There's been a car accident over there…
Don't move him,
he may have some fractured bones.
Mun!
My secretary said you were asking for me.
What's the matter?
Will you help me?
Sure, of course I will. Do your eyes hurt?
-Will you believe me?
-Yes.
What is it?
That black figure,
he came to take the dead.
What black figure?
When I was at the hospital…
I saw a black figure.
He took an old lady with him.
The next morning, the old lady was dead.
My room keeps changing suddenly
into a different room.
I even saw a person
with the lower half of her body missing.
When they rushed over,
it was like an electric shock…
my whole body went numb…
Calm down. Tell me slowly.
When I was little…
Granny told me…
I was not an ordinary child…
God had given me some obstacles,
so that I would grow up
to be an extraordinary person.
Now, I finally understand
what it means to be extraordinary.
An extraordinary person
can see things other people can't see…
feel pain other people won't feel.
Maybe, I was never meant
to see this world.
I don't want to be confined
in my own world anymore,
terrified in bed every night…
then awakening to horrors every morning.
I just want to be an ordinary person.
Wah, can you help me?
Yes, yes.
One of my psychology professors
from the States
has just come to Hong Kong for a visit.
Let's meet him tomorrow,
maybe he can help you.
How can you help me without believing me?
Sis, what's going on?
Excuse me, I have to go.
Call me if you need anything.
Goodbye.
Who's that?
A friend.
He asked Yee to take something
to a friend in the States.
Yes, that's right.
You are home early.
Aren't you supposed to be back next week?
Well… a co-worker
switched her shift with mine,
so, I'm back early.
You go home first, it's so smoky here.
Go on!
14TH FLOOR, UNIT-C
Sis, have you seen my report card?
Why keep asking me?
I already told you I haven't!
Sis, have you seen my report card?
15TH FLOOR, UNIT-C
Uncle, listen to me…
No way!
Only you can help us out!
I've already said no!
If you still respect me as your uncle,
and respect yourself as my nephew,
you should have
never approached me on this!
First of all,
you should know only too well
what medical ethics are,
regarding organ transplants.
And you should know better that
the identity of the cornea donor
is concealed from me.
What black figures?
One cornea transplant
and she starts seeing ghosts?
You actually believe that?
What if I do?
Then we have even less to talk about!
Uncle…
Don't tell me,
you're in love with your patient.
Hello?
Wah, is this you? Mun is in trouble!
Can you come over immediately?
Yes, right away.
Yes, I admit,
she's more than a patient to me.
Mun! Mun!
How long do you plan
on hiding in this little room?
Five years? Seven? Or 10?
You have to confront your problem
sooner or later.
You want to play violin?
Go play with the group!
I can accept you pretending to be blind.
But even when you were blind,
you didn't just stay here.
I just want to help.
-Mun.
-Mun!
Sister.
Ying Ying, what are you doing here?
Sister, I can leave the hospital now.
You can leave?
Yes, I don't need any more operations,
I can go to school now.
Then…
Then once I am out of here …
we can go out and play together…
we can take pictures, we can even…
I'm so happy that you can see now…
because this world is really beautiful.
Ying Ying…
It's all right! Cheer up.
Stay strong and things will be all right.
Sis, I have to go now.
Ying Ying!
Wong Kar Mun, I want to tell you…
Ying Ying has already--
I know. I just saw her.
I know she's dead.
YUEN KIT YING
What are you looking at?
Ying Ying.
Can you see her?
It wasn't her.
Don't know why she didn't show up today.
Are you not afraid anymore?
I don't think I have a choice.
I have to see all these things anyway.
At least, I get to see the ones
I care about.
SIS MUN
What's this?
Ying Ying made this for you.
What's it say?
"Don't forget me."
DON'T FORGET ME
She put in the wrong photo, though.
Who's this?
That's you!
You still don't recognize yourself?
What is going on?
Who the hell are you?
We believe that the last bit
of consciousness of a mortal
carries over to the afterlife.
That is, the very thought of a person
in their final moment,
would become the eternal consciousness
of their soul.
So, those who die a sudden death,
would have no recollection
of the instance of death.
Their souls remain in this world,
as if they're still alive.
But there are others
who refuse to leave intentionally,
mostly because of unsettled problems
in their lifetime.
These souls can't be consoled
if their problems persist.
There is only one way to help them out,
that is, to resolve
what they left unresolved.
The woman Miss Wong
keeps seeing after regaining her sight.
We have to resolve her problems
so that she can move on.
I hope I haven't done anything wrong.
Even if it's wrong, it'd be my fault,
but I won't regret it.
Were you reincarnated into the wrong body?
Why are you so different
from the rest of the family?
Be careful.
BANGKOK, THAILAND
Dr. Lo believed you in the end?
Let's take it that Dr. Lo is not involved.
He's a professional after all…
-you know what I mean?
-Yes.
How much further?
I'm not sure.
It says here, that her Chinese name
was Chiu Wai Ling,
a Thai-born Chinese, I suppose.
Here are her hospital records.
This is Siam Rach Hospital, Siam Rach.
"Si-am-la?"
Does "Si-am-la" mean "Siam"?
Let's get off to take a look.
SIAM RACH HOSPITAL
Hi.
Excuse me, is this hospital named
Siam Rach Lunteban?
-Yes.
-Yes?
I need to speak to a doctor here,
his name is Eak.
Please come and take care of this.
Can I help you?
Hi, I need to speak to a doctor
in this hospital,
his name is Eak.
Do you know him?
No?
But there is a doctor named Eak, right?
It says here,
this is the hospital, his name is Eak.
He's not here now.
He's not here now?
Wah!
What is it?
-This is the place.
-What place?
The place I've been
having nightmares about.
Nightmares?
This has to be it!
-Doctor!
-What's the matter?
You have two visitors.
Mister, this is Dr. Eak.
-Are you Dr. Eak?
-Yes.
My name is Wah.
-Hi.
-Nice to meet you.
It's about her.
She's just had a cornea transplant.
So, we would like
to thank the donor's family.
We hope you can give us some details.
This is the information.
Are you two from Hong Kong?
You speak Mandarin?
Can you help us?
Sorry, I can't disclose
our hospital records,
not without the proper authorization.
Please understand.
Wait! We need to see
the donor's family urgently,
could you perhaps contact them,
and see if they are willing to meet us?
Her family will not be willing
to meet with you.
Who are you to Ling?
Please leave.
Wait!
After I got Ling's corneas,
I started to see things she used to see!
Ling was a sad girl,
everyone in the village
stayed away from her.
Why?
From time to time,
she would weep outside someone's door,
and afterwards,
a person in that house would pass away.
So, everyone took her to be a devil
and always chased her away on sight.
The children treated her like a monster.
I, too, threw stones at her
when I was a kid…
Because none of you could believe
that she foresaw death?
Maybe it was because of fear.
So, do you believe it now?
This is it.
Mrs. Chui, these two friends
are from Hong Kong.
Nobody welcomed Ling…
so, she hardly ever set foot
in the village.
Yet, on the night of the big fire,
many saw her running around
and shouting hysterically,
as if talking to herself.
Since everyone detested Ling,
no one paid any attention to her.
I only heard,
some villagers threw water on her
to drive her away.
Around midnight, a big fire erupted
and kept burning till noon the next day.
Among the deceased,
300 were burned beyond recognition.
-How exactly did Ling die?
-She hanged herself.
Ling killed herself
the day after the big fire.
Is Mrs. Chui all right?
She's fine.
So, you too believed
that she wasn't insane,
that she only saw things
no one else could.
She foresaw a big disaster
and tried to warn everyone,
but no one listened to her.
I don't understand
any of this spiritual stuff.
I just want you two to know
that Ling was a very kind person…
and she had a tough life.
Can I take a look at Ling's room?
Tonight… I want to stay here.
I'll take you to Ling's grave
tomorrow morning.
You've been very kind to us, thank you.
You should go to bed now.
All right, I'm staying next door,
shout out if anything happens.
I know you've wanted me
to come here all this time.
Here I am now.
What do you want to tell me?
…ill-fated!
Hurry! Take her to the hospital!
You are disaster!
Everything you speak is evil!
Shut up, for God's sake!
You jinx! It's all because of you!
Told you not to come here!
She's evil! Don't ever play with her!
Go save him! Save my boy…
Help him… Make him breathe!
For God's sake…
She's evil!
It's all your fault!
Mrs. Chui, I know how to help Ling.
Let's go upstairs to see her.
Her most painful time was not in the past,
it's right now!
Since she killed herself,
she's been trapped
in a time warp,
constantly repeating her suicide.
She's already dead, how can she die again?
Mrs. Chui, listen to me.
Your daughter will appear upstairs
very soon.
Let's go up to see her!
I won't see her!
I spent my whole life protecting her,
I never once gave up on her,
but she gave up on herself!
For that, I can never forgive her!
Just listen,
I'm sure you hear this sound every night.
Ling died at 3:00, didn't she?
Mrs. Chui, come with me
and you'll understand.
I'm not going anywhere!
Mama…
Help me…
Ling?
Help me!
Help me…
Is it Ling?
Is it really Ling?
Mama…
Help me…
Ling, you were the one who left me…
You were the one who left me…
Mama, help me!
Ling, Mama's coming!
Ling! Ling!
Daughter, Ma's right here.
Don't be afraid…
no one can bully you anymore.
Mama, I'm so sorry,
I was wrong…
please forgive me!
I've already forgiven you.
Mun!
What happened?
Are you all right?
IN LOVING MEMORY OF BELOVED DAUGHTER
CHIU WAI LING
MAE CHAEM
Hurry! Pull him out!
Careful! Come on, keep pulling!
Over there! Move!
Run for your life!
Go, go!
Something's happening, get out, quick!
Granny, leave your house now!
Leave your house now!
Brother, run for your life!
Run quickly! Run!
Please come out now! Run!
Please come out now! Run…
Pack and run! A disaster is coming!
Run now!
What's she saying?
Run! Get out!
To your left. Move over!
Move over!
Mun!
Go! Move over!
Run now!
Mun…
Ling disappeared ever since that day.
I hold no resentment towards her,
as I saw and experienced
the same pain that she did.
But I've seen more.
I've seen pain, but I've also seen beauty.
Never again will I ask why am I blind
for I've seen the most beautiful things
in this world,
things I'll never forget.