Invisible to the naked eye
Doesn't mean it's not there
And seeing is not believing
Why does the truth seem so unreal?
While the fake seem so convincing?
It looks calm on the surface
But it is actually scheming to kill you
Some things are not what they seem
And some people are just not human
Don't think you will never meet a ghost
For you never know who is around you
Don't ever think there are no ghosts
Because you don't know what they look like
IN A FORESTED AREA IN THE 1990S
Why were we dispatched here?
Were there no other options?
I absolutely agree.
There are rumors
that this place is haunted.
I've heard that from my relatives, too.
Seven of them came here once for training,
only six left.
I hear you, one of my cousins
told me the same story.
-He was here for training.
-Here?
Yes, here,
one week later after he came back,
he could miraculously speak
several languages.
Chinese, English, Spanish, rubbish.
-Why?
-I don't know.
He lost his ability to speak Malay.
What's this?
A tree root.
I think it's hair.
Really?
Pig!
Barbie doll.
If it's really a Barbie doll,
pull it out if you are not afraid.
I am not scared.
I am pulling.
Barbie doll has a spring.
Seems like there is a spring attached.
Let me try.
I am sure it's hair.
That's what I said earlier.
Do you smell something?
What is it?
I remember last week when I ate satay,
the taste of it still lingers in my mouth.
Forget about the satay,
it's the sauce that is unforgettable.
Shall we relive our fond memories there?
-Is the place still around?
-Sure.
-Of course...
Still there...
Still... there...
What is the Olympic record
for the 100-meter race?
It's 9.5 seconds.
Oh, yeah?
How fast can you run?
I think I will break that record
within four seconds. How about you?
Same, four seconds.
But there won't be witnesses around
to see us break the record.
And the two soldiers
were scared to death just like that.
I heard souls that die this way
cannot be reincarnated.
Their souls will never be appeased.
Wait, let me ask you,
do I look like your grandmother?
No.
Then why are you telling me
a grandmother's story?
Sir, I am a medium.
My god has told me
our training area is haunted.
If I went there,
I would have to perform the rituals
to capture the spirits here,
to catch the spirits there.
Sir, I will definitely
mess up the exercise.
Sir, it's not me requesting
to be exempt from my duties,
it's my god requesting it.
So it's not you who wants to be exempted,
-it's your God.
-Yes, sir.
In that case,
please ask your God
to come see me about this.
If your God is not free to see me,
please ask your God to page me.
Understand?
Ask my god to page you?
Shut up! Get out!
If you fail this field exercise,
I'll make sure you are back here
and I'll teach you a lesson.
-F...
-No vulgarities, sir.
Chicken pie!
-Is that vulgar?
-No, sir.
What?
Has your God asked you
to be excused as well?
No, sir.
I will not resort to unorthodox means,
to use spirits and God
to be excused from training.
I know this field exercise
is very important.
The safety of our nation depends on us.
Are you crazy? You idiot.
If you really believe that,
why are you here to ask for exemption?
Shut up.
You two get out!
Sir, I'm not here to ask for exemption.
It's because...
because...
my grandmother just passed away.
Grandma.
My dear grandma has passed away.
But you told me
she passed away last year.
The record is here.
Really?
That's my paternal grandmother.
This is my maternal grandmother.
My grandma...
Grandma!
Maternal grandmother?
But didn't she pass away
during in-camp two years ago?
Look at this record.
You took two days off.
That's your autograph, right?
It's all recorded.
Sir, I remember now.
That is my god-grandma,
and this is my maternal grandma.
How many grandmothers do you have?
How come they keep dying?
You can't say that
about my grandmother.
If her time is up
and she has no time to inform me
before she passes away,
then I can't help it.
What do you mean you can't help it?
Every year during in-camp training,
all your grandmothers
will pass away in time
so that you've got an excuse to take off.
You two, you better go and f--
No vulgarities, sir.
...fly out before I fail
your in-camp this year,
and make sure you return to join me
for one more exercise!
Sir! We are here for reservist training,
we are no longer recruits.
I advise you to close one eye sometimes,
so life will be easier for everyone.
You two get out. Close the door.
Sir, what are you doing?
I will show you who is the boss here.
Don't say I'm pulling rank.
Come!
Attention soldiers!
March off!
Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye.
Trying to get day off?
It'll be tough.
Good morning, sir.
You also want to be excused, is that it?
Sir, it's okay if you can't
grant me a day off,
but can you excuse me
from the field training?
I am sick.
I have internal injuries.
You know what I mean?
I have internal injuries. Inside the body.
-You should report to the Medical Officer.
-I can't.
This is my last in-camp training.
If I report sick,
I will have to stay in the sick bay,
then I will have to
come back again next year.
Sir, I can't afford to come back
for training next year.
This sickish chicken
is really good at feigning sickness.
Sir.
Good prop.
You're from SBC, right?
A props man, right?
He even coughed blood.
Really professional,
he even prepared props.
What about you?
His cough is so unconvincing.
If he manages to get an exemption,
I will...
Sir, I am not lying,
I am really suffering
from internal injuries.
I will not make things difficult for you.
Can you grant me light duty instead?
All of you know defense exercise
is very tough,
so you cook up all sorts of excuses.
Hello, you think
I just joined army yesterday, is it?
Being skinny and frail
will get you nowhere.
I can still detect your lies.
Wake up, soldier!
You want to idle, I'll make sure
you come back again next year!
Is that clear?
Darn!
This officer is really very XL.
XL? Extra-large?
It's a vulgarity in English.
I bet you do not know what it means.
X-I-A L-A-N.
You liar!
This is a Hokkien vulgarity.
Of course I know what it means.
The sickish chicken is here.
Come here.
I tell you, cut the acting.
The officer is not here.
We all know you work
in the props department.
-Stop acting.
-I am really sick.
If not for your interruption just now,
we would have gotten our leave approved.
It's all your fault.
Stop!
Good afternoon, Encik.
Bloody hell, you again!
Last year when I caught you,
you promised me
that you won't color your hair.
This year I caught you,
still the same color.
It's not the same.
Last year, yellow color.
This year, gold color.
How dare you talk back to me!
You don't respect me, huh?
Please don't take it that way.
This is our last in-camp.
We are reservists, not recruits.
So what?
I want this color to be black.
Just like this?
Yeah.
Please cut me some slack.
Okay, I'll give you two options.
One, become like this.
Trying to be smart
Shut up.
What are you doing?
I'm helping you polish up.
Lower, please.
What are you doing?
Why are you spitting on my head?
What is this?
We are even.
I caught you both!
What can two men be doing at the stairway?
Chinese pretending to be a Caucasian
But he can't even speak English
Happy birthday to you
Isn't this English?
This is my head,
it does not belong to the Army.
Why are they still so strict
for our last training?
Irritating officer.
I wish you'd get killed by a car!
Which officer is that?
The bald Encik Muthu!
You really saw him?
Of course. What's wrong?
He was killed in a car crash last year.
You are spouting rubbish!
Really, he died last year
in a terrible accident.
Didn't you read the newspapers?
He even lost his head in the crash.
It's a very serious case.
You guys are really evil.
You can't joke about this, it's unethical.
Time to draw weapons.
You better go pray for protection.
Go pray.
Platoon. Fall in.
Platoon. Stand at ease.
Okay, gentlemen, this defense exercise
is our last exercise.
After this, no more in-camp training.
All of us will go ORD.
Anyway, I will read out the details
for tonight's exercise.
Detail one.
Corporal Tan,
Corporal Lim.
Detail two.
Corporal Goh...
Look, Encik!
Where?
Not there anymore.
Don't frighten me, I have no guts.
...Lance Corporal Soh.
Detail Three.
Corporal Koh, Private Teo.
Look!
Encik!
Who says I'm dead?
Who says I died in an accident?
We have been sabotaged by them.
You are afraid of ghosts?
You too?
You look like a ghost yourself,
and you are scared?
Don't you dare make fun of me.
I'll tell your wife
you're fooling around with two women!
Quiet!
-Is this a holiday camp?
-No, sir.
-Is this a marketplace?
What's going on?
Sir, every time, they say I die.
Every time, they say I die.
I'm superstitious.
Encik, I know you are not dead,
but if we don't move out now,
we will be late,
and then we will be dead.
Yes, sir.
And?
Everybody on standby, move out!
A corporal has two black stripes
A sergeant has three black stripes
Three black stripes plus a crest
We call them Company Sergeant Major
Please fall sick, CSM!
Please be killed in an accident...
Quiet!
You think you are singing karaoke?
You think there's no government?
Bloody hell!
My grandmother can move faster than you!
Move, move! Come on!
Very good!
They are fighting the battle.
Both of you are smoking and hiding here.
Move, bloody hell!
Move!
This is such a big training area.
So tiring.
Wonder where our platoon mates are now.
-How did you get the egg?
-I brought it myself.
You can have some in exchange
for your luncheon meat.
What is this?
How come there's three men,
but only one shell scrape?
Encik, this one's mine.
Encik, we are sharing it.
-How?
-I'll show you.
Demonstration Alpha!
It's possible to share.
Wake up!
Relax, please!
Demonstration Bravo!
Fire!
Position change!
Change!
Change your head up, bloody hell!
I don't know how you pass your BMT!
What's that smell?
No, not this one.
What's that?
Can you go and get it for me?
Yes, Encik.
Encik.
Encik, this is my Chinese medicine.
What kind of medicine is this?
Encik, I'm sick.
Inside one.
How can you cook
Chinese medicine in the field?
Are you crazy?
If you are sick,
then you should report yourself.
Not that I don't like
your Chinese medicine,
not that I wanted to scold you...
During wartime, if you cook in the jungle,
enemy's aircraft fly past,
if they see the fire,
they will bombard the whole area
and all of us will die. Die!
Understand?
You and I will also die!
-Do you understand?
-Yes, Encik.
Let me give you another example!
During wartime,
if you cook in the jungle,
enemy's aircraft fly above,
if they see the fire, same thing,
they will bombard the whole area!
You will die! I will die!
Everybody will die!
-Understand?
-Yes, Encik.
Let me give you another example!
If you cook in the jungle,
enemy's aircraft fly above,
if they see the fire,
they will bombard the whole area!
You will die! I will die!
Everybody will die!
Is that clear?
Yes, Encik.
I don't think you understand!
Let me give you one final example!
For example,
if I cook in the jungle...
...the enemy aircraft fly above...
...see the fire...
...and bombard the whole area.
-You will die.
-I will die.
Everybody will die.
Very good!
Finally you understood what I said!
So, no more cooking in the jungle!
Do a proper job for the fire trench later,
understand?
Yes, Encik.
It's all your fault, you sickish chicken!
Why must you brew Chinese medicine?
I'm having tummy ache
and need to defecate.
Yeah.
Me too.
Sickish chicken,
we have been gone so long,
that's all you have managed to dig?
Don't try to pretend!
You better dig faster!
Or I will beat you
till you shrink by three inches!
You want a beating?
This is the best durian.
Where did you find it?
Dropped from the tree.
Encik is here.
Carry the durian.
How come three of you only dig like that?
Encik, hair!
I have no hair.
There's hair at the bottom of the trench.
There are ghosts here.
So what?
My god tells me
someone has died here.
Encik, better tell C.O.
Exercise, cut!
Cut? I will cut your head!
I'm in the Army for 35 years.
If you happen to see the ghost again,
tell the ghost to come and report to me.
I will throw him into the Guard Room.
Okay?
Stupid Encik!
Hope you will really meet with a ghost!
My God, please let Encik
meet with a ghost,
or please let a ghost meet with Encik.
Thank you, God.
Lord Ganesha,
brothers and sisters,
I have not committed anything wrong.
Now it seems like I am the one at fault.
It's okay if you don't
show me any respect,
but please show him some respect.
The ruler of kings.
What's that?
Devil!
Stupid Encik!
Stupid bald man!
Why did he run so fast?
He must have seen a ghost.
Let's hurry back
before our ploy is exposed.
I swear,
I saw the ghost here, sir.
Encik, we are soldiers,
please stop this nonsense.
Why don't you believe what I say?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Please change the channel!
I saw the ghost with my own two eyes.
-You sure you saw the ghost?
-Yes.
-You confirm you saw the ghost?
-Confirm.
Then next time you see the ghost,
you ask the ghost to report to me.
Okay.
I will charge the ghost,
I will throw the ghost
into the Guard Room.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Quick. Keep it quick...
Before the officer finds out.
You have no guts to come with us
to scare Encik!
Really a chicken!
What happened to your face?
I'm really ill.
Still putting on an act in front of us?
Are you after the best actor award?
Officer is here.
Believe me! Trust me!
Hello, just now, all of you
saw the ghost with long hair
flying here and flying there?
Don't be like that.
I really saw the ghost.
I saw it, so scary.
This place is haunted.
There's no ghost in this world.
Ghosts only exist in here.
If you think there's a ghost,
there will be.
If you think there's no ghost,
there won't be any. Understand?
Yes, sir.
Sickish chicken!
Sir, see, he is down.
Just see for yourself,
I told you this place is really haunted.
I think it would be better
to terminate the exercise.
Shut up!
Don't teach me what to do!
-Encik.
-Yes, sir.
-Call the medics.
-The medic has reported sick.
-What?
-The medic is also human being.
Sir, I will bring him
to the medical center.
-Go!
-Yes, sir.
Don't worry.
I will get him
to the medical center safely.
Crazy!
I'll ask both of you again.
-You really saw the long-haired ghost?
-Yes, sir.
That ghost is really terrifying.
-So that ghost is for real?
-For real.
So your rites
to get rid of ghosts are fake?
It's for real, too.
For real? The ghost appeared.
Where's your God?
Sir, I know the answer.
-His god is on medical leave.
-Stop talking nonsense!
Your god is just like you.
Always faking your way through.
-No, sir.
-You two lazy Privates!
From National Service
till Reservist Training,
you two have been faking it all this time!
How long do you want to
continue like this?
I know you want to be excused
from the exercise.
You will do anything.
Let me tell you this,
I am not scared of anything.
If I catch you one more time,
I will make sure
you fail this year's training,
and come back next year.
Don't challenge me!
You are a pig!
You are a banana!
You are an ice-cream!
What kind of God do you have?
Nothing good comes along.
But the bad ones, you have it all.
You have it all...
Shut up and start digging.
Are you okay? Can you answer me?
Ah Tan!
Encik.
Can you stop talking?
Let me rest for a while.
Then can you answer my questions?
If not, I will assume you are dead,
Ah Tan.
My God! Don't die in my car!
Ah Tan?
Ah Tan, are you okay?
I can't control it anymore.
How dare that stupid officer
say I'm a fake medium?
-But you are a fake.
-Now you are after me, too?
-What do you plan to do?
-Look at how frightened Encik was.
Now it's time to scare the officer.
I will put on my nails,
wear my wig,
apply some fake blood...
And we will put on
the white contact lenses.
Let's give him a really good scare
and that will send him crawling.
Then the exercise
will definitely be terminated.
I will bet my money on this.
There's something there.
"If I had known earlier."
He is one of us.
What did you say just now?
Secret code.
I almost forgot.
He is one of us.
Who is it?
Hey. Who is it?
Stop the act.
Who is it?
Don't frighten me.
Stop the act.
Is that Tan?
Sickish chicken?
I am a medium, so I'm not afraid.
Sickish chicken.
I thought you went to the medical center.
Why did you come back?
And with make-up, too?
You don't have the guts to scare Encik,
but now you are pretending
to be a ghost with special white lenses!
You deserve a beating!
Don't think we are afraid of you!
We have what it takes, too.
Show it to him.
These are old tricks in movies.
I know the tricks too. See?
I know how to do it, too.
Go and give the officer a scare now.
-Make sure it's a real scare.
-Make sure he collapses from fright.
Make sure he terminates the exercise,
or I will make sure you get a beating.
When you are doing it,
don't get too worked up
or the make-up might peel off.
And your identity will be exposed.
Sir, die!
You said I'm dead?
Bloody hell, talk properly!
Tan is dead!
-Tan is dead?
-Yes, sir.
I was driving him to the medical center,
the Land Rover crashed,
that's how Ah Tan is dead!
-Are you sure Tan is dead?
-I'm very sure Tan died.
Are you sure Tan is dead?
I'm very sure Tan is dead because of me!
But Tan is behind you!
What are you trying to do?
Are you trying to scare me?
Ghost!
Darn!
Encik!
You are really upsetting me.
Other people said you died,
you are not happy.
But you keep saying other people are dead.
You said Tan is dead.
But he is not dead?
Tan is right here!
Encik!
Please don't make me treat you
like a private soldier?
Go check on the men!
Yes, sir.
-Then?
-Okay.
God, please save me!
The sickish chicken
is really good at his act.
Encik has fled with fear.
Those not in the know
may really think he's a ghost.
Why are you still here?
Do you still want an exemption?
Still want light duty?
Darn!
Don't frighten me!
From the first day
you said you were sick,
I asked you to go see the medical officer,
you rejected the idea.
Now that you have seen
the medical officer,
you are still not excused,
that proves that I was right.
Tan is dead already.
Now you come back here
and pretend you are sick?
Or pretend you are dead?
Encik.
We just spoke to
the sickish chicken a while ago.
We met with an accident earlier on
and he died.
If you don't believe me, look.
Tan is dead.
He's dead.
If you don't believe me,
go see for yourself.
Tan is dead.
You are a faker, always faking.
You think I'm stupid?
You want a day off.
Hatch a plan.
Come up with a story at least
show me some sincerity.
Is that some trick?
That's a good move, smooth and fast.
And you are here already.
Do you think I don't know this?
Do you think I'm a rookie?
When I was writing,
this is what you did, right?
Like this?
I can do it, too.
Michael Jackson was my neighbor.
You fake!
If you had given me sick leave,
or given me light duty,
then I would not have died.
That's quite creative!
Normally,
when the men come to ask for leave,
they will say their grandparents
or someone has died.
You said you died.
Just put on some powder and expect me
to believe you're dead?
But you don't look dead.
This is very good, very fast.
You stuck so much
broken glass on your face.
Within seconds!
Let's run!
We are doomed!
Sickish chicken is back for revenge!
It's all your fault,
you have been bullying him!
Have you ever been kind to him?
You are the bigger bully!
We are doomed! This time we are doomed!
Encik, it's all your fault!
If only you didn't crash the vehicle!
This is where the vehicle crashed.
Yes, the vehicle has really crashed.
Tan died here.
There are trees everywhere.
I can see Tan's body.
Tan is dead...
Sickish chicken, you are dead!
Look!
-Why is there another body?
-Who could it be?
Encik!
This time I'm dead for real!
I'm really dead.
I'm dead...
My leave has been approved.
ONLY GHOSTS WILL MARRY YOU
DIRECTOR, LI GUOHUANG
Keep your mouth smaller.
Just stick your tongue out.
You bit me!
Do you know how to kiss?
Darn!
How dare you fool around behind my back?
How dare you fool around with my woman?
I am your ex-girlfriend.
To think I treated you so well!
You should thank the gods for it!
You were good to me?
Do you own a house?
No.
He does.
Do you own a car?
No.
He does. And you expect me
to spend my life with you?
Cut the crap about how I am the moon
and you are my sunshine,
and stop saying you are my bra
and I am your brief,
and you can't walk properly without me!
What era are we living in?
Who says these things anymore?
You are nothing compared to my darling!
You want to compare?
I am shorter!
I am uglier!
I am older!
My darling has something that is longer.
It is not the length.
It is not the size.
The important is,
he can do how many times?
Your English is atrocious
and you have a filthy mind!
Let me ask you,
how will you say I love you?
I love you.
Not the least bit sincere.
How will you say it?
I...
love...
Some more.
Love...
Love... you.
That felt good.
Hear that?
My darling can "love" me
much "longer" than you.
Let's go!
Let's go to somewhere else to kiss!
I have not had my fill, I need more!
Don't go!
You said you would marry me.
Let go of me!
I am not marrying you.
Only a ghost will marry you.
Let's go, darling. Let's go
to Mount Faber to continue our kiss.
Just broke up?
Hey.
Who are you?
It is not important who I am.
There are still many good girls out there.
Let that fat lump of lard go.
I have been dumped by
more than 20 girlfriends.
So I lowered my expectations,
and found myself a fat and ugly girl.
Yet she still left me.
I am useless.
It is not a problem.
If you are rich,
women will come to you.
But I have no money!
Don't tell me I have to rob and steal?
I am over 50 years old,
I don't have the energy anymore.
Don't tell me I have to borrow
more from loan sharks?
If I have a way for you to strike it rich
without having to break the law,
do you dare to try?
If I can strike the lottery,
I'll try anything!
Why did you bring me here?
This place has
the best fengshui in Singapore.
The descendants
of those whose urns are placed here
will always enjoy good fortune and luck.
What has it got to do with me?
Follow me.
These people
had good fortune and luck
that was not totally used up
before they passed away.
So I have brought you here
to "borrow"
some good fortune and luck from them.
To "borrow"
good fortune and luck from the deceased?
Don't be afraid.
I have brought many people here,
and they have all struck it rich.
However, you must abide by the rules.
If you have gotten what you asked for,
you must return what you have promised.
Understand?
Relax.
I will definitely do that
if I win the lottery.
Tell them what you want.
I, Ong Kim Hui--
Are you trying to wake up the dead?
Keep your voice down.
I, Ong Kim Hui, am penniless,
so all my girlfriends
left me for other men,
even with a fat and ugly one,
and I have borrowed money
from the loan sharks.
Payment is due in two days.
May all good brothers
from the netherworld bless me,
so I can win the lottery.
If I do,
I will return to thank all of you
with car-loads of paper ingots.
Thank you very much.
Prosperity!
You said the people you brought here
have all become rich?
Of course.
Did they get the top prizes?
Or any numbers they bet on
will hit the jackpot?
Or just consolation prizes?
The last one struck second prize,
followed by first prize the next day.
Really?
Of course,
I will be a ghost if I lie to you.
What's that red thing on the floor?
Red packet.
-Don't pick it up, don't pick it up.
-Already did.
-Don't open it, don't open it.
-Too late.
You are hopeless,
how can you just open it like that?
Don't put it on.
It's on.
How dare you pick up,
open and wear anything from here?
You are really mad!
You have the guts to come here
to "borrow" fortune and luck,
but you are frightened by a red packet?
Since I was young,
I have treaded on numerous paths,
but I have never once
found a red packet.
It's fate. So smooth.
-What did you just say?
-Smooth as silk.
-The line before that.
-It's fate.
Beg your pardon?
Fate...
Go eat shit if you don't understand!
You are really hopeless.
There are two sets
of numbers in here. Look!
0-3-2-9.
1-2-2-8. You betting?
Save it for yourself.
I wouldn't dare to bet on
anything found here.
Not betting?
If these numbers emerge
as top prize, don't regret it.
Still not interested?
I am going ahead.
What a stroke of luck!
Are you stupid?
Your hands are clumsy like your legs,
your legs are as clumsy as pig trotters.
It's better to engage
a pig than employ you!
If you break my bowls,
I will deduct your pay!
Pig!
-Be careful!
-It's you!
You came in time to save me
or my pay will go down the drain today.
If you need help, I will always be here.
Where shall I put these?
-To the wash area.
-I'll help you, allow me.
Don't you have to work?
I wanted to be a teacher,
but they didn't allow me
to keep my long hair, so I quit.
I wanted to be a principal,
but I prefer washing dishes.
You are funny.
1-2-2-8.
Isn't 1-2-2-8 the number you bet on?
You are right! What a waste.
I just bet $10 big and $10 small!
I would have placed
more bets if I had known!
So long as you have won,
it's a good thing already.
0-3-2-9.
Isn't that
the number in the red packet?
-You are absolutely right!
-You are so lucky!
I bet $30 big and $30 small
on this number!
Did you place any bets?
No, the luck is yours.
If I had placed any bets,
you might not win.
I told you to bet on the numbers!
I told you these might be winning numbers!
You just did not listen to me!
Since I was young,
I have never won any top prize!
Top prize!
How dare you play with my water?
Water charges
are getting higher and higher!
If you dare waste my water,
I will deduct your pay!
Are you all right?
Can you confirm that
1-2-2-8 is the second prize number?
Yes.
And 0-3-2-9 is the top prize number?
Yes, confirmed.
-Boss.
-What?
You are a pig! Pig!
-Are you crazy?
-You are a pig!
Your father is a boar.
Your mother is a sow.
You are the pig!
LOTTERY PRIZE NUMBER - TOP PRIZE : 0329
SECOND PRIZE : 1228 - THIRD PRIZE : 9648
Here's $50,000 to repay
the $30,000 debt!
You blood sucker!
This is your IOU.
Scissors, paper, stone!
You lost!
Here's $100 for you.
I want it too.
Once more.
Scissors, paper, stone!
Backside up for beating
for those who lose!
These are for you.
You all lose.
Come.
Scissors, paper, stone!
She is pretty!
Here's $200 for you!
All yours!
What do you want?
What... What do you want?
You know what?
You broke my heart when you left me.
The saddest part is
you said he beat me
in length, in everything.
You are right.
I like my dearie
because he beats you
in terms of length, in everything.
Long...
Being long is good. Being long is heaven.
"Long is good"?
"Long is heaven"?
Hey! Open it!
I'll give you a cage now
to send you to heaven!
Push her in!
Hands off! Release me!
Hands off!
Let me out!
You like long things?
I'll give you something very long now.
Look at her, so pitiful.
Let me out!
Relax, we were once lovers.
Why would I harm you?
So long as your dearie
can count to three,
I will let you out.
It's extremely easy
to count to three, right?
Let me out!
Start now!
Quickly, open it!
One...
Since my youth,
I have never seen
a snake with broken teeth!
One...
Shout two!
You know it is hungry?
Let me tell you.
This snake has not eaten for a month!
Your dearie has my full respect.
I have given him
such a short and easy task,
he can drag it to such great length!
One...
Can you count to two faster,
you're still at...
One...
Release her when he can count to three!
Do you know why a cobra
does not put on spectacles?
Because it wears contact lenses instead!
I will buy you drinks, let's go!
One...
Count to two!
Five, five, three.
Total 13 points on big!
-Here's your winnings, $2000.
-I won!
Money!
$10,000 in just half an hour!
Let's go. I'll buy you a meal!
You have successfully
"borrowed" good fortune and luck.
Besides winning the lottery,
you have won in everything you bet on.
Those who have "borrowed"
the good fortune,
they will win till they drop
on the gambling table.
Do a few more games.
You might just triple your winnings.
You are right.
You stay here and watch me win, okay?
One, three, six.
Ten points on small.
Four, five, six.
15 points on big.
One, two, three,
six points on small.
Three, four, five,
twelve points on big.
Triple six!
Banker wins!
He has left on seeing me lose.
Hands off the table.
Three, four, five,
12 points on big.
Should have quit when I was winning,
now I have lost every penny!
-Don't frighten me!
-What is it?
Where were you yesterday?
You left me alone
to go to the parking lot.
It was very dark there.
I'll tell you what happened,
a few thousands urns surrounded me.
They came from the front,
from the back, from the left,
from the right,
in the end, one exploded in front of me!
No one has ever chased me before,
and now I am being chased by urns!
When we "borrowed"
the good fortune and luck,
you promised that if you won the lottery,
you will burn car-loads
of paper ingots for them.
Did you forget about it?
You are right, I forgot.
I was so engrossed in winning,
why would I remember?
You are wrong to say this.
If you have asked
for blessings from the gods,
and broke your promise to thank them,
the gods will just ignore
your request for blessings in future.
The good brothers from the netherworld,
don't mess with them!
They will not let you off lightly.
Ever listened to
Taiwanese singer Tiger Huang's song?
What song?
It's not so simple!
They will come after you.
Or else you pass me some money,
I will help you buy and burn
the paper ingots for them now,
to settle this.
-Don't tell me you have spent it all?
-Not really.
I had $300,000 and I am left with...
-$30.
-$30? What did you spend it on?
You told me to go gamble.
I did tell you to have a game,
but not to bet in the thousands.
Just a few dollars would do.
You told me to visit the KTV lounge
and massage parlor and to get some girls.
I meant the KTV lounge for you to sing,
not to get girls.
And I mean just normal massage,
not to do a full package
of manicure and pedicure.
You even had your eyebrows trimmed!
You had no control over your tips,
and now you are putting the blame on me?
What can I do now?
I will not leave you in the lurch.
That's your promise.
Where are you going?
Do you remember
when we were at the columbarium,
there was this red packet on the floor,
I was against you taking it
but you refused to listen to me.
-Do you remember?
-What's your point?
The red packet belongs
to a girl named Xiao Juan.
She is very pitiful.
She died in her early 20s.
-She was still single then.
-How do you know?
Her ashes are placed at the columbarium.
It was her who
"loaned" you her good fortune
for you to strike the top two prizes.
You won't be so lucky without her.
I see.
Can I burn the paper ingots
for her?
Do you think that will settle the problem?
Who wants your joss paper money?
Not after the ingots?
What is she after then?
You haven't told me what she wants.
What does she want?
I have already told you
she died young.
She is very lonesome down there.
She wants to find a husband.
She needs a man to marry?
She is a ghost.
Who wants to marry a female ghost?
-It's not so simple.
-Of course it's not so simple.
That's why she searched
for such a long time.
But all's well, she found him.
Really? Who is it? Where is he?
He's right in front of us.
You?
You are sacrificing yourself for me?
I am really touched!
She likes you!
Me?
You must be joking.
Right?
If you marry her,
she will ensure you strike it rich,
do you dare?
Why would I have the good fortune?
By marrying her,
I will strike in everything,
I am okay with it.
You said it! You said okay!
Come!
This is where Xiao Juan lives.
Her family is waiting for you now.
Are you sure you want to go in?
Are you sure if I go in,
I will strike it rich?
-Confirmed?
-Confirmed.
Come in.
Are they Peranakans?
No, they adore the Peranakan culture.
So they have designed their house as such.
-No one is home?
-Hello.
-They are Xiao Juan's parents.
-Uncle, Aunty.
-Please have a seat.
-Sit down.
So this is Hui?
Yes.
Xiao Juan is our youngest daughter.
We have always been worried
about her marriage.
However, she was very insistent
on looking for her own partner.
Unfortunately, she passed away
without finding the right one.
She was only 22 when she died.
-It's a pity to die at the age of 22!
-Don't spout nonsense!
Who are they?
I am her eldest sister.
I am her second eldest sister.
Her sisters are pretty.
They are prettier than my ex-girlfriend.
Anyway, Xiao Juan has passed away,
I'll just choose one amongst them.
Don't joke on this!
He is the husband to my eldest daughter.
He is the husband to my second daughter.
What a waste!
Where is Xiao Juan?
I would like to see her photograph.
Photograph?
He says he has not met you?
Him?
You are saying...
Hai is Xiao Juan?
He is Xiao Juan?
You must be joking!
Hai, they say you are...
Where is Hai?
Hui.
When can we meet your family
to discuss your marriage with Xiao Juan?
Wait.
Are you saying I am marrying Hai?
He is not Hai.
She is Xiao Juan.
I am not homosexual.
How can I marry a man?
Who says she is a man?
She is a lovable lady.
Dear.
You are not Xiao Juan.
You are Hai.
You are a cross-dresser
with make-up and a wig!
Don't play any pranks on me!
I am not joking.
Stop calling me a cross-dresser.
Are you satisfied?
You have seen what you should.
You have also seen what you shouldn't.
What more do you want?
-It is awkward.
-You are pushing your luck.
We are fated to be bonded in marriage.
Why don't we do this?
I will marry one of your other daughters.
I can be the second husband.
At least she is prettier.
I know you detest my looks,
but you must know this.
In our love,
I have never forced you into anything.
When we went to the columbarium
and saw the red packet,
I advised you against
taking it, you told me...
Picked it up.
I told you not to open it,
you said...
Opened it.
I warned you against wearing it,
you said...
It's already on.
Moreover, you repeatedly said...
Fate.
When you told me to eat shit...
Go eat some shit!
Do you know how glad I was?
You said you were fated
to wear the bangle.
It means you are fated to be with me.
I have always believed in fate.
When I realized I'd fallen for you,
I "borrowed" luck for you
to win the lottery.
Do you really think it was your
lucky stars at work to win the lottery?
I am deeply in love with you now,
and you are going to abandon me?
How would I know you are so ugly?
The girlfriends you dated
were getting uglier with time,
and getting heavier in weight,
I am good enough for your standards.
If I had higher expectations,
I would have looked for
Takeshi Kaneshiro or Tom Cruise.
You won't stand a chance!
Treasure what you have now!
You are not human, you are a ghost.
Worse thing is you don't even look human
or even like a ghost!
You are the ugliest ghost!
Enough!
What is wrong with being a ghost?
We used to be humans, too.
When humans pass away,
they become ghosts.
If you are going to abandon Xiao Juan,
it will be an insult to her mother,
I will turn you into a ghost!
He does not want me!
No one wants me!
He does not want me.
The happiest moment for a woman is
when she puts on the wedding gown.
Only when she has put on the gown,
does she truly feel like a woman.
Why won't you help me?
What is ugliness?
What is terrifying?
This is ugly.
This is terrifying.
If you are not marrying me,
it is the same as banishing me to hell!
Only you can save me from hell!
Or I will be trapped here forever!
Look at my hair!
Its growing longer and longer.
Listen up!
If Xiao Juan is trapped here...
I will bring your family along
to roast together with us in underworld!
How do I get in?
With your heart.
Come in.
Come here.
I know you love me.
The fire has stopped burning.
Hell is transforming to heaven.
Are you marrying me?
Is it really so painful to marry me?
You are a ghost!
Ungrateful man!
Go to the underworld!
There are a lot of men out there!
Why me?
Let me out!
Fine!
I will marry you!
You let me out!
I'm really down on my luck.
I am going to marry
a cross-dressing ghost.
Hui, you are home.
Have you eaten?
Mother. Things are bad.
What happened?
I am going to get married soon.
You?
Only a ghost will marry you.
Right.
I am marrying a ghost.
Is it Caucasian, Chinese or Japanese?
Please don't talk like that.
Don't spout nonsense!
We did not install air conditioning,
why do I feel cold?
Aunty, I am Chen Xiao Juan.
Call me Juan.
I truly like Hui.
I hope you can give us your blessings
in the marriage.
Who the heck is that?
Is it a female ghost
or a cross-dressing ghost?
-Why is her voice so hoarse?
-Enough.
Your son has nothing to his name.
Still single at his age,
and he is going to die soon.
We have no complaints about him.
Sorry, sorry.
If I marry her,
you will not hurt my mother and me, right?
Fool.
If you marry me,
I will be your wife.
Why would I harm you and your mother?
Hui is my only son.
If they are married,
then I won't have any grandchildren.
Crazy!
We are reasonable.
If Hui can find a suitable partner,
we will agree to his marriage.
Really?
However, Xiao Juan
must be his first wife in status.
Mother-in-law,
we will be family once they are married.
Don't worry.
You will have our blessings
to strike in everything you bet on.
Bet on any numbers,
and they will emerge as winning numbers.
Really?
Shall we just agree to it?
Dear.
Crazy!
FAMILY PAPER INGOTS STORE
Boss.
How are you? Can I be of help?
I am getting married.
To a ghost?
Relax, you have come to the right place.
We have everything here.
Take your pick.
Okay.
Dear.
I will check out the bungalows.
Okay, this way please.
I want this bungalow.
It's freehold. High ceiling.
Three storeys high.
With a car and a bicycle as free gifts.
Plus two servants.
And the male servant is handsome.
Just one condition.
Change the unit number to 0329.
Tell her.
-Tell her!
-Okay.
Miss, I want this bungalow.
-Okay, no problem.
-I need to change the unit number.
Sure, no problem.
What's your new number?
-0329.
-Okay.
Okay.
Look at that bed.
The spring mattress is really good.
-I want this bed.
-Really?
You can't sit if you are not a ghost.
-You are right.
-Tell her I want this bed.
-I want this bed.
-Okay, no problem.
I need a mobile phone, too, tell her.
-No.
-Yes, convenient for me to "SM."
I mean, send text messages
to you, tell her.
Miss, do you sell mobile phones here?
Mobile phones are outdated.
I have something else for you.
-I want it.
-No.
-Okay.
This way, please.
This is our latest product.
-You have iPads here as well?
-It's called iPad here,
-but it's called iOne down there.
-iOne.
Will the system hang?
Don't worry, our system will not hang.
We use "My-ghost-soft" here.
The system will never hang.
You can use one version
for ten thousand years.
Ten thousand years.
You are right, there's no need
for frequent upgrades, right?
-I want three.
-No.
-Three.
Three.
We will give you a plane
when you buy three sets.
A plane as a gift? Where do I fly to?
The 18 levels in the underworld,
it's quite far.
Hence, I am giving you two pilots.
Caucasian.
What is that?
Bling-bling!
Diamonds!
I want a diamond, too.
I have an electric drill at home,
with a big stone.
Why do you sell diamonds here?
These diamonds are not ordinary ones.
We created the diamonds
from human ashes or hair.
You can pass it on as a family heirloom
or as a memento for your loved ones.
New model!
I am going bankrupt.
E200?
Ask if they have E500?
I want ten if they do.
Negative.
You did not even ask.
-Do you have E500?
-Yes.
E500.
Just like this?
You are so nice to me.
I feel like kissing you now.
Let's go home to kiss.
There are people around.
They can't see me, kiss me!
-No.
-Come on.
-Do it!
-No!
-Don't move!
Mouth in position!
-No!
-Do it!
More.
Can you do it willingly?
You are so cute.
HAPPILY MARRIED
MAKE A FORTUNE
Bow to Heaven and Earth.
Bow.
Bow to the parents.
Couple, bow to each other.
Bow.
To the bridal room.
Serving tea to the groom's mother.
Serving tea to the bride's parents.
Dear.
Time is precious tonight.
Let's not waste it.
I have to leave at 6:00 a.m.
Quick.
Come.
Shall we start?
You remind me of Hai.
I can't concentrate.
Okay, since this is our first night,
I can transform myself.
Who do you want me to transform to?
I like Japanese films.
Just say pornography.
What Japanese films? Who do you want?
Just name her.
And just for tonight.
How are you tonight? I am Chen Xiao Juan.
You can start now.
Can you change your voice, too?
Don't push it.
Crazy. Darn unlucky!
Don't drive if you don't know how to.
Why is there a crowd?
Dear.
Don't call me that.
You promised not to harm me.
If you marry me,
I will be your wife.
Why would I harm you and your mother?
You are extremely naive
to believe what a ghost said.
-You...
-Enough said.
The joss paper warehouse is having
a Great Singapore Sale.
-Let's go.
-What about my body?
-Leave it to the police.
-My face is stained with blood.
Don't worry.
Ang Chin Moh Casket
will help to beautify your face.
Let's go.
Come on!
IF YOU CHOOSE TO ASSOCIATE YOURSELF
WITH THE DEVIL,
BE PREPARED TO PAY A HEFTY PRICE.
So if you think there are ghosts,
there are ghosts. If you...
Sorry, if you think no ghosts,
then no ghosts, right? Sorry.
I understand.
A ghost might jump out
and cut off your ears. Understand?
You better watch...
When you're walking along
and there's someone behind...
I said there's electricity...
Should be no electricity
-F...
-No profanity, sir.
Chicken pie! That's vulgar.
"Is that vulgar?"
He even used a prop.
What about you? Focus!
I tell you...
I think I saw someone much better than me.
Our government asks us to speak Mandarin.
It's the right thing to do!
There's no need to find someone better.
I should really think about it.
I'll wear our national emblem.
We can learn Mandarin together!
Both of you go and clean the bloody store!
Before you check out.
Before you're both gone.
Encik, I think it's better
to tell the CO...
Tell the CO... Cancerous...
-Tell the CO... Cancer...
-Excellent!
Oh, my mama!
You're right! Lucky hand.
You stay here and watch me win, okay?
Cut! What is "lucky hand"?
-No one's home.
-Hello.
They're Xiao Juan's parents.
Tell them to adjust the watch...
The clock.
Coming... Coming...
You son of a bitch! How dare you
fool around with him behind my back?
You son of a bitch!
You whore! How dare you
fool around with man behind my back?
You son of a bitch! Fooling around
with him behind my back!
You son of a bitch! Fooling around with...
It's not the length. It's not the size.
I'm shorter!
I'm uglier! I'm older!
Cut the crap about how I'm the moon
and you're my sunshine.
Stop saying that you're my bra
and I'm your briefs
and that you can't get dressed without me!
How about that?
I genuinely like Brother Hui.
Brother Hui.
Ah Hui. Brother Hui.
You have iPads here as well?
-Yes.
-At home?
Here.
You said you have an iPad at home.
-Here.
-No. Do you want to go there...
-Negative.
-You did not even ask.
You did not even ask.
-Do you have E500?
-Yes.
You are the ugliest ghost!
Cut!
You're so stupid. Who is uglier?
Take a break.