Stay by my side…
and don't go anywhere.
Your mom said,
love isn't about doing
something for someone.
It's about putting your heart into it.
How are you involved with what happened
to Nut and his mother?
You're nosy because you're jealous
of Nut's mother, right?
Why would I be jealous?
Well, everybody loves her.
This includes Mr. Saen too.
Have you heard of the phrase
"Pity is the foundation of love"?
No. I've only heard of sympathy.
I'm off, Mom.
Tofu.
Want to see the series you were in?
Juea just finished editing the teaser.
Do you?
I shouldn't.
I just went out yesterday.
I was going to help your mom
with the chores.
Don't worry about me.
I'm healthy now.
I can take care of myself.
You should do what you want,
so you don't get bored.
Maybe another time.
I have a lot to do.
That's up to you. I'm off.
Bye.
Bye, Keunchai.
Song.
Oh, Tofu. What is it?
Song. Can you do me a favor?
Do you know
which close friend of Neung
has a name that begins with "T".
Is it Thanayut,
Title,
or Tatarn?
Neung's close friend
with a name beginning with a "T"…
I think he's the only one.
Tatarn.
That one. They have a picture together.
This one?
That's right.
Watch this. I just finished editing.
There.
AN OLD STORY RETOLD…
AFTER A LONG WHILE
There's only one moon.
How about I draw another moon?
If you draw another moon,
the first moon will lose its meaning.
Then one is enough.
TATARN: SOMETIMES RAIN FALLS DOWN,
BUT SOMETIMES IT POURS UP.
TATARN: I MIGHT BE FAR AWAY,
BUT I'M NEVER GONE.
TATARN: I DON'T WANT HIM TO BE SAD.
I WANT THE WORLD TO BE NICE TO HIM.
TATARN: SOME THINGS,
WE HUG TO FILL OUR ARMS.
TATARN: BUT SOME THINGS,
WE HUG TO FILL OUR HEARTS.
Tatarn's Facebook is public.
It seems like he wants
to send someone a message.
That someone
could be Nut.
But there's not
a single photo of Nut here.
There's also no information
about Tatarn's whereabouts, job,
nor how to contact him.
TATARN, OUR LIFE
That man seems familiar.
Is it someone who knows Nut?
He's not just someone he knows.
He's someone Nut loved.
Why would you look at his pictures?
Don't worry about it.
He's the past.
Now, you're the only one for Nut, okay?
Are you and Nut in love?
Yes.
You got it right.
We are in love.
Tofu makes me happy.
He's the reason I can tolerate this house.
What are you trying to do
by asking him behind my back?
Are you driving him away again?
Are you doing the same thing again?
Don't go anywhere,
or I'll go with you.
If you can't accept it,
then I won't stay here.
Where are you going?
You're my son.
Your son is gay!
If you dream of a happy family
like you find in books,
I can tell you now
that it will never come true
because I like men.
I can never marry a woman
and give you grandkids.
Calm down, Nut.
Are you hurt
to have me as a son?
It hurts me, too,
that you're my mom.
You can hate me all you want.
But I will never be who you want me to be.
Nut.
If you want me to stay,
I'll stay,
but I'll be myself.
I'll love him like this.
What are you doing?
Nut.
Let's talk.
You'll never understand
what I went through.
All you do is side with her.
I don't.
I just didn't want you to do that.
Nut.
Nut!
Song.
Here.
Why did you come all the way here?
I had a fight with Tofu.
I don't want to see him.
What did he do?
I'll change the question.
What did you do?
My mom knows I'm with Tofu.
What did she say?
I don't care
if she yells at me.
I won't break up with him like last time.
Are you saying
that you broke up with your ex
because of your mom?
What does Tofu have to do with it?
He doesn't understand me.
I kissed him in front of Mom to spite her,
and he just pushed me away.
I wouldn't just push you away.
I would dropkick you.
Why are you acting like a child?
Don't you ever consider his feelings?
What about your mom's?
Fine.
I know I was wrong,
but I wanted to hurt her
like she hurt me before.
All right.
Hey, come. Let's have lunch.
Here. These are all Nut's favorites.
It has been a while.
Let's eat.
He has a boyfriend now.
He has forgotten about his friends.
Stop talking about him.
If I can't talk about him,
then you can leave.
Go home. Get out.
Hey, you're always welcome here,
but I would be glad
if you were happier at home.
Who's here?
How did you know Nut was here?
Lovers should know each other well,
just like how I know you.
You brought Tofu all the way here,
you can anticipate war.
Our weekend seems jolly today.
You guys must be hungry.
Let's dig in.
-Come on.
-Okay.
Let's eat.
I remember that you like eggplant.
-Nut.
-Get that for me.
I want that piece.
-Nut.
-Give me some fried pork too.
Do you want anything else?
I'll get it all for you now.
I don't.
Just eat. Don't bother me.
How can I eat when you're mad?
Whose fault is it that I'm mad?
Hey.
Whoever's fault it is,
let's clear it up after we eat.
It would be a shame to ruin lunch.
I don't know what you fought about,
but there aren't many chances for us
to eat together like this.
So the time that we spend together
should be a happy time.
The dining table is a war-free zone.
-We should enjoy the food.
-Right.
-I'm sorry.
-Okay.
I'm sorry.
All right. That's that.
Let's eat,
so we can cheer up with desserts.
Do you think you own the place?
What?
You almost destroyed my home
by bringing Tofu here.
Just leave.
I won't.
-You won't?
-Right.
Your dad invited me to stay.
Nut. Talk it out nicely, okay?
Thank you for lunch, Gen.
Thank you, too, Song.
Right.
Thank you for your meddling.
I'm so darn touched.
Let me tell you about Gen.
-What are you doing, Nut?
-Don't worry.
Nut. What did you say?
You'll find out soon.
What did he say, Song?
What is this?
Can we turn it off?
Gosh, Nut.
Nut.
Ouch.
Tofu.
If something is bothering you,
you can tell me.
You might feel better.
I'm sorry
for what I did just now and at home.
I'm not mad.
I know you probably feel bad too.
Don't you?
I know I was wrong,
but Mom was wrong too.
It may be hard to imagine,
but Mom and I used to be close.
But as I grew up,
I found out
that we were never really close.
-Mom.
-Yes?
They say that Thailand
was never colonized.
What about the two times we lost to Burma?
Well…
we only count the Western Colonization
during the Rattanakosin period,
not during the Ayutthaya period,
since we weren't a country back then.
What are the pros and cons
of never being colonized?
What are we talking about?
I have something for you.
I'm hungry.
I'll cook you something.
Isn't this pretty?
Nut. That's a girl's dress.
You can't wear that.
Why not? Can't boys wear it?
I like this dress.
Pink is for girls.
What color is for boys, then?
Why can't it be pink?
Haven't I told you
not to let him play with these?
Sib.
-You shouldn't go so far--
-Shut it.
He's turning gay
because of your negligence.
-He's just a nice boy.
-Don't talk back to me.
Boys have to be strong.
What kind of mom are you?
Nut!
Honey!
Hey! Stop!
Do you see
he's wearing heels like a queen?
Do you want to be one?
Do you want to be gay?
Don't you want to be a man?
Answer me!
What are you looking at?
What did I do wrong?
Why can't boys play with paper dolls?
Why can't we like pink?
Why can't we wear heels?
They never explained it to me.
just that they're not for boys.
My parents ruined my self-esteem
and made me feel abnormal.
Nut is a normal boy like anyone else.
Can't you see how girly he is,
-that he's queer?
-That's not true.
That's not what he is.
Are you saying I'm making this up?
How did you let him turn out this way?
Instead of saying,
"Nut might not be so manly,
but nothing's wrong with him,"
she just said,
"Nut is a normal boy like anyone else,"
because she didn't want to admit
that she let me turn out this way.
What are you doing?
I just want to know what you wrote.
Is there something I can't see?
What's this poem? It doesn't even rhyme.
What I write is my business.
The only thing I could do at home
was write,
but they took that from me.
They told me to stop writing
and focus on my studies
because I should join the military.
Mom knew that I didn't like it.
I hated everything about the military.
I didn't want to be like Dad,
but Mom asked me to.
They forced me to move
to a school where someone
can watch me for Dad.
I thought my world had ended.
But you know what,
that place gave me a new world.
A world that's bigger than home.
A world that changed my life.
Hey.
Hey, are you okay?
Neung, we should take him
to the infirmary.
What's going on? My goodness, Peeranut.
You're in trouble on your first day.
You two, take him to the infirmary.
Quickly.
Be careful.
Hurry up.
My goodness.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
You're claiming them all.
Neung. Here's a snack.
Thank you.
Bye. Thank you.
I'm so tired today.
I waited for ages.
I barely played.
Hey, Neung.
You got snacks again?
-Man, I'm jealous.
-Right.
I can't eat them. Whose are they?
Throw them out.
I'll take them off your hands. I'm hungry.
Don't you want any? It's good.
Go ahead.
BASKETBALL TEAM ASSISTANT WANTED
New assistant?
Yes.
What's your name?
I'm Nut.
I'm Tarn.
Tatarn.
Tarn, come on.
Okay.
You can do it.
Hey, why aren't you in the girls' toilet?
You want to see our junk?
Does your dad know
you're a sissy?
Hi, sissy!
Think you can fight me?
Why don't you go
ask your beloved Neung for help?
Oh, sissy!
This is a toilet, not a kennel.
If you're not peeing, get out!
If you want to gang up,
meet me on the court.
I'll play all of you.
Hey, let's go.
Are you okay, Nut?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
What do you want to eat?
Up to you.
What about hotpot?
You were great.
Hey! Be careful!
Daydreaming again.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry. I wasn't looking.
Tarn, get ready.
Let's play, Tarn.
Go on, Mr. Hero.
Do you like this book too?
I'm just looking. I don't like it.
Just admit if you like it.
Why hide it?
I don't like it.
Take it if you do.
BE WITH YOU
What are you doing?
What were you doing?
I…
Wait.
Take this one too.
Okay.
Please move.
Just go.
-I'm going to the toilet.
-Hurry up, then.
Please let me go.
I'm begging you.
Are you that scared?
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
What are you looking at?
I tried to avoid him.
But you know what,
the more I hid, the more I saw him.
I was such a child back then.
I was afraid he would find out
that I liked Neung.
He was a real prankster.
If he found out,
everyone else would too.
I was afraid my parents would know.
-Tuck your shirt in.
-Yes.
Don't come to school looking so scruffy.
I was in a hurry.
You still have to dress properly.
Where's your belt?
I forgot it.
Buy a new one. We sell them in the shop.
-Okay.
-Go.
Hey.
You're dropping him off.
Hello.
Go to class.
Goodbye.
Look after him for me.
Yes. Don't worry.
He's a good boy.
How is he at school?
He doesn't misbehave
and fits in with friends.
Waiting for me?
-Let's go.
-We can guide him.
Just guide him little by little.
It's still possible.
I chose to stop going to the club,
but there was still a cause
for us to meet.
They were one person short,
so they asked me to help.
I don't know why,
but I didn't feel the same with Neung.
Catch it.
Pick up the ball.
Tarn!
Focus!
Come on.
There you go.
Go.
-Ouch.
-Tarn, are you all right?
What's going on?
My arm hurts.
Let's take a rest.
You two, give him first aid. Go on.
-Hey.
-What is it?
My leg hurts too.
Slowly.
Next person, get ready.
You should practice.
I'll ask Nut to take me to the toilet.
Take care of him.
Come on.
Hurry up. I have to pee.
Do you need help?
Do you mind?
Do you really not want to see my face?
Just hurry up.
Wait for me.
I don't know if I held it too long
or if there's someone here,
but I'm nervous.
Are you done?
Yes.
You haven't answered
if you were really that mad at me.
If you can stand on your own,
I'm leaving.
Nut.
I'm sorry
for making you upset.
I don't want any bad blood between us.
It's okay if you don't want to look at me,
but please
don't hate me.
I don't hate you.
But you don't like me.
You not liking me now
doesn't mean
you won't like me ever, right?
I didn't answer,
so he planned to make me confess to Neung
on Valentine's Day.
He was a crafty guy.
He knew I would get turned down
since Neung already had a girlfriend.
Didn't you go see Neung?
I did.
I gave him the socks you asked me to.
He asked me to thank you.
Why are you here?
Well…
I brought you a Valentine's Day gift.
Let's exchange.
BE WITH YOU
TO NUT FROM 'T'
Let's go for milk near the school.
I'll wait until you come.
I didn't know that a rough guy
could be sweet.
You didn't stand him up, did you?
I didn't, because I…
waited for him myself.
I didn't know why I went there.
I probably wanted to challenge my parents
or just
wondered what would happen.
I thought you weren't coming.
You would drag me here
if I didn't come.
You know it's not you that I like.
Why do you keep bothering me?
Once you like someone, it's hard to stop.
Hey.
You've never dated, right?
I'm going to college next year.
If this year we try dating
and it doesn't work out,
then that's that.
Sounds good?
No.
What? Why not?
I thought so hard about it.
BE WITH YOU
You know it's not you that I like.
You also know
that Neung will only see you
as his junior.
I know that.
It's good.
Nobody needs to know about this.
Nut.
It's not like our lives will end
if we choose this path.
There's nothing wrong with it.
Even if you don't agree to date me,
BE WITH YOU
I still want you to reconsider.
Why so?
Have you tried their dessert?
No.
My parents don't like it
because it's too sweet.
Then try it
and see for yourself,
not from what others said.
If I eat this, you'll take it
as a yes, won't you?
Just try it.
How is it? Good?
BE WITH YOU
IT'S SWEET, BUT I LIKE IT.
I didn't know
that a rough guy like you can be sweet.
Here you go.
Are you a masochist?
You keep listening even when it hurts you.
I won't tell you any more stories.
I'm really fine.
Do you want a mirror?
Your face doesn't look fine.
I just envy him a little,
I'm a bit jealous.
But when it comes to your stories,
I want to know everything.
You're just thinking of him,
but you aren't missing him.
Finally, I got to know
how Nut ended up with Tatarn.
Their love seemed fine,
but…
what happened
between Nut, Tatarn, and Nut's mom?
Why have Nut and his mom
had a problem for so long?
Right. What's your problem?
My dad asked what the problem was.
You've been watering for five minutes.
My vegetables are probably dead.
Gen cherishes that plot.
It will rot if you water it too much.
Gen will yell at you.
I don't cherish it.
My mistake.
You used to cherish it.
That plot was for his ex.
Dad! Don't.
Is that true?
Yes. Well…
my ex wouldn't eat vegetables,
so I tried to get him to eat those.
He would only eat those
if I planted them.
That kid liked cabbage,
so he paid special attention to those.
Dad! Again?
I guess they're useless now
since you broke up.
Can't I plant them for myself?
I like ivy gourd leaves, though.
Listen.
When you leave my house,
turn left and you'll find a market.
Buy as many as you like.
Come on, mister.
I want you to plant those for me.
Just like this.
Please.
-Just a few.
-Why should I?
Plant them yourself.
I have the seeds.
Really? Where?
Over there.
I got them for free.
Are my vegetables just a giveaway?
Are you going to plant them or not?
Of course, I am.
Hey.
Mr. Sitha, cool it.
Well, yes.
Yes. Okay.
Wait. What's that?
What's that?
Meow.
-Meow?
-Hey!
What? Don't.
I know why you like ivy gourd leaves.
Why so?
They're creepers.
Hey.
There. Take that.
Come here, Song.
Stop.
I'll wash it for you.
Come on. Stop pestering me.
I'm tired of yelling.
I'm not fooling around anymore.
Let me ask something serious.
Do you not like younger guys?
What are you saying?
Earlier, Nut told me…
Gen won't like you.
He doesn't like younger guys.
Is it because of your ex?
Earlier,
your father said you went out
with someone younger.
Did your ex-boyfriend traumatize you
from dating a younger man?
Not all younger men are the same.
Don't generalize us.
The difference in our age
was only a few years,
yet my ex and I broke up.
Our age gap is nine years.
What if you meet someone better
in the future?
What if you become famous?
Your life has a long way to go.
That time hasn't come yet.
Why would you worry?
Do you think I'll turn out like them?
Don't you have confidence in me
when I'm with you at all?
I…
I don't want to risk it.
Hey, Gen.
Drink some water.
Thank you.
It's a little tough.
Gen is a stubborn kid.
I'm very serious about him.
I don't know what else to do.
Kanya and I were the same.
When I pursued her,
she was hard to get like Gen.
When older women marry younger men,
they worry about a million things.
People would say
she's going out with her brother,
or that she's my mom.
What did you do, then?
I just kept going?
You just kept going?
What else could I do?
If you really like him,
then show him that.
Just do it.
It won't be a waste.
As Gen's father
who raised him with my own hands,
his life has always been a breeze.
He got to study what he wanted.
He has a good job.
Nobody minds who he is.
Kanya and I have always understood
and supported him,
so he wants some things to be difficult.
Love, for instance.
I have to try harder, do I?
Do your best, if you can.
If you want some help, tell me.
I'll understand if you want to give up.
My son is high maintenance.
Thank you.
Cheer up.
Have you two eaten?
I'm sorry for keeping it from you.
I didn't want to do that.
I was just afraid you wouldn't like it,
and that it would affect your health.
I didn't want it to bother you.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm working.
A change of scenery.
I'm writing a boys' love screenplay.
I get inspired with you around.
I'll try not to make loud noises,
so you can focus on work.
You want to know
what I'm writing about?
If you want to tell me, I'll listen.
I'm writing about a boy's love.
Despite being a high school love,
it's not as jolly as a fantasy world.
I won't write about
such an idealistic world.
In reality,
it's hard for men to be in love.
Family, friends,
or people next door don't accept it.
That's just reality.
Oh. It's time for Keunchai's dinner.
He's probably starving.
Then,
I won't bother you anymore.
Work hard.
Come on, Keunchai. Let's eat.
Come on.
Let's eat.
What are you trying to do?
Aren't you curious to see
what will happen if Mom sees us?
Let me help.
Tofu.
I want coffee.
Wait a second. I'm helping your mom.
I want it now.
You should make him coffee.
You're so slow.
Let me see it.
What are you doing?
I want your attention. Can't I do this?
You usually know how to make coffee.
Today, I forgot.
In case you're hungry.
Thank you,
but I'm not.
Tofu.
Feed me. My hands are busy.
Thanks.
SCENE 36. BOOKSTORE. KAWEE, TONNAM.
KAWEE IS LOOKING AT BOOKS ON THE SHELF.
KAWEE IS LOOKING
AT THE FRONT OF THE BOOKSTORE.
I'll take it off for you.
You can go.
Since you're so inspired, any progress?
Quite a lot.
Perfect timing.
Do a scene with me.
What scene?
You've only got that.
Just do what I say.
Stay still. I'll do the work.
Let's do a romantic scene.
Like this, Tofu.
What are you doing?
Come on.
Nut.
Nut!
Let's talk.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you do that?
You couldn't write a single scene anyway.
That's my problem.
It's not just your problem.
We live together.
Are you saying that if you're not happy,
no one else is allowed to be happy?
That's not right.
Tofu.
You saw it.
I went that far, but Mom still ignored me.
The more she ignores me,
the more invisible I feel.
Nut, it's not your fault
for being who you are,
but it's not hers either.
Your mom is just trying
to keep everyone in the household happy.
It's fake happiness.
She keeps fooling herself.
She has never really known me.
How can we love each other
when we barely know each other?
What do you want, then?
If she knows the real you, she'll be hurt.
When she's hurt, you're hurt.
It's a circle of pain. When will it end?
Why don't you try talking about it?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
I just happened to hear it
while passing by.
I'm really sorry.
What are you fighting about?
-I'm here.
-You're here.
What took you so long?
Gosh. Oh, take a seat.
Well…
Tofu.
You don't look so good.
Is there a problem at home?
Nut and his mom are fighting.
I don't know how to help.
It's a tough job.
Ever since I moved here,
Na and Nut are always arguing.
It's not that hard, Nhong.
Of course, there's something we can do.
Listen.
Na and Nut are mother and son.
Of course, they have some issues.
It's called a generation gap.
Generation gap?
Right.
Nut grew up in an open world
with freedom
and all sorts of information.
Whatever he does or asks, he needs facts.
On the other hand,
Na is framed within her society.
She's from my generation.
She needs to be meticulous
in everything she does.
That's her quality.
She was taught that way
since she was born.
They're from different generations.
They both have expectations.
Mother expects her son
to be a certain way.
The son expects his mother
The expectations
aren't met on either side,
so they hurt each other
without realizing it.
Wherever there's a gap,
you need to pay special attention.
It can be dangerous
if the gap is too wide.
How do we reduce the gap?
Hey.
The gap can be filled
with family ties.
If Nut and Na love each other,
they should talk it out
and maintain the ties.
It will be fine
as long as they communicate.
Because Mrs. Na and Nut won't communicate.
she does things
without asking what Nut wants,
as she thinks those are her duties
as a mother.
Nut also has demands from his mom.
He always acts sarcastically,
but he doesn't tell her what he wants.
The gap between mother and child
should be narrow,
but it keeps widening.
I don't want it to be like this.
Is there a way I can help them?
I'm sorry.
Okay.
It's not all your fault.
I don't know how hard it is to be you,
but it's not easy being your mom either.
You might have faced
many things in your life,
but your mom has too.
I want you to think about her feelings.
Thanks for reminding me.
I'll try to be a better person.
You're not that bad.
Try to be positive.
I think there are a lot more good things
in your life.
You're the good thing in my life.
It's not just me.
Think harder.
I told you.
I won't talk about him anymore.
It's okay.
I want to know everything about you.
I don't want you to act fine,
when you're actually not.
As long as you're not hurt
when you talk about it,
I'll be fine.
Continue.
After you agreed to go out with Tatarn,
how happy were you?
It wasn't just happiness.
The world at home
and the world when I was with him
were drastically different.
Nut.
Don't spend too much time on activities.
Your dad is worried about your grades.
And regarding that other matter,
you should behave.
I won't stand it if you disobey me.
Let's eat.
I already ate.
My parents act like I don't fit in
and that it's embarrassing.
Hey, Nut.
I wrote it.
How is it?
It's great.
-Really?
-Yes.
You could become a writer.
But Tarn
made me feel like
I had discovered another world.
He made me feel like
I wasn't the only odd one out anymore.
Having a rough guy like him around,
who dared to do things
that wouldn't hurt anyone,
got me to open my mind
and I started to feel free.
Wait.
Nut!
Happy birthday, Nut.
I didn't think I would get one this year.
I wouldn't forget your birthday.
I added jelly for you since you like it.
Thank you.
Try it.
Is it good?
Feed me.
Okay. You can have a big bite.
Is it too big?
Here you go.
Oh, wow.
Your lips are sweet
and soft like jelly.
What happened to you in the past
made you lose faith in love,
NEXT EPISODE
but I'm going to show you
how serious I am about you.
The reason you blow up at your mom…
is to resist the feeling of love.
But now that you've acknowledged
what happened,
you feel better, don't you?
You get irritable with your mom,
but you're not really angry.
You just…
hold a grudge.
You're such a know-it-all.
Mom.
-Mom!
-Mrs. Na.
Subtitle translation by:
Pattranun Bunyanund