I may be smiling but I'm not happy
I may be crying but I'm not weak
A, HOT GIRL LY COCO IS BACK!
Nobody understands women
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN I MISS YOU SO MUCH
Don't think
You'll ever have us figured out
Hello, everyone!
SHE IS SO BEAUTIFUL JUST LIKE HER VOICE!
LY,
WHY HAVEN'T YOU BEEN TO SCHOOL RECENTLY?
What are you doing, Ly?
Sorry, folks.
That's my roommate, her name is…
I'm Huyen. I'm Ly's manager.
If you want to get to Ly,
you'll have to go through me first.
Somebody is asking…
What if I want to introduce a boyfriend?
Of course,
I'd have to check him out first.
If he turns out to be a good catch…
I'll keep him for myself!
Oh no! I'm late for class.
Bye, everyone,
we'll livestream again tonight.
I'm going to class with you today.
Wow. Livestreaming and going to class?
So you're done
moping over your broken heart?
It's been two months already.
There's no use sitting around crying.
My dad would kill me
if he knew I skipped out on school.
So have you been able to reach Phuong?
Her phone is still off.
What are you doing?
Water's shut off.
You didn't pay the bill did you?
Here's the water bill.
Don't tell me you didn't
pay the electricity bill either.
Where's the electricity money?
Are you done admiring yourself?
It's so sad, I've been trying to
find a bad angle but there isn't one.
Hey Ly, have you heard?
How was Phuong the last time you saw her?
Damn, it was just a sex clip.
Why kill yourself over that?
SINGER LAM PHUONG DIED OF SUICIDE
AT AGE 25
Ly, where are you going?
The body of singer Lam Phuong
was found last night in her home.
Preliminary investigations
point to suicide,
just days after a sexually graphic video
of her was leaked on social media,
leading to a wave of boycott from fans.
The clip going viral
also shows three other men with Phuong
but none of them have been identified.
As the only heir
to Alpha Group corporation,
Lam Phuong did not follow
her father's footsteps,
but instead chose the music industry
and found her own success.
Her educational and family background,
as well as a private life free of scandal,
had vaulted her into being
the princess of the music industry,
which was why the leaked video
came as a shock to many.
Moreover, the discovery of a Kumanthong
doll at the scene of her death
has spread rumors of
voodoo and superstition.
Dad!
Why are you not at school?
I miss you.
Oh, please.
You should quit drinking.
Don't change the subject.
Be honest.
Some boy break your heart?
Good grief, no!
Are you pregnant?
What are you on about?
I'm just worried, that's all.
Study well and find a good job, don't
be like your good-for-nothing mother.
All that singing and fame nonsense
got to her head and ruined her life.
What's wrong with singing?
Everything's wrong with singing!
The way those damn singers dress,
they might as well be naked.
Just a bunch of drug addicts!
Yes, Dad.
-Hello.
-Are you looking for someone?
Is this the home of Nguyen Mai Ly?
Yes, I'm her father.
I'm Detective Manh.
We need to ask Ly some questions
about Lam Phuong's suicide.
Your daughter was
a back-up singer for Lam Phuong.
Is that true?
Yes.
Please calm down.
I told you a thousand times,
there would be none of
that singing bullshit in this house!
We just need her help
in our investigation.
You can come with us if you want.
Get her out of my sight.
The clip seems
to have been recorded at a party.
What do you know about it?
I don't know anything.
I was just her back-up singer.
But Khanh, her manager, said otherwise.
According to
one of Phuong's text messages,
you went to the party with her.
Phuong's suicide note: who's "all of you"?
Recognize this?
Yuki. Phuong's doll.
She loved it.
It was her guardian angel.
Not a very reliable guardian angel then.
Didn't seem to help you either.
You have one too.
And they look like
they were bought from the same place.
No, that's not true.
I bought mine at the market.
Kumanthong dolls, they all look similar.
I may be smiling but I'm not happy
Cash up front, that's why
everyone loves working with this team.
Phuong's new album is coming out soon.
Try to make rehearsals, okay?
Yeah, I know.
Khanh,
you gave me extra.
Phuong asked me to.
Time to pay rent, right?
I work the same as everyone else,
so I shouldn't receive more.
I feel awkward.
No need to feel bad.
You two are like sisters.
So?
What did you think about my performance?
Same as usual.
Same as usual?
Not ground breaking? Not mesmerizing?
No, what I meant is
your usual is already the best.
Because I have the best manager!
And, of course, my little Yuki!
I think ever since you got Yuki,
you've had non-stop hits.
Be careful, someone may get jealous.
Sure, Yuki handles all the bookings,
right?
Yuki schedules the band,
Yuki places the ads,
Yuki butters up the reporters too.
See?
I adore Yuki but I love you.
Let's go, I'm starving.
Go get changed while I get the car.
-Hey, Ly!
-Yes?
Your birthday's coming up, right?
-What's this?
-Open it.
I love it. Thank you.
Take care of her,
she'll bring you good luck.
I will.
Ly,
if you don't tell us what you know,
I'm afraid more people will get hurt.
Phuong, let's update story.
-Have you applied a filter?
-Of course. Now pose!
What happened?
There's blood… in the bathroom.
Are you okay? There's no blood.
Rest in peace…
Phuong.
-Are you Ly?
-Yes.
I'm Phuong's dad.
The police met with me.
I know you were
there with her at that party.
You told them you don't remember
anything about that night.
We were drugged,
I really can't remember anything.
Tell me the truth, did they threaten you?
It's over, I just want to move on.
I think Phuong would want the same too.
Don't you want them to get punished?
-I said everything I needed to say.
-Nothing but lies!
Look at Phuong.
She was only 25, successful and talented…
why would she dabble in drugs
and those kind of parties?
I don't think
you know everything about her.
She wasn't as strong as she looked.
She kept a Kumanthong doll
because she yearned for a mother's love.
What did you say?
Her mother left when
she was very young, right?
Shut up!
You don't know anything about our family.
I'm a victim too.
I'm in pain too.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
You have to help me,
you have to help me clear her name.
I'm sorry.
Hello?
You have fun talking to Mr. Ngºc?
Who is this?
If you don't want to end up like Phuong,
watch your mouth.
We're following you.
SIX MONTHS LATER
ACOUSTIC COMPETITION
Look here.
You have to show off a little more
like this to get an audience.
Unlike you.
No, thanks.
Try it. Who knows,
maybe you'll get a million views!
Leave her alone.
Ly can actually sing,
she doesn't need tricks.
No need to strip if you got the gifts.
Hey that almost rhymes.
You should be a rapper.
There's that singing contest
that's been running ads like crazy.
Yeah, I only have a few hundred friends
and their ads still pop up on my page.
Yeah.
Here it is.
The finals will livestream on YouTube.
Sounds like a big deal.
Ly can win this easily.
Yeah, you'll be so famous if you win.
Give me some of
that reward money so I can pay the bills.
SING FOR YOU COMPETITION
You're so going to win.
For sure.
And the winner is…
Tram Anh!
Please come up to the stage, Tram Anh.
Will our sponsors please join us on stage.
Congratulations to our winner.
Hey, did she bribe somebody?
Her voice isn't even
suitable for busking on the street.
Oh, well… that's my life.
You did very well.
Thank you.
If it were up to me,
you would have been the winner.
Can we change the rules of the game?
There should be a second prize
or consolation prize.
Have some self-respect, would you?
Water’s been off for three days now.
I need to shower real bad.
What’s her name?
Little Ly.
Wow. Yeah!
-Look at this.
-Please, enjoy.
Can’t remember the last time
we got to eat this well!
Can I have the cash equivalent
of this meal?
Shush!
Eat and stop talking.
Where did you summon Little Ly?
What do you mean?
I got her as a birthday gift.
And did you do the summoning?
What summoning?
You kids really don’t know anything.
For Kumanthong dolls,
you have to go to the right master.
He will decide who’s most suitable for you
and bless the doll.
If you don’t do it right,
it will backfire on you.
I've never really thought about that.
You know Lam Phuong the singer?
Her voice was just so-so,
so why did she become an idol?
Because of Kumanthong.
But Kumanthong didn’t protect her, did it?
You have to understand,
the doll is just the shell.
What's most important
is the soul of the baby inside.
How you treat it
decides how your life turns out.
You were the best singer tonight,
you lost to the winner by only two votes.
I think you have the look,
you have the voice.
But I’ve never
heard of you before tonight,
which means
your doll is not working right now.
My master, he comes
to Vietnam every month.
Look. Ask him to summon a doll for you.
It'll be the best investment of your life.
Just think about it and let me know.
I’ll show you the real master.
There are all kinds
of charlatans out there.
Okay.
Mrs. Tam is right.
Little Ly is cute,
but she’s never been blessed.
Ever since I got her,
all I've had is bad luck.
No job, no boyfriend.
You're nuts.
I'm this good looking
and I still don't have a boyfriend!
Mrs. Tam said ever since
she got the Kumanthong,
everything worked out for her.
Don't be stupid!
She's always been crazy rich.
And you’ll be famous in no time.
You don't need any guardian angels…
you have one right next to you.
That's me!
This is going to be
the best investment of my life.
When I’m rich and famous,
I will supply you with
a lifetime of sushi and boba tea.
Nah. I’m just a ramen kind of girl.
How about a year supply of Vifon ramen?
Cheers.
Whoa! Why so many dolls?
Looks more like the Nguyen dynasty.
They’re pretty cute.
Oh, please.
Barbies are cute.
These look more like
descendants of Annabelle.
Shush. Be serious.
I'm being dead serious.
Why does she look like Yuki?
Who?
Yuki, Phuong’s doll.
The accessories, the aura.
Exactly the same.
Aura of a doll?
I'm going to call you Na.
I'm going to be your mommy from now on.
I'm going to love you
like my own flesh and blood.
So cute.
Yeah, cute.
Hey.
That looks like Khanh.
Khanh who?
Khanh the producer, Phuong’s boyfriend.
The one you had a crush on?
Keep it down.
Don’t get your panties in a twist.
Shit. He saw us.
Hey, Khanh! Ly's hiding right behind me!
You!
Ly. Long time no see.
I’m Huyen, her manager.
What have you been up to?
Me?
I'm still going to school.
My office just moved to District 1,
stop by some time if you want.
I have a few projects coming up.
We’ll definitely be there.
Make sure you line up the reporters,
we can only spare five minutes.
I’ll roll out the red carpet for you both.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Why did he give me this?
What?
He didn’t have to.
Why did he suddenly
invite me to sing for him?
Oh, that’s just chit chat.
You'll audition
and he’ll say, "Oh you’re very good
but oh, I'm so sorry."
Then he'll make you a back-up singer.
He’s in need of back-up singers, you know.
That's not what I meant.
In a city this big, how could
we run into each other by chance?
It's good luck, don’t you see?
What the hell?
I'm serious.
He never paid any attention to me before.
It must be for my baby Na.
He looked at me differently today.
It’s two a.m. at the intersection
We sit side by side watching the city
There is a storm inside me
You ask me what you should do
When the one you love is gone
Stealing your heart without a word
Why can’t you see?
Day by day, the one next to you
Can't make you feel the way I do
Why are you in such a hurry?
I am the one who loves you
Your vocal range is impressive.
It’s hard to believe you
didn’t have any professional training.
I’ve loved singing since I was a kid.
My mom used to be a singer,
just a bar singer,
but she was very good, and very pretty.
Why didn’t you go to music school?
My mom left my dad when I was young.
She was so into singing that
she followed the other man.
If he knew I was involved with singing,
he would be so mad.
After Phuong passed away,
the company slowed down too.
I still can’t believe it.
She was my idol.
You just lost an idol.
I lost a fiancée,
a soulmate,
a partner,
the future of our company.
Khanh,
you're the best producer in town,
you can build it up again.
We're drinking in the middle of the day?
Just one glass.
To celebrate our company’s new talent.
Are you serious?
Very serious.
We're going to make you a star in no time.
This will be your new home.
This is Ms. Nam,
she'll take care of things
around the house.
I hope you like it.
Thank you!
Baby Na.
Thank you for bringing me
all these great opportunities.
I know you listened to all my prayers.
I promise to love you
and take care of you forever.
I love you too, Mommy.
Hello, kids.
-Hi.
-Hello, auntie!
I mean, hello sis!
We just got started. Come on in.
Okay.
Hi, everyone.
This is baby Na and her mommy, Mai Ly,
our newest members.
Baby Na!
Say hi to all the aunties and uncles.
Hi, Na.
Happy birthday to Phuc.
This is lovely.
Phuc is saying thank you to auntie Ly.
Phuc, say hi to Na. Hi Na! Look at that.
There. You can now take pictures
or videos if you want.
Hey, you.
You just told me I could take pictures.
Just go do your thing. Go.
-Hey, sis.
-Yes?
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
I'm just curious, when I pray to Na,
can you ask for anything?
Are there any limits?
What do you want to wish for?
Career, fame.
Yes.
Fortune.
Love.
What's so funny?
Someone's in love!
Why aren't you eating?
You keep staring at me.
It's so cozy here.
Phuong used to love this place.
You don’t like the food?
No, it’s… wonderful.
Ly?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Ly?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
KHANH
Phuong used to love this place.
This must be
the nicest studio in the city.
You know that Khanh
built this studio for Phuong, right?
She recorded all her songs exactly
where you are standing right now.
Are you ready? Let’s get started.
Yeah, okay.
Phuong left so suddenly.
Recently, she's been appearing to me.
I’m scared.
I never wanted to hurt her.
I loved her.
Don’t worry, Mommy.
She’s not upset with you.
You’re like her little sister.
You’re really good
for someone who’s untrained.
Thank you.
Is it difficult to learn the piano?
Sure, but someone like you
could probably learn faster than others.
Sit down.
The white keys are
the natural notes of each octave,
the black keys are half tones.
During the time of Mozart,
it was the opposite.
I didn’t know that.
Yes.
Some things that are white used to be
black and black used to be white.
Just like human nature.
You can’t tell
until you watch very closely.
Focus.
Play that melody again.
Phuong used to like this song.
Do you know its name?
-I…
-"Ah, vous dirai-je, maman."
Mozart's variation.
Then they turned it
into a children’s song,
and the original title meant
"Mother, if I could tell you."
What would Phuong say to her mother?
Khanh.
I’m an addict… and a whore?
Wow, I love it, thank you.
Take good care of her
and she’ll bring you good luck.
I will.
Cuong, did you call for me?
Hello, Ly Coco! Have a drink!
I have class tomorrow.
If you can't drink with me,
how about with him?
Hello, Ly Coco.
I’ve been listening to you on Instagram,
finally got a chance to hear you live.
Thien, what a surprise to see you here.
He’s known as the star maker.
You get to sing a song of his
and you’ll be famous overnight.
I don’t know what to say.
Then you don't have to say anything,
just have a drink.
Here you go.
Cheers.
Look at you.
Your voice still needs some polish
but on certain notes,
you’re even better than Phuong.
Come on, I’m just her back-up singer.
Mariah Carey, Pink, Cher, Gwen Stefani.
What do they all have in common?
They all used to be back-up singers
before they became stars.
All you need is one hit song.
I have a few new songs
that I haven’t sold.
They might fit your voice.
If you want,
come over to Cuong’s next week to try out,
we’re throwing a party.
This is a huge opportunity, how could I?
Opportunities only come to
those who truly deserve them.
You can ask Phuong to come with you.
Things will be much easier for you
if Phuong is there.
Drink up.
Cuong is throwing a party this weekend,
you should come with me.
You keep hanging out with those guys,
they’ll chew you up
and spit you out one day.
Cuong is a nice guy,
and I like Thien’s music.
Nobody gives you things for free.
You have your dad’s support,
and Khanh to take care of everything.
Things are much easier for you.
Me, I have nobody.
If you’re busy, I can go by myself.
It's alright, I’ll come with you.
Really?
But you have to do
what I say when we’re there.
Ly?
Sorry, I just wanted to drop off
a few contracts for you.
-Just leave them there.
-Okay.
I'm going now.
Baby Na.
Khanh looks normal on the outside
but I think he’s actually sad
and lonely deep down inside.
Only I can help him.
You have to be there for him,
and one day he’ll love you.
You called me?
Come in, Ly.
Hey, I just wanted to apologize
for hugging you the other day.
I think…
What do you think?
-Well… I'm embarrassed.
-What?
I couldn’t help myself. I was scared.
No, I'm talking about the song.
How is it?
Have a seat.
It sounds familiar.
Don't make me wait.
Stay with me tonight.
What?
What's a better title?
"Don’t make me wait" or "Stay with
me tonight," which title do you like?
Oh… "Don't make me wait" sounds trendier.
Okay, the singer has spoken!
-Ly!
-Yes?
Will you sing this song?
But you wrote this one
for Phuong.
I've adjusted it to suit you better.
Are you sure?
I’m certain that only
Mai Ly can replace Lam Phuong.
MAI LY DON’T PLAY WITH FIRE
Khanh has been so nice to me.
He’s texting me all the time,
and picking me up
and dropping me off everywhere.
I love you the most.
Huyen,
you can head home first.
Why?
I’m going with Khanh for a nightcap.
Be careful, don't get caught in scandals
before you’re even famous.
I know, but I love him.
His fiancée passed away
like six months ago
and he’s already all over you.
You might just be a rebound,
some temporary replacement,
but it's certainly not real love.
Shut up.
You're just jealous.
What did you say?
Khanh.
Babe! What's wrong?
I…
I'm fine.
Ly,
did I do anything to upset you last night?
It's just that I haven't been with anyone
in a while
so I'm not completely comfortable.
I won't force you into anything
if you're not ready.
I'm going to protect you.
But do you love me?
I never thought
I could feel this way again.
But to be honest,
sometimes…
I don't think I'm ready to love again.
Phuong was my whole world.
After the clip came out,
Phuong didn’t say anything to me.
I felt betrayed.
I felt like a fool.
Maybe it was difficult
for Phuong to open up.
You two were very close.
At the party,
did she say anything to you?
She just asked me to come with her,
I didn’t know anything else.
Hi, Ly Coco.
This is my friend Cuong.
It’s such an honor to have you here.
Ly is the guest tonight,
I’m just tagging along.
Let me show you in.
I heard you had an offer for Ly?
Business talk already?
Have a little fun.
We’re recording a new album soon
so we can’t drink.
Otherwise, we’d outdrink all of you!
I have a new song,
which I think would be perfect
for a duet with you and Ly.
How’s your production schedule?
Can I squeeze my song in?
I have to check with Khanh first.
Do you have a demo?
Of course!
Wow, it’s cool.
It's going to be a hit.
So, you see how nice we are to Ly Coco?
I’m going to wait for Khanh to come back,
and if he's okay,
we can all have a drink together.
Then just one glass for now.
Go on.
Let’s drink.
-Cheers.
I'm going to stop by the studio,
I’ll pick you up later.
Okay.
-Yes?
-Flower delivery.
Can you come to the lobby to sign for it?
I’ll be right down.
WITH DEEPEST SYMPATHY
Are you Nguyen Mai Ly?
Who’s the sender?
I have no idea.
I was just told to deliver it here
for you.
This must be some mistake. I’m sorry.
How can it be a mistake? It's your face!
WHY DID YOU CHANGE YOUR NUMBER?
WANT TO PARTY WITH US AGAIN?
OR DO YOU WANT TO END UP LIKE PHUONG?
Cuong, I’m telling you one last time,
I’m not afraid of you.
I’m not that kind of girl.
Don’t try to threaten me. It won't work!
Phuong, they just called me too.
The hell with them!
But they said this was the last warning.
If we don’t come, they will…
They've been threatening me
for two months now.
These bastards
don't have the guts to do anything.
There's an ancient proverb:
"Inner beauty outweighs beauty
on the outside."
But I don't see anything wrong
with looking beautiful.
Tell you a secret… I've got both!
My dear sisters,
true beauty comes from within.
Your confidence, your take-charge attitude
are your best accessories.
But don't forget this,
pretty girls always get the guys.
This is Phuong, it’s her.
What is it?
-Sex clip?
-Oh, that’s bad.
Is that true?
Khanh.
Phuong, can you explain all of this?
Phuong.
Lam Phuong.
A lot of people are
questioning your lifestyle!
You go to these events often?
Who are those men?
I don’t know.
I was drugged. I am a victim.
Go!
Lam Phuong.
SEX CLIP OF SINGER LAM PHUONG
ANGRY BACKLASH FOR LAM PHUONG
SHE'S HIGH LIKE A DRUG-ADDICT!
HER SINGING IS BULLSHIT!
WHAT ABUSE? SHE LOVED IT!
SERVES HER RIGHT! WHAT AN INNOCENT COVER!
HAPPY NOW? GO TO HELL!
DIE!
These people are dangerous.
I’m going to die if I don’t do something.
What you need,
Na can’t give to you.
It’s very difficult.
I’m going to die.
Please, you have to help me.
Fetus…
Fetus?
You can't find this in Vietnam.
Have to bring it in from Thailand.
And even over there it’s illegal.
-Hello, sister.
-Hi.
Welcome, master.
Baby Na needs to be cleansed from within
in order to receive a new soul,
that of the sacred demon spawn.
The dark liquid is made of gold dust
and dirt from Napran temple,
allowing the new soul to enter.
The demon infant is led
through the gateway of the soul,
at this time baby Na
is in her weakest state.
The enchanted knife
makes sure that only the right person
can lead other spirits
through the gateway of the soul.
Roc-sam-long…
this is the tamed demon infant,
called upon by the shaman.
Sam-sat-yam ritual
is to connect you
to both Na and Roc-sam-long,
to insure these infant souls
will do as you command.
Baby Na,
if you love Mommy…
please protect me from these bad people,
please don't let them hurt me.
You have to save me.
I'm so scared.
They threatened my life!
It's all because I was hungry for fame,
and I was a coward.
Now I'm just a puppet
in the hands of these bastards!
Can you save me, baby Na?
Nguyen Vinh Cuong,
son of a real estate tycoon.
He has a history of drug abuse.
A staged death.
Some sort of gang war?
No, this looks more like personal revenge.
I have bad news for our superstar!
Why does your place feel so morbid?
So? What's the bad news?
You just got suspended from school
for skipping class too much.
That’s not bad news.
You rushed me for this?
My hair is still wet.
Come wait upstairs.
What are you doing?
Why do you have a dead man's photo?
What do you mean?
Didn’t you read the news?
How do you know him?
Why?
Why did he die?
Who is he?
The party.
He’s the one who invited me and Phuong.
He drugged us.
He raped us and recorded the whole thing!
They wanted Phuong to become their slave.
He released the video
when Phuong refused to do what he wanted.
And now it’s my turn.
Why didn’t you tell me?
So all those months,
you lied about being depressed
from a break up.
I was a nobody back then,
so they didn’t bother me.
But it’s different now.
I’m scared.
I don’t want to lose everything,
like Phuong.
And his death had nothing
to do with you, right?
No, I was just asking for protection,
I didn’t mean anything!
Baby Na killed him to protect me.
You’re out of your mind.
You have to get rid of this thing!
Don't touch my baby!
She’s just protecting me.
This is voodoo!
It's evil! You get that, right?
This doll is messing up your head,
you have to tear down this room!
Or there’ll be consequences.
Leave me alone.
Go away.
Ly, someone just died. This is no joke!
Are you done? Just get out!
SON OF RICH LAND DEALER FOUND DEAD
I thought I would get exactly
what I asked for.
I asked Kumanthong for protection,
not murder.
But now he’s dead,
he can’t hurt you anymore.
Isn’t that what you wanted?
I want to return baby Na.
You young people are so ungrateful.
You're selfish and superficial.
You think anything can be bought,
used up and returned
whenever you feel like it.
Ly, you’re dealing with a spirit here.
Your guardian angel is a baby,
it lost its chance to be born.
You accepted her into your life,
she did your bidding
and now you want to abandon her?
I’m telling you,
an angry spirit can do a lot of damage.
This doll is messing up your head,
you have to tear down this room!
Or there’ll be consequences.
-These three seem pretty close.
-Hold on. There's more.
This is what we got from Cuong’s laptop,
there must be hundreds.
Get me information on the other two.
What are you doing, Ms. Nam?
What’s wrong?
I came this afternoon…
When I was cleaning, I heard something.
Heard what?
It’s hard to describe. But…
Like something scratching on the wall.
And…
It came from the altar room.
I thought maybe you got a cat,
but the scratching
got more and more frantic.
What did you see?
You should see for yourself.
YOU THINK YOU CAN GET RID OF US?
THIS PHOTO IS TOO BLURRY,
WE’VE GOT BETTER ONES.
Mommy’s so sorry,
I’m never going to leave you again.
Can you please help me one more time?
Take a close look,
these people want to hurt me.
I beg you…
punish them for me!
I THINK MS. TAM AND HER GROUP
ARE UP TO NO GOOD.
YOU HAVE TO BE CAREFUL.
Can I go up to the penthouse?
Are you interested in renting it?
Sure.
SHADY KUMANTHONG GROUP BUSTED!
Why did Baby Na hurt Huyen?
Huyen only meant well when she warned me.
She’s my best friend.
Warned?
Warned you about what?
She said something
about a shady Kumanthong group
and police were onto their scams.
Is that so?
Sis.
What if… you and I…
we’re being played here?
Huyen was just imagining stuff!
Look here! It's your penthouse!
Why did you trick me
into joining that group?
What are you up to?
What’s wrong with you? Are you possessed?
There’s no trick here.
You’re lying!
What about the penthouse?
You're so paranoid. I moved, that’s all.
I needed a bigger place
because we have more members now.
A few joined after you left,
you’re not the only one
in need of a guardian angel.
What the hell are you laughing at?
You think it's funny?
You wanted to silence Huyen, didn't you?
You think I’m scared of you?
I’m going to call the police on you.
I'm going to reveal all
of your deranged schemes.
I only see a deranged girl sitting here.
You can’t deny the power of Kumanthong.
Baby Na gave you everything.
Fame, love, revenge.
The three who hurt you are now dead.
You got Khanh.
What else do you want?
Khanh?
I never told you his name was Khanh.
Thank you for bringing me
all these opportunities.
I know you listen to all my prayers.
Only I can help Khanh.
Na, if you love me… punish them for me!
The three who hurt you are now dead.
You got Khanh. What else do you want?
I never told you his name was Khanh.
Khanh, they recorded me!
They heard it all, they know everything!
You see. Huyen was right.
It was all a scam.
It’s all right. Calm down.
I can’t breathe.
What are you doing?
It's over, Ly.
What are you saying?
If you had just told the police
everything you told Baby Na…
it wouldn’t have turned out like this.
What?
Phuong loved you like a sister.
But…
Even after Phuong was shamed in public
and died a tragic death
you still would not reveal
the identities of those men.
You were afraid of losing your shot
at fame and fortune.
This was the only way…
and I knew my plan would work.
Plan?
You helped me get revenge for Phuong.
WITH DEEPEST SYMPATHY
OR DO YOU WANT TO END UP LIKE PHUONG?
Phuong was everything to me.
We were going to get married.
You know…
I loved Phuong more than anything.
When she died…
I had nothing left to live for.
I swore
I would avenge her at any cost.
I would stop at nothing.
So it was…
all part of a plan?
I thought…
What did you think?
That you deserved all that?
Everything you have now,
belonged to Phuong.
Even your doll.
Na…
was Yuki.
And according to my plan,
you have to die.
To bury the evidence.
All the blame would point towards you.
I planned everything that way.
Khanh.
You can do whatever
you want to me but please,
can you let me do one last thing?
One last thing that I need to do.
I beg you.
This is the truth
that I want everyone to know.
HUYEN, LY IS CONFESSING.
SO SHE'S BEEN LYING TO US ALL ALONG.
Phuong warned me
about those people but I didn’t listen.
There were three men
in masks who hurt Phuong.
And I…
WHAT A SHAME I CAN'T HELP YOU
WHAT'S THIS NONSENSE. TIRED!
I wore a mask every day to protect myself.
Uncle Hai, Ly has a new clip.
If it wasn’t for me,
you would still be alive.
You would still be a star,
admired by millions of people.
If it wasn't for me,
your father would still have a daughter.
I’m so sorry,
Phuong.
Huyen,
now I know there’s
no such thing as a guardian angel.
But I know
I have one true friend, that’s you.
You were always by my side,
protecting me.
Dad,
please don’t be disappointed in me.
I still remember all you have taught me…
but I couldn't help it.
I got to live the life
I always dreamed of,
but perhaps I didn't deserve it.
If there’s a next life,
I still want to be a singer.
But not like this.
Even if you clear Phuong's name…
it's too late.
I want you to live,
to truly pay for what you did.
HUYEN
I’m sorry.
We found blood from a third person
at the last crime scene.
It didn’t belong to the two victims,
nor the prime suspect, Ly.
So… whose blood is it?
The one seeking vengeance.
A blood test will tell us everything.
NGOC THIEN
VINH CUONG
FIANCÉ
FATHER MR. TRAN NGOC
UNCLE
MRS. DO THANH TAM
I'm sorry.
I still can’t believe it.
After all these years,
I came back for my daughter’s wedding.
But in the end…
I couldn’t protect our daughter.
I'm sorry.
SING FOR YOU COMPETITION
May you rest in peace.
POLICE
Wow, you’re getting so popular,
you’re going to get advertising deals!
You should be a full-time influencer.
-Why bother with school?
-Stop it.
I need to focus on school,
I have two months till graduation.
Let me check it out.
HELLO @HUYENNERTAKEITALL, I’M NGHIEM
FROM STARLIGHT, THE MODEL AGENCY.
I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOUR VIDEOS
AND I LOVE THEM.
CAN WE MEET UP AND HAVE A CHAT?
I THINK I HAVE SOME OPPORTUNITIES
THAT ARE JUST RIGHT FOR YOU.
THANK YOU.
BUT I NEED TO FOCUS
ON MY EDUCATION AT THIS TIME.