Being able to fix
what seems like junk to everyone
and being able to make things
functional again
always make Jock happy.
A TV Fan.
You won't feel hot
while watching TV again.
Though things might be
a little unconventional.
You freak.
Go to hell.
Go.
Even when his life isn't going well,
he is still happy to try and fix things.
LOAN CONTRACT
MANA
So he does his mission with confidence.
You're on the right track, Jock!
SOLAR CELL BBQ PORK
-Move to the left.
-A little more.
Yes, that's it.
Hey, everyone! Look!
I'm too good.
But his confidence is sometimes useless.
I'm damn proud of myself.
Because there is a part of life
that is inevitably attached to...
destiny.
CLOSED FOR GOOD
One day, destiny brought Jock
to a turning point.
THE BEDSIDE DETECTIVE
THE JOURNAL OF THE TRUE ENCOUNTERS
OF A PRIVATE DETECTIVE
URGENT! DETECTIVE WANTED!
-Hey! You lowlife!
-What the hell is that?
Hey!
Although it's a risky job,
the compensation puts a smile on his face.
And because of his innate talent
as an inventor,
Jock became a detective
while repairing things on the side.
-Jock.
-Yes?
Can you fix my TV?
He has Rue-Tai,
a karaoke girl next door,
to take care of him.
Thanks, Rue-Tai. You smooth it out.
Ironing clothes is a piece of cake.
My mom taught me
that a woman is considered a good wife
when she is good in the kitchen
and a whore in bed.
Together with his personal
motorbike handyman, Jack,
who dreams of being a detective like him.
If you're looking for a partner,
just tell me.
Just tell me.
Okay.
I'm going.
Hey, don't forget my side view mirror.
Okay.
No, don't bother. Let me.
The fun part of being a detective
is having an adventurous lifestyle
and a chance to become someone
you couldn't imagine yourself being.
Is it nice? Do you like it?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Jock starts to discover
a new form of happiness.
One that comes with a risk.
Surprise!
Jock.
It's spicy noodles today.
Come on, sit here.
I don't know if you'll like it.
Fan Chopsticks.
-What an idea!
-Yes.
Here.
It's hot. Perfect for your chopsticks!
-Is it delicious?
-It's good.
Making the soup took me...
a long time.
It's kind of viscous because it's...
Wow, it's hot. I mean...
I simmered it, you know?
And the coriander...
I...
Who is that?
Did you hear the intro
of the song I chose?
I'm going to sing it now.
I'll be back.
Excuse me, guys.
Hold on!
-Hey, Curly Sue.
-Yes?
There's nothing happening here, right?
Yes.
It's quite calm.
Not even a breeze!
-Are you in a hurry?
-Yes!
Please.
Goodbye, then.
Should I remind you what day it is today?
No, sir.
Hey!
Search!
Eight thousand baht.
How much do you owe her?
Three hundred thousand, sir.
Do you know what's going to happen
if you miss the payment again?
You know what is coming, right?
You've already missed two installments.
I'm charging an additional 30% interest
for your late payment.
And last month had 31 days,
so that's another 1.5%.
Including the cost of wasting my time...
What is the usual rate for that?
-Five thousand baht.
-Five thousand.
Five thousand.
Yes. So you owe us 583,000 baht.
Altogether, if you round it up,
it's easier to remember...
Six hundred thousand baht.
Now you should know...
how torturous it is
when you're being suffocated.
He's here, Madam Saowapa.
Come sit over here, Mana,
so we can talk.
Hello.
It's my girl calling from the US.
Get it for me.
Yes, sweetie?
Yes.
Daddy is busy.
He doesn't have time to call you.
Yes.
All right, I'll remind him this evening.
Okay? Yes.
I really miss you.
That stupid prick!
Take a photo of that bitch
so I won't shoot the wrong one.
Easy, ma'am. Before you shoot anyone,
let me hear the whole story.
I smelled a rat
when I saw that plane ticket.
That jackass hasn't bought me
anything for ages.
Surprise!
You know what this is?
Hey.
You want to visit our kid
in the US, right?
Here. You can stay there
for the entire two weeks.
You'll definitely
have a great time with her.
What a sneaky idea!
Pay a little more
for a much bigger return.
Imagine, while you're gone...
Bang!
Baking his tube steak every day!
Until one night,
I caught him red-handed.
Wait.
What?
An inmate breaking out?
All right. Sure.
There is an emergency.
I have to go to the precinct.
You don't have to spy on him.
Your husband is surely having an affair.
Damn! Bitch!
All mistresses are bitches.
I want proof
of his guilt.
I want him caught red-handed.
So he won't mess around anymore.
If that's what you want, I'm with you.
Good.
He told me he'll be having
a meeting tomorrow night.
I think they must be planning to meet up.
Take photos of them.
All right.
Hey.
MANA ELECTRIC REPAIR SERVICE
FOR A LOW PRICE
Where did you come from?
Enough with that pitiful look.
Hungry?
Raise your front legs.
Wow...
Holy crap! What kind of dog are you?
Scratch your balls!
Just kidding. Come here!
Hey, what's your name?
Let me give you a name.
How about James Bond? Cool, right?
All right.
Eat up.
Hey!
What a mess!
Butt out!
Leave!
-Go!
-Get out of here, you shitty mutt!
That damn dog is making a mess
all over the place!
Very nasty!
Anyway...
I brought your side view mirror.
It smells like chicken!
Well, Mana...
I'm ready to join your detective venture.
Again?
Don't you have anything to do, Jack?
The life of a detective
is hanging by a thread.
When you eat, you have to hide.
When you sleep,
you can only close one eye.
Can you endure that, Jack?
I believe I was born to be one, Mana.
To be a grease monkey?
Great! You know yourself well
so you don't have too much ambition.
It's not that bad.
But Rue-Tai is right.
You know nothing about detective shit.
Right.
How can you say that?
You can ask me anything
about being a detective.
I know all about it.
Do you even remember the detective's
rules of thumb you've told me?
-I know them all. Ask me.
-What are they?
The first rule,
"Working for a mistress is prohibited."
The second rule,
"Don't ever fall in love with the target."
And the third rule
is also the most important.
"Do not blackmail your clients."
You're speechless?
See? I can help you.
We don't need your help.
Jock and I are the perfect partners.
Remember the pizza?
I baked a pizza for you.
-A pizza?
-Yes.
I assembled the pizza bike for him
until my hands almost burned.
Oh, really?
-You assemble his bike every day?
-Yes, I do.
Because I cook for him every day,
you know?
Three meals a day, seven days a week!
I'm the only one doing it,
the only one taking care of him.
-This asshole...
-Yes, this asshole!
He had me fix his bike,
but he never paid a dime.
I got scolded by my boss
-and I cried every night.
-Oh, really?
So it's just you?
Do you see what I'm holding?
The basket.
Which ones are mine? None!
His shirt, his pants, and this!
The masterpiece, his underwear!
I've never even washed my dad's.
You see any stains? Who washes all these?
It's me! Only me!
You still remember when you took a shit
and couldn't flush it down?
Hey!
What's going on here?
I know the two of you love me.
Actually, there is a big job waiting.
I'll give you two a chance,
so stop fighting.
Good.
-Hello.
-You are here too?
Come on in. I'll buy you a meal.
-Can I go now?
-Yes, sir.
Please.
No! I don't mess around at all.
Jesus.
Welcome.
Good evening, sir.
He just drank too much tonight.
Oh, I see.
-Let's go. Don't waste time here.
-Please. Go ahead.
Feeble hands!
That's for having a young wife.
Okay.
This way.
Target A still looks gloomy.
Target B hasn't shown up yet.
Nam-Pan... Over here!
Over here!
Nam-Pan! Right here!
Nam-Pan...
What kind of woman is Nam-Pan?
Just the sound of her name
makes me tingle.
I'm sorry.
Don't get mad at me, okay, darling?
Hey, Mana.
Do you see that chick?
I feel like breaking the second rule.
Falling in love with the target
is wrong, right?
Are you a good girl?
I brought you a reward.
Here.
Thank you, darling.
My pleasure.
It's 12:05 a.m.
Target B arrived at the pub.
Having a great time?
Pathetic!
You are just a mistress.
Jock, look! They're going out to dance.
Shall we dance too?
Like...
Hey!
You want to dance?
You're dancing with me?
What exactly do you want?
Give me the address and phone number
of that whore.
Sorry. Could you lower your voice?
My job is to take photos.
I can't do anything else besides that.
You should talk to your husband.
Give me her number
or you won't get paid.
I don't support violent response.
It violates my ethics as a detective.
Can you lift up the skin on my face
just like that slut?
You should go
to a plastic surgeon instead.
Really?
Wow, really,
there's a mega sale?
All right. I'll be there in 15 minutes.
Emporium Mall.
Turn right in the alley, it's a shortcut.
Please give me directions.
This is not my area.
Make a left.
Oh, no. Right.
What's wrong with your bike?
What's wrong with it?
It's out of gas.
I just filled the tank this morning.
If you didn't give the wrong directions,
we could've arrived there by now.
Here. Your soda.
It's quite a long walk to the main road.
Thank you.
Come on. We'll get there soon.
Don't you feel hot with that helmet?
Why don't you take it off for now?
It's pretty tight. It's hard to take off.
This housing project is kind of nice.
With a little front yard...
Cool. I will use it to grow jasmine trees.
Sixty square yards is just right.
It's not too big.
Like being a minor, you mean?
Thank you.
How many times have you done this?
Please give me a few more days.
-I'll find 2,000 baht to pay you.
-Shut up.
As you know, selling noodles
doesn't provide much.
One bowl is around 20 to 30 baht.
I beg you, I'll pay you back
as soon as I can.
Please don't hurt me.
Tee, who's next?
Jock.
IT WILL BE YOUR TURN NEXT TIME,
NOT THIS CURLY SUE!
-Are you all right, Rue-Tai?
-Jock.
Why did they have to do this?
I'm sorry.
Madam Saowapa.
It's me, Mana.
Have your money ready.
I will exchange it
for her number in two days.
Wash your eyes, sweetie.
Why are your eyes closed?
I'm afraid
I will have nightmares.
What's wrong?
Rue-Tai, can I borrow your car?
All right.
If you want to have my Red Cutie,
you have to have her owner too.
Of course, I will.
We are all going together.
Naughty.
Shit.
Is that a flat or convex screen?
Target B has shown up.
It is a laptop, not a TV.
It is neither flat nor convex.
Well, too bad!
I like screens with protruding parts.
Can I have something like that?
Thank you.
Prepare the goods tonight.
I'll stop by to check it out.
You can't check anything today.
The port is temporarily closed
due to the monthly flood.
Isn't that...
supposed to be next week?
Damn!
Look!
What is this crap?
Why didn't he give me cash instead?
I didn't know
you also liked antiques.
I'm thinking about ditching him.
Three months with him
is all pain and no gain.
Unlike your new rich guy?
Yes,
I haven't lost anything
and he gave me a big gift.
A brand new Mercedes, right?
The target is reading Home magazine.
Hot.
Still reading Home magazine.
You don't even care...
if I can't sleep until tomorrow?
She is in the lingerie department.
The lace?
It's itchy. You'll get a rash.
No way! What year were you born in?
Even my grandma calls that outdated.
No.
That one over there.
That will work.
No, not purple.
The one next to it.
Yes, that's it.
The blush-rose color
with hooks in the back.
B-cup.
Superb!
Pretty and cute.
Standby.
Be at the meeting point in five minutes.
Jeez!
How the hell do you drive your car?
Look, my car is all busted.
Hey.
How could you?
What?
What are you talking about?
You're the one who bumped into me.
It's my lane.
You're supposed to wait,
-not cut in like this.
-It's useless to argue about it.
Let's call insurance.
Hello? Car accident.
Yes, in the parking lot.
-Insurance?
-Yes.
In case of a car accident,
we have to see your...
Well...
She...
She cut in from this side.
Can I have your ID?
Yes.
No!
My poor baby.
Can you write down
your address in Bangkok?
And your phone number.
-Red Cutie...
-Your phone number here
-if I need to contact you...
-Red Cutie...
So which service garage can I go to?
I mean, which garage
have you been dealing with?
Right.
I see.
You can call this car service center.
This one right here.
JIRA GARAGE
Wait a minute.
Don't I need to fill out some paperwork?
I'm supposed to present something
to the repairman.
You don't need to.
I always remember a cute face.
THE PRICE STARTS AT 5.2 MILLION BAHT
Address confirmed.
Guess where I am right now.
I'm not very far from you, Nam-Pan.
I really miss you.
Wow!
It's nice.
How beautiful!
You made everything yourself?
You know my style.
That's why I'm crazy about you.
It's 11 p.m.
The target is with another man.
Isn't being one man's mistress bad enough?
Why are you like this?
Why?
You shouldn't...
You're kind of cute.
Damn it!
NAM-PAN
Good work.
I'll transfer your money
in a couple of days.
I hope you still remember what you said
about not doing anything violent.
No way!
No matter what, I won't get a divorce.
You!
If you want a divorce,
all assets must be divided in half.
Otherwise, you won't get one.
The only thing that should
be divided in half
is your age.
Then your lust
might need to be divided by four.
Your weight must be divided into eight
and subtracted by a hundred.
You son of a bitch!
Bastard!
You good-for-nothing!
Chunky Pig!
Fat Cow!
-Son of a bitch!
-Chunky Pig!
Madam!
The reporters are here, ma'am.
Okay, ma'am, we need to take some pictures
for the PR.
-Oh, sure.
-Go ahead.
-Come on.
-Here.
-Show some love.
-How?
-We love each other so much.
-We do.
-Yes. We're very much in love.
-Hug.
-Let's hug.
-Hug...
I love you.
Let's make it 70-30.
Again.
No, 50-50.
Just 60-40.
No, 50!
You've got a phone call, ma'am.
Thanks, honey.
Excuse me. I have to answer the phone.
-Honey.
-Yes?
-I'll be right back.
-Okay.
Just a second.
Don't make it too long, honey.
Want a single shot of me?
Well? Did you collect all the payments?
There is one who refused to pay.
But don't worry...
I'll take care of it.
Holy shit!
Fix it without telling anyone.
Hello? Is anyone home?
We are here to collect the debt.
You think he will answer you?
Come on. Get away from me...
before I punch your doggy eyes.
Oh, you're here.
I've been looking for you.
That is my line, isn't it?
Should I remind you what day it is today?
Sir,
can I have two more days?
I'll surely have the money for you.
Mommy!
You are such a pain in the ass.
Don't you remember
what will happen to you
if you don't pay me today?
Hey.
You are mine.
You dare fight back?
Are you afraid?
Scaredy cat.
If you don't pay up
your debt next time,
this bullet
will be...
buried in your brain.
Got that?
Come in, ma'am.
Hungry, my boy?
Have you eaten yet?
-Well...
-I've already fed you. Hungry again?
-You're hungry again?
-Your...
Your dog...
May I?
Let's cut to the chase, ma'am.
Here.
Are you taking your car to the garage?
Yes.
I don't want to wait, it might get rusty.
I want the pictures of him
sleeping next to that slut.
I want their faces to be as clear as day!
Clear enough for me to win
a divorce case in court.
What type of evidence do you want?
Still pictures
or video clips?
I want a clip
showing their movements close-up.
Can you zoom in on their faces
as closely as you can?
I've made countless couples divorce.
And yours...
will be next!
Who is right there?
You're so cute.
What's your name?
Wow! You're wearing a yellow shirt.
Biggy Nose!
JIRA GARAGE
Are you Nam-Pan?
Yes, I am.
Nam-Pan the Pretty Presenter, right?
Are you contacting me for a job?
Well, what stuff do you sell
-I sell...
-besides your body?
Who is this?
You're the one I'm sharing
my husband with.
Let me know when you put
the skin on your face on sale.
I'll be sure to buy it
so I can stitch my shoes with it.
You are a shameless whore.
Stop fucking around with my man!
To be a detective,
you should have
what it takes.
You fat ass!
If you two keep behaving like this,
I'll work alone next time.
Oh, no, Jock.
I'm just kidding.
We're not fighting, right?
Hey.
Well, the spare part you ordered
-Spare part?
-is over there!
Follow me.
-The ones you ordered.
-Oh, the spare part!
You gave my number
to the Inspector's wife?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Stop playing dumb.
Give me the money for the repair now,
or I'll call the cops.
Hey!
-Take it easy. We can talk.
-No!
I want my money right now!
Hold on.
Hello, Mana speaking.
He's leaving the office in 15 minutes.
-Come here immediately!
-Yes, ma'am.
-Take as many shots as you can.
-All right.
I'll capture every position.
Okay. I'll give you
the pictures right away.
I see.
You're a detective for love affairs.
You're a sinner.
Give me a break!
Between you and me,
you are the wicked one!
Where do you think you're going?
Oh, you're trying to run away?
-We need to talk.
-I'm busy.
Hey!
Ouch!
Hey! That's too much!
How am I going to ride this?
Where are you going?
To work. The sinful one, remember?
What about my money?
For God's sake.
You still want it?
How about the cost of my bike repair?
Sure.
I'll pay you to fix your bike.
And you pay me to fix my car.
You're unbelievable. I'm in a hurry. Bye.
"In a hurry"?
What the hell?
What are you doing?
Why did you get in?
Aren't you afraid of me running away?
Let's go together, then.
Don't you get it?
What do you want? I'm leaving.
Where to?
Drive. I'll tell you the directions.
Turn right here. Go straight ahead
past the next two intersections.
Then turn left.
There will be a big building on your left.
Park nearby and keep your lights blinking.
I'm not a cab driver!
Stop bossing me around.
If you want me to take a cab,
just pull over, I'll get off.
I'm not that stupid
to let you go without paying.
Is that all you think about?
So stingy.
Come on! Follow that BMW.
The black one.
Come on!
You're so silly.
Stop it,
Mr. Songpol.
You're always teasing me like this.
Faster. They're over there.
I know!
This is my car.
Stop telling me what to do.
Well...
if you didn't crash my bike into the bush,
I wouldn't ask you for any favors.
I don't know if it's still there.
Slow down or they will see us.
What exactly do you want, fast or slow?
Do you want to drive yourself?
Wait.
Why did you get past them?
I already paid.
What am I waiting for, then?
We are supposed to be following them,
not the other way round.
Got it?
Oh, yes...
To the left lane.
What are you doing?
I'm just going to take their pictures.
Jesus! Where have they gone?
How would I know?
You reached for my boobs.
And you almost touched it.
That's what you're thinking.
Such dirty thoughts!
You jerk!
Hey, where are they?
Which way, left or right?
Left or right?
I'm turning left, then.
There they are.
-Surprise!
-Wow!
Black forest!
Oh, yes!
Are you all right, darling?
Nui Bang Lumpu case closed.
Case closed!
You think he's going to be all right?
You punched him in the eyes.
You were great,
you handed me the camera and saved my ass.
If it wasn't for me,
you would've probably gotten lost
on the expressway.
Luckily,
you turned the correct way.
Otherwise, we would've been flying blind.
There is only one motel in that area.
We should have taken pictures
before they got into the motel.
No way!
Those girls always
hide themselves while entering the motel.
Nam-Pan.
I think that the driver wants
to take a shit.
How do you know?
Look at his license plate.
"Fart 8888."
That jerk is so poor.
"Starve." Nothing to eat,
just one meal a day.
That is a sex bomb's car.
"Boob 36."
That's enormous.
This car's owner
is surely a hen.
KK 0000
BANGKOK
You mean like a hen
that sits on her four eggs?
If the plate gets bigger,
there will be dozens of them.
This one is funny.
His wife might chew him up.
"Wimp."
What's wrong with you?
Excuse me. It's all set.
-It's all set.
-Let me pay.
-How much is it?
-A thousand baht.
What?
A thousand?
I'll pay for you next time.
I'll drive you home.
Where are you going?
Madam,
would you like to test the engine first?
Yes, that's a good idea.
No need to go.
She knows all about it.
Come on. Let's keep on singing.
Let's sing.
Nam-Pan.
This is Rue-Tai and Jack.
Mana, isn't this against the rules?
What rules?
The detective's rules of thumb.
Oh, that's all right. We're off duty now.
Sing for us, Rue-Tai.
Even professional singers
can't beat her, you know?
I believe Thai people can fly!
Hey.
You're off duty now.
And what about her,
what time does she get off?
What are you talking about?
The mistress.
What are their working hours?
Jack, listen!
I think you are drunk.
You'd better go to bed.
You're fooling me.
RUE-TAI KARAOKE
You should leave
I don't want to be like this
And I don't want to be called a bad person
Everything between us is just an illusion
Don't go further than this
Please stop
Come with me, Nam-Pan.
Where to?
Come on.
-Oh! That day...
-Got you!
I know you like them.
I still have a lot more upstairs.
I'll show you.
Come on.
You made them all by yourself?
Come here.
This one...
The pedal-powered massage chair.
An innovative invention
for relieving muscle pain.
When I pedal, the machine
will start to operate.
See?
Now your back pain is gone.
And I get sore legs instead?
No...
You can hand massage your legs.
But you can't reach your back.
Right?
Anyway, our legs don't get sore easily.
Back pain can render people disabled.
It needs to be massaged when it aches.
You can try pedaling.
I mean pedal my bike, not me.
Here...
I proudly present this invention.
Oh, wow!
The great bathing machine.
Be careful.
That's so awesome, Jock!
Hey! Give it a try.
Don't worry, I turned off the tab.
Get in there.
I don't want to get wet.
No. See? Just a few drops.
This is
for washing your hair.
You can try it.
Isn't it cool?
This is for scrubbing your body.
This is for your legs.
Yes, it works!
It can be operated simultaneously.
Hell, no! Stop it.
There.
This machine here,
it's for...
a single man like me
who needs somebody to rub his back.
I think a regular shower is easier, Jock.
Let's go over there.
You're going to like it. The Genius Hand.
Take a look.
Tell me. Where is he?
Or you can do this.
One, two, three.
Or something like this.
Are you mad at me?
Please forgive me?
Or something like this.
What's his name?
I don't know.
It's just a mongrel. Don't touch him.
He's so cute.
The next challenge is...
a bird!
Hey.
Who taught you
how to fold a paper bird like that?
What?
You're helpless.
Or do you just want beer for free?
Are you crazy?
Come on.
Okay.
Let's do this!
The next challenge is...
a chameleon!
Hey!
Who the hell can fold a paper chameleon?
That's cheating.
No, it's a work of art.
It's a giant chameleon,
Godzilla!
Quack!
It's all right if you can't make it.
I can.
Gosh.
You drank the whole bottle.
I will...
let you fold whatever you want
and I'll go down to get more beer.
And then we'll have another round.
See? I'm giving you an advantage.
Good.
A cat.
You can't do it, right?
NAM-PAN
Nam-Pan.
What kind of woman is Nam-Pan?
Just the sound of her name
makes me tingle.
Don't smile.
I can't stand it.
Well, she's kind of cute.
Oh, she has beautiful eyes.
The blush-rose color
with hooks in the back.
B-cup.
Superb!
Pretty and cute.
I'd give her a big kiss on her cheek.
Address confirmed.
The target is with another man.
Isn't being one man's mistress bad enough?
Why are you like this?
Why?
You shouldn't...
You're kind of cute.
Damn it!
One day you will pay the price
for messing with other people's families.
Faking innocence.
You are just a mistress.
Get out!
I'll slap your ear off.
Do you hear me?
Get out!
That almost turned me on.
Hello, Nam-Pan.
Why didn't you wake me up?
You were sleeping.
I didn't want to disturb you.
I'm driving, I can't talk right now.
Okay.
Don't tell me that you...
What's wrong with you?
What's up?
Why are you here?
I...
I forgot.
Can I recall it inside?
Somebody is here.
Go hide.
Where are you going, my bunny?
Take it easy.
Gosh! Your apartment is like a rat hole.
I bump into something every time I move.
How about
I buy you a new house?
A big one with plenty of space.
A big one.
Go play somewhere else.
Come inside the house, love.
What's wrong with you?
Cut the crap!
Hey.
Who the hell are you?
The target is in.
Everything is going according to plan.
I think I'd better go.
Thank you for allowing me to hide here.
Goodbye.
Hey, wait! What is going on here?
Don't panic, sir.
I'm looking for
an international terrorist.
My intel said he is hiding
in the room next door.
Are you an FBI agent?
No. I'm just a private detective.
If there's anything I can help you with,
don't hesitate to call me.
Here.
But for now,
I have to excuse myself
to serve my country.
The door is right there.
What kind of detective is he?
Excuse me.
Can you help me find my contact lens?
Yes?
-Contact lens?
-Yes.
Yes. I don't know where I've dropped it.
-Around here?
-Yes.
Help me look for it on that side.
Sure.
-Hold my camera for a second.
-Okay.
What do you want?
Do you have any enemies?
What enemies?
Come here.
You see that pizza boy?
Yes?
He asked me
about a guy with a receding hairline
and a mole, who looks like a freak
and is wearing a black shirt and khakis.
He told me that
he has been hired
to take pictures
of a man and his mistress.
And the camera he's holding...
Even a retard knows
that it's equipped with a superzoom lens,
the latest model.
It can even capture
a tiny object from afar.
Fuck it!
That fat cow
is really whooping my ass.
Oh, you found it?
Not yet.
What should I do?
I think you'd better get out of sight.
I will lure him the other way.
And you'll go this way.
Okay.
Thanks a lot, man. I appreciate it.
-I found it.
-Oh, you did?
Where did you drop it?
I dropped it over there.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
You are handsome and very kind!
-I get that all the time.
-Yes.
-What room are you delivering this to?
-Room 501.
That room is downstairs.
-Downstairs?
-Yes. I'll take you there.
Thank you.
This was left at your door.
DEAR MANA, YOU DON'T HAVE TO KNOW WHO I AM
I WANT PICTURES OF THE OLD HAG
MAKING OUT WITH HER PIMP
JUST FOLLOW THE MAP I HAVE PROVIDED
HALF OF THE PAYMENT
FINISH THE JOB AND GET THE REST
Jack, I need your help.
CLOSED FOR THE DAY
Rue-Tai didn't pick up the phone.
I'll try again.
Never mind, Jack.
I'm already inside. What's next?
Do you see the target?
Yes, I do. Should I go in now?
Yes.
Don't be afraid, Nam-Pan.
I'm looking out for you.
Are you here alone, miss?
-Yes.
-Do you mind if I join you?
-This way, please.
-Okay.
What would you like to drink?
This way, please.
Shit! Jack...
we have to switch to plan B.
Ready?
Ready.
Let's drink.
No, thank you.
Harder! I like it rough.
Go get your stuff.
All the drinks are on me tonight.
Very good, ma'am.
Come on!
Hey!
Rue-Tai!
You're also here to help me? Oh, thanks!
I just passed by
and saw this nice place.
But I didn't know
it would be this crowded.
I don't like it.
I'll go back with you.
Sorry, my boyfriend is here.
Wow!
That's exactly my type.
Come on!
Come with me.
It's a misunderstanding. He is my husband.
What? Get your hands off him, bitch!
Go back to your farm, you milk cow!
Jock!
Come here. Come with me.
-Come here!
-No, Jock.
Come with me.
Come on! Help me.
I think you have a talent as a detective.
Do you want to be with me?
I mean, join my team.
I know you like doing things in secret.
Being a detective seems more fun
than being a mistress.
So awesome.
That's it for now.
I'll have a watermelon frappe too.
I like frappes, Nam-Pan.
What should I eat first?
Do you want to talk to me, Mr. Sorn?
Sure.
It's about your new house.
We have to make a down payment tomorrow.
I've seen it.
It's as big as a mansion.
Only six million baht.
I'm not sure if you'll like it, Nam-Pan.
Let me have a look at those pictures.
This fat cow!
Shit! I can't believe
she has such bad taste.
You won't even get a penny
after the divorce.
That day will come
when we'll be a happy couple.
Give me a moment.
I will be back to write you a check.
I have to step outside
to attend to some business.
Yes, Adisorn speaking.
-What does this mean, Jock?
-Are you happy now?
Once they get divorced,
you'll become his wife.
That's why you were so willing to help.
Did you enjoy
using me?
You think I'm that wicked?
Thanks a lot.
Why haven't you
eaten anything yet?
Why are you sitting still
and not eating? The food is getting cold.
Here.
Let's eat.
It's good.
Damn!
This Mana has missed so many payments.
Next time,
double the interest for his account...
-Got it, Somsak?
-Yes, madam.
Madam,
you have a phone call.
Thanks.
Hello? Who is this?
Hello, madam.
I've already made
a copy of that CD.
The script is very clear.
All right.
I'll have your money ready.
It all costs 100,000, right?
Well...
it turned out the job was tougher
than expected.
I have to charge you more
because of the risky nature of the job.
How much more?
I'm raising it to 300,000?
If you're okay with that,
the CD and its case are yours.
I won't even give you a single penny,
you crooked detective!
You guys!
Go get the CD from that detective.
Understand?
Yes, madam.
MR. SORN
Where are you, honey?
Have you forgotten about our date?
I've been waiting for you
at the sales office.
I'm so hot and hungry,
and I miss you so much.
You don't want a house anymore?
-No, I don't want it anymore.
-Why?
-Thank you.
-You said you wanted it.
Hello, Nam-Pan.
Are you interested
in a CD of a scandalous pretty girl
and her businessman?
Who are you?
My identity is not important.
The point is...
if you want this CD, follow the map
placed on your wardrobe.
Bring 300,000 in exchange for it.
Come alone. If you try anything funny,
this CD will be sent to your mother.
Can we talk?
This is not funny at all.
Back off! I'm in a hurry.
Give me a second chance.
Not now.
I have a very important thing to do.
Where are you going?
You're not going to tell me?
You're going nowhere, then.
Jock!
Jack! Don't you even care?
She needs our help.
Is it a good idea?
Working for a mistress
is against the rule.
I don't want to do it.
Forget those damn rules.
Listen to me.
You will understand it
when you love someone.
Damn!
You sound like a fucking gentleman!
Cool, man, all right. See you there.
See you.
I'll take you there.
Hello, Nam-Pan.
Did you come alone?
Do you see anyone with me?
James Bond.
It's showtime.
My dog.
Tee, park the humvee here.
Let's go.
Hold on.
If we go this way, he will notice it.
I think we'd better use
the other route.
Follow me.
Please have a seat.
My name is Sutin.
What would you like to drink?
Wine, orange juice,
or bael fruit juice?
-Where is the CD?
-Wow!
Do you have an appointment with your man?
Take it easy.
You'll get it soon.
Where is my 300,000?
Give me the CD
or you'll never get the money.
Tee,
keep a lookout right here.
I think this house is dangerous.
It must be equipped with laser traps.
What should we do, then?
Unzip it.
The zip on your backpack!
What are you doing?
Uploading data.
How did you get in here?
What data?
It's the file we have to give to Madam.
Moron!
There's a copy of it right here.
Well, yes.
We've got company.
Find a place to hide.
Hey! Help me first.
I guess it's on his computer.
It's dark in here. Turn on the flashlight.
Just a second.
-Here you go.
-Who are they?
Gosh.
Damn!
I thought you'd ask a pro to help you.
It's just this useless detective.
Rue-Tai!
What's going on here?
Shit!
VIDEO OF NAM-PAN AND MR. ADISORN
Give that CD to me.
-I have a knife.
-Give it to me.
Can't you just hand it to me?
You can't die. I haven't paid off my debt.
Watch out!
You asshole!
Ouch, boss. That hurt.
Son of a bitch!
You think you're tough?
I got it. Let's get out of here.
Hey!
Why did you do that?
Get in the car!
Hey! Get in.
Get in.
-I can't open it.
-Why not?
The key is with Tee.
And where is Tee?
Tee is with the key.
Wait. Where is James Bond?
James Bond?
Wait!
James Bond.
-James Bond.
Get down here!
Come on! Get in!
Come here!
James Bond.
Good boy, James Bond.
Let's go before they come after us.
-How did you get in here?
-What?
Why are you in our car?
Get the hell out!
Get out!
How the hell did you get in?
Look! He's behind us.
-Hurry up!
-Oh, no!
What do we do now?
-Jock, which way?
-Straight ahead.
Why is he making so many stops?
Bastard!
Why didn't you
drive the humvee?
The key is with you.
Did you think I was going to push it
all the way here?
Tee, here's your knife.
Wow...
Bastard! You think you're tough?
Fuck! He's still alive.
Bastard!
Oh! Hey! Wait for me.
Boss, what's going on there?
Rue-Tai.
Do you really want this CD?
It's because of that fucking CD.
Go to hell, you slut!
James Bond!
James Bond. Hold on.
You're going to be okay.
-Breathe.
-Hold on, sweetie.
Let's go to the hospital.
-Go to the hospital.
-Let's go.
-Just breathe.
-Handcuff him.
Get the gun and take him away.
Let's go.
Get up.
In the end, everything is all right.
AYUDHYA BANK
Come on. Pick it up.
MR. SORN
There is a car
blocking the front door, sir.
All right. I'll check it out.
KRUNGSRI AYUTTHAYA BANK
Do you want to rent a room?
Where is the owner of this room?
She moved out this morning.
She said she was heading back home.
She...
left a lot of things here.
May I have a look inside?
Yes, go ahead.
NAM-PAN
Address confirmed.
The target is with another man.
Isn't being one man's mistress bad enough?
Why are you like this?
Why?
You shouldn't...
You're kind of cute.
Damn it!
One day you will pay the price
for messing with other people's families.
Faking innocence.
You are just a mistress.
I've dreamt of having a house
since I was young.
I can do anything
to fulfill that dream.
I never thought
I would break up other people's families.
Maybe my life being ruined
is the price I have to pay.
This house was Nam-Pan's dream.
I have also designed the house for her.
NAM-PAN'S HOUSE
Take a look!
What do you think?
This is the bedroom.
The roof can also be opened.
She can look at the stars at night.
A living room with a karaoke machine,
so Jack and Rue-Tai can enjoy singing.
Like the other night.
A jasmine garden.
Nam-Pan will like it.
And this house is for you, James Bond.
But I'm not giving it to you for free.
Your job is to be a good guard dog, okay?
James Bond...
Do you think Nam-Pan would
want to stay in this house?
Should I remind you what day it is today?
If you still don't have it,
that's all right.
Take your time.
I'll talk to Madam for you.
Because he was grateful to Jock
for saving his life,
Somsak has changed his attitude.
This is for you, Mr. Jock.
Give it a try.
Rue-Tai
finally got to live her dream.
-Hey!
-I'm sorry.
You can have it. I will...
TO RUE-TAI
FROM PALMY
MR. MANA
Jack has become a professional detective.
Can you handle it?
Yes, of course.
Jack.
Thank you so much.
With such compelling evidence...
Adisorn and Suwimol
decided to get a divorce
and divide the properties in half.
-That's it.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
As for Madam Saowa...
She has finally found a way
to win her husband's heart.
Damn!
They look like shit.
I guess Jock
wants to go back to fix his past.
Let alone a man...
If a dog like me
could choose,
I wouldn't be stupid enough
to act like a hero by blocking the bullet.
Anyway, we can't turn back time.
All we can do is keep moving forward.
Deer, Floating Airport case closed.
Case closed.
Is the built-in furniture
in the kitchen included?
Yes.
It also comes with all the items
in the house.
I like it.
It's near our offices.
Thank you.
Let's take this house.
-I like its design.
-It's up to you, then.
-Do you like it, sweetie?
-Yes, Mom.
Looking for a house?
Don't ever leave me again.
Thank you, Jock.
Subtitle translation by
Thanatcha Saksiamkul