You've had him follow me
since we separated.
Are you a psychopath?
Why are you doing this?
I'm doing all this because I love you.
If I can't be happy, then no one will be.
If I wasn't indecisive,
if I had been firm…
I wouldn't have made the wrong choice.
She didn't really love him.
I'm just a product of their mistake.
Am I supposed to give up
and be a coward like you?
And behave immorally like you?
-I can't do it.
-Tarn!
I already have plenty of friends.
But now,
I want you.
Happy birthday, Nut.
We made you a cake.
What decoration do you want
on your cake this year?
I want a rainbow.
With these colors please, Mom.
That looks hard.
You need to help me then.
All right.
You are a boy.
You shouldn't like pastel rainbows.
It's silly.
You should teach him right from wrong.
Don't spoil him.
Nut.
How about we pick a new pattern?
How about an ocean?
Nut.
What pattern would you like
on your birthday cake?
Anything is fine, Mom.
Can you put a piece in a box for me?
I want my friend to try it.
Sure.
Look at the activities you do.
Don't you know how to do
any manly activities?
It might be almost 20 years late.
But I still want to do this for you.
I may have made mistakes in the past.
But please know that…
you are not one of them.
You are my gift.
Happy birthday.
I'm not too late, am I?
Happy birthday, Nut.
I wish you happiness.
Thank you.
-Sure.
-Let's go inside.
It might seem a little old,
but doesn't it look like
the teddy bear you lost?
Yes, it really does.
I didn't think I would find a teddy bear
similar to your last one.
I was lucky, I guess.
Do you know
that I worked really hard to find it?
I put in a lot of effort.
The same goes for the feelings
that I have for you.
I know
that we haven't known
each other for so long.
It might be too early
for me to be saying this.
But I can't let any more time pass by.
On my first day at work,
you scolded those drunks for me.
You looked so damn cool.
I became your fan after that day.
Although you pretended not to care,
ignored me,
and had that confused look on your face,
your heart was filled with warmth
and I couldn't stop myself
from falling for you.
I didn't know
the best way to confess my feelings,
so I bought you this special gift.
Thank you so much
for this special gift, Prib.
However, no matter how similar
this teddy bear is to my old one,
I can't accept it.
Prib.
You know that I don't feel the same way.
I understand.
I know
that I can't change your mind.
I just wanted to show you
how serious I am about you.
It's okay
if you feel differently.
if you don't love me.
I'm okay.
Prib.
I came to wish you a happy birthday.
I wish you all the happiness in the world.
Even though
I can't be that someone for you,
-we can still--
-Stop.
I know what you are going to say.
You're going to say
that I can be your sister, right?
Can you?
I'm not ready right now.
But I will be.
Prib.
Shall we go home?
It's okay.
I got here on my own.
I can go home alone as well.
I'll be all right.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm okay.
You're not okay.
You're eating barbecue with a teddy bear.
Are you sure you're okay? Are you?
I'm hungry.
And I'm sad.
I saw her holding the teddy bear
and tripping over
in front of the restaurant,
so I called you.
Prib.
What are you going to do
with that teddy bear?
I'm going to donate it.
Nut doesn't want it.
But I'm sure somebody
will want it one day.
All right then.
Cheer up. Somebody will want you
one day too.
Right?
I'm beautiful, kind, and cute.
Plus, I've got time for him.
How can nobody want me?
Why am I so unlucky?
I always end up in the friend zone.
Prib, your soulmate might be a foreigner.
A foreign creature from another world.
Being his friend
is better than being a stranger.
That's right.
You are better off as his friend.
The bond will last longer.
Are you comforting me or rubbing it in?
I'm comforting you.
I love you.
Eat this.
It will keep you quiet.
It's hot.
I love you too, mister.
Wait, what?
What a sneaky little bastard.
Stop.
You can drink,
but don't throw up like last time.
What are you doing, Nut?
Well…
I'm recording this moment like you do.
You're recording it?
Then I should be in it too.
Thank you
for throwing me a birthday party.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Do you like the party
or me?
What a cheap shot.
Well…
I like both of them.
What about the teddy bear?
Did you not like it?
No.
It kind of freaked me out.
How could they look so similar?
But the truth is
their colors,
eyes,
and smells were different.
And most importantly,
it wasn't as warm to hug.
That's why you didn't like it.
Yes.
Despite their similarities,
the teddy bear is irreplaceable.
What if
it's me?
Am I good enough
to replace your teddy bear?
You are you.
You can't replace anyone.
When you asked me what I wanted
for my birthday
and I said nothing,
that's because
I already have you.
Stay by my side…
and don't go anywhere.
What did you do, Tofu?
It's how adults make promises.
I promise
to be with you forever.
In that case…
please stay
with me tonight.
What a wonderful night.
I've become Nut's special someone.
And I'm going back to Nut's room.
Hey.
You weren't sleeping.
I was curious to see
what you were going to do.
Why didn't you wake me up?
Well…
I wanted to stay like this.
Thank you
for coming here.
Thank you for caring about me.
Thank you for everything.
Without you,
I'm not sure
if I would have gotten through it.
Your mom said
love isn't about doing
something for someone.
It's about putting your heart into it.
My heart is all yours.
Yes, I know.
I wish we could stay this way forever.
You smell nice.
So does your hair.
But I think
you stink.
It's your hair.
Smell it.
It doesn't stink.
It stinks.
It doesn't.
Trust me. It stinks.
Go take a shower.
I'll wash your hair for you.
Kuenchai.
Kuenchai, come eat.
I'm leaving, Mom.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Did you forget something?
What?
Your lunchbox.
Thank you.
I'll get going then.
I realized
why people were yearning for love.
Love is a wonderful thing.
It's so wonderful that I don't want
to be a teddy bear again.
Prib, are you heartbroken again?
You're drawing men.
Yes, I'm permanently heartbroken.
Did you confess your feelings to that guy?
Yes, we talked it out.
Are you sad?
It's no use being sad.
I better put my time into something else.
I have an important mission.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to find that person for Tarn.
Perhaps,
I was born for this.
You…
Kuenchai, come and eat.
You already gave him his food.
Did I?
When?
What's wrong, Tofu?
You were happy this morning.
It's Mrs. Na.
Lately,
she has been forgetful.
She forgot that she had fed Kuenchai
this morning.
And this book,
she has been reading the same page.
Maybe it's…
The medicine makes her…
Is everyone okay?
Well…
I'm sorry.
I guess I didn't get enough sleep.
I was going to say
maybe it's a side effect of her medicine.
The medicine makes her drowsy.
I guess so.
By the way,
are you sure you're okay?
I don't know.
I've been feeling sleepy.
I'm sleepy all the time.
Sleepy?
Ms. Sofa.
Mr. Right Slipper.
Can you hear me?
Ms. Sofa and Mr. Right Slipper fell asleep
since the big fight.
I thought they were taking a nap.
But it has been too long.
We don't usually fall asleep
for more than two days
except…
Except what?
Except when we don't ever wake up again.
Don't wake up again?
Have there been pieces of furniture
that fell asleep
and not woken up again?
Of course.
Mr. Sib's chair.
It happened after he died.
Mrs. Na and Nut barely spoke.
The house was quiet,
so were the pieces of furniture in it.
Ms. Sofa and Mr. Right Slipper
might not wake up again.
So, it might happen to me too, right?
What should I do?
Do you want to know
where I got the teddy bear?
Yes.
It's really important to me.
How did you get it?
I drew a sketch of the teddy bear
as you suggested
and posted it on Instagram.
After that, someone messaged me
saying she saw it at a store.
She sent me a photo
and I saw that it looked really similar.
So I reached out to the store's owner.
She said it was still available.
She gave me a special discount
because it was old.
I took the offer without even thinking.
After I transferred the money,
she shipped it.
By the way,
what's the name
of the store?
It's called "Beloved".
It's in an old mall near Nut's house.
That's right.
I was hiding from Nut here.
This is why everything feels
very familiar,
especially
this store.
Have I reached a dead end?
I must have come from this store,
just like the teddy bear Prib bought.
But…
It can't end like this.
BELOVED
The store is closed.
Yes, I heard.
I just called the owner.
She said she got two teddy bears
at the same time.
She sold one of them a long time ago.
I bought the last one.
Do you want one?
No.
Did she say
who bought the first one?
Yes.
She said it was a tall male student.
Could it be the same teddy bear Nut lost?
Yes.
It's the same one.
If I can't find that person,
I might fall asleep like Mr. Sib's chair,
Mr. Right Slipper,
and Ms. Sofa.
What should I do?
I don't want to leave Nut.
Here, boss.
It's lacking something.
I can't think of it.
It's at the tip of my tongue.
Is it character?
Yes, it's lacking character.
We want to set up a scene like this.
This location won't do.
Are there other options?
Yes, there are two more.
Show me.
Hold on. Go back to the second last photo.
Okay.
Yes.
I like it.
It's perfect for the storyline.
Will this place do, Nut?
Nut.
It's perfect for the script.
What do you think?
Nut!
Yes.
I asked, what do you think?
If everyone thinks it's a good location,
we can go with it.
Okay, contact the place
and check the price.
I just got off work.
Let's go out.
What's wrong?
Where are you now?
What?
Where?
What are you doing here?
I came to buy something for your mom,
then I realized that we had chased
each other here before.
Let's go somewhere else.
Nut.
Why didn't you
follow me inside back then?
Did you dislike something inside?
Why are you asking me that now?
Or were you
scared of something?
No.
Get in the car.
If Nut's special someone
bought the bear from that store,
why was Nut hesitant to go inside?
Did something happen in there?
Why didn't you
follow me inside back then?
Did you dislike something inside?
Or were you
scared of something?
Nut.
Nut, hurry up
or we will miss the trailers.
Wait a second.
Let me use the toilet first.
Fine.
It's cute.
It's as warm as a person.
It's warmer to hug a person.
Don't you need the toilet?
The movie is starting.
Let's go.
That scene really impressed me.
-Which scene?
-Take a guess.
-The book opening scene?
-Yes.
When the book was opened
and the music started,
I almost cried.
-Were you sucked in?
-Of course.
That person had a crush
on the other person for a long time
-but they had to say goodbye.
-Nut!
Nut.
You're right.
A lot of things happened there.
My best and worst memories
happened there at one point in my life.
I'll tell you about it
when I'm ready.
You went there with him,
didn't you?
Yes.
Are you jealous?
Can I be jealous?
You don't need my permission
to be jealous.
You shouldn't be jealous.
Right now,
you are my present.
Let's go.
Although Nut hasn't completely opened
his heart to me,
I will keep waiting.
Yes, Mom.
What?
We've run out of it again?
All right, Mom.
Let's go.
These three, please.
Didn't I just buy some last week?
Why have we run out?
Your mom has been feeding Kuenchai
a lot more often.
Some days she feeds him several times.
Nut.
Please send your mother my regards.
-It has been a while.
-I will.
Oh, my…
You're shopping together as a couple.
How adorable.
Who?
You and Tofu.
I mean, who asked you?
Come on, don't be shy. I understand.
The world has changed now.
You haven't changed one bit.
You're as nosy as always.
We aren't strangers.
You're like a nephew to me.
I need to watch over you
on your mom's behalf.
Since your mother is mentally unstable,
she doesn't have enough time.
By the way,
you've been living in that house
for months now.
When are you going to come out?
Does she know the status
Tofu is staying there as?
Her son-in-law or daughter-in-law?
His status in my house
does not concern you.
Don't walk away.
You can't even admit you are gay.
You're running away from the truth
just like your mom.
How are you involved with what happened
to Nut and his mother?
Don't pretend like you don't know.
I do know.
You're nosy because you're jealous
of Nut's mother, right?
Why would I be jealous?
Well, everybody loves her.
This includes Mr. Saen too.
Am I wrong?
Is it because
you are unhappy?
You want other people to be unhappy too.
Am I right?
Tofu.
Let's go home.
Is the food ready?
Wait, Nut.
Why can't we hold hands?
We were holding hands before we saw Jan.
Nut.
I hate being under the spotlight.
I don't want everybody talking.
You saw
what Jan could do just by herself.
What's wrong
with us holding hands,
living together,
and liking each other?
Is it illegal
for two men
to fall in love?
No.
If it's not illegal,
who is our love bothering?
Men are still human.
It's not wrong to fall in love.
I want to know why too.
I'm sorry
for hurting your feelings.
It wasn't your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
I know how you feel.
You're afraid to hurt your mom's feelings
if she finds out about us.
Nut.
It's not wrong to love somebody.
Love isn't at fault here.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I'm going to hold your hand like this…
until you stop brushing it off…
and until you feel comfortable
holding mine.
No matter what happens,
don't let go of my hand.
I'll never let go of your hand.
I promise.
Are you doing laundry?
Yes.
Do you know how?
Let me help you.
It's okay.
I can do it.
Kuenchai.
I'll help you.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
I'm partly the reason
you're doing laundry.
I can't let you do it alone.
We used it together,
so let's wash it together.
Press the button.
You don't even know how to do laundry.
I'm sorry.
-You're sorry?
-Nut.
-Tofu.
Tofu.
I have to shower again.
Ask Kuenchai who started the fight.
-Yes, Juea.
-I need your advice.
Don't ask questions. Come now.
All right.
I'm going to the office.
Okay.
Nut is so cute.
Mr. Rocking Chair.
Ms. Sofa.
Ms. Phone.
Are you still sleeping?
I'm so sleepy.
I don't want to get up.
Ms. Phone.
What are you doing?
It went off.
I was going to charge it.
I've been trying to charge it
since yesterday, but it won't work.
I guess it's broken.
Kuenchai.
He's digging again.
Is it possible
that Ms. Phone fell asleep too?
What about me?
How much time do I have left?
Kids are so rude these days.
Oh, my…
There must be a thunderstorm.
My niece is working early in the morn…
You're not working.
What are you looking at?
Doesn't the guy with the book
seem familiar to you?
No.
Look carefully.
Why do his nails, joints, and finger hair
look familiar to me?
These fingers definitely belong
to a handsome person.
How are the fingers of a handsome man
and an ugly man different?
Well…
This means
I am
really damn handsome.
Seriously?
They are so different.
Your fingers
-are so tanned.
-Prib.
Hey.
Why is he covering his face with a book?
I don't know.
If I run into him,
I'll ask him why he's trying
to hide his face.
Instead of looking at his fingers,
why don't you ask
his friends or relatives?
Is it possible that he's an orphan?
He's an orphan with relatives.
I see.
That's right.
I'll ask his relatives.
Please move.
Aren't you going to work?
Gosh.
-Nut.
-Juea, hello.
Hello.
Can you give me
the location of the school?
And the mall
didn't give us their permission.
-Okay.
-Let's talk inside. Come on.
Wait.
-Juea.
-Hold on.
What are you doing?
All men's hands look the same.
I shouldn't suspect anything.
Come on, Nut.
Okay, Prib. I'll send it to you.
But I don't know how much
he knows about Tatarn.
As far as I know,
their relationship wasn't going well.
It's okay.
It's worth a shot.
Thank you, Mr. Anik.
You're welcome.
Let's go, Dad.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
I've booked us a table.
-Let's go.
-Yes.
Yes, Lieutenant Kong.
What?
You can go to work.
Don't worry about me.
I can go with a friend.
We can go next time.
I'm coming back next week.
Be honest with me.
Are you so involved in this case
because it's Neung's friend?
Mister.
Where are you?
I'm at the hospital.
What happened?
I'm fine.
Song.
Why are you at the hospital then?
I was selling an ad nearby,
so I came to visit my mom.
Is something wrong?
What's with you?
I prepared you very well.
How did this happen?
What did you say to your dad?
He ditched me for work
before I could say anything.
Don't be such a crybaby.
Your dad is a cop.
He had an urgent case.
You've been his son for 18 years.
You should get it by now.
I wouldn't mind
if he went to work on another case.
But the victim
is Neung's friend.
Neung always comes first for him.
That's crazy.
You think too much.
It's true.
Neung was his favorite
ever since I was a baby.
He was handsome, smart, athletic,
into music, popular,
and good at everything.
When Neung died,
Dad's hope died along with him.
I'm just someone
he neglects.
No matter how hard I try,
I can only be Neung's shadow.
All parents
love their children the same way.
That's not true.
Maybe they love their children equally,
but not in the same way.
I'm sorry for eavesdropping.
The conversation happens
to be about family,
so I'm hoping to give you
my opinion as a mother.
Parents can't love
their children the same way
because every child is different.
Some children who can take good care
of themselves
may be neglected by their parents.
But some children
who can't take care of themselves
require more attention from the parents.
Because parents treat them differently,
children tend to think that parents
love their children unequally.
The truth is
they just love and care about
their children in different ways.
That's right.
I express my love
towards my parents differently.
But I love both of them.
I talk to each of them
about certain things.
The fact that your father
gives you freedom
doesn't mean he doesn't love
or care about you.
It's because he trusts you.
Your father has stuff he needs to work on,
but you do too.
You always
compare yourself to your brother.
You want to be as good as him,
so your dad would praise you.
You don't need to be like anyone.
Just be yourself.
You are second to none.
Thank you
for reminding me.
You're welcome.
Can I
hug you?
I don't have a mother to hug.
Of course.
Gen's friends
are like my own children.
That's enough.
You sneaky punk.
He's being protective of me.
Mom, are you not coming home with me?
-I'm not going back to the office.
-I have to meet two more patients.
You can go home first.
I'll see you at home.
I need to check on my patients.
Go home safely, both of you. See you.
Mister, come have dinner with me.
I've booked a table.
Don't you have any friends
other than me?
You are not my friend.
Please, come on. Have dinner with me.
Please.
Where is it?
Wait, mister.
Ms. Phone has fallen asleep
along with Ms. Sofa and Mr. Right Slipper.
Mr. Rocking Chair looks sleepy too.
Am I going to be next?
Maybe
only the furniture downstairs
is falling asleep.
The rest of us upstairs are fine.
But Mr. Right Slipper
followed Mrs. Na around the house.
He still fell asleep.
Teddy goes around the house too,
so he might fall asleep next.
We don't know why the furniture
is falling asleep.
And you don't know how you became a human.
I don't know if those two things
are related,
but you might be the only one
who can find the answer.
If you discover where you came from,
you might find a way to stay awake,
unlike the others.
Did you find any more clues yesterday?
Yes.
Yesterday, Prib said…
She said it was a tall male student.
After he bought me,
he put a bandana on me.
Excuse me.
I'll take these two items
and please swap the bow
for this pink bandana.
Don't you like the bow?
I want it to be special.
Plus, he likes the color pink.
-All right.
-Thank you.
You hid the teddy's scarf
in my room, didn't you?
Didn't you?
I didn't.
It had fallen, so I put it away.
Don't lie!
You were going through my personal stuff!
What do you want?
The scarf. The book.
Still think it's unrelated?
Could it be…
BE WITH YOU
You're home early.
Yes.
I talked to Juea and had a meeting.
I have to write more scenes.
I'm pulling an all-nighter tonight.
He's writing about his life.
Even if it's a little sad,
that's okay,
because I'll add sweetness to his life,
There might be clues
about that man in the screenplay.
Then you should get writing.
What's with you?
You usually tell me to rest.
Well,
finish it so you can rest.
Keep on writing.
I'll give you a massage.
You're being weird today.
I might be weird,
but I look cute every day.
SCENE 14A. BASKETBALL CLUB.
HIGH SCHOOL. DAYTIME (CONTINUED).
The character Kawee
is sensitive,
not talkative,
introverted,
and not athletic.
That must be Nut.
Song
plays Nont,
the popular basketball player
whom Nut had a crush on.
He didn't like Nut back.
He's probably
Neung,
Song's brother.
The character Tonnam
is Nont's best friend.
Wow, that's beautiful.
Thank you.
Tonnam
is a young and confident thinker
who loves to read
and is obsessed with art.
There's only one moon.
Right?
How about I draw another moon?
If you draw another moon,
the first moon will lose its meaning.
TONNAM
Tarn.
Why would you do that?
Why?
-Tarn.
-It's funny.
That hurts.
-My ear hurts.
-Did your ear explode?
This "T" guy
is definitely portrayed by Tonnam.
I need to find the person
the character Tonnam is based on.
BASKETBALL TEAM BATCH 128
What are you doing?
You…
Ma'am.
Are you okay?
Anont.
Are you still wandering here?
You should go to the light.
I'll make merit for you.
-Ma'am, I'm human.
-No…
You've been dead for ten years.
Don't you know?
Sathu.
Ma'am, my name is Tofu, not Anont.
I'm here to shoot the series.
Really?
Are you really human?
Yes.
My heart almost stopped.
Listen.
Peeranut told me
that the script
is based on his experience.
I never thought
he would find an actor
who looked so similar to his senior.
Do you know Nut?
Of course.
Look.
I even know his parents,
let alone him.
I was afraid
his puppy love was going to stop him
from graduating.
Why? What happened?
He got a boyfriend.
Luckily, I stopped him in time.
Do you know his boyfriend?
Look.
I took care of Peeranut
as if he was my own son.
-What was his name?
-I…
He was Anont's best friend.
-His name was--
-Tofu.
You're here.
My goodness.
You interrupted our conversation.
Were you afraid I would say something?
No.
I just hate it when people talk
behind my back,
the way they used to.
Listen.
If that's your way
of calling me a busybody,
you should know that I meant well.
Are you sure
it wasn't for your own benefit?
Peeranut.
If you think badly of my goodwill,
I want you to think again.
You should realize
that you grew up with a good life
because I pulled you back on track.
Yes.
You are partly the reason
my life is like this.
Thank you so much.
Let's go, Tofu.
Nut.
Why did you go back to the club?
I forgot my phone.
What did she say to you?
Nothing much.
She asked why I look like Neung.
Don't listen
to anything she says.
She's a dictator
who thinks she's always right.
Go back to the shoot first.
I'm going to the toilet.
It's okay. I'll ask Song myself.
Sir.
Song told me
he was shooting his series here.
Hey.
Can I ask you something?
Has Song complained
or come to you for advice?
No.
Song is a talented guy.
He's my hero.
If someone were to ask for advice,
it would be me.
Song used to call Neung his hero.
Today, someone who looks like Neung
is calling Song a hero.
It's a little weird to me.
But Song is really my hero.
Think about it.
How can someone be handsome,
hardworking,
smart,
talented,
good at basketball,
and good at riding a bike?
He's good at everything.
Is that so?
You might not realize how talented Song is
because you're busy
thinking about your dead child.
Maybe you're neglecting
the child you have left.
What part of your life
don't I take an interest in?
There's a lot.
You don't remember the food I like.
You don't even remember my birthday.
I wasn't the one who gave birth to you.
But you always remember Neung's birthday.
Even after he passed away,
you still remember.
Song never told me anything.
He's a strong person.
But every strong person
can get weak sometimes.
I'm a terrible father.
No.
No one's perfect.
And it's not wrong
to mourn and miss your dead child.
However, you can't neglect
the child you have left.
To be forgotten while you are still alive
hurts more than being separated by death.
Thank you.
Study hard and take care of the club.
Put this on me.
Now, we have one each.
That's it for today.
-Thank you so much.
-The shoot is over.
I said, the shoot is over.
Girls, the shoot is over.
Congratulations.
The shoot will be done soon.
Does this mean I won't see you anymore?
Yes.
We're going separate ways.
Can I live at your house then?
My dad will ask for your hand.
Jeez, as soon as your stress goes away,
you're here to annoy me.
Have you talked to him?
Not yet.
What are you waiting for?
Shall I talk to him?
How will you introduce yourself to him?
Well…
I'll say I'm a senior who pities you.
Have you heard of the phrase
"Pity is the foundation of love"?
No.
I've only heard of sympathy.
I wasn't expecting you.
I came to support you.
You've invited me many times,
but I never came.
You didn't tell me
it was a love story.
You don't mind, do you?
Of course not.
It's just acting.
You're not really gay.
Are you?
Song.
I'm sorry.
I keep breaking my promises.
I flew here as soon as I finished working.
Dad, don't worry.
I know you are busy.
Song.
I'm not working hard
because the victim is Neung's friend.
I would do the same with any case.
I'm sorry
if I hurt your feelings.
In the past,
I've neglected you
because I knew you could
take care of yourself.
But the truth is, deep down,
you're still a puppy
who needs his daddy, aren't you?
I will try
to be here for you more.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault
for never telling you how I feel.
We are going
to be honest with each other
to avoid any misunderstandings
in the future.
We only have each other.
You are my life and soul.
I love you.
I love you too.
Come on.
Let's give them some privacy.
Tofu.
Go get changed.
I'll wait in the car.
Okay.
Sometimes,
we forget that we are still breathing.
But it doesn't mean
that breathing isn't important,
does it?
Do you want to be gay?
Don't you want to be a man?
Are you and Nut in love?
Yes.
You can hate me all you want.
But I will never be who you want me to be.
Did your ex-boyfriend traumatize you
from dating a younger man?
Not all younger men are the same.
Don't generalize us.
Don't you have confidence in me
when I'm with you at all?
Subtitle translation by:
Pet-chompoo Sa-ngarmangkang