Ha ha ha ha!
Helga: When your father
was a boy like you
and living with me
here in Norway,
I told him
about witches, too,
so that he would
always be aware.
Now, the most
important thing
you should know about
real witches is this--
now listen
very carefully--
real witches dress
in ordinary clothes
and look very much
like ordinary women.
They live
in ordinary houses,
and they work
in ordinary jobs.
Every country
in the world has witches.
And there is a leader,
a high witch
of each country.
And the ruler
of all the witches
is the most evil woman
in creation--
the grand high witch...
Herself.
Witches spend their time
plotting to kill children,
stalking
the wretched child
like a hunter stalks
a bird in the forest.
Did they hunt you?
You said
it was an accident.
A very unpleasant
accident.
You know,
when I was younger,
I traveled the world in search
for the grand high witch,
but I never found her.
I don't really believe
that anyone
has ever found her.
So if no one's seen
the grand high witch,
how are you sure
she exists?
Nobody's ever seen
the devil,
but we know he exists,
don't we?
Yeah.
For all you know,
a witch might be living
next-door to you.
When I was little,
I lived beside a girl
called Erica,
who was taken
by a witch.
Erica had very
strict parents.
But even that
didn't save poor Erica,
because when a witch
chooses a victim,
there is only
one hope of escape--
knowing everything
about them
that I am telling you.
I'm warning you.
Erica. Come in.
What makes her
dangerous
is the fact that she
doesn't look dangerous.
You can never be sure
if it's a witch
you are looking at
or a kind lady.
[Ribbet ribbet]
Ah, Erica.
How do you like
my new painting?
It's magnifique,
papa.
Go to Larsen's
and buy...
A liter of milk.
Hmm?
Ja, papa.
Come straight home.
Ja, da.
Real witches
hate children.
are quite bald,
although, of course,
they wear wigs...
That itch...
And cause them
scalp rash.
Do you know
what scalp rash is?
No.
Itching under the wig.
It must drive them crazy.
They look quite hideous
behind their human
face masks
and can only be distinguished
from ordinary women
if you are sharp enough
to spot the purple tinge
to their eyes.
Real witches
have no toes.
Their feet
have square ends,
revolting stumps where
their toes should be,
so they never wear
pointed or pretty shoes--
just plain,
sensible shoes.
Remember these things.
Perhaps if Erica
had known them...
[Cat screeches]
Ha ha!
Helga: Oh, my poor Erica.
For weeks
they searched,
but witches
don't murder children
with knives or guns.
That's for people
who get caught,
and witches
never get caught.
They searched
for miles around.
Everyone in the town
searched,
but she had completely
disappeared.
I was there in Erica's house
six weeks later.
Good day,
frau Larsen.
Come in, Helga.
Have some cake.
Helga: I was her best friend
when it all happened.
Then that day,
while Erica's mother
was pouring the coffee,
her father came
walking towards us.
It was as though
he had seen a ghost.
His face
was all twisted up
as he walked towards
the painting behind me.
There, as if it
always had been there,
was Erica,
locked in the painting,
gazing at us.
Papa.
I don't believe it.
You saw her in
the painting, grandma?
Many times.
But the peculiar thing
was that little Erica kept on
changing her position
in the picture.
So one day she'd be
feeding the ducks,
the next day she'd be
inside the farmhouse,
looking out of a window.
Did you see her
moving in the picture?
Nobody did.
She was always
just a figure
motionless
in the painting.
As the years went by,
Erica grew older,
too.
And only
five or six years ago,
the old woman
that Erica had become,
bent and frail
in the painting,
began to disappear...
Until one morning,
she was gone.
You mean she died?
Who knows?
Mysterious things go on
in the world of witches.
Hey,
it's almost 9:00.
Grandma's been tellin'
me about witches, mom.
And frightening you before
you're supposed to go to sleep.
Good night,
darling.
Everything all right,
mother?
Helga:
Very all right.
Go off. Enjoy
yourselves.
Good-bye,
mom.
Here you go.
Good night, son.
Good night, dad.
No more stories, ok?
Oh, no.
Come on, grandma.
Just one more story.
All right, then.
One more.
But very short.
Witches...
Are very cruel.
And they have a highly-developed
sense of smell.
A real witch could smell you
across the street
on a pitch-black night.
She couldn't smell me.
I just had a shower.
Oh, yes, she could.
The cleaner you are,
the more a witch
can smell you.
That doesn't make sense.
Oh, yes, it does.
A dirty child,
it's the dirt she smells.
A clean child,
it is the child.
Wow.
I'll never have
a shower again,
and I'll have you
for an excuse.
Well, just not too often.
Only once a month
is probably safe.
So a witch could
smell me right now?
To me, you smell
of raspberries and cream,
but to a witch,
you would smell
absolutely disgusting.
What kind
of disgusting?
Like dogs' droppings.
I don't believe it.
You don't believe it?
What's more, to a witch,
you would smell
of fresh dogs' droppings.
That's not true.
There's no point
in arguing.
It's a fact of life.
So if you ever see
a woman in the street
holding her nose
as she passes you,
she could easily
be a witch.
And now it is
definitely bedtime.
Good night, grandma.
Mmm...
Mmm! [Chuckles]
[Blowing a kiss]
Mom?
Dad?
Frau evershim, could i
come in for a minute?
I'm afraid
i have some bad news.
Ja, come in.
Wait here.
[Sobbing]
Come on.
Come here to me.
Let's cuddle up
here.
Sit on my lap,
all right?
There.
[Changing stations]
Shall we bring them
to england?
Yeah.
Ja, we'll do that.
I think
they're very good.
I really do.
Quite a talent there
which I didn't know
anything about.
Thanks.
[Tuning through stations]
Helga:
After the accident,
I didn't take Luke
back to America right away.
We went to england,
where I had a house,
and he started
at the school
his mother and father had
chosen for him before they...
Bald?
That's why
they wear wigs.
...before they came to me
on their vacation.
They itch
and scratch a lot.
I saw a woman yesterday
with purple eyes.
[Bell rings]
[Sniffing]
Mmm.
Unh.
Hello, young man.
What a magnificent
tree house.
Did you build it
yourself?
My dad and I did.
I've got something
for you here...
Something I think
you'll like.
[Gasps]
Jump down,
and I'll show you.
No!
What?
No, thank you
very much.
It's worth
a lot of money.
This is
private property.
There's nothing
to be frightened of.
I just wanted
to give you this.
[Gasp]
I found him
on my walk.
He's quite harmless.
See?
Little boys
love snakes.
Here, he's yours.
Grandma! Grandma!
I'll leave him here
if you like.
Then you can come
down on your own
and get him. Hmm?
But they wriggle away
quite quickly,
unless you tell them
not to.
Grandma!
Perhaps you'd like
some chocolate instead?
Grandma!
She can't hear you.
What's your name?
Is it...
Luke?
[Gasps]
Thought so.
Here you are...
Luke.
A big bar
of chocolate.
If you c--
Helga: Luke.
Luke, it's dinnertime.
Luke!
Luke, dinnertime.
[Hissing]
Grandma,
did you see her?
Yes.
I think she was a witch.
Gloves, purple eyes.
She wanted me to climb
down from the tree, and
she hypnotized a snake
she wanted to give me.
A real one?
A real snake, yes!
[Chuckles malevolently]
I swear.
Yes, Luke.
I believe you.
Ha ha ha ha!
[Thunder]
Close your eyes.
No cheating.
To your chair.
There we are.
¶ Happy birthday
to you ¶
¶ happy birthday
¶ happy birthday,
dear Luke ¶
¶ happy birthday
to you ¶
there.
Oh, grandma!
They're great!
I'll build them
a whole circus,
teach them tricks
and acrobatics
and stuff.
It must be so neat
being a mouse.
Just play all day
and eat, and then
play some more.
I'm gonna rig up
a whole room
with ramps and--
grandma!
Grandma!
Your granny has a very
mild case of diabetes.
It's nothing
to worry about.
Have a good rest,
now,
and in a couple of days,
you'll be right as rain.
You're gonna
be better.
Good.
I'm putting you
on a sugar-free diet.
No cakes, candies,
or sugar at all.
Those cigars won't
do you any good.
See?
And there are
some more pills to take.
With that and a good
holiday by the seaside,
you'll be good as new.
Come on, young man.
Leave your granny
to get some rest.
Perhaps you can bring her
breakfast in bed in the morning.
By tomorrow afternoon,
you can boss her around
like before.
Bye-bye,
Mrs. evershim.
Bye-bye.
See you
in a couple of days.
Good-bye,
doctor.
Can you find
your way?
Yes.
How come doctors
speak to everybody
like they're babies?
I know.
I'm sorry for spoiling
your birthday for you
and for giving you
a fright.
Is it all right
if I play with
William and Mary now?
Yes, of course.
[Squeak squeak]
Listen, Mary mouse,
when grandma gets better,
we're goin' with her
to a hotel by the ocean.
You've never been
to the ocean.
I'll tell you, it's big.
Ha ha ha ha!
Wow! Look
at the hotel, grandma.
It's not half bad.
Welcome, madam.
Thank you very much.
I think it'll be
a nice day, yes?
Can you manage,
Luke?
Yeah.
Yes.
Luke...
Come on.
There we go.
Oh, welcome,
miss Ernst.
Nicola Cole.
I've been so
looking forward
to meeting you.
You look
marvelous.
Wish I could say
the same for you.
Ah, miss Ernst.
I am the owner
of the hotel.
We're very happy
to have you.
Delighted. Shall I sign
or something?
No. Everything
will be fine.
This is my secretary.
Oh, yes.
How are you?
Ah, ladies.
Ina Clay
Beckman.
Indeed.
Julia Whitman.
Julia, yes.
Where are you from?
Dallinger.
Ah, yes.
Lois leffour
from southampton.
Lois.
[Excitedly]
Ohh! Ohh!
In there, I think.
That's where
you must live.
Oh, um, the carpetbag
on the bed, please.
I'll have
a wash and brush-up
while you explore
the place, Luke.
And then we shall
have tea together,
and you'll show me
around, yes?
Thank you.
Don't
lock me out.
I promise I won't.
Hmph.
You look wonderful,
miss Ernst.
Oh, we are looking forward
to this afternoon!
Mmm.
Allez.
What are you doin'?
Oh! The raisins
are all around
the edge of these cakes.
They're really good!
Thanks.
My name's Luke.
Bruno Jenkins.
The cucumber sandwiches
are all right, too--
except when they use
margarine instead of butter.
How much pocket money
do you get?
My dad's rich,
but he's very tight.
We've got three cars.
Hello, boys.
I hope there's butter
in the sandwiches today.
I really do
hate margarine.
Ah, you've got those
excellent cakes again.
There should be
14 of--
aah! Aah!
Mr. stringer!
Oh! Oh!
Shh, shh.
What happened?
I went in
to turn down the bed,
and they were there.
What?
White and disgusting
little--
now, look. Calm down.
[Sobs]
[Knock on door]
Is this your room?
Yes.
Yes?
I see.
I'm sorry, madam,
but I cannot permit
mice in my hotel.
How dare you
say that
when your rotten hotel
is full of rats anyway?
Rats? There are no
rats in this hotel.
I saw one
this morning
running along the corridor
into the kitchens.
Madam, you only
arrived in the hotel
this afternoon.
Ahh, morning,
afternoon.
I saw a rat
in your hotel,
and if matters
do not improve,
I'll shall have to
report you
to the public
health authorities.
Look...
Madam,
I'm not prepared--
the cakes
in the lounge
are nibbled
around the edges, too.
I can show you.
Helga: If you are not
careful, the health people
will order the whole hotel
closed before everyone gets
typhoid fever.
You can't be
serious, madam.
I have never been
more serious in my life.
Now, will you or will you
not let my grandchild
keep his hygienic and
perfectly harmless pet mice?
Uh...Well...
Well, if they are
kept in the cage
and only
in this room,
nowhere else
in the hotel...
Agreed.
Very well.
Grandma, I can't
train my mice
if they're
in a cage.
Nibbled cakes, indeed.
There were, only it was
a boy called Bruno Jenkins.
I'm teaching
William and Mary
how to be
tightrope walkers.
Mm-hmm!
I brought some of the circus
I'm building with me.
Good. Show me.
Let's see.
Look. I'm planning
them a major house.
Rampways here.
A bathtub.
This elevator's
pretty neat.
You really did this
yourself? It's good.
It's really good.
I'm impressed.
Of course you must
train your mice,
but you must not
get caught,
and you must not
do it in here,
'cause if that hysterical
maid comes back...
Well, now it's teatime.
I just love
English hotel teas.
Cream cakes
and shortbread
and, uh--
no, grandma.
No cream cakes.
No shortbread,
either.
It's full of sugar.
I shall end up eating
the same diet
as your mice.
That's the trouble
with this country.
A queue for everything.
They wouldn't think
to have two tea trolleys.
That'd be too convenient
for the paying guests.
They'll want
two lumps of ice
in their whiskey
next. Ha ha ha!
They'd queue for their own
funerals if they could.
I know that woman
from somewhere,
but I can't for the life
of me remember where.
Her face
is so familiar.
Which one?
My memory's going.
But it's as if
i met her before.
She's probably
on TV or something.
Mmm. Cucumber
sandwiches.
Mmm--
fish paste.
Luke: Grandma,
you got the wrong one.
Oh, no. Sugar.
Grandma,
sugar can kill you.
I know, but
it was very little,
very little,
my dear.
Something very odd
is going on.
Are you listening to me?
You'll have some fresh air
if I have to take you
out by your ear.
We didn't come here
for you to sit eating
and watching telly
all day.
Look at
the lovely sunshine.
All the other boys are out
there playing in the water.
Pick up
your knife.
Just like your father.
Good afternoon,
madam.
Go on.
You're sure you're
all right now?
Yes, yes.
Fine, fine.
And what are you
going to do now?
I'm going to take
William and Mary
and explore
this place.
All right. Just don't get
into trouble, will you?
I won't.
Come on.
Excuse me, please.
All right,
that's fine.
Carry on with
the rest of them.
No, in the kitchen.
In the kitchen.
[Door hinges squeak]
[Mouse squeaks]
Wait there.
Ohh...
[Squeak squeak
squeak squeak]
Great.
Now do it again.
[Squeak squeak squeak]
Come on, come on.
I'm sure your delegates
will be comfortable in here.
If there's anything
we can do,
obviously, please
don't hesitate to...
Nicola,
down in front!
To let me know.
Now, drinks will be served
on the terrace after...
Fine, fine, fine.
You've concluded
your meeting.
Um, skies are clearing...
Come on, ladies.
Sit.
Sit down.
And we've prepared
a fine meal for you tonight.
The chef's special soup...
[Indistinct chatter]
Hey! Look at her eyes.
Then lamb and
fresh raspberries.
Well, I'll
leave you to it.
Fine. Thank you.
Everybody sitting?
Up front, sit down!
Not...Yet!
We gotta get
out of here.
Come along, ladies.
When you're ready,
we can start.
Thank you very much
for letting me stay.
That's all right,
Elsie.
I'll lock up.
Oh. Right. Ok.
Ernst: Then we'll begin.
You may remove
your shoes.
[Woman sighs with relief]
You may remove
your wigs.
The doors. Are they
locked and bolted?
Locked and bolted,
your grandness.
Good.
Help me.
No, no!
Wow.
Witches of england...
You're a disgrace!
Miserable witches.
You're good-for-nothing
worms!
Everywhere I look...
I see
the repulsive sight
of hundreds...
Thousands...
Of revolting
little children.
I ask you...
Why?
One child a week
is no good to me!
We will do better.
We will do
much better.
Huh. Better
is no good, either!
I demand
maximum results.
So...
Here are my orders.
My orders are
that every child
in england
shall be rubbed out.
Destroyed!
Every single child
eliminated!
Ohhh!
Do I make myself
clear?
Yes.
[Cough cough]
We can't possibly
wipe out all of them.
Who spoke?
Who dares
to argue with me?
It was you?
I didn't mean to argue,
your grandness.
You dare to argue
with me?
No. No, honestly.
It just was a--
a stupid witch
who answers back
must burn until
her bones are black!
No! No!
A foolish witch
without a brain...
Must sizzle
into fiery flame!
A witch who dares
to say I'm wrong...
Will not be with us
very long!
Aah!
What the devil?!
I hope nobody else
is going to make me
cross today.
No.
So...
Now, this
is my plan.
Each of you
will go back
to your homes
and resign
from your jobs.
Give notice.
Retire.
Retire?
You will then buy
with the money
i give you
sweet shops...
Candy stores...
The very best
and most respectable
sweet shops in england.
Ha ha ha ha!
Ah!
Oh!
Upstairs I have a trunkload
of this English money,
so you'll be able
to offer
three, maybe four times
what these shops are worth.
Go, go.
On a certain day,
when all our plans
are prepared,
you'll announce
a great gala opening
with free sweets,
candies, and chocolates
for every child.
Poisoned sweets.
We'll wipe them out
like weasels.
Who spoke?
She did!
It's brilliant.
Poison?
And you don't mind
getting caught?
Exposed?
Vilified?
Well,
i just thought--
brainless bumpkin!
You blithering
bogvumper!
No wonder england
is swarming with--
[gulp]
Everything you sell
that day
will have been treated
with my very latest
and very greatest
magic formula.
¶ Witches work
only with magic ¶
[squeak squeak]
Hey, wait. Come here.
William. Mary.
Formula 86.
My greatest triumph.
A work of...
Genius.
Formula 86!
In this bottle,
500 doses
with a delay mechanism
that prevents it from
working until two hours
after it has been taken.
Ha ha ha ha.
What does it do...
Genius one?
Yes?
What?
[Excited indistinct chatter]
One dose, and the time
works to the second.
But more
than five doses
breaks
the delay barrier,
and the formula
works instantly.
The child...
Starts to shrink.
Shrink?
Ha ha ha
ha ha ha.
The child...
Starts to...
Grow fur.
Fur?
Starts...
Growing a tail.
A tail?
All this happens
in precisely 25 seconds!
Shrinking
more.
The child is
no longer a child.
Heh heh heh
heh heh heh.
Ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha!
The child...
Is a mouse!
Ha ha ha ha!
Silence. Silence.
Shut up. Shut up.
Silence.
Enough.
This afternoon,
at precisely 4:15,
I put one dose
of my formula
on a bar
of chocolate.
I gave it to
a repulsive, smelly boy
who was in the lobby.
[Excited giggling]
"Was that good?"
I asked him.
[English accent]
"Got any more?"
Said the nauseating child.
"Six more bars
like that one,"
I told him.
Ha ha ha
ha ha ha!
In two minutes' time,
this appalling,
foul-smelling creature
is coming to collect
his reward.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
In five minutes' time,
you'll see my magic
formula in action.
We're going to see.
Quickly!
Wigs! Gloves!
The appalling child
will be here...
And you'll see
my miracle.
Come on. Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Come on. That's good.
Hurry up, everybody.
Come on!
Quickly! Quickly!
You're not on holiday!
I'm being as quick
as I can.
Hurry up!
Ready.
Hello, little boy.
Come on in, then.
Come on.
Wait just there.
One moment.
[Locks door]
Now, what's
your name, then?
Br--Bruno.
Ooh!
Madam.
Madam!
That lady promised me
six whole bars
of cream-whip hazelnut
milk chocolate.
I've come
to collect.
Ladies...
May I introduce Bruno?
Come up, Bruno.
I have
the chocolate here.
I said 6:15...
And that is
in 15 seconds from now.
[Laughing
with the witches]
You are in for a treat.
Ha ha ha!
We all are!
What's going
on?
Just a few moments.
5...
I can't see
any chocolates.
3...
2...
1...
0!
Ooh!
Uhh!
[Burp]
We have ignition!
Everybody, look!
It's fantastic!
It's begun!
I can't stand it,
it's so wonderful!
Look at you!
It's fantastic!
Squeak squeak.
[Squeak squeak]
[Burp]
Where'd he go?
Bravo!
Keys.
Keys!
Enough!
Silence!
Before the banquet
tonight,
you'll come to my room
in groups of 10.
Room number 208.
I will give you each a bottle
containing 500 doses.
Also plenty of money.
Do not forget your
nose plugs for the dinner.
The dining room will
be full of filthy children,
and without
your nose plugs,
the stink will be
unbearable.
Now we will have drinks
on the terrace
with that ridiculous
manager.
Are there any questions?
What if one of the
chocolates we give away
were accidentally
eaten by a grownup?
Ha ha.
Then that's just too bad
for the grownup.
The meeting is over.
Until next year.
Wait!
[Sniff sniff]
I smell...
Dogs' droppings.
Ohh!
What?
She's right.
Oh! The smell!
Ooh! Yuck!
This really
does smell.
She's right!
Search out this small
lump of dung!
Find it!
It must be exterminated
immediately!
There he is!
He's wiggling through!
He's getting away!
Come here, boy.
Bring him to me!
Aah!
There he is!
Stop him!
[Moaning]
I saw him come
this way.
Yes.
Where could he be?
[Gasps]
Bye-bye.
Ha ha ha ha!
Mother:
Aah! Oh, no!
No! My baby!
Stop! Stop!
Oh! My baby!
A baby in a pram.
Oh, oh.
[Crying]
Lovely! Ha ha ha ha!
Oh, no.
Get the boy.
He's getting away.
[Breathing hard]
Grandma!
Grandma, wake up!
Oh, please, grandma!
My grandma!
An old adversary,
i have discovered.
Very old.
If you hurt
my grandma--
silence!
We got him,
madam.
madam. Oh!
Don't bite.
Open up.
500 doses.
Ha ha ha ha!
Come along.
Come on.
Get up. Get up.
Come on. Come on.
Ha ha ha
ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
Look.
This stinking
little carbuncle
has had 500 doses.
We are having
instantaneous action.
Ohh...
Bye.
[Laughter]
Kill him. Ha ha!
Kill him!
Ha ha ha ha!
[Gasps]
Ha ha ha ha...
Leave that little stinkpot!
It's not worth
bothering about.
Come. Some whiskey
and champagne to celebrate.
Bruno?
I don't believe it.
I can talk.
Bruno?
Bruno: Who's that?
Bruno, it's me--
Luke.
I'm down here.
Where? I can't see you.
Down here.
You can talk, too.
This is weird.
This icing
is terrific.
Are you ok?
They didn't give me
the six bars of
chocolate they promised.
You couldn't eat six bars of
candy now that you're a mouse.
Don't be stupid.
I'm not a...
Now, just because
you're a...
That doesn't mean
that I'm a, uh...
Good lord.
Hmm. Hmm.
Well, I'm not too keen
on being a mouse.
We've got to find
a way out.
How long before we change
back, do you think?
I don't think
we will.
Of course we will.
We've gotta get upstairs
and wake my grandma.
I'm real worried
about her.
I mean, maybe
it was the witch...
Or maybe it was
her diabetes.
I only know she didn't
wake up when i--
she's got
some peanuts, too.
Mmm. Dry roasted?
Mm-hmm.
Oh. All right.
Come on.
[Gasps]
William and Mary!
Hi. It's me--Luke.
Are you two all right?
Crikey! Did they eat
the chocolates as well?
They were
my pet mice.
But I guess they can't
talk like we can.
Catch you two later.
[Squeak squeak]
Hmm.
Come on, Bruno.
This way.
Ohh.
Luke?
Hmm.
They're gone.
It's all clear,
Bruno.
Come on.
Unmmh! Unh!
Wait for me.
Unh...Unh...Unh.
Running...
Running on a full stomach
isn't good for you.
Better than
being caught.
Keep up, Bruno.
Sports give me
indigestion.
Umhh!
[Gasps]
Get back.
Ok, Bruno,
when I say go, go!
Go!
Run!
Wait.
Follow me.
Aah!
Uhh!
How are we gonna
get upstairs?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what
I'm paying for.
I really don't.
An over-heated room...
Dad? Hey!
There's my dad!
Shh! He doesn't know
what's happened.
He'll kill you.
Come on!
My own father?
Whoever took the photos
in that brochure
should be arrested
for fraud.
I'm going to tell him.
He'll put
a stop to it.
No. Not now.
Trust me, Bruno,
please.
He'll stamp on you
the moment he sees you.
It's so nice not having
the kids around.
Bruno: I smell food.
Is there anything
in this bag?
They'll be fine.
I think John
was getting a cold.
Look, it's always
the same. You must
relax once in a while.
Oh, all right.
[Elevator bell
rings]
This is it.
Let's go.
Oh, no more sports.
Hurry!
Faster. Faster!
Ooh!
Ouch!
I forgot my tail.
Ooh. Ohh.
Keep to the side,
Bruno.
You know,
being like this
might not be so bad.
There won't be any more
school from now on.
That would be
all right.
Hey, look at that.
Don't eat
the cheese, Bruno.
Remember, from now on,
we've got two enemies--
humans and cats.
Yikes! We've got
three cats at home.
They'll have to go.
My mother loves them,
but she's terrified of mice.
Grandma!
[Door opens]
Take your afternoon
off tomorrow.
Oh. Sorry.
Come on, Bruno,
let's go.
What? Hey, wait!
There are four more
floors to be done.
Yes, sir.
You do over there.
No. I'll get this one.
Shh. Back.
Aah! Aah!
It bit me!
What bit you?
A mouse
in the towel.
A mouse?
Oh, no.
Is she sober?
Yes, of course
she's sober.
I've been with her
all aftern--
uh, i--i--i, uh...
I saw her...
Yes, she's sober.
Don't be stupid.
Go and do
the second floor.
Grandma!
Here by the phone.
It's me--Luke.
Are you all right?
Luke?
It's me,
grandma.
Luke!
It was the grand
high witch.
She's in this hotel!
Oh, my god!
Don't cry, grandma.
It's ok.
Things could
have been worse.
I got away
from 'em.
I'm still alive.
Oh, my darling Luke.
What have they
done to you?
They turned me
into a mouse.
Oh, I'm...I'm sorry.
I can't stop shaking.
The grand high witch--
here?
There's hundreds
of them...
Right here
in this hotel.
I knew it.
I could see it
in her eyes.
Oh, lord.
Uhh. Uhh.
You squashed me.
Huh?
Grandma, this is
Bruno Jenkins.
He said you've got
dry roast peanuts.
Yes. Oh, yes.
Oh, good.
Thanks.
We've gotta stop them,
grandma.
They leave tomorrow
with a bundle of money
and gallons
a formula
that'll change
every kid in england
into a mouse.
We must stop them.
Miss Ernst.
Lois.
Nice to see a bit of
international clientele.
How do you do?
Just flew in,
did you?
What?
Jet lag's the curse
of the business classes.
Hope you don't mind
me joining you.
You're most welcome, sir.
Herbert Jenkins.
I'd like
to say hello
to a fellow
philanthropist.
You collect stamps?
Charities.
This rspcc.
What is this rsp--
cruelty to children!
Oh, of course.
You give money
for the little...
Children.
And...
We, of course,
we also give money
for the little...
[Money dropping
in bowl]
I see you're holding
your annual meeting.
Funny enough,
I recently addressed
the last annual meeting
of our rotary club.
I wonder
if you know much
about the rotary club
organization
in this country?
Luke: I can get the formula
into their food.
You just have to get me down
to the grand high witch's room.
Grandma, I'm ready.
I don't know.
I've gotta find
the formula, grandma.
No. This is
too dangerous.
Grandma!
It's not far down,
grandma.
You're asking me
to lower you
into the jaws of death.
You two can't take on
the grand high witch.
Yes, we can.
We've got to.
No one else is
going to believe us.
Quick, before
she comes back.
Luke...
Luke, be careful.
Please be careful.
I'll be careful.
Don't worry.
Not so fast.
Be careful.
I will, I will.
[Snarling]
Oh, no.
Grandma!
Luke, what happened?
Are you all right?
Luke. Why don't
you answer?
[Snarling]
Down, cat.
No, cat.
Grandma! Help!
Ohh...
Down, cat!
Oh, no. Go, cat.
Luke!
Grandma!
Get away.
Help! Help!
Get him away, grandma!
Help, grandma!
Grandma, help!
Help me, grandma!
Puss!
Grandma, come on!
Do something,
grandma!
Get it.
Get it, cat.
Cat. Cat. Puss. Puss.
Come here. Get it.
Luke!
Keep him there,
grandma.
Come on,
you little kitten.
Come on, pussy.
Keep him busy.
Here. Take it.
Helga: Ah, come on.
Come on.
Take it,
you silly cat.
Don't let him in,
grandma.
Puss. Puss, puss.
Here. Here.
Whoa!
Hang on, tail.
Whew.
Come on, formula.
Where are you?
Come on, come on.
Oh, no.
Whoa!
[Gasps]
Oh, no.
It has been unforgettable,
Mr. Jenkins.
My pleasure, madam.
What a stimulating
conversation it has been.
It's not every day
one meets a lady
of such quality
and...And compassion.
Whoa!
[Telephone rings]
[Ring ring]
[Cat growls]
It's gotta be
somewhere up here.
It's just gotta be.
[Ring ring]
[Cat screeches]
Whoa! Ohh!
Ow!
Oh, man.
Hey!
We've got it, grandma.
[Cat screeches]
Irvine: Did you realize
that was Bruno's father?
Ernst: What a nasty man.
It's an act of mercy
on my part.
Uh-oh.
The child will never grow up
to be like the father.
Umhh!
Thanks.
Liebchen?
Pshh! Pshh! Pshh! Pshh!
Lipshin?
Liebchen?
Liebchen.
Was ist das?
Oh. I--I'm so sorry.
I--i dropped my knitting.
You!
I'm...I--I'm, uh, knitting
something for my grandson.
You haven't seen him,
by any chance?
No, no.
Come, liebchen.
I'm dreadfully sorry.
I do apologize.
That's quite all right.
If I see your grandson,
i will...
I will turn him
into a mouse.
And you,
meddling old woman,
I will deal with later.
[Cat snarls]
Liebchen.
I do hope we're not
the first.
Miss Ernst!
Ahh!
Who is this?
You told them to come up
after the drinks.
Oh. All right.
Let them in.
Come in.
You were wonderful
this afternoon.
[All talking at once]
[Snarls]
Ohh!
You bad cat, liebchen.
You're early,
in fact.
[Snarling]
[Gasps]
Man: So...When do you think
they'd implement it?
Second man: First of
the year, I suppose.
She's a very pleasant
woman.
Yes. Now,
the question is,
would she like
to work with us?
Luke: Ow! Oh...
Whew!
Uhh!
Grandma, grandma!
I've got it!
I've got the formula.
Oh, thank god.
Luke, darling,
i was so worried.
There's 500 doses
in this one little bottle.
It's enough to change
all the witches
in this hotel.
Where's Bruno?
There's some jolly good
grapes here.
What's happening?
Nothing until dinnertime.
Now, we've got to get you
back to your parents.
What time
is it?
7:00.
They'll be
in the bar.
A Sherry and a large
malt whiskey at 7:00 sharp.
It gives you
an appetite.
Does it?
Come on.
Into my handbag,
both of you.
This is going
to be difficult.
Oh, I'm full.
Luke: After that, we've
gotta get to the kitchen
as quick as we can.
Bruno: Ha ha ha.
That tickles.
Is that them?
Luke: Yes.
Listen, grandma.
Maybe we
ought to--
shh.
Wait! Listen...
Don't drown it.
Oh, sorry.
Now look what
you've done!
She was drowning it.
Are you Mr.
and Mrs. Jenkins?
Hole in one,
madam. What
can we do for you?
I would like to have
a word with you
about your son.
[Chuckles]
Sit down, sit down.
Now, what's the little
tyke been up to now?
Raiding the kitchen,
i suppose.
If we could go somewhere
more private...
Private?
Well, it is
rather a...
Personal matter.
Look, Mrs. whatever
your name is,
if Bruno has broken a window
or smashed your spectacles,
I'll pay for it, but we're
not budging out of this seat.
We always sit
at this table.
Where is Bruno, anyway?
You tell him to come
here and see me.
He is here already.
What?
In my handbag.
Your son has
suffered a mishap.
He has been
drastically altered.
Altered? What do
you mean, altered?
I'm trying to tell you
as gently as possible.
My grandson saw them
doing it to him.
Saw who doing what?
Saw the witches turn
him into a mouse.
Are you crackers?
Get the manager, dear.
Tell them to throw this old
nutcase out of the hotel.
You need a funny farm,
you do.
Tell them, Bruno.
Aah! A mouse!
Shh!
Aaahh!
I can't stand them!
Get it away!
It is Bruno.
Tell them, Bruno.
Get out of here!
How dare you!
Come on.
Tell them, Bruno.
Aah!
It's me, mum. I--
out! Out before
i call the police,
you barmy old looney.
Just go on! Push off!
Never come back,
you stupid old witch!
I did my best,
Bruno.
Don't worry, dear.
Just go on.
Evening, madam.
I'm just popping in
to turn down your bed.
How is
the room service here?
Diabolical.
Good.
How do you know
that woman upstairs?
Come along! Walk downstairs.
The elevator is out of order.
Is it?
Must be.
It's a five-course meal.
Good.
I'm rather hungry.
Mmm.
Oh...
I'd like to go home.
That's what I'd like.
What are you
doing here?
The banquet,
miss Ernst.
No! You must go to your room
and prepare for--
hello!
For tomorrow's flight.
Yes, have a good flight.
But it's
our banquet.
You are not here
to enjoy yourself!
You are here
as my staff!
Go to your room now.
Ladies.
[Applause]
I quit!
[Indistinct chatter]
I can't go
through with it.
We could run away,
go home, yes?
Luke: Grandma,
if we don't try,
every mother and
father in england
will lose
their kids.
I know.
We must do it,
grandma.
8:03 now.
8:15 exactly.
I'll remember.
Luke, darling,
I'm so terrified.
Grandma, now!
No, no, no, madame.
The dining room is
down the corridor.
I am sorry, truly.
The guests are not
permitted, madame.
I am sorry, but...
They want more bread rolls.
They ready yet?
One moment.
Where are my peas?
And how is the cress soup for
the children's charity group?
The soup!
Very good,
but no more salt.
No more?
Hmm!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ohh!
[Gasps]
They're everywhere!
Chef, table five says
the veal's too tough.
I will take care
of this personally.
[Flies buzz]
Chef!
The rspcc party
all want soup.
That's 87
for watercress.
Debby, bring
the soup tureens.
He'll adore it now.
The magic touch,
n'est-ce pas?
Whoa!
I'll just check the soup
before it's served.
Whoa. Whoa.
Ohh. Oh, god.
She's eating the soup.
I'll see you
later, then.
We're short-staffed
tonight.
I--i may be
a little late.
I can wait.
What is it?
[Gasps]
[Squeaking]
Now!
Uhh!
Ow!
A mouse!
Aah!
It's a mouse!
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Get him off!
It's running around
in me bloody underpants!
For goodness' sake,
get out of the way.
Aah!
Get it out!
Somebody, help me!
Take your trousers
off, you idiot!
Take your pants off.
Oh, give me that.
Somebody get it out
before he bites me!
Whew! I gotta
get out of here.
Somebody, get it out!
Ohh! Ohh, ohh, ohh!
I saw it.
See it?
I saw nothing.
There's nothing much
in there.
A lot of fuss about nothing.
It's gone.
Uh...Ee---uhh!
[Squeaking]
Uhhh...Unh...
Ooh...Ooh...Uh...
Eee! Eee!
Oy!
Yes?
What kind of soup
is that?
That is
the cress soup, sir.
Well, if they're all
having cress soup,
I'll have a cress
soup, thank you.
Yes, that soup is specially
made for their party, sir.
The soup on the menu
tonight is cock-a-leekie,
and very nice
it is, too.
But I don't want
cock-a-leekie.
I don't like
I like cress.
So just
take that back
to the kitchen
and tell
the chef de cuisine
that there's one more
order for cress soup.
Now, there's a laddie.
[Whimpering]
What's that, eh?
[Whimpering
and groaning]
Don't touch it!
It's in the soup!
Don't touch the soup!
Aah!
Child!
Good.
Come along.
[Sighs] Nearly 8:15.
Oh, I can't believe
she's still here.
Dear me!
No, madam, please.
Please.
Just a moment.
8:15. I made it!
One more--
one more cress soup,
table nine.
[Luke panting]
Luke: Hi, Bruno.
Lovely, isn't it?
Red.
Yes. Red.
I didn't want to be
one of them anyway.
I'll bring you
your main course.
Well?
I put it
in the soup.
The whole bottle?
Every drop.
You angel. [Gasps]
You're bleeding.
One of the cooks
tried to cut off
my tail with
a carving knife. Look!
The grand high witch
is eating the soup!
They all are.
Would you like
another roll, sir?
Oh. No, thanks.
I'd like some...Yes.
Well, I'd like some...
I'd like some
black pepper, please.
Ohhh! My god!
Luke: What?
Bruno's father is about
to eat the soup, too.
Stop him!
Quick!
Oh, so that's it.
This is a nightmare.
At least we got
some cress soup.
Don't touch it!
I told you
she was a loony.
She's
an absolute nutter!
Look at
my bloody soup!
All that stuff
about Bruno!
Bruno has been
turned into--
he has not been
turned into a m--
yes, I have.
Hello, dad.
Aaahhh!
Don't worry, dad.
It isn't all bad...
Well, just so long as
the cat doesn't get me.
Bruno.
No more school,
no more homework.
I'll live in
the kitchen cupboard.
No, no, no. This is...
This is a trick.
It's the whiskey.
Hello, mum.
[Whimpers]
Would you like to know
who did this to Bruno?
[Whimpers]
[Belches]
[Screaming and moaning]
It's working!
[All shrieking
and yelling]
Let go of me!
My formula 86!
Give me that spoon!
[Squeaking]
That woman over there.
She is
the grand high witch.
[Snarls]
Grandma, she needs
more time to become a...
She did it to Bruno...
And thousands of other
children before him.
Good evening.
You're--you're doomed,
old woman!
You're doomed forever!
It must work, grandma.
Oh, you--aah!
Bruno!
No, Bruno.
[Belches]
[Moaning]
This is it, Bruno.
Rrahhr!
Come on!
Get the mice!
Rrahhr!
The most evil and appalling
woman in the world.
A loathsome,
hideous disgrace!
Yeah, grandma!
I'm not finished
with you yet, old woman!
Next time!
No!
No next time.
This time
it's your turn.
Herbert! Herbert,
do something!
Hold still. It's in your
foundation garment.
Good night.
Aah!
Get that brown one!
No, not that one.
The other one, there!
Look, grandma,
it's her.
Ohhh!
Revenge on you!
Revenge!
Luke: Don't let her
get away.
Get away from me!
Hey! Get me
out of here! Help!
Get--get out
of my hotel!
[Squeak]
Mr. stringer.
Yes, madam.
There's an especially
infectious one
over there...
Under the water jug.
Thank you, madam.
Oh, it's a pleasure.
Get away from me!
I tell you,
get away from me!
Get me out of here!
Get away!
Get away from me,
i say!
No!
Eek!
Ah--uhh!
My mum's not
very crazy about mice.
So I see.
Here is Bruno.
Oh. Thank you.
He needs to go
on a diet.
Hi, dad. Hi, mum.
[Sobbing]
Will you stop it?
Stop it, dear.
Stop it.
This is our Bruno.
Don't cry, mum.
You'll get used to me.
Just a minute,
grandma.
Bye, Bruno.
Bye.
Excuse me.
Oh, mum.
You always wanted me
to lose weight.
Well, look at me now.
There. But I still
don't understand.
I won't be long.
Come on. This way.
Mice in
the main dining room.
Come on, hurry up.
Your taxi, madam.
Good-bye. Thank you.
[Honk honk]
Honk honk]
Let's get away!
Put it down, bill.
That's it.
You all right?
Yeah.
Can you manage?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Look out.
There's a step.
Mrs. evershim?
Yes, it is.
There's a trunk
for you.
A trunk?
Will you sign
for it?
Yes, all right.
Come in.
[Train whistle blows]
Luke: Oh, great!
Great! It's arrived!
Don't open it yet,
grandma.
Wait for me.
Put it down there.
That'll do fine.
All right.
Yeah, that's it.
Luke: Here I come.
Thank you.
Thank you, madam.
But I still have no idea
who it could be from.
This is really
gonna surprise ya.
Ok. Open it, grandma.
Yes, but what is it?
Open it.
Money!
Luke?
I saw it when I was in
the grand high
witch's room.
I figured we could
really use it
when we go
to America.
America?
Yes. We've got to go
home because...Look!
It was
the grand high witch's.
It has the name and address
of every witch in America.
Luke!
You are a genius.
Aw...Ha ha ha!
Aw.
¶ It doesn't matter who
you are and what you are ¶
¶ as long as somebody
loves you ¶
oh, Luke, what a day.
Perhaps we could find
a good witch
to turn you back
into my grandson.
I'll never be able to drive
a real car, will I, grandma?
Oh, I don't know.
How long do mice live,
grandma?
I hope we have time to take on
those American witches.
Can we go to New York?
I've never been
to New York.
[Train whistle blows]
Can we travel there
by ship?
First class.
The best cabin.
The best of everything.
Good night, grandma.
Good night, Luke.
I really am happy
to be a mouse, you know.
I know, my darling.
Hee hee hee
ha ha ha!
[Moaning]
Grandma!
Grandma,
what's happening?
Luke!
Uhh!
Hee hee hee hee!
Luke!
[Gasps]
Hee hee!
Ohhh...
Oh! Ha ha!
Off you go,
back home to Luke.
Look, grandma!
They're back!
Don't forget Bruno!