1
00:01:54,906 --> 00:01:58,158
You don't have to come
if you don't want to.

2
00:01:58,868 --> 00:02:02,246
I want to, but l have
a million things to do first.

3
00:02:09,879 --> 00:02:11,213
BOBBY:
Mom, what's this?

4
00:02:12,257 --> 00:02:14,758
SUKIE: Peanut butter.
BOBBY: Peanut butter and what?

5
00:02:15,135 --> 00:02:16,552
Peanut butter and jelIy.

6
00:02:16,719 --> 00:02:19,054
KIDS:
What kind of jelIy?

7
00:02:19,514 --> 00:02:20,722
Zucchini jelIy.

8
00:02:20,890 --> 00:02:22,766
[KIDS COMPLAIN lNG]

9
00:02:29,774 --> 00:02:31,775
[BELL RINGING]

10
00:02:51,921 --> 00:02:54,339
Five, six, seven!

11
00:02:54,507 --> 00:02:56,508
[PLAYING]

12
00:03:16,196 --> 00:03:17,279
How we doing?

13
00:03:17,447 --> 00:03:19,781
We're doing fine, WaIter.

14
00:03:20,700 --> 00:03:23,327
I wish we could afford
to keep you fulI time.

15
00:03:23,703 --> 00:03:25,829
So do I, especially now.

16
00:03:26,122 --> 00:03:29,291
Hmm. ls the divorce final yet?

17
00:03:30,001 --> 00:03:32,836
-Yes, today. Thank you.
-Hmm.

18
00:03:33,004 --> 00:03:37,716
Let's put our heads together and
maybe we can work something out.

19
00:03:47,268 --> 00:03:48,644
All right.

20
00:03:49,520 --> 00:03:50,854
Uh, horns up.

21
00:03:51,356 --> 00:03:54,233
One, two, three, four...

22
00:03:54,651 --> 00:03:56,652
. ..five, six, seven.

23
00:03:57,153 --> 00:04:03,325
WOMAN [SlNGING]:
<i>O beautiful for spacious skies</i>

24
00:04:03,493 --> 00:04:09,498
<i>For amber waves of grain</i>

25
00:04:09,666 --> 00:04:15,671
<i>For purple mountain majesties</i>

26
00:04:15,838 --> 00:04:21,343
<i>Above the fruited plain!</i>

27
00:04:22,470 --> 00:04:28,600
<i>America! America!</i>

28
00:04:28,768 --> 00:04:34,856
<i>God shed his grace on thee</i>

29
00:04:35,024 --> 00:04:41,321
<i>And crown thy good with brotherhood</i>

30
00:04:41,489 --> 00:04:48,203
<i>From sea to shining sea!</i>

31
00:04:48,663 --> 00:04:50,664
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDS]

32
00:04:52,625 --> 00:04:55,168
WeIl, wonderful.
Thank you very much, Felicia.

33
00:04:55,336 --> 00:04:59,214
We appreciate your taking the time
to be here with us today.

34
00:04:59,382 --> 00:05:03,051
Ladies and gentIemen, a big hand
for our most prominent selectman...

35
00:05:03,344 --> 00:05:07,556
. ..or selectwoman or selectperson,
FeIicia Alden.

36
00:05:07,724 --> 00:05:10,183
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDS]

37
00:05:10,351 --> 00:05:12,561
Thank you, children and Mrs. Spofford.

38
00:05:12,770 --> 00:05:15,856
I can see we have our work
cut out for us.

39
00:05:24,324 --> 00:05:27,451
In these days of
disintegrating vaIues.. .

40
00:05:28,119 --> 00:05:29,953
. ..and Iost mores. . .

41
00:05:30,330 --> 00:05:33,040
. ..when our chiIdren
are exposed daily. ..

42
00:05:33,207 --> 00:05:38,253
. ..to the hazards of divorce, separation
and families torn asunder. . .

43
00:05:39,130 --> 00:05:41,840
. ..it's comforting to think back
to the days. ..

44
00:05:42,008 --> 00:05:45,218
. ..when a famiIy like the Lenoxes
strove together.

45
00:05:45,386 --> 00:05:49,222
Those vaIues, embodied
in a man like Major Lenox. . ..

46
00:05:49,474 --> 00:05:53,310
They were men who labored
aIl their lives. . .

47
00:05:53,519 --> 00:05:57,939
. ..so their chiIdren wouId be
welI-fed and clothed and educated.

48
00:05:58,775 --> 00:06:00,984
The families endured great hardship. . .

49
00:06:01,277 --> 00:06:02,944
[CLANGS LOUDLY]

50
00:06:04,072 --> 00:06:06,156
. ..yet kept their honor...

51
00:06:06,491 --> 00:06:09,326
. ..their dignity and their faith in God.

52
00:06:10,244 --> 00:06:15,624
We are the same peopIe;
the same body, the soul. . .

53
00:06:15,875 --> 00:06:19,669
. ..the hands and the feet
of our fathers...

54
00:06:20,004 --> 00:06:23,173
. ..fighting the wars of modern vice.

55
00:06:23,674 --> 00:06:26,676
What was it that tied
these people together?

56
00:06:27,011 --> 00:06:29,179
What was it that made them. . .

57
00:06:29,514 --> 00:06:33,392
. ..not a loose gathering of individuals,
but a singIe bond?

58
00:06:33,684 --> 00:06:39,064
That bond that held them together,
as it holds us together today.

59
00:06:39,482 --> 00:06:42,150
That bond that has stood every test.. .

60
00:06:42,819 --> 00:06:45,195
. ..is found deep in our consciousness.

61
00:06:45,363 --> 00:06:48,031
An abiding Iove of liberty.

62
00:06:49,200 --> 00:06:52,411
For Iove of liberty, our forbearers. . .

63
00:06:52,620 --> 00:06:56,206
. ..coIonies few in number and
with Iittle to defend themseIves. ..

64
00:06:56,707 --> 00:06:59,418
. ..fought the war for independence. . .

65
00:06:59,919 --> 00:07:03,338
. ..what was then the world's
most powerful empire.

66
00:07:03,506 --> 00:07:04,589
[WlND WHISTLlNG]

67
00:07:04,757 --> 00:07:05,924
For Iove of liberty. . .

68
00:07:06,092 --> 00:07:09,177
. ..those who came before us
tamed a vast wilderness...

69
00:07:09,345 --> 00:07:11,179
. ..and braved hardships. . . .

70
00:07:13,224 --> 00:07:16,351
Tamed a vast wilderness
and braved hardships.. .

71
00:07:16,519 --> 00:07:19,396
. ..which at times were
beyond the limit--

72
00:07:19,564 --> 00:07:20,689
[THUNDER RUMBLlNG]

73
00:07:20,857 --> 00:07:23,442
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]

74
00:07:23,609 --> 00:07:28,405
Braved hardships, which at times were
beyond the limit of human endurance.

75
00:07:28,948 --> 00:07:30,949
[WALTER CONTINUES SPEECH
THEN THUNDER CRASHlNG]

76
00:07:40,042 --> 00:07:42,794
Come on. Go with your mom. Go on.

77
00:07:42,962 --> 00:07:44,963
[PEOPLE YELLlNG AND CHATTERlNG]

78
00:07:46,048 --> 00:07:50,760
Liberty must not be taken for granted.
We thank God for our bIessings. ...

79
00:07:56,559 --> 00:07:58,560
[THUNDER CRASHlNG]

80
00:08:22,084 --> 00:08:24,628
Oh, hi, come on in.
Janey, come on!

81
00:08:27,423 --> 00:08:29,341
Do you beIieve it's raining?

82
00:08:29,509 --> 00:08:30,634
Duh, no.

83
00:08:30,801 --> 00:08:32,427
I mean, since this morning.

84
00:08:32,595 --> 00:08:33,929
At least it shut WaIter up.

85
00:08:34,096 --> 00:08:36,806
The same boring, sanctimonious speech.

86
00:08:37,600 --> 00:08:42,270
I thought he'd go on forever.
I was praying for something to happen.

87
00:08:42,438 --> 00:08:45,440
-I was thinking the same thing.
-You were?

88
00:08:45,608 --> 00:08:50,320
I was thinking we're aIl wet and
how nice it wouId be to just leave.

89
00:08:50,613 --> 00:08:52,113
SUKIE: Were you reaIly?
-Yeah.

90
00:08:52,823 --> 00:08:54,282
And then it rained.

91
00:08:54,450 --> 00:08:57,786
JANE: He's a liar and a lech
and he deserved it.

92
00:08:57,995 --> 00:08:59,579
No, I'm not talking about Walter.

93
00:08:59,747 --> 00:09:01,706
Don't you think it's strange
that we were--

94
00:09:01,874 --> 00:09:04,960
We were thinking the same thing
at the same time? So what?

95
00:09:05,169 --> 00:09:07,170
It won't get us on David Letterman.

96
00:09:07,380 --> 00:09:09,130
-I know, l--
-Let's just have a drink.

97
00:09:09,340 --> 00:09:12,175
Good idea, Janey, party-baby!

98
00:09:17,181 --> 00:09:19,182
[THUNDER CRASHlNG]

99
00:09:25,940 --> 00:09:28,858
You know, he made
a pass at me last week too.

100
00:09:29,026 --> 00:09:32,529
JANE: Walter? Oh, please.
ALEX: I can't even stand to think about it.

101
00:09:32,697 --> 00:09:34,823
Be prepared.
He does not give up easily.

102
00:09:35,408 --> 00:09:39,327
It was broad daylight and his wife
was standing ten feet away!

103
00:09:39,495 --> 00:09:40,579
Poor woman.

104
00:09:40,746 --> 00:09:45,166
Poor woman, my ass. Why does she
put up with it? The man is a Nazi.

105
00:09:47,003 --> 00:09:49,504
Do you think they still...you know?

106
00:09:49,755 --> 00:09:50,839
Yes.

107
00:09:51,299 --> 00:09:54,342
-RealIy?
ALEX: I hope his dick is bigger than his I .Q.

108
00:09:54,510 --> 00:09:57,220
SUKIE: Once a week. He told me.
-He told you.

109
00:09:57,638 --> 00:10:00,181
Otherwise she starts throwing things.

110
00:10:00,349 --> 00:10:02,892
At least someone's getting
something once a week.

111
00:10:03,060 --> 00:10:04,436
Yes, heartburn.

112
00:10:04,979 --> 00:10:08,857
Mm. I keep forgetting how many calories
are in these.

113
00:10:09,025 --> 00:10:10,191
Two minutes on the Iips,

114
00:10:10,359 --> 00:10:12,027
Forever on the love handIes.

115
00:10:16,699 --> 00:10:17,741
[THUNDER CRASHES]

116
00:10:17,908 --> 00:10:19,367
Ooh. And congratuIations.

117
00:10:21,746 --> 00:10:24,205
Oh, God, I forgot. Your divorce.

118
00:10:24,373 --> 00:10:26,750
As of today, l'm a free woman.

119
00:10:27,168 --> 00:10:29,669
SUKIE: Join the club.
-Thanks.

120
00:10:31,213 --> 00:10:33,381
Heh. Here l go again.

121
00:10:34,634 --> 00:10:37,552
It's over, honey. You'Il be okay.

122
00:10:37,762 --> 00:10:40,597
It's a beginning, not an ending.
Right, Alex?

123
00:10:40,973 --> 00:10:43,516
Besides, we still have each other.

124
00:10:43,684 --> 00:10:45,769
Have some more martooni.

125
00:10:46,479 --> 00:10:48,313
-Did you bring the cards?
-Was l supposed to?

126
00:10:48,481 --> 00:10:51,775
-I have them.
-Okay, come on Iadies, let's do it! Whoo!

127
00:10:55,488 --> 00:10:57,989
SUKIE:
I feel like I'm being unfaithful. . .

128
00:10:58,157 --> 00:11:00,617
. ..even if I just think about it.

129
00:11:01,827 --> 00:11:05,580
Sukie, Monty deserted you
and left you with five kids.

130
00:11:05,748 --> 00:11:07,499
-Six.
-Don't start, Alex.

131
00:11:07,917 --> 00:11:10,877
Her husband left because
she had too many kids.

132
00:11:11,045 --> 00:11:13,338
-That's his problem.
-You're oversimplifying.

133
00:11:13,506 --> 00:11:17,384
-Yours left because you can't have any.
-You are definitely oversimplifying.

134
00:11:17,593 --> 00:11:19,135
That's not the point.

135
00:11:19,345 --> 00:11:21,513
What I'm saying is
that it's not your fault.

136
00:11:21,681 --> 00:11:24,974
That doesn't matter.
It's just not that easy.

137
00:11:25,142 --> 00:11:27,894
We're too young to lock it up
and throw away the key.

138
00:11:28,062 --> 00:11:29,521
It's not natural.

139
00:11:30,189 --> 00:11:32,315
What are we doing with ourseIves?

140
00:11:32,525 --> 00:11:35,485
Look, Ozzie's dead. I loved him.
He's dead.

141
00:11:35,820 --> 00:11:39,698
So l spend Thursday nights
with you two the rest of my life?

142
00:11:39,865 --> 00:11:43,535
I like our Thursdays.
It's the only time l can reIax.

143
00:11:43,953 --> 00:11:47,497
Quilting, macramé.
What did we do Iast Thursday night?

144
00:11:47,665 --> 00:11:49,290
[IN UNISON]
Chinese aphrodisiac cooking.

145
00:11:49,458 --> 00:11:52,711
Fabulous. Stimulating.
We're not reIaxing, we're hiding.

146
00:11:53,003 --> 00:11:54,796
-What from?
-WaIter Neff.

147
00:11:54,964 --> 00:11:58,133
Fuck Walter Neff.
I'm not talking about him.

148
00:12:00,720 --> 00:12:03,847
All right, who should we be Iooking for?

149
00:12:04,515 --> 00:12:07,642
Somebody nice. Somebody you couId Iike.

150
00:12:07,810 --> 00:12:10,145
Somebody with a brain.
Somebody you could talk to.

151
00:12:10,312 --> 00:12:12,564
Somebody you could be yourself with.

152
00:12:12,898 --> 00:12:18,987
[SINGlNG]
<i>Someone to watch over me</i>

153
00:12:19,238 --> 00:12:21,781
All right, l've had it with you two.

154
00:12:23,117 --> 00:12:25,160
[CHUCKLES]

155
00:12:26,328 --> 00:12:29,164
He would have to be from out of town.

156
00:12:29,373 --> 00:12:31,833
EspecialIy considering what's in town.

157
00:12:32,042 --> 00:12:34,878
A stranger. That wouId be interesting.

158
00:12:35,755 --> 00:12:38,882
A taIl, dark prince
traveIing under a curse.

159
00:12:39,258 --> 00:12:40,759
In Eastwick?

160
00:12:41,177 --> 00:12:42,761
Romantic.

161
00:12:43,012 --> 00:12:46,055
A foreign prince on a big, black horse.

162
00:12:47,349 --> 00:12:48,725
[LAUGHS]

163
00:12:48,893 --> 00:12:53,271
All right, no, no, no.
If we're going to have it...

164
00:12:54,190 --> 00:12:55,857
. ..let's have it all.

165
00:13:03,240 --> 00:13:04,699
[THUNDER CRASHES]

166
00:13:07,077 --> 00:13:09,162
He should be reaIly handsome.

167
00:13:09,413 --> 00:13:10,872
Not too handsome.

168
00:13:11,081 --> 00:13:12,373
Nice eyes.

169
00:13:12,541 --> 00:13:14,000
Nice ass.

170
00:13:14,168 --> 00:13:15,835
[CHUCKLES]

171
00:13:27,014 --> 00:13:28,431
Huge.

172
00:13:28,808 --> 00:13:29,849
[CHUCKLES]

173
00:13:30,017 --> 00:13:31,351
I prefer small.

174
00:13:32,645 --> 00:13:34,229
Aesthetically, l prefer smalI.

175
00:13:34,396 --> 00:13:38,316
Sam was huge and there were times
when I couId not face it.

176
00:13:38,484 --> 00:13:40,860
I'm in the middIe myself.

177
00:13:41,028 --> 00:13:43,696
But who cares?
As long as it works, it's in.

178
00:13:43,864 --> 00:13:45,573
-It's in.
-Okay.

179
00:14:10,641 --> 00:14:14,936
It's a nice thought, but wishing
for it won't make it happen.

180
00:14:17,731 --> 00:14:20,358
Men are not the answer to everything.

181
00:14:23,362 --> 00:14:26,656
So why do we aIways end up
taIking about them?

182
00:14:48,137 --> 00:14:49,554
[HORN HONKS]

183
00:14:56,395 --> 00:14:59,188
SUKIE: I said, some man bought
the Lenox mansion.

184
00:15:01,358 --> 00:15:03,192
Did you hear me?

185
00:15:03,402 --> 00:15:05,194
ALEX [OVER PHONE]:
<i>Yeah. Who is he?</i>

186
00:15:05,446 --> 00:15:08,406
He's from New York, no wife, no family.

187
00:15:08,699 --> 00:15:12,535
He toId the realtors he needed room
for his pianos.

188
00:15:12,912 --> 00:15:15,121
Apparently, he has a lot of pianos.

189
00:15:15,331 --> 00:15:17,916
How many pianos can one guy have?

190
00:15:18,208 --> 00:15:21,878
Don't you think it's kind of
strange and funny?

191
00:15:22,338 --> 00:15:23,838
<i>What's his name?</i>

192
00:15:24,673 --> 00:15:27,050
You know, that's strange too.

193
00:15:28,844 --> 00:15:30,637
<i>What's strange about his name?</i>

194
00:15:30,804 --> 00:15:34,182
They told me his name
for the coIumn and I forgot it.

195
00:15:34,350 --> 00:15:37,268
So l called back and it's gone again.

196
00:15:37,770 --> 00:15:40,063
It's not Iike me to forget a name.

197
00:15:41,231 --> 00:15:43,107
<i>It's the big news of the day...</i>

198
00:15:43,275 --> 00:15:47,320
<i>...considering the history of the place.</i>
<i>l wonder if he knows.</i>

199
00:15:47,488 --> 00:15:48,738
WOMAN:
<i>I don't know.</i>

200
00:15:50,032 --> 00:15:52,075
Is that CIyde and FeIicia?

201
00:15:54,870 --> 00:15:58,831
Yeah. Clyde?
I'Il call you back, okay?

202
00:15:59,750 --> 00:16:03,586
I have this cuIinary piece.
Hi, Felicia.

203
00:16:03,754 --> 00:16:06,965
"Cheeseburger pie"?
Is your column finished?

204
00:16:07,466 --> 00:16:12,095
Here's the track meet, births and
deaths, the senior citizens' news.

205
00:16:12,471 --> 00:16:16,975
The toxic waste articIe
should be done this afternoon.

206
00:16:17,142 --> 00:16:18,559
This pie looks good.

207
00:16:18,769 --> 00:16:21,354
Did you hear someone bought
the Lenox mansion?

208
00:16:35,244 --> 00:16:39,080
That house is landmark building.
They have no right to selI it.

209
00:16:39,415 --> 00:16:41,791
I can't do anything about that.

210
00:16:42,918 --> 00:16:44,127
FELlCIA:
No.

211
00:16:44,628 --> 00:16:45,920
You're too busy. . .

212
00:16:46,130 --> 00:16:51,092
. ..reporting on the horse trough and
Herbie Prescott's trip to Bermuda.

213
00:16:52,302 --> 00:16:56,806
What's going to happen
to those birds now? TelI me that.

214
00:16:57,099 --> 00:16:58,141
What birds?

215
00:16:58,308 --> 00:17:00,018
The snowy egrets.

216
00:17:00,519 --> 00:17:01,769
Where will they nest?

217
00:17:02,187 --> 00:17:03,479
I don't know.

218
00:17:05,024 --> 00:17:06,274
Exactly.

219
00:17:07,693 --> 00:17:09,652
FeIicia, what's the matter?

220
00:17:11,780 --> 00:17:14,907
Honey. lt's only a house.
Why are you so upset?

221
00:17:15,117 --> 00:17:16,659
I have a feeling.

222
00:17:17,036 --> 00:17:19,037
The most terrible feeling.

223
00:17:19,663 --> 00:17:22,665
Something is happening.
Something evil.

224
00:17:30,799 --> 00:17:33,468
I'm just gIad they're seIling.
I was afraid that--

225
00:17:33,635 --> 00:17:36,596
They're not seIling, they sold.
Just like that.

226
00:17:36,805 --> 00:17:37,972
I don't understand.

227
00:17:38,140 --> 00:17:42,643
You know I adore the Iittle creatures.
So unreal, and yet the detail.

228
00:17:42,978 --> 00:17:47,815
Little fingers and toes, little pudenda
making a bump. So sweet.

229
00:17:48,150 --> 00:17:51,652
But nobody's even Iooked
at them sideways in months.

230
00:17:51,987 --> 00:17:53,571
Then this morning. ..

231
00:17:53,989 --> 00:17:57,617
. ..this man appeared
out of absoIutely nowhere.

232
00:17:57,785 --> 00:18:02,246
So charming. Not really handsome,
but. . .riveting.

233
00:18:02,456 --> 00:18:05,958
That's it. I was riveted.
I looked into his eyes. . .

234
00:18:06,668 --> 00:18:09,962
. ..and had thoughts I hadn't
entertained since World War l l.

235
00:18:10,130 --> 00:18:13,424
I think l actually blushed.
Can you imagine?

236
00:18:13,592 --> 00:18:16,219
No, I mean, yeah. So he bought one?

237
00:18:16,512 --> 00:18:19,013
He bought aIl of them.
Every single one.

238
00:18:19,515 --> 00:18:20,807
So who was he? A tourist?

239
00:18:20,974 --> 00:18:24,519
No, he just bought the Lenox house.
He's moving in.

240
00:18:25,354 --> 00:18:27,146
Do you remember his name?

241
00:18:27,314 --> 00:18:29,524
Of course. His name is... .

242
00:18:33,529 --> 00:18:35,029
He toId me.

243
00:18:35,697 --> 00:18:37,532
I wrote it down, even.

244
00:18:38,617 --> 00:18:39,700
It was. ..

245
00:18:40,369 --> 00:18:41,619
. ..foreign.

246
00:18:43,038 --> 00:18:44,539
It sounded.. . .

247
00:18:45,707 --> 00:18:49,377
It's right on the tip of my tongue,
but I can't....

248
00:18:52,381 --> 00:18:53,714
Oh.

249
00:18:53,882 --> 00:18:55,716
Isn't that diabolical?

250
00:18:59,763 --> 00:19:01,764
[PLAYING CLASSICAL MUSIC]

251
00:19:42,431 --> 00:19:44,432
[GROWLlNG]

252
00:19:48,937 --> 00:19:50,771
What is that noise?

253
00:19:53,025 --> 00:19:54,775
I don't know.

254
00:20:17,633 --> 00:20:18,716
Outrageous!

255
00:20:32,606 --> 00:20:34,607
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDS]

256
00:20:47,454 --> 00:20:51,415
Brava!

257
00:20:54,336 --> 00:20:58,256
Bravis!

258
00:20:59,132 --> 00:21:01,509
[LAUGH lNG]

259
00:21:07,432 --> 00:21:09,350
SUKIE:
He bought aIl of them?

260
00:21:09,518 --> 00:21:12,353
-And now he's here.
-Making goo-goo eyes at Jane.

261
00:21:12,521 --> 00:21:14,939
And the interview too. How weird.

262
00:21:15,190 --> 00:21:19,068
Didn't l telI you?
Oh, it was after we taIked.

263
00:21:19,361 --> 00:21:22,530
The paper called him
and asked to interview him--

264
00:21:23,699 --> 00:21:25,950
About the house renovation and alI.

265
00:21:26,118 --> 00:21:29,203
He said he'd love to be interviewed
and asked for me.

266
00:21:29,371 --> 00:21:30,413
Why?

267
00:21:30,580 --> 00:21:33,332
I don't know, I mean he wants me
to do the interview.

268
00:21:33,542 --> 00:21:36,085
-Who is he?
-He must have a name.

269
00:21:36,253 --> 00:21:37,878
I just can't remember it.

270
00:21:38,255 --> 00:21:39,922
Why would he ask for you?

271
00:21:40,299 --> 00:21:44,635
Because I'm good at it.
You act like l'm so stupid.

272
00:21:45,220 --> 00:21:47,054
He was in my shop.

273
00:21:47,306 --> 00:21:50,599
You're not stupid. But how does
he know who Sukie Ridgemont is?

274
00:21:50,767 --> 00:21:51,934
I don't know.

275
00:21:52,227 --> 00:21:54,770
He bought the Lenox estate
just like that.

276
00:21:54,938 --> 00:21:58,316
-From New York.
-He has some kind of a foreign name.

277
00:21:58,734 --> 00:22:01,527
Van something or other.

278
00:22:04,823 --> 00:22:07,908
Oh, there you are. How sweet.

279
00:22:08,243 --> 00:22:11,078
They're from him. With a personal note.

280
00:22:11,830 --> 00:22:15,124
-Just the initiaI "D."
-Yeah, it starts with "D."

281
00:22:15,417 --> 00:22:19,086
-David?
-No. It has an "R" in it.

282
00:22:19,254 --> 00:22:20,588
Doberman?

283
00:22:20,839 --> 00:22:22,089
-Drake?
-Darren.

284
00:22:22,257 --> 00:22:25,843
It's "D" something, "R" something, "L."
DaryI!

285
00:22:26,511 --> 00:22:27,928
[GASPS]

286
00:22:29,097 --> 00:22:30,556
-Van Horne.
-Yes!

287
00:22:30,724 --> 00:22:32,433
-Daryl Van Horne.
-Daryl Van Horne?

288
00:22:32,601 --> 00:22:34,268
What kind of name is that?

289
00:22:36,605 --> 00:22:39,607
[SCREAMS]

290
00:22:40,025 --> 00:22:41,233
CLYDE:
FeIicia!

291
00:22:47,449 --> 00:22:48,741
Sweetheart?

292
00:22:57,709 --> 00:22:59,377
Oh, Clyde, honey.

293
00:23:00,796 --> 00:23:02,797
I think l broke my leg.

294
00:23:55,517 --> 00:23:57,184
DARYL:
Looking for me?

295
00:23:59,688 --> 00:24:04,191
Are you looking for me?
Or is this just a happy coincidence?

296
00:24:04,526 --> 00:24:07,027
-Actually, l was--
-Just looking.

297
00:24:07,362 --> 00:24:09,530
WeIl, too bad.

298
00:24:09,865 --> 00:24:13,242
Have you seen any snowy egrets out here?

299
00:24:13,410 --> 00:24:15,870
-No.
-Neither have I.

300
00:24:16,079 --> 00:24:21,208
Not that I'd know a snowy egret if l was
pissing on one. You want some lunch?

301
00:24:22,210 --> 00:24:24,712
I think it's a little late
in the season.

302
00:24:26,465 --> 00:24:27,631
For Iunch?

303
00:24:27,799 --> 00:24:29,258
No, pissing on birds.

304
00:24:34,973 --> 00:24:36,557
DARYL:
DaryI Van Horne.

305
00:24:36,808 --> 00:24:38,058
Alexandra Medford.

306
00:24:38,560 --> 00:24:41,228
The local sculptress.
The one who makes. . .

307
00:24:41,396 --> 00:24:43,230
. ..the littIe booby dolls.

308
00:24:43,565 --> 00:24:45,107
They're just littIe--

309
00:24:45,567 --> 00:24:49,069
Little, yes, but potent. FulI of juice.

310
00:24:49,988 --> 00:24:53,574
Potent. You can feel it
when you pick them up.

311
00:24:53,742 --> 00:24:55,743
I sent a coupIe to New York.

312
00:24:55,911 --> 00:24:59,497
I have a friend down there.
Terrific feIlow.

313
00:24:59,748 --> 00:25:03,083
He has a galIery.
I wanted to hear his opinion.

314
00:25:03,460 --> 00:25:06,378
Of course the scale is wrong.
Get bigger.

315
00:25:06,546 --> 00:25:10,174
Let yourseIf go.
Get some size into it.

316
00:25:11,009 --> 00:25:14,678
Do you like fish?
We're having fish for Iunch.

317
00:25:28,443 --> 00:25:29,902
[SIGHS]

318
00:25:34,449 --> 00:25:35,950
Interesting, huh?

319
00:25:36,493 --> 00:25:37,660
Oh, yes.

320
00:25:37,869 --> 00:25:39,620
FideI, that's his name.

321
00:25:39,955 --> 00:25:42,790
Women love him.
They're crazy about him.

322
00:25:43,625 --> 00:25:45,793
He has a big schIong.

323
00:25:46,169 --> 00:25:47,378
Huge.

324
00:25:47,546 --> 00:25:51,131
WeIl, there you are.
Scale again. Size.

325
00:25:51,299 --> 00:25:53,884
Who knows, maybe it's a mascuIine thing.

326
00:25:54,052 --> 00:25:59,682
They say women don't care. I'm in
the middle myself. How about you?

327
00:26:00,058 --> 00:26:01,642
How about me, what?

328
00:26:01,810 --> 00:26:05,145
See, women are in touch
with different things.

329
00:26:05,397 --> 00:26:10,234
That's my opinion. It's not a
fashionable one right now, but fuck it!

330
00:26:10,569 --> 00:26:15,239
I see men running around,
putting their dicks. ..

331
00:26:15,448 --> 00:26:18,200
. ..into everything,
trying to make something happen.

332
00:26:18,368 --> 00:26:22,371
But it's women who are the source,
the only power.

333
00:26:22,872 --> 00:26:25,499
Nature. Birth. Rebirth.

334
00:26:25,709 --> 00:26:27,960
CIiché. Cliché.

335
00:26:28,128 --> 00:26:30,129
Sure. But true.

336
00:26:31,006 --> 00:26:32,840
Why are you teIling me this?

337
00:26:34,092 --> 00:26:37,219
You're an honest woman.
I'm being honest with you.

338
00:26:37,387 --> 00:26:40,723
I like women. I admire them.

339
00:26:41,016 --> 00:26:45,352
But if you want me to treat you
like a dumb twit, l wiIl.

340
00:26:45,687 --> 00:26:48,814
But what for? You have brains, Alex.

341
00:26:49,024 --> 00:26:53,444
More than brains. But you don't
know it. Most women don't.

342
00:26:53,695 --> 00:26:54,987
Are you married?

343
00:26:55,196 --> 00:26:56,363
Good question!

344
00:26:56,531 --> 00:26:59,116
You see? Brains.

345
00:26:59,367 --> 00:27:02,369
The answer is no.
I don't believe in it.

346
00:27:02,537 --> 00:27:05,205
Good for the man.
Lousy for the woman.

347
00:27:05,707 --> 00:27:11,003
She dies. She suffocates.
I've seen it. Then the husband...

348
00:27:11,171 --> 00:27:14,048
. ..complains to everyone that
he's fucking a dead person.

349
00:27:14,215 --> 00:27:15,591
And he's the one who killed her.

350
00:27:15,759 --> 00:27:18,719
[LAUGHS]

351
00:27:18,887 --> 00:27:20,888
-Where is your husband?
-Dead.

352
00:27:21,222 --> 00:27:24,391
Sorry, but you're one of the lucky ones.

353
00:27:24,726 --> 00:27:28,896
When a woman unIoads a husband
or a husband unloads a woman.. .

354
00:27:29,064 --> 00:27:33,567
. ..however it happens. ..
death, desertion, divorce: the three Ds.

355
00:27:33,735 --> 00:27:38,238
When that happens, a woman bIooms.
She blossoms.

356
00:27:38,782 --> 00:27:42,076
Like flowers. Like fruit.

357
00:27:42,243 --> 00:27:43,577
She is ripe.

358
00:27:44,579 --> 00:27:46,914
That's the woman for me.

359
00:27:54,756 --> 00:27:57,091
Would you like to see my house?

360
00:27:58,301 --> 00:27:59,802
Yes.

361
00:28:01,096 --> 00:28:03,263
DARYL:
In case anybody ever...

362
00:28:03,431 --> 00:28:05,599
. ..needed any exercise...

363
00:28:06,101 --> 00:28:09,853
. ..the pooI is right over there,
past the piano. . .

364
00:28:10,021 --> 00:28:12,439
. ..where the ballroom used to be.

365
00:28:12,941 --> 00:28:15,275
Interesting word, "balIroom."

366
00:28:15,610 --> 00:28:16,944
It's one of my favorites.

367
00:28:17,112 --> 00:28:19,113
DARYL:
Over there is. . .

368
00:28:19,948 --> 00:28:22,366
. ..my study.

369
00:28:24,744 --> 00:28:26,120
Oh.

370
00:28:26,955 --> 00:28:29,623
-This is my bedroom.
-Yes, it is.

371
00:28:29,874 --> 00:28:32,376
The Borgias once owned the bed.

372
00:28:33,461 --> 00:28:37,965
Of course, you have to pay for it
with your soul, but...

373
00:28:38,508 --> 00:28:41,301
. ..what the heIl,
I deserve a little luxury.

374
00:28:41,636 --> 00:28:43,887
You have to take care of yourself.

375
00:28:44,055 --> 00:28:46,765
No one will do that for you, wiIl they?

376
00:28:47,308 --> 00:28:48,642
Hmm?

377
00:28:52,981 --> 00:28:56,734
Ha. Ha-ha.
What do you think you're doing?

378
00:28:58,319 --> 00:29:02,823
Being as direct with you as l know how.
I thought you'd appreciate it.

379
00:29:05,076 --> 00:29:08,746
I aIways like a Iittle pussy
after lunch. What do you say?

380
00:29:09,581 --> 00:29:12,833
-Hmm?
-Are you trying to seduce me?

381
00:29:13,168 --> 00:29:16,837
I wouIdn't dream of seducing you,
Alexandra.

382
00:29:17,005 --> 00:29:19,339
I wouIdn't insuIt your intelIigence. . .

383
00:29:19,507 --> 00:29:22,676
. ..with anything as trivial
as seduction.

384
00:29:23,344 --> 00:29:27,389
But, l would love to fuck you.

385
00:29:31,186 --> 00:29:35,397
I have to admit that l appreciate
your directness, DaryI.

386
00:29:35,565 --> 00:29:37,024
I will try to be as direct. . .

387
00:29:37,192 --> 00:29:39,568
. ..and honest with you
as l possibly can be.

388
00:29:39,736 --> 00:29:41,779
I think... .

389
00:29:42,030 --> 00:29:46,950
No, I am positive that you are the most
unattractive man I have ever met...

390
00:29:47,118 --> 00:29:48,911
. ..in my entire life.

391
00:29:49,078 --> 00:29:53,999
This afternoon, you have demonstrated
every loathsome characteristic...

392
00:29:54,167 --> 00:29:57,085
. ..of the male personality
and even added some new ones.

393
00:29:57,253 --> 00:30:00,506
You are physicaIly repuIsive,
inteIlectuaIly retarded...

394
00:30:00,799 --> 00:30:05,636
. ..morally reprehensible, vuIgar,
insensitive, selfish, stupid.

395
00:30:05,887 --> 00:30:09,097
You have no taste, no sense of humor
and you smelI.

396
00:30:09,557 --> 00:30:13,101
You're not even interesting enough
to make me sick.

397
00:30:14,521 --> 00:30:18,398
Um.... Would you Iike to be
on top or the bottom?

398
00:30:20,235 --> 00:30:23,570
Goodbye, DaryI, and thank you
for a lovely Iunch.

399
00:30:23,905 --> 00:30:26,740
If that's the way you feel about it. . .

400
00:30:27,075 --> 00:30:29,451
. ..that's the way you feel about it.

401
00:30:29,744 --> 00:30:31,829
Is that the way you feeI about it?

402
00:30:38,336 --> 00:30:39,628
Who are you?

403
00:30:41,464 --> 00:30:42,840
Just your. . .

404
00:30:43,091 --> 00:30:45,926
. ..average horny little devil.

405
00:30:47,095 --> 00:30:48,637
I have to get home.

406
00:30:49,264 --> 00:30:51,723
What have you got to go home to?

407
00:30:51,891 --> 00:30:54,351
There isn't anybody there, is there?

408
00:30:54,936 --> 00:30:56,937
The kid will take care of herseIf.

409
00:30:57,605 --> 00:31:01,608
She'lI eat and fall asleep
on the bed doing homework.

410
00:31:01,943 --> 00:31:03,610
I promise.

411
00:31:04,445 --> 00:31:06,280
And housecleaning?

412
00:31:06,614 --> 00:31:10,284
You cIean up the dirt,
there's just more dirt tomorrow.

413
00:31:10,618 --> 00:31:13,912
Make the beds, they just
have to be made tomorrow.

414
00:31:14,080 --> 00:31:17,499
Wash the dishes.
There's more to wash tomorrow.

415
00:31:17,667 --> 00:31:19,668
-I have to make--
-Make dinner?

416
00:31:19,961 --> 00:31:21,628
It just gets eaten.

417
00:31:21,963 --> 00:31:23,797
You've done your best, Alex.

418
00:31:24,132 --> 00:31:27,885
You've done the wife bit,
the motherhood bit.

419
00:31:28,052 --> 00:31:31,471
The car pools, the vegetable garden.. .

420
00:31:31,639 --> 00:31:34,808
. ..the needlepoint,
the macramé potholders...

421
00:31:35,143 --> 00:31:37,978
. ..a cup of coffee with
a neighbor in the morning. ..

422
00:31:38,646 --> 00:31:42,482
. ..a couple of drinks,
a coupIe of pilIs. . .

423
00:31:43,067 --> 00:31:45,402
. ..a little psychoanalysis....

424
00:31:46,654 --> 00:31:48,322
Where are you now, Alex?

425
00:31:48,656 --> 00:31:51,283
Exactly where I want to be
and l'm doing fine.

426
00:31:51,451 --> 00:31:56,663
Pretending to be somebody else?
To be half of what you are?

427
00:31:56,831 --> 00:31:59,333
How Iong can you last Iike that?

428
00:32:00,168 --> 00:32:03,545
The world keeps growing,
and you feed it.

429
00:32:03,713 --> 00:32:05,839
But it doesn't feed you, does it?

430
00:32:06,007 --> 00:32:09,843
It washes through you,
down the drain, wasted.

431
00:32:10,053 --> 00:32:12,721
A woman is a hole,
isn't that what they say?

432
00:32:13,014 --> 00:32:16,516
All the futility of the world
pouring into her.

433
00:32:17,143 --> 00:32:18,518
Hmm?

434
00:32:19,687 --> 00:32:23,857
How much can you take, Alex?
How much can you take...

435
00:32:24,359 --> 00:32:26,026
. ..before you snap?

436
00:32:28,029 --> 00:32:31,531
Lying on your bed,
looking at the ceiling. . .

437
00:32:31,741 --> 00:32:33,700
. ..waiting for something to happen.

438
00:32:33,868 --> 00:32:38,455
And knowing aIl the time that you
were meant for something better.

439
00:32:39,040 --> 00:32:40,666
Feeling it.

440
00:32:40,833 --> 00:32:42,459
Wanting it.

441
00:32:43,753 --> 00:32:45,462
Use me, Alex.

442
00:32:46,547 --> 00:32:47,881
Use me.

443
00:32:48,383 --> 00:32:50,717
FiIl me up. I can take it.

444
00:32:50,927 --> 00:32:54,012
Make it happen. Don't wait.

445
00:32:54,555 --> 00:32:56,390
Time is the kiIler.

446
00:32:57,100 --> 00:32:58,725
Make it happen.

447
00:32:59,727 --> 00:33:01,561
Do it, AIex.

448
00:33:02,063 --> 00:33:03,563
Do it now.

449
00:33:23,751 --> 00:33:25,752
[PLAYING CLASSICAL MUSIC]

450
00:33:58,911 --> 00:34:00,537
You know. . . .

451
00:34:02,123 --> 00:34:04,124
You sit there in that...

452
00:34:05,209 --> 00:34:07,711
. ..pathetic excuse of an office. ..

453
00:34:09,630 --> 00:34:11,298
. ..reporting gossip. . .

454
00:34:15,261 --> 00:34:17,429
. ..while under your very nose. . .

455
00:34:18,306 --> 00:34:19,639
. ..evil.. .

456
00:34:20,808 --> 00:34:22,809
. ..is doing its worst.

457
00:34:27,315 --> 00:34:29,149
You have no spine, Clyde.

458
00:34:31,069 --> 00:34:33,236
Not one ounce. . .

459
00:34:33,863 --> 00:34:35,155
. ..of morality.

460
00:34:36,324 --> 00:34:37,657
Christ!

461
00:34:38,159 --> 00:34:40,160
Even common sense.

462
00:34:42,580 --> 00:34:44,206
Nuclear holocaust.

463
00:34:44,499 --> 00:34:45,832
Murder.

464
00:34:46,000 --> 00:34:48,293
Rape. Apartheid!

465
00:34:49,670 --> 00:34:52,339
Why, these words mean nothing to you.

466
00:34:54,342 --> 00:34:56,343
It's just a local newspaper.

467
00:34:56,677 --> 00:34:58,470
It is local turpitude.

468
00:34:58,638 --> 00:35:02,682
You are a failure, Clyde!
You should be strung up...

469
00:35:02,850 --> 00:35:06,103
. ..along with that son of a bitch
who bought that house!

470
00:35:06,521 --> 00:35:08,313
[SCREAMS]

471
00:35:08,689 --> 00:35:10,857
CalI the nurse!

472
00:35:19,659 --> 00:35:21,034
I am in pain!

473
00:35:21,536 --> 00:35:24,371
-Then take the pilI.
-I don't want to.

474
00:35:24,539 --> 00:35:27,040
I'm not going to force it on you.

475
00:35:28,251 --> 00:35:30,252
Is it AIzheimer's?

476
00:35:30,670 --> 00:35:34,881
No. It's the bone marrow.
When a bone breaks...

477
00:35:35,216 --> 00:35:39,719
. ..bits of fat get in the bloodstream
and the blood vessels of the brain.

478
00:35:40,054 --> 00:35:41,638
It affects the behavior.

479
00:35:41,848 --> 00:35:46,143
She's hysterical. She says things that
I don't know where they're coming from.

480
00:35:46,310 --> 00:35:47,686
It's bone marrow?

481
00:35:47,854 --> 00:35:52,232
Yes. She'lI be very upset.
She'lI say terrible things.

482
00:35:52,400 --> 00:35:54,568
She may even be paranoid.

483
00:35:54,735 --> 00:35:58,113
It is perfectly normal. lt wilI pass.

484
00:36:16,257 --> 00:36:18,258
What's happening to me, CIyde?

485
00:36:18,426 --> 00:36:20,218
It's all right, sweetheart.

486
00:36:23,598 --> 00:36:26,766
I open my mouth and
the strangest things come out.

487
00:36:28,686 --> 00:36:33,732
You've had a hard time
and you're tired. Try to sleep.

488
00:36:43,951 --> 00:36:45,577
[SIGHS]

489
00:36:48,122 --> 00:36:50,457
Something is inside me, Clyde.

490
00:36:53,002 --> 00:36:55,503
Something is crawling inside me.

491
00:36:57,006 --> 00:36:58,256
I can feel it.

492
00:36:58,466 --> 00:36:59,799
Something evil.

493
00:37:00,968 --> 00:37:02,802
It's almost here.

494
00:37:04,013 --> 00:37:05,096
Hi.

495
00:37:06,140 --> 00:37:07,724
You!

496
00:37:08,142 --> 00:37:09,643
In there!

497
00:37:09,810 --> 00:37:13,438
[SCREAMlNG]

498
00:37:14,982 --> 00:37:16,983
[PLAYING CLASSICAL MUSIC]

499
00:37:50,184 --> 00:37:51,935
[DOORBELL RlNGS]

500
00:38:06,534 --> 00:38:07,951
Jane.

501
00:38:08,202 --> 00:38:09,869
At last we meet.

502
00:38:10,705 --> 00:38:12,372
DaryI Van Horne.

503
00:38:24,844 --> 00:38:26,177
Cream and sugar?

504
00:38:26,387 --> 00:38:27,679
Sugar.

505
00:38:28,389 --> 00:38:30,724
-One lump or two?
-Four.

506
00:38:31,559 --> 00:38:33,893
-Sweet tooth.
-Sweet everything.

507
00:38:34,061 --> 00:38:38,231
I'm a sugar junkie.
Sugar, chocolate, Coca-Cola....

508
00:38:38,899 --> 00:38:42,736
UncontrollabIe appetite.
In every department.

509
00:38:45,072 --> 00:38:46,865
That's not good for you.

510
00:38:51,579 --> 00:38:53,246
It doesn't bother me.

511
00:38:53,581 --> 00:38:57,083
I have a supernatural constitution.
It's genetic.

512
00:38:57,710 --> 00:39:00,545
I don't hold on
this health consciousness shit.

513
00:39:00,921 --> 00:39:02,380
Pardon the language.

514
00:39:02,548 --> 00:39:04,341
I see guys, 60...

515
00:39:04,759 --> 00:39:06,926
. ..70, breaking their baIls...

516
00:39:07,595 --> 00:39:09,929
. ..to stay fit. What for?

517
00:39:10,264 --> 00:39:13,224
When l die, I want to be sick,
not healthy.

518
00:39:14,101 --> 00:39:16,936
I suppose that's one way
of Iooking at it.

519
00:39:17,938 --> 00:39:19,439
Oh.

520
00:39:20,107 --> 00:39:21,399
Do I make you nervous?

521
00:39:21,567 --> 00:39:22,817
Yes, you do.

522
00:39:23,277 --> 00:39:25,779
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I said that.

523
00:39:26,947 --> 00:39:28,782
Truth is best.

524
00:39:29,617 --> 00:39:31,451
Yes, that's so true.

525
00:39:43,631 --> 00:39:45,632
So what brings you to Eastwick?

526
00:39:46,592 --> 00:39:47,884
Ah.

527
00:39:48,302 --> 00:39:50,804
We're going to have
a polite conversation.

528
00:39:51,097 --> 00:39:52,263
I'm sorry.

529
00:39:52,473 --> 00:39:54,099
No, I don't mind.

530
00:39:54,266 --> 00:39:57,936
I came to Eastwick
because l was drawn here.

531
00:39:58,979 --> 00:40:01,648
I needed a pIace to settle down and. . .

532
00:40:02,983 --> 00:40:04,609
. .. l Iiked the house.

533
00:40:05,653 --> 00:40:07,112
It has a history.

534
00:40:08,155 --> 00:40:09,489
Rubbish.

535
00:40:09,657 --> 00:40:11,324
No, it's true.

536
00:40:12,326 --> 00:40:15,161
They say they used
to burn witches there.

537
00:40:16,497 --> 00:40:18,331
Hocus-pocus.

538
00:40:18,833 --> 00:40:21,167
The entire witchcraft scare.. .

539
00:40:21,335 --> 00:40:26,131
. ..as far back as the 1 4th century,
was started by the medicaI profession.

540
00:40:26,590 --> 00:40:27,924
That's right.

541
00:40:28,092 --> 00:40:31,761
They were trying to get midwives
out of the child-birthing business.

542
00:40:32,346 --> 00:40:36,683
That's what most of the women
they burned were. Midwives.

543
00:40:37,309 --> 00:40:38,476
Is that true?

544
00:40:39,520 --> 00:40:41,187
You better believe it.

545
00:40:41,355 --> 00:40:45,692
Just another example of
male-dominated professional society. . .

546
00:40:46,026 --> 00:40:50,196
. ..exploiting femaIes
for their own selfish purposes.

547
00:40:51,031 --> 00:40:53,658
Men are such cocksuckers, aren't they?

548
00:40:56,704 --> 00:40:59,706
You don't have to answer that.
It's true.

549
00:41:00,374 --> 00:41:02,584
Their dicks get limp. . .

550
00:41:02,751 --> 00:41:05,795
. ..when confronted by a powerful woman,
so what do they do?

551
00:41:05,963 --> 00:41:08,882
CalI them witches.
Burn them, torture them...

552
00:41:09,216 --> 00:41:12,719
. ..until every woman is afraid.
Afraid of herseIf...

553
00:41:13,888 --> 00:41:15,722
. ..afraid of men.

554
00:41:16,056 --> 00:41:17,891
And alI for what?

555
00:41:19,226 --> 00:41:21,561
Fear of Iosing their hard-on.

556
00:41:21,770 --> 00:41:23,521
[LAUGHS]

557
00:41:26,066 --> 00:41:27,817
Let's pIay some music.

558
00:41:29,570 --> 00:41:30,778
[CHUCKLES]

559
00:41:39,955 --> 00:41:41,372
Mm.

560
00:41:44,543 --> 00:41:46,085
[THUNDER CRASHlNG]

561
00:41:46,962 --> 00:41:48,963
[PLAYING CLASSICAL MUSIC]

562
00:41:58,933 --> 00:42:01,434
[THUNDER CRASHlNG]

563
00:42:05,272 --> 00:42:07,273
You play beautifuIly.

564
00:42:08,108 --> 00:42:10,276
Nothing compared to you.

565
00:42:10,611 --> 00:42:12,445
You're an artist.

566
00:42:12,613 --> 00:42:13,947
Intonation.

567
00:42:14,365 --> 00:42:16,616
Vibrato. Stretch.

568
00:42:17,117 --> 00:42:20,119
You think I'm crazy, but I know music.

569
00:42:20,454 --> 00:42:23,414
It's the one thing that makes me humble.

570
00:42:23,958 --> 00:42:27,085
Not prissy? Our leader says
my intonation is prissy.

571
00:42:27,253 --> 00:42:29,212
You have precision.

572
00:42:30,464 --> 00:42:35,134
Precision is not prissy.
Precision is the foundation of passion.

573
00:42:35,636 --> 00:42:38,972
Passion without precision? Chaos.

574
00:42:39,265 --> 00:42:43,101
Look at your thumb.
Your sublime thumb position.

575
00:42:43,310 --> 00:42:45,645
You really keep the pressure on.

576
00:42:45,813 --> 00:42:48,147
Most men can't, but you. . . .

577
00:42:48,732 --> 00:42:51,568
You have the most beautiful caIlus.

578
00:42:52,653 --> 00:42:54,320
This hand.

579
00:42:55,990 --> 00:42:59,492
This is your failure.
Your bowing sucks.

580
00:43:01,328 --> 00:43:02,996
My bowing? Why?

581
00:43:05,958 --> 00:43:09,961
Your spiccato sounds like marcato.
Your Iegato like détaché.

582
00:43:10,170 --> 00:43:14,674
You kilI the passion. Let it go.
Why are you holding back?

583
00:43:15,009 --> 00:43:17,468
These aren't just notes
you're pIaying. . .

584
00:43:17,678 --> 00:43:20,513
. ..they're phrases. Human outcries.

585
00:43:20,681 --> 00:43:23,516
I understand that! And l practice!

586
00:43:23,684 --> 00:43:26,144
I practice until my fingers bleed!

587
00:43:27,187 --> 00:43:28,813
I know.

588
00:43:29,023 --> 00:43:32,191
It's the sixteenth notes in the alIegro.
I can't do it!

589
00:43:32,526 --> 00:43:34,027
Yes, you can.

590
00:43:35,195 --> 00:43:36,821
It's no good.

591
00:43:40,534 --> 00:43:42,035
I don't have it.

592
00:43:42,328 --> 00:43:43,536
I can't do it.

593
00:43:43,829 --> 00:43:46,706
-Yes, you can.
-No, I can't, l can't.

594
00:43:49,209 --> 00:43:50,543
[GASPS]

595
00:43:52,046 --> 00:43:53,379
DARYL:
Trust me.

596
00:43:54,340 --> 00:43:55,673
Trust me.

597
00:44:07,895 --> 00:44:12,231
Try.

598
00:44:13,067 --> 00:44:14,692
Let it go. Don't be afraid.

599
00:44:14,860 --> 00:44:17,820
You have great passion in you.
Let it out.

600
00:44:18,405 --> 00:44:20,239
I can take it.

601
00:44:20,574 --> 00:44:22,075
I want it.

602
00:44:26,455 --> 00:44:28,456
[PLAYING]

603
00:44:31,126 --> 00:44:35,588
Yes.

604
00:44:37,508 --> 00:44:39,592
Yes, that's it.

605
00:44:41,011 --> 00:44:45,098
Relax. Just breathe into it.

606
00:44:45,432 --> 00:44:48,434
Don't tighten up. That's it.

607
00:44:49,228 --> 00:44:51,396
Feel it. Hold it. Love it.

608
00:44:51,772 --> 00:44:53,272
That's it, yes.

609
00:44:53,440 --> 00:44:55,066
Yes, that's right. Now!

610
00:45:03,909 --> 00:45:06,077
That's right. Do you feel that?

611
00:45:06,328 --> 00:45:08,996
Let it wash over you.
Let it tickle you.

612
00:45:38,610 --> 00:45:40,194
[THUNDER CRASHlNG]

613
00:45:45,576 --> 00:45:47,201
[CHUCKLES]

614
00:45:54,585 --> 00:45:56,586
[MOAN lNG]

615
00:46:12,144 --> 00:46:14,145
[KIDS YELLING]

616
00:46:20,110 --> 00:46:21,694
[KNOCK ON DOOR]

617
00:46:22,863 --> 00:46:25,698
[ALL GREETING EACH OTHER]

618
00:46:26,700 --> 00:46:27,950
CAROL:
Did you miss me?

619
00:46:28,160 --> 00:46:30,119
-Yes.
-Good. l missed you too.

620
00:46:30,287 --> 00:46:31,871
-Like my new top?
-Yeah, it's cute.

621
00:46:32,039 --> 00:46:33,998
Do you want to listen to some tapes?

622
00:46:34,166 --> 00:46:36,292
[KIDS CHEER]

623
00:46:36,502 --> 00:46:38,878
Alex! Yoo-hoo.

624
00:46:39,213 --> 00:46:40,880
ALEX:
I'm out here!

625
00:46:43,217 --> 00:46:44,759
-Let's go.
-What is that?

626
00:46:44,927 --> 00:46:49,055
We're going to be late.
Carol, the number is on the fridge!

627
00:46:49,890 --> 00:46:52,892
-But you're not dressed.
ALEX: I'm not naked.

628
00:46:55,187 --> 00:46:57,355
-I don't beIieve it!
-Neither do I !

629
00:46:57,523 --> 00:46:59,732
But l swear to God,
I couldn't waIk for two days.

630
00:46:59,900 --> 00:47:02,235
[LAUGH lNG AND SCREAMlNG]

631
00:47:02,402 --> 00:47:05,196
His penis is amazing.
It bends the wrong way.

632
00:47:05,364 --> 00:47:07,448
The wrong--? Wait a minute!

633
00:47:07,908 --> 00:47:09,575
It bends like that!

634
00:47:09,868 --> 00:47:12,203
-You're terrible.
-No, I'm fabuIous.

635
00:47:13,413 --> 00:47:15,623
But just because you went
to bed with him--

636
00:47:15,791 --> 00:47:18,918
No, it's not just that!
It's Iike he knows me.

637
00:47:19,211 --> 00:47:23,214
He knows everything!
I can't wait for you to meet him.

638
00:47:23,423 --> 00:47:27,260
And l can't wait for Jane to meet him!
Jane wilI love him!

639
00:47:27,427 --> 00:47:30,012
[LAUGH lNG]

640
00:47:34,309 --> 00:47:35,643
SUKIE:
Jane?

641
00:47:35,894 --> 00:47:37,061
Is that you?

642
00:47:37,229 --> 00:47:40,064
JANE:
Sukie. Alexandra.

643
00:47:40,774 --> 00:47:42,942
Did you come to fix the plumbing?

644
00:47:43,235 --> 00:47:46,487
I didn't have time to change.
What's your excuse?

645
00:47:46,655 --> 00:47:48,656
I don't need any. l was invited.

646
00:47:48,824 --> 00:47:49,949
So was I.

647
00:47:50,117 --> 00:47:51,450
DARYL:
HelIo!

648
00:47:51,618 --> 00:47:53,619
Mm. DarIing!

649
00:47:53,787 --> 00:47:54,912
There you are.

650
00:47:55,080 --> 00:47:56,622
ALEX: Are we late?
-Not at alI.

651
00:47:56,790 --> 00:47:58,291
JANE:
Weren't we playing singles?

652
00:47:58,458 --> 00:48:00,543
-You don't pIay tennis.
JANE: I do now.

653
00:48:00,711 --> 00:48:03,796
Sukie. At last we meet.

654
00:48:04,464 --> 00:48:06,549
Hi. HelIo. How are you?

655
00:48:06,800 --> 00:48:08,467
Let me...

656
00:48:09,136 --> 00:48:11,804
. ..look at those eyes of yours.

657
00:48:13,140 --> 00:48:15,808
You are a fertile creature, aren't you?

658
00:48:16,143 --> 00:48:17,310
Thank you, I think.

659
00:48:17,477 --> 00:48:21,147
I'm reading that rag of a newspaper.
You are a genius.

660
00:48:21,648 --> 00:48:24,650
Wasted. Pearls before swine.

661
00:48:25,652 --> 00:48:30,489
When are we going to do our interview?
I love interviews.

662
00:48:30,824 --> 00:48:33,117
-They're so intimate.
-Anytime you say.

663
00:48:33,285 --> 00:48:37,288
Just the two of us,
banging away, head to head.

664
00:48:37,664 --> 00:48:39,999
Yes, yes.

665
00:48:40,167 --> 00:48:41,417
But not today.

666
00:48:41,585 --> 00:48:44,503
Today is for tennis.
Are you ready, ladies?

667
00:48:49,676 --> 00:48:54,347
What a day!

668
00:48:55,641 --> 00:48:56,682
[SN lFFS]

669
00:48:56,850 --> 00:48:58,851
Is that your perfume?

670
00:48:59,728 --> 00:49:00,770
[GLASS SHATTERS]

671
00:49:10,864 --> 00:49:12,698
[BOTH GRUNT]

672
00:49:12,866 --> 00:49:14,492
ALEX:
Double fauIt!

673
00:49:14,701 --> 00:49:18,537
I'm not blind or deaf!
You don't have to shout!

674
00:49:18,705 --> 00:49:21,499
We're aIl good friends.
Let's pIay fair.

675
00:49:22,000 --> 00:49:25,336
I aIways play fair, okay?
Love-forty, Jane.

676
00:49:25,504 --> 00:49:27,380
-Okay, okay.
-Okay?

677
00:49:27,547 --> 00:49:30,091
-What do you mean?
-Don't Iet them rattle you.

678
00:49:30,258 --> 00:49:32,885
They're just trying to get you.
Let's go.

679
00:49:33,095 --> 00:49:34,178
[JANE GRUNTS]

680
00:49:42,604 --> 00:49:43,896
-Uhn!
-Ah.

681
00:49:45,065 --> 00:49:47,066
Sorry, darIing. Lost my head.

682
00:49:49,236 --> 00:49:50,736
Fault.

683
00:49:55,951 --> 00:49:57,952
[GRUNTING]

684
00:50:01,415 --> 00:50:02,832
Ow!

685
00:50:21,101 --> 00:50:22,768
JANE:
I've got it! l've got it!

686
00:50:27,399 --> 00:50:28,899
It's not coming down.

687
00:50:40,328 --> 00:50:41,370
[SUKIE GlGGLES]

688
00:50:45,584 --> 00:50:46,792
Come on.

689
00:50:47,127 --> 00:50:49,295
Our game. Sukie serves.

690
00:51:09,107 --> 00:51:11,108
[MUTTERING]

691
00:51:25,123 --> 00:51:26,290
Stop!

692
00:51:31,254 --> 00:51:32,671
[EXHALES]

693
00:52:04,871 --> 00:52:06,539
Good going, Daryl.

694
00:52:16,550 --> 00:52:18,050
SUKIE:
Jane!

695
00:52:40,240 --> 00:52:41,657
[THUNDER CRASHlNG]

696
00:52:49,374 --> 00:52:50,916
[SPEAKS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]

697
00:52:51,501 --> 00:52:53,002
[LAUGHS]

698
00:52:53,712 --> 00:52:55,171
SUKIE:
Strong drink. What is it?

699
00:52:55,338 --> 00:52:58,215
DARYL:
Rum. . .vodka. . .

700
00:52:58,425 --> 00:53:00,092
. ..brandy.. .

701
00:53:00,260 --> 00:53:01,594
. ..acid.

702
00:53:02,387 --> 00:53:03,929
I'm only kidding.

703
00:53:04,264 --> 00:53:07,141
I don't mind.
Drugs have no effect on me.

704
00:53:07,309 --> 00:53:09,435
-RealIy?
-Neither does aIcohol.

705
00:53:09,769 --> 00:53:12,605
It's true. lt's boring, but it's true.

706
00:53:17,903 --> 00:53:20,237
Are you going to seduce me too?

707
00:53:21,948 --> 00:53:23,115
Yes.

708
00:53:25,076 --> 00:53:26,410
How?

709
00:53:28,955 --> 00:53:30,414
I don't know.

710
00:53:32,792 --> 00:53:35,294
I should warn you. I get pregnant.

711
00:53:36,630 --> 00:53:39,632
I get pregnant alI the time.
At the drop of a hat.

712
00:53:39,799 --> 00:53:42,092
I could borrow your toothbrush
and get pregnant.

713
00:53:42,969 --> 00:53:44,970
I'Il keep that in mind.

714
00:53:47,307 --> 00:53:48,724
That doesn't bother you?

715
00:53:50,018 --> 00:53:51,268
No.

716
00:53:53,980 --> 00:53:55,814
You're not like other men.

717
00:53:56,816 --> 00:53:58,275
-I'm not.
-Uhn-uhn.

718
00:53:58,485 --> 00:54:02,988
Most men, welI, my husband,
try to keep everything under control.. .

719
00:54:03,323 --> 00:54:05,658
. ..pretend everything is normaI.

720
00:54:05,825 --> 00:54:09,995
Always rational,
aIways an explanation for everything.

721
00:54:10,664 --> 00:54:15,000
Men need that, don't they?
To feeI everything is solid.

722
00:54:15,293 --> 00:54:17,962
And the worId just isn't Iike that.

723
00:54:18,672 --> 00:54:21,340
Certainly not with you three around.

724
00:54:25,470 --> 00:54:27,096
I don't think--

725
00:54:38,984 --> 00:54:41,986
We're not so different from other women.

726
00:54:42,195 --> 00:54:44,363
Women are more natural, right?

727
00:54:44,698 --> 00:54:48,200
And nature is crazy,
no matter what science says.

728
00:54:50,704 --> 00:54:52,371
So l don't mind.

729
00:54:54,374 --> 00:54:58,711
I don't mind when peculiar things
happen. lt's naturaI. ..

730
00:54:59,045 --> 00:55:01,588
. ..because the world
is a peculiar pIace.

731
00:55:02,048 --> 00:55:04,383
And you're a very peculiar person.

732
00:55:05,677 --> 00:55:06,802
Thank you.

733
00:55:09,222 --> 00:55:11,515
I wouId Iove to be a woman.

734
00:55:11,933 --> 00:55:14,184
You would? Really? Why?

735
00:55:14,561 --> 00:55:18,063
Just look what you can do
with your bodies.

736
00:55:18,565 --> 00:55:20,733
Make babies and. . .

737
00:55:21,735 --> 00:55:24,403
. ..make milk to feed the babies.

738
00:55:27,407 --> 00:55:29,408
If l could do that. ...

739
00:55:31,244 --> 00:55:33,245
Who are you, really?

740
00:55:35,915 --> 00:55:38,250
Anybody you want me to be.

741
00:55:58,730 --> 00:56:00,731
[OPERA MUSlC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]

742
00:57:27,444 --> 00:57:29,236
[SCREAMS]

743
00:57:32,157 --> 00:57:34,199
[DOG BARKING]

744
00:57:37,203 --> 00:57:39,204
[SUKIE AND ALEX LAUGH lNG]

745
00:57:53,887 --> 00:57:55,262
[GASPS]

746
00:58:03,021 --> 00:58:05,022
[LAUGH lNG]

747
00:58:13,740 --> 00:58:16,074
DARYL:
Look at what they can do.

748
00:58:17,577 --> 00:58:19,578
These are human beings.

749
00:58:25,084 --> 00:58:26,835
[RlNGS BELL]

750
00:58:27,003 --> 00:58:28,420
[JANE SCREAMS]

751
00:58:30,256 --> 00:58:33,926
SUKIE: When you're a kid
and don't understand anything. ..

752
00:58:34,260 --> 00:58:37,429
. ..you think when you grow up
it will all make sense.

753
00:58:37,764 --> 00:58:40,891
Then when you grow up,
you keep waiting for the day.

754
00:58:41,059 --> 00:58:42,851
You think it ever happens?

755
00:58:44,812 --> 00:58:49,525
It starts when you open your eyes and
reaIize what the future has in store for you.

756
00:58:50,610 --> 00:58:54,112
And what do you see
when you open your eyes?

757
00:58:56,991 --> 00:58:58,450
WeIl. . . .

758
00:58:58,993 --> 00:59:01,328
It's a short Iife, isn't it?

759
00:59:02,664 --> 00:59:05,874
Sometimes I look in the mirror
and l see everything...

760
00:59:06,042 --> 00:59:08,001
. ..disintegrating faster and faster.

761
00:59:13,675 --> 00:59:15,676
I aIways see snakes.

762
00:59:16,010 --> 00:59:18,011
Hundreds of them.

763
00:59:18,513 --> 00:59:21,014
They crawl all over me and l disappear.

764
00:59:21,349 --> 00:59:23,684
Then l'm just not there anymore.

765
00:59:29,649 --> 00:59:34,361
WeIl, I don't mind that it's a short life
or growing old or disappearing.

766
00:59:35,029 --> 00:59:39,032
It's the pain that scares me.
I don't know why there has to be...

767
00:59:39,701 --> 00:59:41,535
. ..so much pain.

768
00:59:42,579 --> 00:59:45,622
Yeah, welI....

769
00:59:46,874 --> 00:59:50,043
We don't deaI the deck
down here, we just. . .

770
00:59:50,378 --> 00:59:52,546
. ..play the percentages.

771
00:59:54,716 --> 00:59:56,717
[DOGS BARKlNG]

772
01:00:07,312 --> 01:00:09,313
[CHOIR SlNGlNG HYMN]

773
01:00:39,260 --> 01:00:47,267
Whores.

774
01:00:48,394 --> 01:00:49,686
CLYDE:
What?

775
01:00:49,937 --> 01:00:52,564
FELlCIA: Whores!
-Shh, shh, shh.

776
01:00:54,984 --> 01:00:57,402
-Whores.
-Sit down, sit down.

777
01:00:57,779 --> 01:00:59,446
FELlCIA:
Look around you.

778
01:01:00,281 --> 01:01:03,116
Look around you.
Do you see what's happening?

779
01:01:03,951 --> 01:01:05,452
In our town.

780
01:01:05,787 --> 01:01:08,205
In our very homes!

781
01:01:11,959 --> 01:01:14,795
You know who l'm talking about.
You know!

782
01:01:15,463 --> 01:01:18,965
You know what's going on in that house!
Vice!

783
01:01:19,217 --> 01:01:20,467
Perversions!

784
01:01:20,968 --> 01:01:22,636
Shamelessness!

785
01:01:23,221 --> 01:01:24,721
Cavorting...

786
01:01:25,139 --> 01:01:27,099
. ..with that devil!

787
01:01:27,266 --> 01:01:29,267
She's fine. She's sick.

788
01:01:31,062 --> 01:01:33,980
No! Drugs! Drugs are next.

789
01:01:34,482 --> 01:01:35,649
Murder!

790
01:01:36,150 --> 01:01:37,484
Rape!

791
01:01:38,986 --> 01:01:40,237
Incest!

792
01:01:40,655 --> 01:01:42,322
Spanish flies!

793
01:01:42,740 --> 01:01:45,158
Dildos! Anal intercourse!

794
01:01:48,496 --> 01:01:50,330
Listen to me!

795
01:01:51,499 --> 01:01:53,125
-PIease.
-Sorry!

796
01:02:11,185 --> 01:02:13,186
Let's go home, Felicia.

797
01:02:13,521 --> 01:02:15,689
You employ one of them, CIyde.

798
01:02:15,940 --> 01:02:17,774
That's nobody's business.

799
01:02:18,234 --> 01:02:22,654
Oh-ho. lt is everybody's business!

800
01:02:23,698 --> 01:02:26,950
You know, once there was a paradise.

801
01:02:27,618 --> 01:02:30,537
Then a serpent came into that garden.

802
01:02:30,788 --> 01:02:33,707
For Christ's sake, Felicia,
would you stop?

803
01:02:36,335 --> 01:02:38,211
Oh, Clyde.

804
01:02:39,213 --> 01:02:41,715
I have nothing against a good fuck.

805
01:02:43,384 --> 01:02:45,635
But there is danger here.

806
01:02:47,722 --> 01:02:50,724
Somebody has to do something about it.

807
01:03:06,449 --> 01:03:08,450
[PLAYING BADLY]

808
01:03:21,088 --> 01:03:22,422
Okay, stop.

809
01:03:22,924 --> 01:03:24,591
Stop! Stop.

810
01:03:25,718 --> 01:03:27,052
Um....

811
01:03:29,764 --> 01:03:31,431
Let's get rid of the music.

812
01:03:32,600 --> 01:03:37,270
Throw it away! Get rid of it.
Let's get rid of the music.

813
01:03:37,438 --> 01:03:39,606
That's it! Right. Okay, now. . . .

814
01:03:39,774 --> 01:03:42,442
I want you all to close your eyes.

815
01:03:44,028 --> 01:03:45,946
Take a deep breath.

816
01:03:47,615 --> 01:03:49,282
Let it alI out.

817
01:03:51,786 --> 01:03:53,787
Now pick up your instrument...

818
01:03:55,373 --> 01:03:57,541
. ..and when l count to four...

819
01:03:58,084 --> 01:04:00,752
. ..we'Il play the shit
out of this thing.

820
01:04:02,338 --> 01:04:08,844
One, two, three, four.

821
01:04:09,637 --> 01:04:11,805
[BAND STARTS PLAYING]

822
01:04:11,973 --> 01:04:14,140
That's it, just relax.

823
01:04:15,643 --> 01:04:17,811
Take it easy. Good.

824
01:04:19,146 --> 01:04:20,480
Nice!

825
01:04:21,482 --> 01:04:22,816
Smile.

826
01:04:23,150 --> 01:04:25,485
Come on, smile, Martha.

827
01:04:29,156 --> 01:04:32,576
That's it, this is fun.
Come on, this is easy.

828
01:04:32,910 --> 01:04:36,329
Easy-peasy. That's it, that's it. Good.

829
01:04:37,999 --> 01:04:41,585
Just let it flow over you. Good.

830
01:04:45,006 --> 01:04:46,840
Let it tickle you now.

831
01:04:48,134 --> 01:04:51,469
Tickle, tickIe, tickle, tickle.

832
01:04:51,679 --> 01:04:54,180
Good! You've got it now. Come on!

833
01:04:54,599 --> 01:04:57,559
Go with it, it's yours! Come on!

834
01:04:57,768 --> 01:05:00,145
Good! Yes!

835
01:05:01,105 --> 01:05:05,984
See? You can do it. That's it.
You're doing great. Flow with it.

836
01:05:07,486 --> 01:05:09,321
That's it, yes!

837
01:05:09,697 --> 01:05:13,033
These aren't phrases,
these are human outcries!

838
01:05:37,350 --> 01:05:38,975
Oh.

839
01:05:39,393 --> 01:05:42,395
Double-double chocolate.
These are fabulous.

840
01:05:45,691 --> 01:05:48,026
Mm-mm.

841
01:05:54,909 --> 01:05:56,701
Excuse me.

842
01:06:17,431 --> 01:06:19,683
Are you buying the paper or not?

843
01:06:20,810 --> 01:06:22,769
-Um....
-SIut.

844
01:06:24,855 --> 01:06:26,189
What did you say?

845
01:06:26,440 --> 01:06:27,774
You heard her.

846
01:06:40,830 --> 01:06:42,622
WOMAN 1 :
Did you see her socks?

847
01:06:43,457 --> 01:06:45,792
WOMAN 2:
She's not wearing a bra.

848
01:06:47,211 --> 01:06:48,837
SUKIE:
How could you do this?

849
01:06:49,005 --> 01:06:51,589
We didn't use any names
except for Van Horne.

850
01:06:51,757 --> 01:06:53,717
You don't know what goes on there.

851
01:06:54,218 --> 01:06:56,678
The whole town is talking
about you and your friends.

852
01:06:56,846 --> 01:06:59,139
This is so unfair. lt's also untrue.

853
01:06:59,306 --> 01:07:01,182
-No, no, no, no.
-Yes.

854
01:07:01,392 --> 01:07:04,894
He fiIled in the wetIands
and ruined it for the birds.

855
01:07:05,146 --> 01:07:08,356
He aItered the landmark building...

856
01:07:08,524 --> 01:07:11,109
. ..and the town is suing him
for $2 miIlion.

857
01:07:11,277 --> 01:07:13,403
How can you do this to me?

858
01:07:13,654 --> 01:07:16,990
I work very hard and you know
I'm a good writer.

859
01:07:17,199 --> 01:07:18,825
All right, Sukie, all right.

860
01:07:18,993 --> 01:07:20,452
-What?
-Look, look.

861
01:07:20,828 --> 01:07:21,870
[STAMMERS]

862
01:07:22,038 --> 01:07:24,497
I don't own the newspaper, you know.

863
01:07:28,502 --> 01:07:30,503
It's Felicia, isn't it?

864
01:07:31,088 --> 01:07:32,255
She's a...

865
01:07:33,424 --> 01:07:34,716
. ..very sick woman.

866
01:07:34,884 --> 01:07:39,345
She's having a very bad time.
And l don't know what to do.

867
01:07:40,347 --> 01:07:42,348
I want her to see a doctor.

868
01:07:42,683 --> 01:07:46,352
WeIl, not a doctor, you know,
but a...doctor.

869
01:07:53,611 --> 01:07:54,903
CIyde.

870
01:07:57,865 --> 01:08:00,366
We went to high schooI together.

871
01:08:02,203 --> 01:08:03,787
She was a catch.

872
01:08:05,873 --> 01:08:10,460
Ever since the accident, she just
hasn't been the same. And now. . . .

873
01:08:15,716 --> 01:08:17,550
I'm so sorry, Clyde.

874
01:08:27,561 --> 01:08:29,145
What am l doing?

875
01:08:29,563 --> 01:08:30,980
Firing me.

876
01:08:32,024 --> 01:08:33,399
Oh.

877
01:08:36,570 --> 01:08:39,239
All these terrible things she says...

878
01:08:41,408 --> 01:08:43,326
. ..they're not true, are they?

879
01:08:46,997 --> 01:08:49,124
We should stop seeing each other.

880
01:08:49,291 --> 01:08:52,252
-Oh, Iet's not overreact.
-Yes, let's not overreact.

881
01:08:52,461 --> 01:08:55,004
-I think we should.
-It's a small town, Daryl.

882
01:08:55,256 --> 01:08:58,216
We haven't done anything.
Why stop seeing each other?

883
01:08:58,384 --> 01:09:00,218
CIyde says that Felicia has visions.

884
01:09:00,386 --> 01:09:01,803
Why is it always women
who have visions?

885
01:09:01,971 --> 01:09:04,013
She sees the devil here in Eastwick.

886
01:09:04,265 --> 01:09:07,433
If you were the devil,
would you come to Eastwick?

887
01:09:07,768 --> 01:09:10,019
Oh, l don't know.

888
01:09:10,187 --> 01:09:11,229
Poor Felicia.

889
01:09:11,438 --> 01:09:15,066
Poor Felicia? She taIked
to alI of my students' mothers.

890
01:09:15,234 --> 01:09:16,985
I had 1 2 cancellations this week.

891
01:09:17,153 --> 01:09:19,654
People teIl Carol her mother is a dyke.

892
01:09:19,822 --> 01:09:21,531
You're being sued for millions.

893
01:09:21,782 --> 01:09:23,449
That is inconvenient.

894
01:09:23,701 --> 01:09:26,035
She's not kidding about
her medievaI moraIity.

895
01:09:26,787 --> 01:09:29,789
I think Sukie is right.
Maybe we should stop.

896
01:09:30,249 --> 01:09:31,332
Maybe she shouId stop.

897
01:09:31,500 --> 01:09:33,877
You can't be serious.
We're a famiIy.

898
01:09:34,128 --> 01:09:36,963
Just for a whiIe
untiI things settle down.

899
01:09:39,633 --> 01:09:41,676
Don't let her get to you.

900
01:09:41,969 --> 01:09:43,469
Have a cherry.

901
01:09:54,440 --> 01:09:58,151
They are selling pornography
at SchyIer's News Shop.

902
01:09:59,320 --> 01:10:01,821
In the open. On the sheIves.

903
01:10:02,156 --> 01:10:04,490
ChiIdren are looking at this. . . .

904
01:10:04,950 --> 01:10:06,659
[GAGS]

905
01:10:07,494 --> 01:10:09,329
It's in broad dayIight.

906
01:10:10,164 --> 01:10:12,999
I can't understand one word
you're saying. Not one!

907
01:10:13,250 --> 01:10:15,501
FELlCIA:
They're standing in line. . . .

908
01:10:22,843 --> 01:10:24,636
FiIth in broad daylight.

909
01:10:24,803 --> 01:10:26,387
CLYDE:
Right.

910
01:10:35,522 --> 01:10:37,398
She made a scene at SchyIer's.

911
01:10:37,566 --> 01:10:40,860
Grabbing magazines from kids
and chasing them.

912
01:10:41,528 --> 01:10:45,281
She's in pain. Clyde too.
He started drinking again.

913
01:10:45,532 --> 01:10:48,576
She's twisted. Getting to me
through my kid is sick.

914
01:10:48,744 --> 01:10:51,746
-We could help.
-By putting her out of her misery.

915
01:10:51,914 --> 01:10:54,499
Please.
They're lucky to have each other.

916
01:10:54,667 --> 01:10:58,044
If they don't appreciate that,
I have no sympathy.

917
01:10:58,545 --> 01:11:01,297
Easy for you to say.
You don't have kids or a family.

918
01:11:02,299 --> 01:11:05,885
You're my family.
I don't want to lose it.

919
01:11:07,054 --> 01:11:09,889
I just can't stand to see you upset.

920
01:11:11,308 --> 01:11:13,559
You don't know what it does to me.

921
01:11:14,895 --> 01:11:16,896
I wish she wouId just go away.

922
01:11:19,066 --> 01:11:20,900
Have another cherry.

923
01:11:40,421 --> 01:11:42,588
He's trying to get inside me.

924
01:11:43,757 --> 01:11:45,341
He's trying to use me.

925
01:11:46,760 --> 01:11:49,095
And he's using these women too.

926
01:11:50,931 --> 01:11:53,266
He wants to take our goodness.

927
01:11:58,439 --> 01:12:00,690
He wants to get inside me.

928
01:12:02,776 --> 01:12:04,444
Just like a man.

929
01:12:05,362 --> 01:12:07,030
Tickle, tickIe, diddle, diddle.

930
01:12:08,115 --> 01:12:09,741
[CLYDE MOANS]

931
01:12:12,619 --> 01:12:16,789
God made us in the image of goodness.
Look what we've become.

932
01:12:17,374 --> 01:12:19,334
[GROWLlNG]

933
01:12:20,794 --> 01:12:22,628
Animals gone mad. . .

934
01:12:23,380 --> 01:12:26,382
. ..devouring the earth and each other.

935
01:12:28,218 --> 01:12:30,553
Eat, eat, eat, eat!

936
01:12:31,138 --> 01:12:32,347
[SCREAMS]

937
01:12:34,308 --> 01:12:36,559
FeIicia, caIm down.

938
01:12:36,852 --> 01:12:40,021
[PANTlNG]

939
01:12:46,153 --> 01:12:47,987
I know who he is, Clyde.

940
01:12:49,490 --> 01:12:51,157
Have another cherry.

941
01:12:52,910 --> 01:12:54,452
[GAGS]

942
01:13:04,463 --> 01:13:06,672
What have you been eating?

943
01:13:07,508 --> 01:13:09,342
Those poor women.

944
01:13:09,802 --> 01:13:11,511
I have to warn them.

945
01:13:18,352 --> 01:13:20,353
He'll propagate, Clyde.

946
01:13:22,356 --> 01:13:24,524
He wilI increase his number.

947
01:13:27,319 --> 01:13:30,363
Those women are going to bear him sons.

948
01:13:31,698 --> 01:13:35,785
He's going to take their love
and destroy the earth with it.

949
01:13:36,703 --> 01:13:37,745
[CHUCKLES]

950
01:13:37,913 --> 01:13:39,372
[STOMACH RUMBLES]

951
01:13:41,333 --> 01:13:45,002
[GROANING]

952
01:13:54,721 --> 01:13:56,389
[RETCHlNG VIOLENTLY]

953
01:13:56,557 --> 01:13:58,391
Let's call it a day.

954
01:14:03,355 --> 01:14:05,022
[THUDDING]

955
01:15:19,640 --> 01:15:22,099
-I don't beIieve it.
-I know.

956
01:15:24,144 --> 01:15:26,312
I know him. He couldn't do this.

957
01:15:26,980 --> 01:15:29,565
Alex, don't you get it? God!

958
01:15:29,733 --> 01:15:30,858
Get what?

959
01:15:31,026 --> 01:15:32,151
Us!

960
01:15:33,320 --> 01:15:35,321
Last night, all that talk.

961
01:15:35,572 --> 01:15:37,406
Those were just words.

962
01:15:37,658 --> 01:15:40,660
They make things happen.
We make things happen.

963
01:15:40,911 --> 01:15:43,287
-We had nothing to do with this.
-Yes, we do!

964
01:15:43,455 --> 01:15:44,914
We should talk to Daryl.

965
01:15:45,082 --> 01:15:47,917
Why? Why do we have to do
everything DaryI says?

966
01:15:48,168 --> 01:15:49,377
She's right.

967
01:15:49,545 --> 01:15:52,338
Some man comes along
and nothing eIse matters!

968
01:15:52,673 --> 01:15:54,507
You are so dumb, Jane.

969
01:15:54,841 --> 01:15:58,094
-This is about us, not Daryl.
-Let's calI him.

970
01:15:58,262 --> 01:16:00,972
Can't you stop thinking
from between your Iegs?

971
01:16:01,139 --> 01:16:02,431
You bitch!

972
01:16:02,599 --> 01:16:03,933
SUKIE:
Alex, don't.

973
01:16:04,101 --> 01:16:05,977
-Shut up, Sukie!
-WiIl you get off of her?

974
01:16:06,144 --> 01:16:09,981
[ALL YELLING]

975
01:16:20,617 --> 01:16:22,285
[SCREAMlNG]

976
01:16:49,980 --> 01:16:51,731
Anybody call?

977
01:17:03,285 --> 01:17:04,994
[THUNDER CRASHlNG]

978
01:17:18,425 --> 01:17:21,469
[PHONE RlNGING]

979
01:17:36,610 --> 01:17:38,861
ALEX [OVER PHONE]: Hello?
-Hi.

980
01:17:39,613 --> 01:17:42,615
<i>-Daryl?</i>
-Yeah. Remember me?

981
01:17:43,825 --> 01:17:44,867
How are you?

982
01:17:46,953 --> 01:17:49,789
I'm hanging in there.
What do you want?

983
01:17:50,957 --> 01:17:55,211
Nothing. I just called
to see how you are, you know?

984
01:17:55,962 --> 01:17:58,297
<i>See how things were going.</i>

985
01:17:59,132 --> 01:18:00,466
I'm fine.

986
01:18:03,178 --> 01:18:04,470
[CLEARS THROAT]

987
01:18:04,638 --> 01:18:08,849
I wanted to see how you were,
you know?

988
01:18:09,643 --> 01:18:11,811
Make sure you were okay.

989
01:18:12,479 --> 01:18:16,482
Make sure you didn't have any
uncontrollabIe desire to see me.

990
01:18:17,693 --> 01:18:22,363
<i>In case you were missing me and</i>
<i>you were too embarrassed to call...</i>

991
01:18:22,572 --> 01:18:24,115
. .. l called first.

992
01:18:24,282 --> 01:18:27,952
Then you could feeI superior
and see me at the same time.

993
01:18:29,746 --> 01:18:31,247
<i>What do you say?</i>

994
01:18:32,249 --> 01:18:35,584
I don't feel superior. I feel terrible.

995
01:18:37,295 --> 01:18:39,296
I feel terrible too.

996
01:18:39,631 --> 01:18:42,925
If we both feeI terrible,
can't we do something about it?

997
01:18:43,093 --> 01:18:44,593
What's going on here?

998
01:18:44,761 --> 01:18:47,763
Nobody's calling me.
Nobody's coming to see me.

999
01:18:47,931 --> 01:18:49,807
-No--
-I just think we need some time.

1000
01:18:49,975 --> 01:18:51,475
We need a little time, okay?

1001
01:18:51,643 --> 01:18:55,146
No, it's not okay, Alex.
I don't understand.

1002
01:18:55,480 --> 01:18:58,232
Somebody died, Daryl.
FeIicia is dead.

1003
01:18:59,484 --> 01:19:01,110
Yeah, welI....

1004
01:19:01,987 --> 01:19:05,489
People die all the time.
She was in a bad way.

1005
01:19:05,657 --> 01:19:07,324
It has nothing to do with us.

1006
01:19:08,994 --> 01:19:12,580
I can't talk to you.
Don't calI me, because I--

1007
01:19:12,831 --> 01:19:14,081
<i>Don't hang up!</i>

1008
01:19:14,249 --> 01:19:17,752
Alex, don't do this! This is not fair!

1009
01:19:22,340 --> 01:19:25,176
[SCRATCHING]

1010
01:19:58,043 --> 01:20:00,211
Happy birthday!

1011
01:20:01,630 --> 01:20:03,047
It's not my birthday.

1012
01:20:04,049 --> 01:20:05,090
It isn't?

1013
01:20:06,218 --> 01:20:08,093
-You sure?
-I'm sure.

1014
01:20:11,223 --> 01:20:12,890
WeIl, what the helI.

1015
01:20:13,892 --> 01:20:15,893
Happy whatever day.

1016
01:20:16,228 --> 01:20:18,395
These are my favorite fruit.

1017
01:20:18,897 --> 01:20:20,981
I can't accept those, Daryl.

1018
01:20:27,906 --> 01:20:30,241
I'm freezing my nuts off out here.

1019
01:20:30,492 --> 01:20:33,077
I can't ask you in, I'm sorry.

1020
01:20:34,913 --> 01:20:38,666
Not even for a little while?
Just to dry off.

1021
01:20:39,751 --> 01:20:42,002
TaIk to the kids maybe.

1022
01:20:42,921 --> 01:20:45,256
No. You have to go away.

1023
01:20:45,924 --> 01:20:49,593
You have to go away now.
I can't see you or taIk to you.

1024
01:20:49,928 --> 01:20:52,263
I'm sorry, DaryI, but l can't!

1025
01:21:31,136 --> 01:21:32,303
Jane?

1026
01:21:43,857 --> 01:21:45,441
HelIo.

1027
01:21:48,528 --> 01:21:49,987
Give me that.

1028
01:22:11,801 --> 01:22:13,761
NURSE: Mrs. Spofford?
-What's wrong with me?

1029
01:22:13,929 --> 01:22:17,014
Nothing. You're pregnant.

1030
01:22:21,186 --> 01:22:22,853
Three or four weeks.

1031
01:22:25,440 --> 01:22:27,024
Are you sure?

1032
01:22:29,819 --> 01:22:33,656
I thought something was really wrong.
Are you sure?

1033
01:22:34,032 --> 01:22:35,908
Do you need a doctor?
We could recommend--

1034
01:22:36,076 --> 01:22:37,660
No, no, no, I-- No.

1035
01:22:37,869 --> 01:22:39,536
Thank you so much.

1036
01:22:40,538 --> 01:22:42,706
Mrs. Spofford, your cIothes.

1037
01:22:56,346 --> 01:22:58,305
SUKIE [OVER TV]:
<i>Do you think it ever happens?</i>

1038
01:22:59,391 --> 01:23:01,058
JANE:
<i>It starts when you open your eyes...</i>

1039
01:23:01,226 --> 01:23:03,727
<i>...and realize what the future</i>
<i>has in store for you.</i>

1040
01:23:03,895 --> 01:23:06,772
<i>DARYL: And what do you see</i>
<i>when you open your eyes?</i>

1041
01:23:09,734 --> 01:23:11,068
JANE:
<i>Well, short life.</i>

1042
01:23:11,569 --> 01:23:13,237
I want to surprise him.

1043
01:23:25,917 --> 01:23:28,252
JANE:
<i>lt's a short life, isn't it?</i>

1044
01:23:29,504 --> 01:23:32,423
<i>I look in the mirror</i>
<i>and see everything...</i>

1045
01:23:33,091 --> 01:23:35,592
<i>...disintegrating faster and faster.</i>

1046
01:23:37,512 --> 01:23:40,097
<i>lt's a short life, isn't it?</i>

1047
01:23:41,182 --> 01:23:44,435
<i>I look in the mirror</i>
<i>and see everything...</i>

1048
01:23:44,686 --> 01:23:46,937
<i>...disintegrating faster and faster.</i>

1049
01:23:49,274 --> 01:23:50,774
[JANE CONTlNUES TALKING OVER TV]

1050
01:24:23,475 --> 01:24:26,143
ALEX:
<i>They crawl all over me and l disappear.</i>

1051
01:24:26,478 --> 01:24:28,479
<i>Then l'm just not there anymore.</i>

1052
01:24:28,813 --> 01:24:29,980
Alex!

1053
01:24:31,858 --> 01:24:33,859
<i>I always see snakes.</i>

1054
01:24:35,153 --> 01:24:37,154
<i>Hundreds of them.</i>

1055
01:24:37,655 --> 01:24:41,909
<i>They crawl all over me and l disappear.</i>
<i>Then I'm just not there.</i>

1056
01:25:09,938 --> 01:25:11,355
[SCREAMlNG]

1057
01:25:26,538 --> 01:25:28,038
Alex, it's me.

1058
01:25:29,874 --> 01:25:33,710
It's me. Just let it go. Let it go!
Look at me!

1059
01:25:34,504 --> 01:25:38,632
Let it go. That's it. Just let it go.

1060
01:25:39,134 --> 01:25:42,553
<i>Pain scares me.</i>
<i>I don't know why there has to be...</i>

1061
01:25:43,721 --> 01:25:45,222
<i>...so much pain.</i>

1062
01:25:45,390 --> 01:25:47,558
[PHONE RlNGING]

1063
01:25:57,485 --> 01:25:59,903
SUKIE:
<i>I don't know why there has to be...</i>

1064
01:26:00,321 --> 01:26:01,989
<i>...so much pain.</i>

1065
01:26:06,327 --> 01:26:08,036
[SCREAMS]

1066
01:26:08,413 --> 01:26:10,414
[GASPlNG]

1067
01:26:25,597 --> 01:26:28,307
[PHONE RlNGING]

1068
01:27:12,977 --> 01:27:14,645
[WHISPERING]
Can we talk?

1069
01:27:17,482 --> 01:27:21,235
She's still hemorrhaging.
We sIowed it down, but....

1070
01:27:21,486 --> 01:27:22,611
Will she be all right?

1071
01:27:22,779 --> 01:27:25,906
If we knew what was wrong,
we'd have a chance.

1072
01:27:26,157 --> 01:27:27,407
Can we see her?

1073
01:27:27,992 --> 01:27:31,161
She's in a lot of pain.
I can't give her anything. . .

1074
01:27:31,329 --> 01:27:33,830
. ..until we know what
we're dealing with.

1075
01:27:34,040 --> 01:27:37,501
Okay. Go ahead.

1076
01:27:42,006 --> 01:27:44,841
ALEX: Sweetheart,
the doctor says you'll be fine.

1077
01:27:46,511 --> 01:27:48,845
He doesn't know what's going on.

1078
01:27:50,098 --> 01:27:53,016
[GASPlNG]

1079
01:27:53,184 --> 01:27:54,601
JANE:
Easy.

1080
01:27:57,855 --> 01:27:59,439
I'm pregnant.

1081
01:28:02,777 --> 01:28:04,361
So am l .

1082
01:28:09,075 --> 01:28:10,784
Alex?

1083
01:28:12,704 --> 01:28:14,705
That son of a bitch.

1084
01:28:14,872 --> 01:28:16,790
[GASPlNG]

1085
01:28:19,127 --> 01:28:21,712
Make him stop, pIease.
Make him stop.

1086
01:28:21,921 --> 01:28:23,922
I will, honey. I will.

1087
01:28:39,397 --> 01:28:41,565
ALEX:
Back off, Fidel!

1088
01:28:42,317 --> 01:28:44,943
DaryI? Daryl!

1089
01:28:45,361 --> 01:28:49,406
ANNOUNCER [OVER TV]:
<i>Tara Flavor, come on down!</i>

1090
01:28:55,705 --> 01:28:57,414
ALEX:
DaryI?

1091
01:28:57,749 --> 01:28:59,082
Alex?

1092
01:29:00,043 --> 01:29:02,461
-Don't "Alex" me.
-What a nice surprise.

1093
01:29:02,628 --> 01:29:04,546
What the helI do you think you're doing?

1094
01:29:04,714 --> 01:29:07,341
I said, what the hell
do you think you're doing?

1095
01:29:07,675 --> 01:29:09,343
A little housework.

1096
01:29:10,595 --> 01:29:14,765
I've been sending these shirts out,
but Jesus, they come back in pieces.

1097
01:29:15,141 --> 01:29:16,767
SmalI town.

1098
01:29:17,435 --> 01:29:19,102
Not enough Orientals.

1099
01:29:19,270 --> 01:29:22,439
FideI's aIl thumbs
with this kind of thing.

1100
01:29:22,940 --> 01:29:24,608
That just leaves me.

1101
01:29:24,776 --> 01:29:28,070
I'm not talking about your damn laundry,
I'm talking about...

1102
01:29:28,237 --> 01:29:30,280
. ..Sukie and Jane and me.

1103
01:29:31,532 --> 01:29:36,453
GoIly. You girls sure are having
a hard time, aren't you?

1104
01:29:38,039 --> 01:29:39,706
Sukie is very ill.

1105
01:29:42,585 --> 01:29:44,544
WeIl, I'm sorry to hear it.

1106
01:29:44,796 --> 01:29:46,546
Then do something about it!

1107
01:29:47,048 --> 01:29:50,133
Me? What can l do about it?

1108
01:29:50,635 --> 01:29:52,844
It has nothing to do with me anymore.

1109
01:29:53,262 --> 01:29:54,846
It does, and you know it does!

1110
01:29:55,390 --> 01:29:56,932
No, I don't.

1111
01:29:58,059 --> 01:30:02,187
All I know is we were friends
and the next day I was shut out.

1112
01:30:02,563 --> 01:30:04,064
That's aIl l know.

1113
01:30:04,857 --> 01:30:07,442
One minute l was the answer
to your prayers.

1114
01:30:07,610 --> 01:30:11,154
Five minutes Iater, you wouldn't
give me the time of the day.

1115
01:30:11,322 --> 01:30:14,491
Sukie couId die!
Don't you understand that?

1116
01:30:14,992 --> 01:30:18,495
-I can't help it.
-Yes, you can. Don't lie to me.

1117
01:30:20,164 --> 01:30:21,998
You deserted me.

1118
01:30:23,084 --> 01:30:24,543
We had a deal.

1119
01:30:24,710 --> 01:30:26,670
-That's no reason--
-Yes, it is.

1120
01:30:27,171 --> 01:30:28,713
You pissed me off!

1121
01:30:29,090 --> 01:30:31,007
Was l supposed to take it like a man?

1122
01:30:31,175 --> 01:30:32,467
I gave you everything I got!

1123
01:30:32,635 --> 01:30:35,846
I gave you more than anybody ever has,
and what do l get in exchange?

1124
01:30:36,013 --> 01:30:38,265
A little thank you?
A little gratitude?

1125
01:30:38,516 --> 01:30:40,559
I get screwed!

1126
01:30:40,768 --> 01:30:43,854
Oh, cut the crap!
What do you want from us?

1127
01:30:44,021 --> 01:30:47,023
I want somebody to do these shirts!

1128
01:30:47,692 --> 01:30:51,695
I want somebody to pay attention to me!
I want some respect!

1129
01:30:51,988 --> 01:30:55,490
I want somebody to take care
of me for a change!

1130
01:30:55,700 --> 01:30:57,909
Huh? How about that?

1131
01:30:58,202 --> 01:31:00,370
What do I want? Christ!

1132
01:31:01,205 --> 01:31:04,040
What does any man want?

1133
01:31:05,042 --> 01:31:06,710
A little affection.

1134
01:31:07,462 --> 01:31:09,379
A little trust.

1135
01:31:11,048 --> 01:31:12,466
Goddamn it.

1136
01:31:12,925 --> 01:31:16,386
Everything l did, I did for you.

1137
01:31:21,809 --> 01:31:23,435
I was wrong.

1138
01:31:23,978 --> 01:31:25,312
Go ahead.

1139
01:31:25,646 --> 01:31:30,066
Go back to your miserable littIe Iife.
Fuck me if I care!

1140
01:31:30,485 --> 01:31:34,321
If that's what you want,
that's what you get.

1141
01:31:34,822 --> 01:31:37,491
You are not the only three women
in the world.

1142
01:31:39,911 --> 01:31:41,912
You're hurting people, DaryI.

1143
01:31:43,498 --> 01:31:45,248
What you did for us was great.

1144
01:31:45,416 --> 01:31:48,001
But you can't use your power
to hurt people.

1145
01:31:49,754 --> 01:31:51,421
Don't you understand that?

1146
01:31:52,548 --> 01:31:53,965
No.

1147
01:31:54,592 --> 01:31:57,928
I want my family back together,
that's aIl.

1148
01:31:59,096 --> 01:32:00,263
You. . .

1149
01:32:00,681 --> 01:32:02,265
. ..and Sukie.. .

1150
01:32:02,433 --> 01:32:04,100
. ..and Jane.

1151
01:32:04,936 --> 01:32:06,770
I couldn't hurt Sukie.

1152
01:32:06,979 --> 01:32:10,190
I couldn't hurt any of you.
How could I?

1153
01:32:10,900 --> 01:32:12,108
I love you.

1154
01:32:12,276 --> 01:32:14,069
You don't know what love is.

1155
01:32:14,237 --> 01:32:16,863
I can learn.
You could teach me.

1156
01:32:17,073 --> 01:32:18,865
How hard can it be?

1157
01:32:20,326 --> 01:32:22,953
Oh, AIex, Iet's not fight.

1158
01:32:23,120 --> 01:32:26,456
You can't win.
There's no way you can win.

1159
01:32:26,958 --> 01:32:30,085
There's nothing to go back to,
even if you could win.

1160
01:32:30,253 --> 01:32:31,878
Can't we just. . .

1161
01:32:32,296 --> 01:32:34,965
. ..put this behind us and be friends?

1162
01:32:44,225 --> 01:32:45,642
There.

1163
01:32:46,143 --> 01:32:47,561
See?

1164
01:32:47,812 --> 01:32:49,646
Isn't that nice?

1165
01:32:52,066 --> 01:32:53,525
TeIl the truth.

1166
01:32:54,485 --> 01:32:57,320
You missed me a littIe bit, didn't you?

1167
01:32:57,822 --> 01:32:59,197
Huh?

1168
01:32:59,824 --> 01:33:01,825
Yeah, I have.

1169
01:33:02,410 --> 01:33:06,329
So let's kiss and make it better.

1170
01:33:07,748 --> 01:33:10,250
Huh? What do you say?

1171
01:33:12,837 --> 01:33:15,005
ALEX:
What are we going to do with you?

1172
01:33:16,591 --> 01:33:19,593
[EXHALlNG]

1173
01:33:21,971 --> 01:33:23,597
It stopped.

1174
01:34:21,197 --> 01:34:23,073
Darling, you Iook perfect.

1175
01:34:23,282 --> 01:34:25,033
Mm.

1176
01:34:28,829 --> 01:34:31,539
[JANE MOANS]

1177
01:34:32,917 --> 01:34:34,209
[CHUCKLES]

1178
01:34:34,502 --> 01:34:35,752
Hi.

1179
01:34:37,755 --> 01:34:39,130
You look gorgeous.

1180
01:34:39,298 --> 01:34:40,674
Thank you.

1181
01:34:40,841 --> 01:34:42,092
Feeling better?

1182
01:34:42,259 --> 01:34:45,929
Much better now.
Everything's going to be much better now.

1183
01:35:15,668 --> 01:35:17,335
[ALL MOANING]

1184
01:35:19,380 --> 01:35:20,964
[SUKIE LAUGHS]

1185
01:35:32,059 --> 01:35:33,476
FideI.

1186
01:35:33,644 --> 01:35:35,395
We're going to town.

1187
01:35:35,980 --> 01:35:40,942
The ladies have a craving
for bagels and ice cream.

1188
01:35:42,236 --> 01:35:43,737
[SPEAKS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]

1189
01:35:57,084 --> 01:35:58,793
[ENGlNE STARTS]

1190
01:36:52,056 --> 01:36:53,515
[RUMBLING]

1191
01:37:03,025 --> 01:37:05,026
Three pinches.

1192
01:37:12,993 --> 01:37:14,577
I'd like...

1193
01:37:14,829 --> 01:37:19,165
. ..a dozen bagels, a pound of gravlax and
what kind of ice cream do you have?

1194
01:37:19,416 --> 01:37:21,835
No ice cream. The freezer's broken.

1195
01:37:22,419 --> 01:37:24,087
Ice cream.

1196
01:37:24,255 --> 01:37:28,216
Um.... WeIl, ahem,
I'Il just take the bread and the fish.

1197
01:37:35,683 --> 01:37:37,016
JANE:
It doesn't look Iike him.

1198
01:37:37,184 --> 01:37:39,978
ALEX:
It doesn't have to. We know who it is.

1199
01:37:40,145 --> 01:37:43,356
He looks funny with no hair.

1200
01:37:43,524 --> 01:37:44,774
It won't hurt him, will it?

1201
01:37:44,942 --> 01:37:48,111
-No. We just want to send him away.
-Jane, come on.

1202
01:37:53,117 --> 01:37:55,535
No ice cream. Imagine that.

1203
01:37:56,120 --> 01:37:59,789
I'Il go see if I can't get some.
You go shopping.

1204
01:38:04,295 --> 01:38:08,298
I said, "A taIl, dark prince
traveIing under a curse."

1205
01:38:08,632 --> 01:38:10,300
"Somebody nice."

1206
01:38:10,634 --> 01:38:12,468
"Somebody you could talk to."

1207
01:38:12,636 --> 01:38:14,762
[WHISTLING]

1208
01:38:17,141 --> 01:38:18,808
-Morning.
-Good morning.

1209
01:38:19,018 --> 01:38:21,978
I'd like some pistachio.
That is pistachio?

1210
01:38:26,108 --> 01:38:30,528
And some chocolate-chocolate chip.

1211
01:38:31,405 --> 01:38:33,656
[SCREAMlNG]

1212
01:38:33,824 --> 01:38:36,034
CLERK: Are you okay?
-No, my Ieg!

1213
01:38:37,161 --> 01:38:38,953
Jesus Christ!

1214
01:38:39,163 --> 01:38:40,705
What is it?

1215
01:38:40,915 --> 01:38:42,123
[SCREAMlNG]

1216
01:38:44,835 --> 01:38:46,169
What's the matter?

1217
01:38:46,378 --> 01:38:48,129
[PANTlNG]

1218
01:38:48,505 --> 01:38:50,381
Are you having a heart attack?

1219
01:39:02,478 --> 01:39:05,021
[WHIMPERS]

1220
01:39:20,371 --> 01:39:22,038
GirIs!

1221
01:39:22,373 --> 01:39:25,208
GirIs? What are you doing?

1222
01:39:28,045 --> 01:39:31,965
GirIs! Girls! PIease, don't!

1223
01:39:36,178 --> 01:39:38,179
[GRUNTING]

1224
01:40:06,125 --> 01:40:08,459
Elijah fled to the mount of God.

1225
01:40:08,752 --> 01:40:12,255
The Lord passed by and a great,
strong wind rent the mountains. . .

1226
01:40:12,423 --> 01:40:14,590
. ..and breaked in pieces
the rocks before the Lord....

1227
01:40:14,758 --> 01:40:16,092
[DOORS OPEN lNG]

1228
01:40:16,260 --> 01:40:18,261
[WlND HOWLlNG]

1229
01:40:20,347 --> 01:40:22,348
[PREACHER TALKlNG lNDlSTlNCTLY]

1230
01:40:30,691 --> 01:40:32,316
[PEOPLE MURMURlNG]

1231
01:40:32,484 --> 01:40:33,735
[LOCK CLICKS]

1232
01:40:34,486 --> 01:40:36,237
[GROWLS]

1233
01:40:38,574 --> 01:40:39,782
[WOMEN GASP]

1234
01:40:45,122 --> 01:40:46,456
Sorry.

1235
01:40:47,291 --> 01:40:49,292
Just having a little trouble.

1236
01:40:50,002 --> 01:40:53,004
A little. ..troubIe at home.

1237
01:40:54,465 --> 01:40:56,632
A little domestic probIem.

1238
01:41:05,309 --> 01:41:08,311
Nothing to be alarmed at.

1239
01:41:11,482 --> 01:41:15,026
Just a little femaIe probIem.

1240
01:41:18,155 --> 01:41:19,197
[RETCHlNG]

1241
01:41:19,364 --> 01:41:21,324
[PEOPLE GASPlNG AND CHATTERlNG]

1242
01:41:22,326 --> 01:41:24,869
[CROWD SHOUTING]

1243
01:41:30,167 --> 01:41:32,001
Don't pay any attention.

1244
01:41:32,544 --> 01:41:34,545
It's a cheap trick.

1245
01:41:34,838 --> 01:41:38,174
Anybody can do it.
I taught it to them myself.

1246
01:41:39,218 --> 01:41:41,677
UngratefuI little bitches, aren't they?

1247
01:41:42,346 --> 01:41:45,681
I want to ask you something.
You alI go to church.

1248
01:41:46,016 --> 01:41:52,438
Do you think God knew what he
was doing when he created woman? Huh?

1249
01:41:52,606 --> 01:41:54,899
No shit! I really want to know.

1250
01:41:55,234 --> 01:41:58,361
Or do you think it was
one of his minor mistakes?

1251
01:41:58,570 --> 01:42:02,031
Like tidaI waves! Earthquakes! Floods!

1252
01:42:03,575 --> 01:42:05,910
Do you think women are like that?

1253
01:42:07,121 --> 01:42:09,455
[GRUNTING]

1254
01:42:09,623 --> 01:42:12,041
[RETCHlNG]

1255
01:42:15,295 --> 01:42:17,296
[PANTlNG]

1256
01:42:23,220 --> 01:42:24,846
What's the matter?

1257
01:42:27,558 --> 01:42:30,226
You don't think God makes mistakes?

1258
01:42:32,396 --> 01:42:34,230
Of course he does.

1259
01:42:34,731 --> 01:42:36,899
We alI make mistakes.

1260
01:42:39,570 --> 01:42:42,738
Of course, we make mistakes,
they calI it eviI.

1261
01:42:43,448 --> 01:42:48,411
When God makes mistakes,
they calI it nature.

1262
01:42:48,579 --> 01:42:51,080
[CHUCKLES]

1263
01:42:51,248 --> 01:42:52,915
So what do you think?

1264
01:42:53,125 --> 01:42:55,960
Women. A mistake?

1265
01:42:56,795 --> 01:43:01,090
Or did he do it to us on purpose?

1266
01:43:01,258 --> 01:43:03,259
I really want to know!

1267
01:43:03,427 --> 01:43:06,971
If it's a mistake, maybe we can
do something about it!

1268
01:43:07,264 --> 01:43:09,098
Find a cure!

1269
01:43:10,434 --> 01:43:12,268
Invent a vaccine.

1270
01:43:15,272 --> 01:43:17,398
Build up our immune systems.

1271
01:43:17,566 --> 01:43:21,444
[LAUGH lNG]

1272
01:43:21,612 --> 01:43:25,198
Get a littIe exercise.

1273
01:43:26,950 --> 01:43:29,785
You know. Twenty pushups a day...

1274
01:43:29,953 --> 01:43:34,790
. ..and you never have to be affIicted
with women, ever again!

1275
01:43:35,876 --> 01:43:39,378
[GROANING]

1276
01:44:05,656 --> 01:44:06,822
[SIGHS]

1277
01:44:06,990 --> 01:44:08,699
All right, that's it.

1278
01:44:09,326 --> 01:44:10,993
How do we know it worked?

1279
01:44:11,328 --> 01:44:13,663
I guess we just wait and see.

1280
01:44:15,165 --> 01:44:17,500
My God, look at this place.

1281
01:44:19,544 --> 01:44:21,420
-Just in case.
-Okay.

1282
01:44:26,093 --> 01:44:27,176
[GROWLlNG]

1283
01:44:39,273 --> 01:44:41,190
[ENGlNE STARTS]

1284
01:45:01,670 --> 01:45:05,047
[GRUNTING]

1285
01:45:05,299 --> 01:45:08,342
[BARKING]

1286
01:45:26,778 --> 01:45:29,155
[BIKER SCREAMS]

1287
01:45:33,118 --> 01:45:36,704
[DOG CONTINUES BARKING]

1288
01:45:36,872 --> 01:45:38,205
No!

1289
01:45:38,373 --> 01:45:40,458
[SCREAMlNG]

1290
01:46:09,321 --> 01:46:11,280
SUKIE:
Here, here. Quick. Okay.

1291
01:46:13,075 --> 01:46:14,992
[BARKING]

1292
01:46:49,277 --> 01:46:51,362
[GRUNTING]

1293
01:46:51,530 --> 01:46:54,115
[SN lFFlNG]

1294
01:46:57,661 --> 01:46:59,662
[GRUNTING]

1295
01:47:09,005 --> 01:47:10,673
[GROWLS]

1296
01:47:14,719 --> 01:47:19,056
[GROWLlNG]

1297
01:47:58,054 --> 01:47:59,096
[NECK CRACKS]

1298
01:48:00,557 --> 01:48:01,724
[SUKIE PANTlNG]

1299
01:48:01,892 --> 01:48:03,225
The doll.

1300
01:48:04,769 --> 01:48:05,811
[SCREAMS]

1301
01:48:11,193 --> 01:48:13,194
[WOMEN SCREAMING]

1302
01:48:16,573 --> 01:48:17,990
[SCREAMS]

1303
01:48:27,125 --> 01:48:29,460
-Jane! Jane.
BOTH: Aah!

1304
01:48:30,420 --> 01:48:32,254
[LAUGHS]

1305
01:48:32,422 --> 01:48:34,089
Jane, laugh!

1306
01:48:34,257 --> 01:48:36,634
[BOTH LAUGH]

1307
01:48:37,677 --> 01:48:39,011
[LAUGHS]

1308
01:48:39,179 --> 01:48:41,096
[WHIMPERS]

1309
01:48:51,149 --> 01:48:54,109
[GROWLlNG]

1310
01:49:01,576 --> 01:49:02,576
[SUKIE GASPS]

1311
01:49:02,744 --> 01:49:05,788
[ALL SCREAMING]

1312
01:49:47,163 --> 01:49:49,164
[THUDDING]

1313
01:49:52,961 --> 01:49:54,962
[RUMBLING]

1314
01:49:58,758 --> 01:50:00,175
[SCREAMlNG]

1315
01:50:20,071 --> 01:50:22,615
[ROARING]

1316
01:51:03,031 --> 01:51:05,866
[MOAN lNG SOFTLY]

1317
01:51:29,724 --> 01:51:31,725
[BABlES BABBLING]

1318
01:51:36,481 --> 01:51:37,981
SUKIE:
Come here, you.

1319
01:51:42,946 --> 01:51:47,783
JANE:
Come on, sweet pea, come on. Oh.

1320
01:51:47,951 --> 01:51:51,537
ALEX:
Come on, littIe mookie boy, come on.

1321
01:51:53,039 --> 01:51:55,040
[BABlES BABBLING]

1322
01:51:56,126 --> 01:51:57,626
[CHUCKLES]

1323
01:51:57,794 --> 01:52:00,546
What a big guy! Sweetheart.

1324
01:52:02,298 --> 01:52:05,467
Look at Fidel.
What does he have for you?

1325
01:52:09,723 --> 01:52:11,724
[CHILDREN CHATTERlNG]

1326
01:52:26,823 --> 01:52:28,157
Janey, stop it.

1327
01:52:28,867 --> 01:52:30,159
What?

1328
01:52:30,493 --> 01:52:31,952
Just stop it.

1329
01:52:32,662 --> 01:52:34,705
I can think about him if l want to.

1330
01:52:34,873 --> 01:52:36,665
Not when we're all together.

1331
01:52:36,833 --> 01:52:38,792
I miss him. I can't help it.

1332
01:52:39,002 --> 01:52:40,919
I do, and so do you. Admit it.

1333
01:52:41,087 --> 01:52:42,671
Okay, we admit it.

1334
01:52:42,881 --> 01:52:44,548
Do you want him back?

1335
01:52:55,101 --> 01:52:56,226
[MOUTHING]

1336
01:52:56,394 --> 01:52:58,395
[PLAYING]

1337
01:53:16,706 --> 01:53:19,458
[HORN SOUNDS]

1338
01:53:32,096 --> 01:53:34,097
[OVERLAPPING NOlSES OVER TV]

1339
01:53:39,729 --> 01:53:41,230
DARYL:
<i>Take it easy.</i>

1340
01:53:41,397 --> 01:53:44,900
<i>We don't want the whole household</i>
<i>in here, do we?</i>

1341
01:53:45,401 --> 01:53:47,402
<i>That's it. Good boys.</i>

1342
01:53:47,612 --> 01:53:49,947
<i>We're going to do just fine.</i>

1343
01:53:51,783 --> 01:53:55,118
<i>Come to Daddy and give me a big kiss.</i>

1344
01:53:55,286 --> 01:53:58,539
<i>Come on. Good boys. Come on.</i>

1345
01:53:58,748 --> 01:54:00,791
<i>Come to Daddy.</i>

1346
01:54:00,959 --> 01:54:05,504
<i>Coochie-coochie-coo.</i>
<i>That's it. Come on.</i>

1347
01:54:05,713 --> 01:54:07,923
<i>Come on. Come on.</i>

1348
01:54:08,258 --> 01:54:09,633
[DARYL CHUCKLES]

1349
01:54:14,472 --> 01:54:17,432
<i>Oh, ladies, come on.</i>

1350
01:57:55,109 --> 01:57:57,110
[ENGLISH - US - SDH]

