Some say juvenile.
I say genius!
Lizzie: Leave me alone!
Matt, I'm getting ready
for graduation!
Matt!
Say goodbye to your little toy.
And say hello to Matt owning
his big sister for eternity!
¶ Never give up ¶
¶ yeah, yeah ¶
¶ never give up ¶
¶ the tide is high,
but I'm holding on ¶
¶ I'm gonna be
your number one ¶
¶ I'm not the kind of girl ¶
¶ who gives up just like that ¶
¶ oh, no ¶
¶ it's not the things you do
that tease and hurt me bad ¶
¶ but it's the way you do
the things you do to me ¶
¶ I'm not the kind of girl ¶
¶ who gives up just like that ¶
¶ no ¶
¶ oh, no ¶
¶ the tide is high,
but I'm holding on ¶
¶ I'm gonna be
your number one ¶
¶ ahh ¶
¶ the tide is high,
but I'm holding on ¶
¶ I'm gonna be ¶
¶ I'm gonna be
your number one ¶
¶ ooh
¶ number one
¶ number one ¶
¶ every girl wants you
to be her man ¶
¶ but I'll wait right here
till it's my turn ¶
¶ I'm not the kind of girl ¶
¶ who gives up just like that ¶
¶ oh, no ¶
¶ the tide is high,
but I'm holding on ¶
¶ I'm gonna be
your number one ¶
¶ the tide is high
¶ the tide is high,
but I'm holding on ¶
¶ I'm gonna be
your number one ¶
¶ ooh
¶ number one
¶ number one ¶
¶ gotta hold on ¶
¶ every time
that I get the feeling ¶
¶ you give me something
to believe in ¶
¶ every time
that I got you near me ¶
¶ I know the way
that I want it to be ¶
¶ but you know
I'm gonna take my chance now ¶
¶ I'm gonna make it happen
somehow ¶
¶ and you know
i can take the pressure ¶
¶ a moment's pain
for a lifetime of pleasure ¶
¶ pleasure, pleasure,
pleasure... ¶
¶ every girl wants you
to be her man ¶
¶ but I'll wait right here
till it's my turn ¶
¶ I'm not the kind of girl ¶
¶ who gives up just like that ¶
¶ oh, no
¶ no, no, no, no, no ¶
¶ the tide is high,
but I'm holding on ¶
¶ yeah ¶
¶ I'm gonna be
your number one ¶
¶ yeah, yeah, yeah
¶ the tide is high
¶ but I'm holding on
¶ I'm gonna be
your number one ¶
whoa!
¶ Every time
that I get the feeling ¶
¶ you give me something
to believe in ¶
¶ every time
that I got you near me ¶
whoa! Aah!
¶ I know the way
that I want it to be ¶
wah!
¶ But you know
I'm gonna take my chance now ¶
¶ I'm gonna make it happen
somehow ¶
¶ and you know
i can take the pressure ¶
¶ a moment's pain
for a lifetime of pleasure ¶
¶ the tide is high... ¶
I shall win the academy award!
I mean, yesterday,
you were in diapers,
and now you're graduating
junior high.
You're growing up,
and I can't believe
you're going to Rome
for two weeks
all by yourself...
Without me...
without me... There...
With you...
without me with you there...
you there without me.
Mom, I think that's about
all the combinations of
those words you can make.
Lizzie, this is a big day
for you, sweetheart.
He's going to
quote a dead guy.
As William Shakespeare
once wrote,
"be not afraid of greatness:
"Some are born great,
some achieve greatness,
and some have greatness
thrust upon them."
Thanks, dad, but I'm
just trying to get
through graduation.
Greatness can wait
till this nightmare's over.
Hey, gordo.
So, do I look okay?
Lizzie,
I'm your guy best friend.
You should really talk
to Miranda about this stuff.
But she's in Mexico city.
Yes... your blue robe
looks way cooler
than all the other girls'.
Thanks.
Oh... My... God.
Only you would think that
you could hide that powder-blue,
puffy-sleeved,
it's-kind-of-a-peasant-dress-
but-it-might-just-be-
a-baggy-disaster-of-
questionable-fiber-content
that you wore
to the spring dance.
I...
Lizzie McGuire, you are
an outfit repeater!
But I...
Maybe I'm an outfit repeater,
but you're
an outfit rememberer,
which is just as pathetic.
Okay, does she not have
anything better to do
than make my life miserable?
I mean...
We used to be best friends.
Yeah, but that was before
she became popular.
McGuire!
Go.
Hey, Mr. Escobar.
Nice after-shave.
Oh, thank you.
Margaret Chan either has ebola
or a very bad cold.
In any event, you're up.
U-u-u-up where?
At the podium.
You are going to deliver
the class president's speech.
B-b-b-but what about
the vice president?
Well, he's not graduating.
The secretary treasurer's
next in line.
A-all I did was handle
petty cash.
Well, I'm sorry,
but you're not buying
your way out of this.
Now, I want you
to deliver your speech
with as much pride
and commitment
as Margaret Chan would...
Even though you're no
Margaret Chan.
You're no Margaret Chan.
Run!!
Ladies and gentlemen,
uh, Lizzie McGuire.
Um...
U-uh, Margaret Chan
couldn't make it tonight,
so I'm going... I'm going to
be filling in for her.
Not that any of us
could really do that,
but, um... Anyway...
Honey...
Honey, I'm losing the feeling
in my knuckles.
I think that
we can all agree that...
Okay.
Junior high is filled with...
Embarrassing and awkward
and sometimes just downright
humiliating moments... Right?
Uh...
Oh!
Me neither.
It is so sad.
Wow.
It's like watching one
of those little furry animals
get killed
on the discovery channel.
Mmm, I-I-I think Margaret Chan
would want me to have
some water right now.
Uhh! Oh!
Oh!
Play something!
Do something!
Yes! Ha ha ha!
Come on! Mom! Dad!
I've got to get out
of the country! Hurry!
Oh, honey, I know
you're still upset,
but it wasn't that bad.
Oh, really, mom?
Was your junior-high graduation
on "good morning America"?
What kind of creep would send
Diane Sawyer a video
to embarrass you like that?
Oh.
Ugh!
What is that?
That is miss ungermeyer.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey!
She's gonna be
our high-school principal
for the next four years.
If you stay on her good side,
it's a one-way ticket
to an Ivy league school.
And what if
you're on her bad side?
Excuse me!
I need to mop up some puke.
Well, you...
You wind up as that guy?
No. You end up working
for that guy.
Miss ungermeyer...
Can you make sure
that there are no garlic
or soy products in
anything my Brittany
puts near her mouth?
Miss ungermeyer,
Luke has tennis elbow.
Could somebody please
carry his luggage?
Miss ungermeyer,
my son has asthma,
and he must have his puffer.
Now, Brittany,
she's got allergies...
Miss ungermeyer...
Attention, parents...
Shut your pie holes.
I'm on a mission here...
To drag your progeny
to 31 historically significant
Roman landmarks
in two weeks.
Now, when these back-talking
miscreants return to you,
they will have dipped their toes
in a lake of culture,
before assuming their destiny
folding shirts
at the outlet mall.
Now, many... actually,
most of your classmates opted
for the 36-hour bus ride
to the water-slide wonderland.
Whoo!
But you...
You, who are not
mouth-breathing trailer trash,
you will get to experience
the delights
of LA città eterna.
Hmm-hmm.
Rome. The eternal city.
Did no one read
the info packets?
Watch and learn.
Um, miss ungermeyer...
I just wanted to
let you know that I'm...
I'm really looking forward
to this exciting
and academically enriching trip.
What's your name?
David Gordon.
Mm-hmm.
Now, I think in Italian,
that means a sneaky brownnoser
with a hidden agenda.
Huh?
- What?
- Uh, uh...
Yeah! Come on,
check those bags!
I want to see that junk
in the trunk
and a seat looking neat.
Okay.
Mom...
Okay, it's only two weeks, mom.
Honey, she...
she's got to go.
Two weeks.
Bye, sweetie.
Bye.
Safe trip, huh?
Okay.
Sweetheart...
Okay?
Mm-hmm.
Flight 72 to Rome.
Final boarding,
flight 72 to Rome.
Hey!
We're going to the land
where they invented spaghetti!
Ah heh.
All passengers now...
Yeah, and the best part is
Kate and all of
the little blow-drying,
teeth-whitening friends
who'd be ragging
on me right now for
messing up graduation
all went to
water-slide wonderland.
How many lizzies does it take
to screw in a lightbulb?
I don't know, but it only takes
one to screw up a graduation.
Hey. Zip it.
Whoa!
¶ Down each Avenue or via,
street or strata ¶
¶ you can see 'em disappearing
two by two ¶
¶ on an evening in roma
¶ do they take 'em
for espresso? ¶
¶ yeah, I guess so
¶ on each lover's arm,
a girl I wish I knew ¶
¶ on an evening in roma
¶ so please meet me
in the Plaza near your casa ¶
¶ I am only one,
and that is one too few ¶
¶ on an evening in roma
¶ don't know what
the country's coming to ¶
¶ but in Rome,
do as the romans do ¶
¶ will you?
¶ On an evening in roma
Here we are.
Step right up.
Number one...
Number two...
Welcome to the hotel cambini.
Now, lest you think
that there are many of you
and less of me
and it will therefore be easy
to pull anything over on me,
think again.
In addition to my being
smarter, faster,
and better-looking than
most of you... heh heh...
I've also enlisted
a little help.
The assistant manager
of the hotel, giorgio averni,
was a commander
in the Italian Navy
and is therefore
as up on his game as I am mine.
Giorgio, would you like
to brief my students
on the security procedures
of the hotel?
We serve... At 5:00...
The cookies.
Yeah.
You heard the man.
Room assignments.
David Gordon...
You will be rooming
with Ethan craft.
You'll be in room 103.
Are those English
or Italian numbers?
You got a problem with that,
Gordon?
Um... No, ma'am.
Um, any... any room is
just... just fine for me.
You know, being
a spineless little jellyfish
is almost as unattractive
as being a little brownnoser.
McGuire!
Seeing as how Margaret Chan
was unable to make the trip,
you will be rooming with...
Okay, I am not,
under any circumstances,
sharing a room with...
I'll be taking the bed
by the window.
You don't mind, do you?
Uh...
Ye-e-e-e-s!!
No.
I sleep much better
with the Swiss eiderdown.
Lizzie, seeing as we're roomies
and we're gonna be spending
all this time together,
I just wanted to
let you know I understand
that you want to put all
that really embarrassing
stuff behind you
and just move on
and have a fresh start.
You do?
Yes.
I understand your dream.
It's a big dream.
It's a huge dream,
and you can't do it alone.
In fact, I don't think
you can do it at all.
Let it go.
Lizzie, come on.
Whoa!
Gordo, what?
Don't... don't worry.
Don't worry.
Where are we going?
Look.
Wow!
Pretty cool, huh?
You know what, gordo?
I'm not gonna let
Kate Sanders get to me.
Promise me something.
Anything.
Promise me
that when we're here,
we'll find adventures.
All right? This is
our chance to start over...
I mean, do anything
that we want to do.
Yeah. I-I know.
You're right.
Hmm. You and me...
adventures. Deal.
Deal.
The trevi fountain was designed
by gian lorenza bernini
and peitro da cortona
in the 17th century.
And I'll tell you, it
took about 100 years
to finish this bad boy.
Now, throughout history,
people have come
from all over the world
to make a wish and toss their
coin in the trevi fountain.
I'll tell you something... those
people are suckers, all right?
You got to make your own luck
in this world.
All right, moving on, people.
Let's go.
Scusi.
Grazie.
Scusi. Grazie.
You know what?
Forget what she says.
Make a wish.
I'm in Rome
with my best friend.
I'm good.
You make one.
Okay.
Hmm.
Isabella?
Huh?
Okay, I was wishing for smooth
sailing through high school,
but this will work.
Uh, I'm sorry.
It's just...
You look an awful lot
like a friend of mine.
Paolo...
You have to get
to your photo shoot.
We got to go.
All right, what you
little halflings are
feeling right about now
is your energy flagging.
We got four more stops today.
I want you people to
at least be able to shuffle
from monument to monument.
We got one word for that,
and it's gelato.
Look... it's him.
Now, keep in mind
that Italian ice cream has
about twice the sugar
of American ice cream.
Means you're gonna want about
two scoops, huh?
I know i do.
All right.
I-I don't mean
to bother you.
I'm Paolo...
Paolo valisari.
Oh, um, I'm Lizzie McGuire,
and this is
my friend gordo.
Hey.
This is my friend Sergei.
Sergei, doesn't she look
exactly like Isabella?
Isabella!
Paolo!
Um...
Woman: Isabella!
Isabella!
Paolo! Paolo!
Ciao, Paolo!
Uh, hmm...
Wow!
That really does look like me.
Paolo: Except for the hair,
you could be her twin.
Isabella is my singing partner,
and you're like her sister...
like, uh...
Two pods in a pea.
Lizzie...
Can I see you again?
Maybe tomorrow?
Please?
What's the word for "yes"
in Italian?
Si.
Uh...
No, I'm...
I-it's okay.
I-I-I can cover for you.
Miss ungermeyer:
Head check!
I'm sorry. I'm here
with my school, so I can't.
1...2...3...
forgive me
if I embarrassed you.
All right,
stop moving around.
It is just that some people,
when they come to Rome,
they want to find
adventure.
1...2...
Oh, it's okay.
...3...4...
I got some cool cheese.
...5...6...
Did you just say "cool cheese"?
Wah!
8...9...
Paolo...
We must go.
...10...
Uh, Lizzie...
If you change your mind,
I will meet you
tomorrow morning
at the trevi fountain
at 9:00.
Hey, Gordon...
McGuire...
Did you not hear me say
"head check"?
15...16...
Who are you?
Paolo valisari.
Put your money
in your front pockets.
She makes me very scared.
Join the club.
Lizzie...
Ci vediamo.
What does that mean?
We will see each other.
Hey.
You know, this
Paolo and Isabella
cd isn't so bad.
I mean, if you're into
the alanis morissette-y,
alternative, dark,
like, brooding,
I-never-go-out-
into-the-sunshine-
and-my-life's-a-miserable-
black-hole-of-depression
kind of thing,
then you'd think they stink.
But, I mean, for a, like,
driving-around-in-the-car-
with-the-top-down,
putting-on-your-lip-gloss,
loving-life kind of thing,
they're good.
Here. Listen.
¶ You don't have to sail
the ocean ¶
yeah, not bad.
You use scented soap, huh?
What?
Um, it...
n-never... never mind.
So,
Paolo wants me to meet him
at the trevi fountain tomorrow.
So go.
But that would mean
I would have to sneak
away from the group.
So?
So I'm, like, physically
incapable of sneaking.
Lizzie, weren't you the one
that said that we were gonna
have adventures on this trip?
Yeah... we. We were
going to have adventures.
And we will.
It just so happens that
you have dibs on the first one.
Okay.
Just as long
as we don't do anything
that would get us
tossed on a plane home
by miss ungermeyer.
Uh... Unh.
Lizzie, are...
are you feeling okay?
Uh...
Is this girl sick,
or isn't she?
She doesn't have a fever,
and yet she's in bed.
Ask yourself why
a beautiful young girl
on her first visit to Rome,
probably seeking adventure,
wants to lie in bed all day.
She's ill.
You know, I heard
she fell down at graduation,
made a complete fool
out of herself.
And you think that could have
something to do with this?
I saw that on CNN.
CNN?
Often, the nervous system
collapses
after that type
of utter humiliation.
Hmm.
Do you have
any recommendations?
Oh, yeah, yeah. Um...
This young woman
should stay in bed.
Uh, she... she should
also eat two apricots.
Oh, for digestion or...
Uh, no, they're in season...
very delicious.
Feel better, signorina McGuire.
You rest up, McGuire.
Don't want you to miss out
on all the adventures of Rome.
Uh, doctor, I have a boil...
Sorry.
Uno, due, tre.
Tre.
Bene.
I...I just...
I had them all wish
for you to come.
Hmm...
I don't have much time.
You know my chaperon,
miss ungermeyer...
Wait, wait, wait.
I have to show you something.
¶ Sometimes the world
¶ is a valley
of heartaches and tears ¶
come on.
¶ And in the hustle and bustle,
no sunshine appears ¶
¶ but you and I have a love
always there to remind us... ¶
wow!
I just thought you should see
Rome the way romans do.
So you knew that I would come.
I hoped you would.
Are you sure you know
how to drive this thing?
This is Rome.
Nobody knows how to drive.
¶ Volare
¶ oh, oh
¶ cantare
¶ oh, oh, oh, oh
¶ let's fly
way up to the clouds ¶
¶ away from
the maddening crowds ¶
¶ we can sing in the glow
of a star that I know of ¶
¶ where lovers enjoy
peace of mind ¶
¶ let us leave the confusion
and all disillusion behind ¶
aah!
¶ Just like birds
of a feather ¶
¶ and the rainbow together
we'll find ¶
¶ volare
¶ oh, oh
¶ cantare
¶ oh, oh, oh, oh
Whoo!
¶ Volare
¶ oh, oh
¶ cantare
¶ oh, oh, oh, oh
¶ no wonder
my happy heart sings ¶
¶ your love has given me
wings ¶
¶ no wonder
my happy heart sings ¶
oh, my gosh!
¶ Your love has given me
wings ¶
wow!
I don't know what catastrophe
is going to happen in Rome,
but with Lizzie there,
something will.
And what precisely
are you going to do
with that information...
just give it away, like you did
with the graduation video?
Hey! She was really
freaked out by that.
And you have what
to show for it?
The pride of a job well done?
Try buying a ps2 with
the pride of a job well done.
Oh!
Matt, Matt, Matt...
We've been over this
before... cash up front.
Melina...
Are you staying for dinner?
I'd love to,
Mrs. McGuire.
Great.
We'll need extra energy
to work on
our summer reading list.
Well, in that case,
I'll make some brownies.
Oh.
I've said it before...
you're weak! Weak!
Don't do anything
without consulting me first.
You rock.
Hey, Paolo...
Can I ask you something?
Si, carina.
Um... I know that our lives
are a little different...
actually, like several
universes different.
But doesn't your friend
Sergei ever get tired
of following us around
everywhere?
Actually,
Sergei's my bodyguard.
So, you see,
between me and Sergei,
you'll always be safe.
Whoa!
How famous do you have to be
before you need a bodyguard?
Paolo, go! Go!
I-it's miss ungermeyer!
It's our bus!
Go, go, go!
I cannot.
Excuse me,
miss... miss ungermeyer...
Didn't we just pass
the castel sant'angelo?
Yep. What about it?
Oh, I just noticed
that it's not on our itinerary.
That is correct.
Well, s-shouldn't it be?
I-I mean, it...
it w-was a papal residence,
and it does contain frescoes
from artists influenced
by the school of Raphael.
What are you up to, Gordon?
N-n-nothing.
I-I just figure that,
While in Rome,
we should be exposed
to as much renaissance,
raphaelite work
typified by chiaroscuro
and hellenic mythical imagery
as humanly possible.
Whew.
Ah, Gordon...
You are on the list.
And the list is not a place
you want to be.
What is this?
Only in Rome, huh?
You know how to
move that thing,
or you want me
to do it for ya?!
What are you looking at?
Want a piece of that...
a piece of the ungermeyer?
And over there
by that statue...
you see it?
Yeah.
That's where
the artist caravaggio
had his opponent
burned at the stake.
Oh, wait...
or was it the pope
who had caravaggio burned
at the stake?
Either way,
this neighborhood was tough.
Paolo...
Si, carina?
Do... You still love her?
Who? Isabella?
Si.
Of course I still love her.
But like a sister.
So why did you break up?
It's, um...
It's complicated.
What?
I mean, yes, we've been
voted "best pop duo
of the year" again.
Uh, but I want to do
more serious music.
And when I told this
to Isabella,
she said flat-out "no."
So I was forced to tell her,
"this is it.
This will be
our last cd together."
What did she do?
Did she totally freak out?
She totally freak out.
And, yes, I feel awful about
that, but what about me?
I need to grow
as an artist, you know?
Yeah.
So, the other day
when I saw you,
I just... I don't know,
I had this crazy...
I just... I don't know.
W-what?
I had this crazy idea
that maybe you could help me.
Come on. How crazy could it be?
Just tell me.
No, I can't.
It's too... it's too...
Please.
Okay.
Isabella and I are supposed to
present an award together
at the international
music video awards.
Cool!
I-I mean, cool for
regular people like me,
but for you,
I guess it's just like work.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I-it's cool for me, too.
You get all kinds of free
gift baskets and stuff.
But now because Isabella's
so mad at me,
she's refusing to appear.
The record company's
threatening to sue her
if she doesn't show up.
And what about you?
For me is no problem.
I write the music.
I don't know
where it comes from.
It just comes from me.
¶ LA LA LA LA
see?
So I can go solo.
But Isabella...
She needs the help to sing.
You mean Isabella
lip-synchs?!
Please, please, please,
please, please!
You must promise me you will
speak of this to no one.
Imagine what would happen
to Isabella's career.
Oh, that's so sweet.
You still care about her.
You're definitely
broken up, right?
Si.
So, when I saw you yesterday
and I saw how all
those people thought
you were Isabella,
I got my crazy idea
that maybe you could...
Pretend to be Isabella
for one night
and present the award
with me onstage.
Present an award?
O-onstage?
In front of an audience?
I-I-I'm really not good
in front of crowds.
I could never do that.
Of course you can do it.
You are magnifico.
I don't know Italian...
But I know what that means.
I don't know, Paolo.
I...
Don't worry, carina.
I could never ask you to do
this crazy thing.
No. You know what?
You don't have to ask.
If this is gonna help
you and Isabella, then...
I'll do it.
Grazie!
Prego!
Head check!
Gordo. Gordo.
You, Lizzie McGuire,
are actually presenting an award
at the imvas with Paolo?
No...
me Isabella with Paolo.
What?
It's a long story,
but I'm doing it because
the real Isabella won't.
You're actually gonna
get up onstage in front
of all these people?
Well, that's the great
thing about it, gordo,
is it's not gonna be me.
It's Paolo's idea
to help Isabella
because he still loves her.
- But not romantically...
- like a sister.
He is so amazing.
And he's 17!
I mean, for being so famous
and so used to getting
everything that you want,
he's just...
He's just so kind.
For real?
Look, that's a lot
to say about someone
just knowing them a day.
I-I know that.
But I feel like
I've known him my whole life,
you know?
A-anyway, um...
I just wanted to come by today
and thank you.
I mean, I had the most
magical day of my life,
and it wouldn't have happened
if it weren't for you.
It was that good, huh?
You're such a good friend.
The sting.
What sting?
You want a little mano a mano?
See, this is one of the reasons
that me and you
aren't friends...
'cause I-I never have any idea
what you're talking about.
You see, some dudes
get the approach.
Others, the sting.
That Italian dude...
he's big-time approach.
I actually feel my brain
turning into goo.
Embrace the sting.
That's what you're vibin' here
from Lizzie.
Wait a minute.
Now, you actually think
that I'm jealous of Paolo?
Word.
Oh, no.
No, see, that would mean
that I like Lizzie
as more than a friend.
See? What do you mean
you and I have trouble
communicating, bro?
You're wrong, man.
Whoa!
This girl looks freakishly
like my sister!
Ow.
Zoom! Zoom!
Another freakish coincidence.
I mean, she has the same
necklace as my sister's.
Huh.
Why do we even pretend
you're in charge?
Okay, let's see
what this says.
Ow.
"Isabella goes blond.
"Italian pop duo
Paolo and Isabella
"wowed the crowd
outside a gelato shop
"near the trevi fountain,
showing off Isabella's
new blond hair."
They must think that Lizzie
is this famous singer!
And if I show this to my mom,
Lizzie will be so busted!
If you show this to your mom,
it's worth nothing.
But if you show this
to the Italian tabloids...
we will be rolling in cash,
my friend.
Interesting!
"We"?
Not up to toughing it
out on the streets with
us, miss McGuire?
I could try, miss ungermeyer...
No, I just hate seeing you
being denied
the cultural experience
of being in a foreign country.
I mean, you missed seven points
of historical significance
yesterday.
I know. It's really
killing me too,
miss ungermeyer.
Which is why I thought
I'd bring you a little something
to help ease the pain, hmm?
Mmh, well, that's really
thoughtful of you.
Well, seeing as how
your teeny-tiny little body
just doesn't have the strength,
we're gonna have to let
your mind do the wandering.
Ah!
The rise and decline
of the Roman empire, hmm.
I'd like one report on the rise
and one on the decline.
Ouch!
If I didn't have a headache
a minute ago, I do now.
You don't have a problem
with that, do you, McGuire?
Um... No.
I mean, what else
do I have to do?
¶ Why not
¶ why not
¶ take a crazy chance?
¶ Why not
¶ why not
¶ do a crazy dance?
¶ If you lose the moment
¶ you might lose a lot
¶ so why not?
¶ Why not?
¶ Why not
take a crazy chance? ¶
wow.
Lizzie, I am
so grateful for your help.
You're doing a very kind thing
for Isabella.
Uh, Paolo, where are we?
Via condotti.
It is one of the most expensive
shopping districts
in the whole world.
We must find you the perfect
outfit for the awards.
Woman: Ah!
Oh, hey, Isabella, Paolo!
Ciao!
Your hair is so blond
and, uh, innocent.
Who did it?
Um...
Th... the island that we were on
was really, really sunny,
so it was j-just the sun.
Sun? We must
get sun, too, no?
Ciao, Bella!
Ciao, ciao, ciao.
They are so tall!
You see,
they all want to be you.
No, they want to be Isabella.
Here, sit and I'll get franca.
I will just be a moment.
Whoa! Take your time.
I'll just be sitting here
in heaven.
Hard as it is to imagine,
as we look at the crumbling
ruins of the forum,
that this was once
the center of commerce,
religion, and politics
in ancient Rome.
All right, now,
the forum came into being
in the sixth century b.C.,
and with it,
a new urban culture was born.
Uh, um... Di...
yeah, craft?
Is it time for the spaghetti?
It's, like,
9:00 in the morning.
Yeah, so? You never had leftover
spaghetti for breakfast?
I don't eat carbs.
Oh, and I suppose you
never had a spaghetti
sandwich, either?
This cultural experience
is, like,
so wasted on you.
Excuse me,
where did you buy
that Prada bag?
Craft! Sanders!
Separate.
Oh, we did, miss ungermeyer.
And thank God.
Why don't you people,
uh, do something at your,
uh, skill level here?
Take a ten-minute
shopping break
while I choke down an espresso.
Whoa, this dude
definitely spent
way too much time on his biceps
and not enough on his abs...
totally old school.
Si, si, si.
Uh... Wha...
nice spy, bro.
Yeah, watch and learn.
The slow curve.
Works every time.
I've got to go talk to them.
Hey, bro, that's not how
the slow curve works.
They come to us.
Um, eh, ciao.
Ciao.
Do you guys speak English?
Yes.
It is your friend we like.
Word.
Word?
Um, is that his name?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, listen, do you guys know
who that is on the cover?
Oh, Isabella.
Certo.
Do you think you guys could
translate it for me?
Um... Only if
you introduce us to word.
Well, can I keep
the magazine, then?
Deal!
All right.
Let's go.
Ciao, word.
Word?
Mmh?
Franca: English?
Paolo: Yes, she's speaking
only English.
Our new single is in English
and Isabella needs to practice.
What have you done?
Uh... Uh, uh...
You look...
well, you look like
a schoolgirl.
Maximus, what is wrong?
You love Isabella.
Nice Maximus.
Very odd.
There is something...
Something very different
about you.
Um...
Rest.
The rest on the island did
Isabella a world of good.
She is transformed.
Yeah.
Well, I cannot
put clothes on this.
You... fix the hair.
Fix the eyebrows.
Fix the lips.
Oh!
And fix the ears!
Fix the ears?
Jewelry.
Now, that's a language
every girl understands.
¶ You better work ¶
¶ covergirl
¶ work it, girl
¶ give it a twirl ¶
¶ do your thing
¶ on the runway
¶ work
¶ supermodel ¶
¶ you better work it, girl
¶ of the world ¶
¶ wet your lips ¶
¶ and smile to the camera ¶
¶ work ¶
¶ turn to the left ¶
ah! Aah!
¶ work ¶
¶ turn to the right oh!
¶ Sashay
¶ chante ¶
¶ well, it don't matter
what you wear ¶
¶ it doesn't matter
¶ they're checkin' out
your savoir faire ¶
¶ ooh, ooh, ooh, yeah ¶
¶ and when you walked
into the room ¶
¶ you had everybody's eyes
on you ¶
¶ supermodel ¶
¶ Work
¶ covergirl
¶ work it, girl
¶ give it a twirl ¶
¶ do your thing
¶ on the runway ¶
¶ work
you've got to work it, girl ¶
¶ of the world ¶
¶ wet your lips
¶ and smile to the camera ¶
¶ work
¶ turn to the left ¶
¶ now turn to the right ¶
aah!
¶ work ¶
¶ sashay
¶ chante ¶
¶ work
¶ turn to the left ¶
¶ work ¶
¶ now turn to the right ¶
¶ work
¶ sashay
¶ chante ¶
¶ you better work ¶
¶ oh, yeah ¶
¶ work ¶
¶ come on, girl ¶
¶ give it up ¶
¶ on the ru-u-u-nway ¶
¶ work ¶
¶ oh, yeah
¶ ah ah ah ah
¶ ohhhh ¶
¶ whoo
Okay. Diva... good.
Tacky... bad.
We'll have to fix that.
Okay, none of these are me.
Why are you laughing at me?
Because you're not supposed
to be you.
Okay, well,
if I have to go onstage
in front of an audience
as Isabella,
then I-I'm gonna have to
be confident,
and that's, like,
the thing I'm worst at.
We are all the same that way.
Not you.
Yes, me.
And Isabella, too.
But it's how she works
through her fears
that makes her strong.
For instance, Isabella doesn't
let franca di montecatini
tell her what to wear.
Isabella tells franca.
Okay, so you're telling me
to tell
franca di monteca-teca-tecatini
how...
how I should dress?
Si.
Test your strength, Isabella.
Vai! Vai, vai.
You don't like my clothes?
No. No.
I-I love your clothes.
But I don't want you
to dress me.
What?!
See, I'm not your Barbie doll.
I am Isabella parigi,
and I dress myself.
So, choices.
I-I need choices.
Whoa.
I really like these two.
You pick.
Both.
Wow.
This is the exact same color
that I wore to my spring formal,
and Danny Kessler thought
that I looked...
Unh-unh.
Look at all of you.
You'd think that I'm American.
I am,
how you say, um...
Awesome?
The island.
You should go more often.
Mmh.
¶ Ooh, ooh, ooh
whoo! Goodbye, Lizzie McGuire.
Hello, fabulous.
¶ Yeah, yeah, yeah
¶ Come on
¶ you make me feel
like a star ¶
¶ oh, baby
¶ you say, "stay, baby, stay
¶ just the way you are"
¶ and tell me, "girl, you're
fine and you will shine ¶
¶ forever in my heart"
¶ that's why you, yeah, you ¶
¶ you make me feel
like a star ¶
¶ ooh, ooh, ooh
there you go.
Grazie.
¶ Ooh, ooh, ooh
I'm ready for my close-up.
Whoo!
Kate: I cannot believe
that not one Roman guy
has asked me out yet.
Ugh.
Look.
Paolo...
We gotta go!
Where's the zoom on this thing?
Uh, uh...
Hello? Excuse me.
Oh!
I'm sorry.
I was just...
Hup! Head check!
Let's go! On the bus,
then back to the hotel!
Come on! Come on! Go!
Andiamo! Andiamo!
Giorgio:
Si, hold on one second!
Okay! Hello.
Hotel cambini.
This is giorgio.
Go!
Huh? What?
Wait.
Si.
Excuse me,
can you fix this?
It will not close.
Ah, but, uh...
Why is it open
when there is no rain?
This umbrella is very stubborn.
Please, it's bad luck to have
an open umbrella inside.
Go! Go!
No, in the hotel cambini,
there is no bad luck.
Hey, thanks.
Ah!
Ungermeyer: All right, people,
one at a time. No running.
Ha ha ha!
Ha! Ha ha!
Age before beauty, huh?
Oh. You look strangely large
and familiar.
Which floor?
Oh. Thank you.
First.
Okay.
Little hint for you...
you want to push the button,
elevator moves.
Elevator is not safe.
You an employee here?
No.
Well, then, who are you
to tell me whether or not
the elevator's safe?
I am Sergei.
Sergei.
Well, Sergei, you're gonna
have to stand down immediately.
Just because you are one hunk
of slavic muscle
does not mean you're not
gonna make it on my list!
Elevator is safe now.
Hey! Your umbrella!
Feeling any better?
Mom?
Still a little warm.
Miss Sanders,
would you be so kind
as to look after her for me?
"Look after her"
as in do stuff for her?
Miss ungermeyer,
why should I be punished?
I'm not the one who's sick.
Next year, I'm joining
the mouth breathers
at water-slide wonderland.
You are so busted. You've been
out of this hotel room.
What?
How do you know?
Please...
Your eyebrows finally match,
your hair has highlights...
Fresh manicure.
I smelled acetone
the second I walked
in the lobby.
Okay, but you
didn't rat me out
to miss ungermeyer.
Yet.
Not until I figure out
what's in it for me.
Now spill, dorkerella.
You'll never make me talk!
I-I know that this
sounds insane, but...
I think Paolo
really does like me.
How could this happen?
How did you get my trip?
How is Lizzie McGuire
living this fantasy
and I can't even get
an Italian boy
to buy me a plate of spaghetti?
Um, Kate,
you don't eat spaghetti.
I'd eat carbs if an Italian boy
bought them for me.
So...
I suppose you want me
to keep quiet about this?
Yeah.
I'd appreciate that.
Well, I'll keep it quiet
if you keep it quiet
about me keeping it quiet.
And...
When we get back home,
I'm the cool one again,
and you turn
back into a pumpkin.
Oh, my God.
It's her.
What are you doing?
Uh, it's a long story.
What do you want?
We're closed.
Uh, I-I just wanted
to talk to Lizzie.
So talk.
I was kind of thinking maybe,
you know,
outside in the courtyard.
If this is about that whole
bizarre, parallel-universe,
Italian-rock-star,
Lizzie's-suddenly-a-diva thing,
I know all about it.
She figured it out.
Evil and smart.
Embrace it. Fear it.
I thought you might want
to take a look at this.
I'm on the front cover
of a tabloid!
Ha!
I wish to thank everyone
who's always believed in me
for this great honor.
Do you know what that says?
It says that Paolo and Isabella
are supposed to be singing
at the music awards.
Well, it's got to be a mistake.
Oh, I had some Italian girls
translate it.
Paolo didn't tell you?
Mmh, no.
Don't you think
it's kind of weird
that he tried to hide this
from you?
Oh, my...
can you believe it?
Maybe it's just
a last-minute thing, gordo.
Aren't these things planned
for, like, months in advance?
Gordo, when did you become
an expert
on Italian award show thingies?
It's called common sense,
Lizzie, which I happen
to have a lot of
to make up for my lack
of the slow curve.
Slow curve?
Forget it. Look...
If you want to believe
some Italian kid
that you think you know
after two days
because he's
an international superstar,
is really rich,
and has nice hair...
Be my guest.
Gordo...
Oh, my God! He's early!
Lizzie...
Oh, my God,
I gotta go get dressed.
Oh, don't worry.
I'll cover for you
in case miss ungermeyer
does one of her
psycho, middle-of-the-night,
head-check things.
Thanks. I owe you.
Duh!
Mom, dad, I found something
on the Internet
I think you both should see.
What is it?
Well, since Lizzie's in Europe,
I thought I'd do
a little e-search on Italy.
That's nice, son.
But what I found out...
it's not so e-assuring.
In fact...
It may shock you.
What are we looking at?
Maybe nothing, and, uh...
Maybe something.
You see, when polled,
74% of Italian teenage boys
said they would most like
to date American girls.
Where'd you get these numbers?
They're available for anyone
who has a computer.
You don't have to
worry about your sister, son.
She's very well-chaperoned.
Miss ungermeyer's there.
Yeah, what is she...
5'1 ", 5'2" Max?
Oh, please.
Matt, as interesting
as this is,
where are you taking it?
All right, you caught me.
I always do.
I don't know why I even try.
I'll deny
I ever said this, but...
I miss my sister.
There. I said it.
Now you know.
I know I rag on her
all the time,
but now that she's gone,
I... I...
Oh, honey...
We miss her, too.
So, so much.
I feel so alone!
Oh! Li...
listen to me.
You don't have to
make fake pie charts.
You just come to us
with the truth, okay?
I know that now, mom.
It's just so hard.
I miss her so much!
Oh!
I can't believe
I let you talk me into
Letting her go
on that trip!
I'll go get the passports.
Oh, honey.
Shh.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Ah, hmm, ah.
Hmm...
Uh...
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmmmm.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Hmm!
Paolo.
Si.
What is this?
Uh... A car.
Look...
Are we supposed to sing?
Scusa?
Don't speak to me in Italian.
It's too adorable.
Are Paolo and Isabella
supposed to sing at the awards?
Si.
Si?! Well,
why didn't you tell me?
I wanted to tell you,
but you told me not to
telephone the hotel.
Come on, come on, get in.
I'll explain everything
on the way.
I want to show you
the tivoli gardens
before sunset.
Come on.
We have to get you
back by 10:00.
Okay.
So, where is Sergei?
You're not the only one
who sneaks off at night.
Paolo: Isabella and I
were going to sing,
but after Isabella
would not speak to me,
I told the producers
we refuse to perform.
I said Isabella
had throat problems.
So, what happened?
I mean, what changed?
Isabella did.
The real Isabella
or me Isabella?
You... a reporter heard
her speaking in front
of the gelato shop,
and he reported
Isabella's voice was fine.
And he said her English
was very good, by the way.
But then
the record company called,
and now they're going to sue
if we don't sing.
What?
So, they're gonna
make you sing?
I... I mean, us sing?
Don't worry, carina.
I'll make this work.
Look.
Ah!
Look, Paolo, I-I don't think
this is going to work.
I mean, I cannot sing
in front of an audience.
I won't even let my mom
hear me sing in the shower.
Lizzie, I will teach you
all you need to know.
Okay.
So, what is Isabella gonna do
when she sees me being her?
Ah, but she won't...
she's off on some island
trying to get over all of this.
Come on.
Here's my vow to you.
I, Paolo valisari,
will never let you,
Lizzie McGuire, be embarrassed.
If I fail...
I have to spend
seven days with that
scary head-check woman.
Her name's
miss ungermeyer.
Carina...
Hasn't everything
I've promised you come to be?
Everyone believes
you are Isabella,
you are having the time of
your life being someone else.
You even
told franca di montecatini
to buzz off!
Don't you trust that we can
do the singing together?
I guess.
Well, you shouldn't.
¶ Hmmm-mmmm
¶ ohhh
¶ ye-e-e-ah
¶ you been searching the world
to find true love ¶
¶ looking in all
the wrong places ¶
¶ when all of the time,
you've been blind to love ¶
¶ it's plain as the nose
on your face is ¶
¶ it's here
¶ it's here ¶
¶ it's now ¶
¶ open your eyes and see it ¶
¶ right here ¶
¶ right now ¶
¶ ohh
this is so beautiful.
Yes, you are.
¶ Ohhhh ¶
¶ love has been
right by your side ¶
¶ oh, so close,
that you couldn't see ¶
¶ if love could speak,
it would shout to the sky ¶
¶ "I've always been here,
i always will be" ¶
wow!
¶ I'm here ¶
¶ I'm now ¶
¶ open your eyes and see ¶
¶ open your eyes ¶
¶ right here
¶ right here ¶
¶ right now ¶
¶ open your eyes to love ¶
¶ open your heart ¶
¶ to love ¶
Hey.
What do you got there,
little man?
Uh, nothing.
What's this?
Uh, that's not Lizzie!
No!
Yes, it is.
No, it isn't.
I know my daughter.
I gave her that necklace.
All right... tell me
what you know that I don't.
It's only
a 14-hour flight, dad.
All right, people,
swallow those biscotti.
We got a big day...
the pantheon, the colosseum.
Oh.
Uh, halt!
Got to get these apricots
to McGuire.
She looked sick as a dog
this morning.
Mr. Gordon,
you having a problem?
N-no, I just...
I-I'm starting to agree
with Ethan.
I-I think we need to eat
more spaghetti.
You da man!
Sorry.
Mr. Gordon,
is there a reason
you don't want me to go
upstairs?
No, I-I just really think
we should get going.
Uh, so much roma,
so little time-a.
Well, you know,
when I get upstairs...
and I will get upstairs...
I expect to find miss McGuire
in her bed.
Well, you... she may
be in the bathroom
or... or something.
You know, I'm beginning
to get the feeling
she was never sick
to begin with.
No, no, no!
She... she was!
You know, I bet
this whole thing was
just a clever ruse
to sneak out of this hotel,
wasn't it?
Yeah, it... it was.
It was?
Well, Lizzie and I were
talking about adventures,
and, uh, I don't know.
Ah, spit it out, Gordon.
Lizzie's upstairs.
It... it's me.
I'm the one
who's been sneaking out.
You?
But... but...
feels good
to get it off my chest.
You realize what this means?
I...Shouldn't look to you
for a college recommendation?
You should look
for your suitcase, Gordon.
You're goin' home.
Oh, I pegged you
right from the start.
David Gordon...
sneaky little brownnoser
with a hidden agenda.
Well, you're busted.
Love lifts us up
where we belong.
Wow. This place is so cool.
Si.
Are you sure it's okay
that we're here?
Si.
And here is where, exactly?
It's the rehearsal hall.
But the colosseum
will look more like this.
Sergei!
If you want to convince
the world you're Isabella,
you must take the stage.
You must dance...
and sing.
¶ Have you ever seen
such a beautiful night? ¶
just move your mouth
with the words.
Oh. So you want me
to lip-synch.
Si.
Just like Isabella.
You said you know
the song, right?
Uh, well, yeah.
I mean, I have your cd, but...
so try it.
I'm not gonna try it.
Okay.
¶ Have you ever seen
such a beautiful night? ¶
¶ I could almost kiss the stars
for shining so bright ¶
Was it awful?
Uh, yes.
But it helps to sing.
Really... really sing?
Si. It looks more real
when you're lip-synching.
But you weren't singing.
But I won't be lip-synching.
Lizzie, no one's going to
hear you.
When you're onstage,
the microphone will be off.
You must try.
Please?
Okay.
¶ Have you ever seen
such a beautiful night? ¶
¶ I could almost kiss the stars
for shining so bright ¶
¶ when I see you smiling
¶ I go, "oh, oh, oh"
¶ I would never want
to miss this ¶
¶ 'cause in my heart
i know what this is ¶
¶ this is what dreams
are made of ¶
¶ this is what
¶ dreams are made of
¶ I've got
¶ somewhere I belong
¶ somebody to love
¶ this is what
¶ dreams
¶ are made of
Brava.
And now we dance!
¶ Hey!
¶ Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Oh, I'm glad you're up.
I had the most amazing night.
I'm gonna go grab gordo
so I can tell you guys
together, okay?
You won't find him.
What?
Why? Where'd he go?
Probably getting on a plane
right now.
Why?
He totally covered for you
and got himself
kicked off the trip.
I-I don't believe it.
W-why would he do that?
You're seriously asking
that question?
Giorgio, you've got to call
the airline
and see if gordo's plane
has left yet!
D-do you know what flight
he's on?
Si, si.
I will call.
I cannot believe that gordo
would do this for me.
M-maybe he's not
on the plane yet!
Maybe I could go to the airport
and I could...
And... What?
I don't know.
I am now on hold.
Woman on p.A. System:
This is the final boarding call
for lufthansa flight 6240
grazie.
Departing for Los Angeles.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you very nice.
The plane is gone.
Who is this girl?
I have been relaxing
on the island,
trying to forget
about this whole situation.
Excu... Isabella!
Can somebody please tell me
what is going on?
I can. That's my friend
Lizzie McGuire.
Hey!
Let him go.
I demand for you to tell me
everything you know
about this Lizzie McGuire.
I demand for you to tell me
everything there is to know
about this...
this Paolo valisari.
I left him and all
of my thoughts about
him on the island.
Well, you may have left him
on the island,
but my friend Lizzie is
out there pretending to be you
so that you don't get sued.
We need to talk in private.
Gordo's life is ruined
because of me...
selfish me!
So what are you gonna do now?
It's over.
I'm going to turn myself in
to miss ungermeyer.
Lizzie, you'll get sent home,
and then you won't be able
to help Paolo.
Okay, well,
I'm never going to be able
to get through this
the way I feel now.
Okay. Fine. Quit.
But then everything gordo did
will be for nothing.
Now, you know things are bad
when Kate starts making sense.
I know one thing's for sure.
What?
I'm not gonna have to
act sick today.
Mr. craft, you are in
the most historic
and beautiful city
in the world.
Has that had no effect on you?
Well, actually, it has.
The cobblestones
are shredding my wheels.
Switched to a pair
of birdhouse pterodactyls.
Have you even made a dent
in your reading list?
I finished it.
You read 11 books?
I mean I read the list.
Shh.
McGuire.
Lizzie McGuire.
Si, si,
we are in the travel guides.
No. No.
No.
We're the parents of Lizzie.
Ah! Si!
Uh, I'll call a cab.
It's very far.
Anybody else want to step up
to the plate?
Who's asking for McGuire?
I've left you
four messages already,
but she's been under
my watchful eye all the while.
Where'd Sanders go?
Hmm.
Lizzie? Sweetheart?
Honey?
Cool!
Where is Lizzie?
And do you have
any embarrassing photos
or videos of her
while she's been here?
Ow.
Uh...
You better tell us
where Lizzie is,
or this deck's gonna catch
some serious air.
Well, it's possible
that she's at
the international
music video awards
doubling for an Italian
pop star named Isabella,
who's, like, totally her twin.
Why does everyone
always look at me like that?
¶ When you wish upon a star
¶ your dreams will take you
very far ¶
¶ Once you see your light
so clear ¶
¶ In the sky so very dear
¶ you're a shining star
¶ no matter who you are
¶ shining bright to see
¶ what you can truly be
Prince William?
Tell him he'll have to hold.
Ooh!
Oh.
¶ Shine its watchful light
on you ¶
man: Hey, Paolo!
¶ Words of wisdom, yes, I can ¶
¶ you're a shining star
¶ no matter who you are
¶ shining bright to see
¶ what you can truly be
Si.
What?
He said for you to enter
from here... stage right...
and I must enter
from stage left, over there.
And what about my dress?
I-I still have to get dressed
and everything.
Si. Franca delivered it.
It's waiting in your
dressing room.
Lizzie, you have time.
Calm down.
You can do it.
Of course i can do it.
This is moi
we're talking about.
I don't think I can do it.
Lizzie, you must.
We've rehearsed this.
You know all the steps.
You know all the words.
You will be great...
I know.
How do you know?
Because...
Because you shine
like the light from the sun.
Paolo... Paolo.
Man:
31 minutes till showtime.
Lizzie.
Gordo!
Oh, my God!
What are you doing here?
Lizzie, Lizzie, that's...
that's not important right now.
Y-you need to listen
to me.
Of course it's important!
I feel so bad.
I cannot believe
that you would do that for me.
Wait a minute.
Why aren't you gone?
It's a long story, but...
okay, well, I want to hear
all about it,
but I've got to go get
my dress on, okay?
Lizzie, listen to me.
Paolo is setting you up.
What are you talking about?
Actually...
He is setting me up.
Freaky, huh?
Way freaky.
Way, way freaky.
That whole story
about Paolo doing his own music
and going solo...
that's Isabella.
She's the one that sings live.
Si. Paolo is the one
that lip-synchs, not me.
Isabella is the one
that wants to quit the act.
Paolo I-is just a liar.
This has all been
some crazy scheme
to set you up
and embarrass you onstage
so it looks
like Isabella can't sing.
Si, si. It's true.
Paolo wants to destroy
Isabella's career.
But Paolo would never
do that to me.
I don't believe you.
Isabella...
Lizzie, who are you
going to believe,
this boy you are knowing
your whole life
or... This boy you are
just meeting who says...
"You shine with the light
from the sun"?
Okay. Well, then,
you're here now,
so go and sing.
But I am not blond.
Paolo will know that it's me,
and he'll make an excuse
to leave.
But if we want to
get back at him
in front of the whole world
on live TV,
we must make him sing...
and really sing,
not lip-synch.
But how?
What am I supposed to do?
I can't sing live!
Change! Change!
Change your clothes
and go up there and do
what you rehearsed, okay?
Everything will be fine.
I-I promise.
I have a plan.
What plan?
Man:
28 minutes till showtime.
So, what's the plan?
I don't know.
Okay.
No, see, it doesn't matter
about the tickets,
because my daughter is
back there
impersonating
a famous pop star,
so... I got to get in!
That's what everyone says.
All right.
Enough of this!
Uhh!
Ha! Let's go!
Sandro, did Paolo bring
the voice track for me tonight?
No. No, he did not.
There is no track.
Paolo, he says
you're gonna sing live,
like you always do.
Paolo and Isabella!
Sandro, turn down
Isabella's mic.
What's that?
Turn down the mic!
¶ Have you ever seen
such a beautiful night? ¶
¶ I could almost kiss the stars
for shining so bright ¶
¶ when I see you smiling,
i go ¶
¶ "oh, oh, oh"
¶ I would never want
to miss this ¶
¶ 'cause in my heart
¶ I know what this is
¶ This is what dreams
are made of ¶
Sing to me, Paolo.
¶ this is
what dreams are made of ¶
Okay.
Say buonasera to my
new American friend,
Lizzie McGuire!
Paolo tried to use her
to fool all of you
into thinking
that I could not sing.
Lizzie McGuire is nice girl.
You try to hurt her.
Let me go, Sergei.
You work for me.
Not anymore, Paolo.
I quit.
Paolo!
Paolo cannot sing music.
Now he must face music.
- Was it all a lie?
- No, it's just...
Do you want to hear us sing?
¶ Have you ever seen
such a beautiful night? ¶
¶ I could almost kiss the stars
for shining so bright ¶
¶ when I see you smiling,
i go ¶
¶ "oh, oh, oh"
¶ I would never want
to miss this ¶
¶ 'cause in my heart
i know what this is ¶
¶ hey, now
¶ this is what dreams
are made of ¶
¶ hey, now
¶ this is what dreams
are made of ¶
¶ I've got somewhere I belong ¶
¶ I've got somebody to love ¶
¶ this is what dre-e-e-ams
¶ are made of
Wait! Isabella!
Go! Si!
Man: Lizzie!
Ru-u-u-u-n!!
¶ Hey, hey, hey!
¶ Have you ever wondered
what life is about? ¶
¶ you could search the world
and never figure it out ¶
¶ you don't have to sail
the oceans ¶
¶ no, no, no
¶ happiness is no mystery
¶ it's here and now
¶ it's you and me, yeah
¶ hey, now, hey, now
¶ this is what dreams
are made of ¶
¶ hey, now, hey, now
¶ this is what dreams
are made of ¶
¶ I've got somewhere I belong
¶ I've got somebody to love
¶ this is what dre-e-e-ams
¶ are made of
¶ hey, now
¶ this is what dreams
are made of ¶
¶ hey, hey, hey, hey
¶ hey, now
¶ this is what dreams
are made of ¶
¶ open your eyes
¶ this is what dreams
are made of ¶
¶ shout to the skies
¶ this is what dreams
are made of ¶
¶ hey, hey, hey, hey
¶ then I see you smile
¶ and I go, "oh, oh, oh"
¶ yesterday
my life was duller ¶
¶ now everything is
technicolor ¶
¶ hey, now, hey, now
¶ this is what dreams
are made of ¶
¶ hey, now, hey, now
¶ this is what dreams
are made of ¶
¶ I've got somewhere I belong
¶ I've got somebody to love
¶ this is what dre-e-e-ams
¶ dre-e-e-ams
¶ are made of
¶ hey, now, hey, now
¶ hey, hey, hey, hey
¶ hey!
Lizzie got everything
you're supposed to get
when you go to Europe...
adventure, romance,
total confidence.
Yeah?
Well... If all that can happen
to Lizzie McGuire,
the only thing i know now is...
I don't know anything.
That's hot.
What?
Girls who think they know
everything are just a turnoff.
Really?
Oh, totally.
Like, what about you
not ratting out Lizzie?
I mean, that was just so...
Not you.
That's good.
Si.
Aaaaaaah!
Mom, dad, I'm so glad
that you guys made it.
You would have never
believed me.
That is for sure.
I thought
after you found out
all the things that I did,
I would be grounded.
You're grounded for the rest
of the summer, sweetheart.
But we're really proud of you.
You know, lying,
even for a good reason,
is beneath you, Gordon.
Yeah.
I know. I know.
I'm a lying, spineless,
brownnosing jellyfish
with a hidden agenda...
I got it.
Well, that may be true,
but I'll tell you something.
Little miss diva over there
told me everything.
The way I see it, you're
a pretty loyal friend, Gordon.
And loyalty goes a long way
with the ungermeyer.
Hmm?
Thanks.
Hey, just think about it...
we got four years
of high school
to look forward to
together, huh?
Ooh. Sammies.
Sergei is hungry.
So is miss ungermeyer.
You are strong woman.
You protect cubs like lioness.
Sergei is impressed.
Hmm.
You're still on my list.
As long as I am at the top.
Hey, there!
I bet you're wondering...
who is this Lizzie McGuire
and where did she come from
and what are her
most embarrassing moments?
Well, I can give you
total access to all of that
for a very competitive price.
Hmm. When in Rome...
Yeah, yeah.
Do as the romans do, right?
No.
We do not blackmail
our sisters.
As a former commander
in the Italian Navy,
I am ordering you
to leave the country.
No!
Hey.
So...
One last sneak-away
for old times' sake?
Yeah. Sounds good.
Okay.
Aha.
No!
So, are you gonna miss it here?
I don't know.
Kate says
that I should just stay
and have my stuff
shipped over from home,
because when I leave here,
it'll never be the same.
Well, she's wrong, as usual.
You didn't have to be in Rome
for all this to happen.
You think?
Trust me.
You had it in you
the whole time.
Gordo?
What?
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Yeah.
So, um... Want to get back
to that party
so we don't get
in any more trouble?
Yeah. I can't afford
any more... more trouble.
Yeah.
¶ why not?
¶ Think you're goin' nowhere
¶ when you're walkin'
down the street ¶
¶ acting like
you just don't care ¶
¶ when life can be so sweet
¶ but why you want to be
like that ¶
¶ as if there's nothing new?
¶ You're not foolin' no one
¶ you're not even foolin' you
¶ so walk a little slower
and open up your eyes ¶
¶ sometimes it's so hard to see
the good things passin' by ¶
¶ and there may never be a
sign, no flashing neon light ¶
¶ telling you to make your move
when the time is right ¶
¶ so ¶
¶ why not ¶
¶ why not? ¶
¶ take a crazy chance? ¶
¶ why not ¶
¶ why not?
¶ Do a crazy dance? ¶
¶ if you lose the moment,
you might lose a lot ¶
¶ so why not? ¶
¶ why not? ¶
¶ oh, I could be
the one for you ¶
¶ oh, yeah,
maybe yes, maybe no ¶
¶ oh, it could be
the thing to do ¶
¶ what I'm sayin' is you got to
let me know, oh, oh ¶
¶ ah, ah, yeah ¶
¶ ah, ah, ah ¶
¶ yeah, yeah ¶
¶ ah, ah, ah, yeah
¶ ah, yeah ¶
¶ ah, yeah, yeah ¶
¶ you'll never get to heaven
or even to L.A. ¶
¶ if you don't believe
there's a way ¶
¶ why not ¶
¶ why not?
¶ Take a star from the sky? ¶
¶ why not
¶ why not? ¶
¶ spread your wings and fly? ¶
¶ it might take a little,
and it might take a lot ¶
¶ but why not?
¶ Why not? ¶
¶ why not
¶ take a little chance
¶ take a crazy chance? ¶
¶ why not ¶
¶ do a crazy dance ¶
¶ do a crazy dance?
¶ If you lose the moment,
you might lose a lot ¶
¶ so why not? ¶
¶ why not? ¶
¶ Hmmmmmm, mmmm, mmmm ¶
¶ ohhhhh, yeah
¶ you've been searching
the world ¶
¶ to find true love ¶
¶ looking in all
the wrong places ¶
¶ when all of the time,
you've been blind to love ¶
¶ it's plain as the nose
on your face is ¶
¶ it's here, it's now ¶
¶ open your eyes and see it ¶
¶ right here, right now ¶
¶ open your eyes to love ¶
¶ you've been down on yourself,
thinking something's wrong ¶
¶ wondering why love
has never found you ¶
¶ don't you know it's been
right here all along ¶
¶ if only you'd look
around you? ¶
¶ it's here ¶
¶ it's now ¶
¶ it's now
¶ open your eyes and see it ¶
¶ right here ¶
¶ right now ¶
¶ open your eyes to love
¶ love has been
right by your side ¶
¶ oh, so close
that you couldn't see ¶
¶ if love could speak,
it would shout to the sky ¶
¶ "I've always been here
¶ I always will be"
¶ I'm here
¶ I'm now
¶ open your eyes and see me
¶ right here
¶ right now
¶ open your eyes to love
¶ open your mind to love
¶ open your heart to love
¶ ooh, ooh, ooh