Didn't I tell you
not to talk to her
as long as you're living here?
When I locked eyes with Nut earlier,
-my heart was beating really fast.
-What?
You're just like him, Little Prince.
You really care for me.
Now that you know
I'm not related to Neung,
you won't kick me out, will you?
If I wanted to,
I would've left you
at the temple that day.
I'm a bear, not a dog.
Listen. He's just a kid.
Haven't you heard people say
that you should never work with kids?
If you don't trust me…
you could try going out with me.
Everyone, look.
Teddy is acting
more and more like a human.
How?
You seem to have a lot on your mind,
like there's something you want to say
but you won't say it.
You used to say all your thoughts
when you were a teddy bear.
I guess the more time I spend with humans,
the more I know that
there are some things we shouldn't say,
because they can hurt someone.
But some things, I just don't understand,
so I don't know what to say.
If being a human is so hard,
turn back into a teddy bear.
Come back to us.
I'm trying.
I almost found out who gave me to Nut,
but I was still wrong.
Maybe Nut won you
after playing darts at a temple fair?
No!
He said someone important gave me to him.
I must be more important
than a prize at a fair.
Calm down, Tofu.
Look, he gets angry
like a real person now.
-He's kind of similar to Nut.
Hey!
Why are you here?
I brought in your laundry.
What should I do next?
You need to go and iron them.
-Iron?
-Yes.
Don't tell me you don't know how to do it.
Listen.
This is linen,
so it needs high heat.
Put the heat on high for linen.
Then start ironing.
Go slowly, see?
Go over the whole thing.
That's it.
You try this side.
Slowly.
Yes.
Don't iron over the buttons.
Here.
What you do
is gently push the iron
between the buttons like this.
Slowly.
See?
Yes.
Try it.
Here.
Oh, Tofu.
Like this, slowly.
Hold the fabric with one hand.
Yes.
Nut, are you hurt?
No,
it's just hot.
Was it hot?
Touch your earlobes.
Is it better?
A little bit.
Hold your earlobes.
What for?
Just do as I say.
No.
-Like this.
-No.
Like this.
It's all right, it's not hot anymore.
Why do I feel so hot?
Is this the sound of my heart or yours?
Get out. You're not good.
I'll do it myself. Go.
Go on.
Beary,
why are you all hot and sweaty?
I was ironing.
Maybe it gave me fever.
Can ironing cause fever?
Right?
Tell me how you feel.
I'm not sure.
I feel hot all over.
There are butterflies in my stomach.
My heart is beating fast too.
You don't sound like you have fever.
Oh, he can't understand you.
Hey, Tofu,
are you sure
that the only thing you did was iron?
It really was.
But while I was ironing,
Nut said he was hot,
so I held his earlobes.
-Held his earlobes?
Did you hold anything else?
No.
You did just that and then got all hot?
Ha, what do single people know?
Little One, tell them.
I think you like Nut, Tofu.
That's why your heart beats fast
and you get butterflies
when you're near him.
It's that feeling you get
when you really like someone.
When you're near them
and lock eyes with them,
your heart starts beating fast.
But I'm just a teddy bear.
How can I like my owner?
Don't forget, Beary,
you're not just a teddy bear anymore.
But I have to turn back
into a teddy bear anyway.
I don't know
when I'll turn back into a teddy bear,
but I've decided that
before that day comes,
I'll make the most of my time with Nut.
Nut, are you hurt?
No,
it's just hot.
Hold your earlobes.
What for?
Just do as I say.
-Like this.
-No.
Like this.
Why do I feel so hot?
Is this the sound of my heart or yours?
I'll be off, Mom.
Nut.
It's my first time making it.
It might not be very good.
By the way, how's the shirt?
Oh,
where's Mom?
Nut.
I'm sorry, I overslept.
Oh, and your lunch?
I already made it for him.
I'm off to work, Mom.
You should go back to sleep.
Bye.
I can't even wake up
to make lunch for Nut.
How am I supposed to do
other things for him?
Don't worry, Mrs. Na,
anyone can oversleep.
As long as you stay healthy,
Nut will be happy.
Have some apple juice.
Song's father said
it's good for the heart.
I want you to try some.
Thank you.
You're so lovely, Little Prince.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Na.
I made you oversleep.
But if I didn't do this…
Nut wouldn't be happy.
Go on.
What are you making?
Apple juice.
Thank you.
FIRST LOVE
It's my first time making it.
It might not be very good.
Want to try it?
Yuck.
Try it. I put a lot of effort into it.
Here.
How is it?
Delicious, right?
Hey,
it's great.
Iced Americano with no sugar,
but with all my heart,
in exchange for your lunch.
How come your food looks terrible today?
The pork is all burnt.
There's no food for me today then.
I'll throw it out for you.
No,
I can eat it.
Gen,
Nut's taste is so weird.
He gives yummy-looking food
to other people,
but eats burnt pork by himself.
What's so special about that pork?
If he can eat stuff like that,
all is not lost for me.
I have an idea.
You're crazy.
What's up?
What?
You bought an air fryer?
Why?
I'm going to learn to fry pork.
I'll impress Nut with my cooking skills.
You never cease to amaze me.
I'll bring you some to try later.
Bye now.
Oh, Prib.
Oh, Mr. Anik.
Any updates on Tarn's case?
The police
still haven't ruled out anything,
for both the conflict with TRD
and his personal problems.
In his personal life,
I'm certain there's no woman involved.
What makes you think so?
Since he came back to Thailand
two years ago,
he hasn't dated anyone.
He never forgot his first love
and he never got serious with anyone.
I was really touched by that,
so I created a page called
"Once Upon Our Time" to tell his story.
If you check it out,
you might understand him more.
ONCE UPON OUR TIME
I didn't know
that Tarn could never love me,
so I made a move on him.
In the end, I failed.
We became good friends instead
and grew a lot closer.
After you've read the page, if you want
to know anything else about Tarn,
you can ask me.
Hey!
You puppy,
you're such a child.
Dad,
are you a BL fanboy?
Are you crazy?
It has to do with my case.
You have cases like this now?
That's pretty trendy.
Of course.
It's Neung's friend's case.
I just realized
that he's not manly.
Not manly?
Just the fact that he's a guy
who likes guys
makes him not manly?
Hey, wait,
what do you think I mean?
What I mean by manly is masculinity.
A person of any gender can be manly.
How did you understand it?
Dad,
keep working.
I'll be the chef tonight.
What do you want,
omelet, fried egg, or steamed egg?
No thanks.
Chef Dad will take care of it.
Go take a shower.
You stink. Go.
Stink? Take that.
Go on, you puppy.
Oh, dear.
Come have some fruit, Mrs. Na.
What are you looking for?
Saen.
I haven't seen him.
Did he come home last night?
I think so.
He probably left before you woke up.
Right,
I woke up late today.
I should scold him though.
He could have woken me up.
I don't know
how long he'll be gone this time.
He used to work in a factory
outside Bangkok
and he would come home every week.
Sometimes he would be gone for a few weeks
or even months.
I'm not coming back to Bangkok
this weekend.
Again?
But it's my birthday this Saturday.
Saen?
Hello?
Did you get cut off?
Saen is in a meeting.
Do you have a message for him?
Please let it be about work only, though,
because he's working right now.
I'm sorry.
I'll call again later.
Since that year,
he and I haven't celebrated
a birthday together.
That's okay,
we can celebrate together
and make it a huge party.
But I just had my birthday.
But Nut's birthday
is coming up this month.
That's right.
It's only a while
until September 8.
You know his birthday?
He told me once.
Nut is back.
Hi, Mom.
Here.
Didn't you eat my food?
Don't look so sad. Open it up first.
YOURS. MOM'S.
Tofu pudding.
Beans in syrup.
-Fried tofu.
-Yes.
You got these for me?
Can't you read?
KEUNCHAI'S
Keunchai's,
Mom's,
yours.
Mine.
Thank you, Nut.
I'll finish all the tofu pudding.
By the way,
who gave you that pork recipe?
I just followed my gut,
why?
Nothing.
But next time, use less heat.
If I keep eating that,
I'll get cancer.
Okay,
it won't be burnt next time.
I said don't burn it.
Yes, not burnt.
I gathered some more evidence.
Before Tatarn was attacked,
apart from his co-worker,
Mrs. Sajjaree Burarat also called him.
-That's Saen's surname.
-Yes.
She's his wife and Tatarn's aunt.
Isn't that odd?
She lives in Bangkok,
but someone saw her in Chiang Mai
when Tatarn was attacked.
Saen never said that his wife
was in Chiang Mai.
It seems like he's hiding something.
Find out
when Sajjaree arrived and left,
and where she went.
Yes, sir.
Please put that away.
Your lieutenant called about the case?
Yes.
We got new evidence
in Neung's friend's case.
So,
do they know who did it?
We still can't say,
but it looks like this wasn't
a normal robbery and attack.
Neung's friend is an activist
and he comes from a wealthy family.
He inherited a lot of money,
so maybe someone is trying to harm him.
The thing I least want to happen
is a family conflict.
That's true, Dad.
If the perpetrator
is someone close to you,
that hurts like nothing else.
Dad,
when do you have to get back to work?
Tomorrow, why?
Nothing.
BRAT
Brat.
What is it, you imp?
Man, you're so cold.
Say what you have to say.
I'm about to sleep.
We start filming next week.
So?
Will I get to see you?
I don't think so.
But I want to see you.
Why do you want to see me?
Well,
my dad is busy,
so I want an older relative
to come and give me support.
When did I become your relative?
I keep treating you like an uncle
because I wish you were my family.
Oh,
or should I call you
little brother?
You punk, brat, hoodlum,
disrespectful crazy person!
Now, I can sleep soundly.
You're such a psycho.
See you around.
Sweet dreams. Good night.
Kiss, kiss.
Song, you idiot!
I don't know why
I'm so sleepy all the time these days.
If I didn't set three alarms,
I wouldn't have woken up.
I think it's good to rest a lot.
You look much stronger now,
and more energetic during the day too.
-Mom.
-Yes?
We start shooting today,
so you don't need to make me lunch.
I'll eat on the set.
Bye now.
Nut.
Chu.
-Hello.
-Hi.
We went to the market and got you this.
Thank you.
-I'll hold it for you.
-What?
It smells so good.
Hey, listen.
Tofu, do you know where Jan went?
Oh,
is she not home?
No. When I woke up this morning,
I saw her get into a taxi with a suitcase.
She probably…
went to see Mr. Saen in Chiang Mai.
No wonder. They just had a fight.
She must be trying to make it up to him.
Why are you so nosy?
You're unbelievable.
By the way,
how's Na, Tofu?
She hasn't been out to give alms lately.
She's fine.
Tofu,
you know you can talk to me.
Well…
Mrs. Na
hasn't been cooking for Nut.
And she's been feeling sad
and even blaming herself.
She feels worthless.
I understand her, Tofu.
She wants to do things for her son,
like cook for him.
She wants to do
whatever that makes him happy.
But now that he's a grown-up
and he goes to work,
she feels like
she's not useful anymore.
Do you understand?
And Na is always at home.
She never goes out.
So now
that she's not cooking for her son,
she probably feels worthless.
And what is it like
to feel you're worth something?
Well,
that has to do with…
I'll let Nhong explain.
He studied engineering.
-Nhong, explain it.
-I went to culinary school.
Come on, explain it.
To feel like you're worth something? Well…
What?
I guess it's when you make
someone else happy.
But it doesn't have to be anything big.
It can be small things,
like giving them support
and making them smile.
And you also feel happy with them.
I guess that's the feeling
of being worth something.
Thank you.
You two are worth a lot to me today.
-Thank you.
-Hey…
-The fried dough?
-What?
Oh, it's so nice. Let me have one more.
I'll be off now.
Why did you eat it?
We bought it for him.
-It's for him.
-It's really good.
How can you say that?
Why didn't you give it to him?
Because it's good.
-Try some.
-No.
-It's great.
-You're so bad.
It's really great.
I think I understand now what it means
to feel like you're worth something.
When I was a teddy bear,
I listened to Nut
when he was happy
and when he was sad.
Now that I'm a person,
I feel I'm worth even more
because I don't just listen,
but I can help Nut and Mrs. Na
with a lot of things.
At least,
I don't have to wait to be hugged anymore.
I can hug someone
to make them feel better.
Even though being a human isn't easy,
I'm enjoying it more and more.
Mrs. Na,
shall we make some snacks?
Do you like this location?
The place we booked canceled on us.
Luckily,
my cousin is the deputy director here.
Who?
Joonjuea.
Oh, hi, Pritr.
-I would be in trouble if not for you.
-Yes.
You never come to me
when you're not in trouble.
Hey…
Oh,
aren't you Peeranut?
This school doesn't actually accept
students in the second semester,
but Na is my friend
and Sib has helped me in the past,
so I begged the director to let you in.
Study hard
and don't get me in trouble,
okay?
Don't forget that your parents asked me
to keep an eye on you.
I thought you wouldn't remember me.
It has been around seven to eight years
and you haven't been back once.
Did you write the script for this series?
What's it about?
-Hey!
About life in high school?
You didn't use your experience
as material, right?
Of course, I did,
but not all of it.
I have both good memories of this place
and not-so-good ones
that I personally want to tell.
But this story isn't just about
the daily lives of kids.
It explores society within a school,
the class system,
power,
and oppression.
Interesting.
Does it
also include your love story?
Of course.
And it's not an odd thing anymore.
But it's still not normal.
If for you, normal means
only thinking the way you do,
then half the world would be abnormal.
For me,
everyone is normal.
Just because I'm not like you
or other people
doesn't mean that I'm not normal.
Please watch this show once it airs.
Maybe
it will help you understand
sexual diversity more
and be respectful to everyone,
no matter their age
or gender.
Please excuse me.
Cut!
See, Gen?
His acting is superb.
It isn't superb.
And he isn't acting.
He's being himself.
If he irritates you so much,
I can deliver the photos to the client
instead of you.
I don't avoid my responsibilities.
And I'm here
to support Nut.
Are you sure you're here just for Nut?
Aren't you here
especially for me?
I'm here to laugh when you fail.
Song,
go get changed right now.
Cameras, lights,
move to the basketball court.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Juea.
What now?
The extra playing
the rival basketball captain
crashed his bike and is in the hospital.
What do we do?
Who can play basketball?
Call and see if we can get
someone in time?
I think we have someone.
I brought some food for Nut.
Isn't that kid with Nut?
That's right.
He plays basketball?
He doesn't just play. He's a god.
And…
action!
Okay.
One more time.
What do you want to eat?
Daydreaming again.
Hey,
Nut!
Neung.
Are you okay?
Hey,
Tofu!
Hey.
Here we are.
Are you okay, Tofu?
Can you keep playing?
Yes, it doesn't hurt anymore.
What's wrong with you, Nut?
Why did you barge into the set?
I'm sorry.
I was distracted.
Are you okay?
I am.
-Juea.
-What?
Keep shooting.
I'll go to the toilet.
-It's over there.
-I know.
Hey, I own this company.
Is it because we're at his school?
Why does he seem so distracted?
This is Nut's school?
I just found out too.
I met my cousin, the deputy director here,
this morning.
She said hello,
but he completely ignored her.
I guess he doesn't like her.
He's really stressed out
that we're shooting here.
Maybe he has some bad memories
about school?
Peeranut.
I know what you did.
Because of that,
I'll have to tell your parents
what you did.
Hey,
why aren't you in the girls' toilet?
You want to see our junk?
Does your dad know you're a sissy?
Hi, sissy!
Think you can fight me?
Why don't you go
ask your beloved Neung for help?
Oh, sissy!
This is a toilet, not a kennel.
If you're not peeing, get out!
If you want to gang up,
meet me on the court.
I'll play all of you.
Hey, let's go.
Are you okay, Nut?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Nut.
I'm sorry.
It's okay,
it's just the film.
I'll get it replaced.
How did you become an extra?
Oh, I…
Jeez.
I brought you a snack.
Your mom and I made it.
There were a lot of apples in the fridge,
so we made apple jelly for you.
I won't eat that.
Please try it. It's good.
How many times did I tell you
there's food on the set?
You don't need to bring anything.
But thanks
for trying to help me.
But don't do it again.
Why not?
People shouldn't get hurt for me.
I don't want you to get hurt either.
If you won't let me help,
then take good care of yourself.
I know.
I won't walk
onto a basketball court again.
Don't worry.
Nut.
What were you staring at
so intently just now?
Song likes to stare
at something like that too.
Facebook.
Facebook?
It's like a notebook for your memories,
for contacting people.
Memories?
Why do you need to record them?
Why not just remember them?
Who can remember everything?
What if I get Alzheimer's
or lose my memory, like you?
Hey,
you should have a Facebook.
If we try to find it,
maybe we'll know who you are.
I don't have one.
Well,
how can I?
I don't even know what it is.
Can you teach me how to use Facebook?
You said that
if I remember who I am,
I have to leave.
I want to record my time with you,
so it can be my memory.
Cut.
That's a wrap!
Good job, everyone.
See you next week.
Let's go.
Mister,
how was I today?
As annoying as ever.
Oh, come on. I'm being serious.
What's your score
for my first day of acting?
Ten.
Out of a hundred.
Hey, that's not true.
I got through every scene in two
to three takes. Even Juea said I was good.
How can you give me just ten?
You've already complimented yourself.
You need me to do it too?
Well, I want you to praise me.
Doesn't your dad do that?
What do you need me for?
Song,
please go get changed.
Yes.
Hey, Song,
come eat with us.
Oh,
no thanks, Juea.
I have to go submit a report.
Okay then.
See you next week.
See you, Juea.
Hurry up.
Are you really mad at me?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were sensitive…
about your dad.
If you feel bad
about hurting my poor little heart,
I'll let you make up for it
by driving me home.
What?
Wait,
are you high?
Why do I have to drive you home?
Just ride your bike home.
How can I?
I left it at home.
I knew you would drive here,
so I didn't bring my bike.
Please take me home.
Please, please,
please, please.
I promise
I won't be mad at you anymore.
Please, mister.
Get your head here.
Get your head here!
Take that!
Come on, take me home.
Go home by yourself.
You're being funny?
Come on,
I'm all sweaty now.
Isn't your dad home?
He works in Chiang Mai.
He rarely comes home.
Why don't you go live with him?
I'm an adult.
I can take care of myself.
Besides,
I want to go to university here.
Where's your mom?
She…
died soon after Neung did.
Hey,
if you're going to ask so many questions,
why don't you come in?
I promise
to tell you my whole life story tonight.
Come on in,
huh?
No, I'm leaving.
Drive safely.
Don't just think about me
and hit someone's car.
Go inside now,
Song, you little brat.
Thanks for bringing me home.
Hey, Song, come eat with us.
Oh, no thanks, Juea.
I have to go submit a report.
You're a delivery boy.
If you can't find food, that's on you.
Oh, man.
Hello?
Hello, sir.
Would you like an egg
with your congee or not?
What?
I didn't order any congee.
Someone ordered it for you.
Really?
Then no egg please.
Okay, thank you very much.
SONG: YOU COULD HAVE JUST SAID
YOU WANTED TO SURPRISE ME.
SONG: WHAT IF I HAD A HEART ATTACK?
SONG: YOU WOULD HAVE WASTED MONEY
AND ALSO BE SAD.
GENSIT: WOULD IT KILL YOU
TO SAY THANK YOU?
SONG: LOVE, LOVE, LOVE, KISS, KISS.
Hi, Tofu.
Today, Nut is wearing a dark blue shirt,
grey trousers,
a black backpack,
and a silver bracelet.
He's leaving the house at 9:06 a.m.
He looks confused
and so adorable
that I have to take a picture.
What are you doing?
Recording my memories with you.
I have a Facebook now.
Well,
you had locked your door last night,
so I called and asked Song to teach me.
You can't even type properly
and you still want one?
What's so special about it
that you needed Song's help?
Do you really want to use it
or do you…
Song said
I had to have a Facebook first
before I can add you as my boyfriend.
Add what now?
Boyfriend.
Song said
I can't add you as a friend
since I don't want to be friends with you.
Boyfriend my ass.
What did Song teach you?
Don't let me catch him.
Wait, Nut.
What is it now?
Please accept my boyfriend request?
Boyfriend my ass.
Nut.
Nut,
be honest with me.
Have you not been in love for a while?
You didn't have to choke.
So? Tell me.
I was startled.
Why did you ask me that?
Because of this.
I read your script. It's terrible.
The cutesy, romantic scenes
aren't cute or romantic at all.
I almost fell asleep.
You said you wrote it from experience.
What's the matter?
Real life
isn't sweet like candy, you know.
This is a BL series.
You need cute and romantic scenes
to please the audience.
I know,
but I'm not good at it.
You keep saying that,
and I understand.
You're used to writing realistic,
socially reflective scripts,
but the network doesn't want that.
They want something new.
Nut,
I think you're stuck in a rut.
I don't know what your problem is.
But I feel like
there's a wall in front of you.
I gave you a ladder, but why don't you
have the courage to climb it?
Go back
and think about
what your problem is and fix it.
I don't want to see a wall
in front of you your whole life.
We've already started shooting. Hurry up.
I don't want to give your ladder
to someone else.
Go find some references.
BE WITH YOU
Nut.
Why didn't you knock first?
Won't you accept my boyfriend request?
Get out.
Go.
Such nonsense.
Nut!
I'm working!
I can't add you as a boyfriend
or a friend.
What must I do to see your profile?
Just keep going at it,
and he'll soften up.
Believe me, Tofu, I have experience.
Really.
Oh, I have to go now.
Is it still edible?
Look,
-I'm eating the congee.
-Hey,
you're eating it just now?
Well, you bought it for me,
so I wanted to treasure it.
Then let it spoil
because that's all you'll get from me.
Oh, you're so mean.
How can I throw it away?
If I did, it would be like
throwing away your heart.
That's enough. Bye.
Enjoy your food.
Did you wolf it all down?
Come here.
We're friends now.
From now on, you're part of my memory,
Kuenchai.
Let's make up.
Yeah.
If I go back to being a teddy bear,
will I still have my memories as a human?
But people's memories
also fade every day, right?
That's why they use things to record them,
like photos, notebooks,
Facebook,
or even text messages.
Nut's Facebook
is probably full of his memories.
And maybe it also includes
what I'm looking for.
Nut's old school,
his Facebook,
and people from his past.
LANNA HOSPITAL
EMERGENCY
If you want it,
wait until I'm dead.
Your land is next to mine.
Just sell yours.
The client wants a big plot.
If you won't sell yours, I can't either.
Since you're not using it for anything,
just sell it.
Wasn't this your intention all along
when you bought the land next to Dad's?
I was just trying to make a profit.
You want a big plot
to sell to a financier, don't you?
Whoever I sell to is my business.
Are you going to sell it or not?
If they plan to build a factory
that will affect the environment there,
I'm not selling it.
I don't need money.
Oh,
you big environmentalist.
You care about saving the world
and helping other people,
but you won't help a relative like me?
You still consider me a relative?
When Mom and Dad died,
I didn't even see your name
at the funeral.
Don't call me family
only when you need something.
If there's nothing else, please excuse me.
Your parents benefited
from the family business too!
That plot of land and your house
should have gone to me,
not a brat like you who has never
contributed to the family business.
If you want it,
wait until I'm dead.
Jan.
When did you arrive?
You said I didn't care about him.
Well, here I am.
I don't believe that you would come here
just because I said so.
Something is up, isn't it?
I did arrive in Chiang Mai
one day before Tatarn was attacked.
We met up at a cafe
near my hotel to talk about land.
Land?
Yes,
the piece of land in Ratchaburi
that he inherited.
A buyer is interested and contacted me
because I'm his last living relative.
I was arranging the business deal.
But after that,
I didn't see him again,
because I returned to Bangkok
the following day.
But you took a late flight.
Where did you go and what did you do?
Oh,
do you need to know all that?
Yes,
I need to talk to everyone
who is involved with Tatarn.
Please cooperate.
Yes.
Well, I didn't do much.
I stayed at the hotel.
In the evening, I went out for dinner…
then I went to the airport.
Even though Tatarn and I
had some problems,
I never wanted to kill him.
I assure you,
I had nothing to do with the attack.
SARAPEE POLICE STATION
She may have a financial motive,
but there's no evidence that she did it.
When I asked Saen
if Tatarn had any problems with anyone,
he didn't mention Sajjaree at all.
Is it possible that they're in
on it together?
Why did the police question you?
Were you here when he was attacked?
Why should I tell you?
You never tell me where you're going.
If you want to know so much,
I'll tell you.
I came to talk to Tatarn that day
about land.
Is that all?
Do you think there's something more?
Do you think I hurt him?
Listen.
If you want to know more,
go ask the police.
I already told them everything.
I'm leaving now.
Man,
people are so complicated.
What's that, Tofu?
He's so eloquent now that he's human,
so highbrow.
It's Nut.
He's so good-looking.
Seriously? How?
He looks mad all the time.
But okay, I get that he's like your god,
so say whatever you want.
He's so cute
and he's usually kind,
but he was really mean today.
What did he do to you?
Nut.
I brought you some milk.
FIRST LOVE
Nut, do you want some fruit?
Yes,
I'm revising it now.
LET'S EAT. YOUR MOM IS WAITING.
I'M HUNGRY TOO.
He does nothing but work.
I don't know what to do.
Kuenchai.
Get down.
Tofu!
Tofu,
where did you get a key to my room?
Well…
Who gave it to you?
It's my Mom, isn't it?
Isn't it?
Why did you go in there?
What do you want?
-Nut.
-Why did you go inside my room?
I'm sorry.
Mrs. Na was worried about you.
You're doing this again, Mom!
When will you understand
that going into someone's room
without permission
is an invasion of privacy?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
You did!
Both then and now.
You meant to.
Stop using love as an excuse.
You just want to control everything
without respecting my rights.
What happened?
I…
Stop talking!
It won't make anything better.
Nut, calm down.
Are you hungry?
I made some of that burnt pork you like.
I won't eat it!
Nut,
come with me right now.
Come here this instant.
What's wrong with you?
You're out of control!
Didn't you hear what my mom did?
What your mom did,
she did it
because she's worried about you.
Okay.
Her method may have been wrong,
but you're guilty too.
It's because you're doing this.
You lock yourself in your room
and just work.
You never pick up my calls,
isn't that true?
Honestly,
what's your problem?
I'm stressed about work.
I can't write romantic scenes for Juea.
Why? I thought the story
was based on your life.
Or did things between you and Neung
not end well?
I never went out with him.
Then who did you date?
Nut,
whatever makes you unhappy,
don't think about it.
Don't obsess over it.
Look ahead,
look around you,
and open up your heart.
It might make you happier.
What are you saying?
You'll find me a boyfriend?
Well, the best way
to get over your old love
is to find a new one, right?
If you're happy,
those romantic scenes
you're struggling with
will come to you naturally.
That's easier said than done.
I've been looking,
but I haven't found anyone.
You know that.
Shall I find someone for you?
It's easy.
Two people you know,
they're crazy about you.
It's either Prib or Tofu.
I'm sorry, Prib.
You cooked for Nut,
but I made him angry,
so…
It's fine.
It's not your fault.
Not Nut's fault either.
It was an accident.
I understand.
I can cook again another time.
It's okay. I'll clean it up.
By the way,
how come Nut's work
has to be revised so much?
Do you know?
Juea said his romantic scenes
still aren't good enough.
I guess his past is pretty bitter.
What does his past
have to do with his work?
He's writing about his life.
Even if it's a little sad,
that's okay,
because I'll add sweetness to his life,
and then things will go well.
I'm sorry, Prib.
You too, Tofu.
Sorry for losing my temper.
It's okay, Nut.
I understand everything.
I'll make you fried pork another time.
You can look forward to that.
Something wrong, Gen?
I have an emergency.
Sorry, Prib. Go home by yourself.
What?
Nut.
All right,
I'll call you a taxi.
You're doing this again, Mom!
When will you understand
that going into someone's room
without permission
is an invasion of privacy?
What are you doing?
I just want to know what you wrote.
What I write is my business.
NEXT EPISODE
Mister.
Song!
I didn't mean to cause any trouble.
But you chose to get involved.
I hope you can put an end
to this problem soon
without affecting our work.
Mrs. Na!
Are you happy, Nut?
Woo-hoo!
Your lips…
are sweet and soft like jelly.
Why do you sound like…
Who the hell are you?
Why are you doing this?
What do you want from me?
Subtitle translation by: Tara Jittalan