Do you want to be an actor?
If I play a character written by you,
I'll get to see you more, won't I?
Not to crush your dreams,
but I wouldn't get your hopes up.
Now that I have the opportunity,
I want to give it a shot.
Which one is your dad then?
Who does he think he is
to poke his nose into our business?
Before you lay blame on other people,
why don't you ask yourself
who it is
that's causing her the most distress.
Does that mean--
Na's husband is not Saen.
I only found out later
that he was dating Na.
You think
that I stole Saen from Na, don't you?
I…
Well…
That's okay.
A lot of people think like that.
But the truth is,
it was Na who left Saen.
She chose to marry Sibmeun.
She left him?
She seemed to love him very much.
I think I know why she did it.
She was dealing with many problems
with her house and her grandmother.
Saen was too busy working.
She ended up turning to Sibmeun.
He was a dependable military man.
He was someone she could rely on.
That's how they became close
and got married.
When I married Saen,
Nut was around two years old.
I don't know how to describe
the way I'm feeling.
It's like the world
has suddenly turned upside down.
Bottom becomes top.
Left becomes right.
Like a tree
whose branches grow into the ground,
pointing its roots to the sky.
Like rain
which pours reversely to the sky.
Like a cocoon that turns into a dragonfly.
The human world is different
and more much complicated than my world.
One person's truth might not be another's.
When I was a teddy bear,
I never knew what pain was.
But I know it now.
It is this kind of pain
that makes Mrs. Na wish
to forget the past.
Come eat and take your pills, Grandma.
Grandma!
Grandma.
What's wrong, Na?
I don't know. Please help her, Sibmeun.
Thanks again for your help.
Without you, who knows
what would have happened?
I'm glad I could help.
Luckily, Saen called and told me
he was caught up at work.
He asked me to check
on your grandmother for him,
so I got there in time.
He said
that he wanted to come and see her
once he was finished working,
but he said something else came up.
He may not be able to come.
In that case,
let me buy you dinner to say thank you.
I insist.
This dish is really delicious.
Here are their recommended dishes.
This one is really good.
Right.
Here's what I owe you.
This is the first installment.
I'll pay you back
all the money you loaned me.
You knew?
Who told you?
It doesn't matter who told me.
Just know I won't take advantage of you.
But I wanted you to have this money.
I don't want it back.
But I must repay you.
Thank you…
for the trouble you went to.
You paid my mortgage
and my grandmother's medical bills.
You must be sick of helping me.
You won't have to anymore.
I'm returning this to you.
What do you mean?
It's Sibmeun, isn't it?
It has nothing to do with him.
I made this decision on my own.
The other night,
Grandma's condition got worse.
Sibmeun promised her
he would take care of me.
And I think it makes sense.
We're getting married,
so Grandma won't have to worry.
Here he is.
Please excuse me.
Bye.
Whether you are separated
in life or by death, the pain is the same.
It's because of this torture and pain
that humans choose to forget.
-Where are you?
-Mrs. Na.
When you face
the worst kind of grief like that,
the only way to survive
is to forget and create a new reality.
One where you won't get hurt
or be upset ever again.
Don't worry.
Thank you, both of you,
for convincing Mom to go see a doctor.
Na isn't a stranger to us.
We're happy to help.
I didn't know that she had stopped
taking her medication.
She always goes by herself
for her appointments.
But she lied to the doctor.
Don't blame yourself.
Now that you know about it,
you can take better care of your mom.
And her condition isn't as bad
as it was before.
I think that's a good sign.
But I still don't get it.
Why won't Mom accept the truth?
Some truths are not easy to accept,
especially the ones that left scars.
You want to bury them as deep as possible.
Those who are strong can handle the truth.
It doesn't affect them.
But for some people,
it's just too much to bear.
In order to accept the truth,
you must first accept
that you have been scarred.
Your mom may have some scars
that she can't bear to face right now.
You've got to give her time.
Give her some time, Nut.
Hang in there.
-Mom.
-Na.
Na.
Come to our house sometime, Nut.
Bring your mom with you
for a change of pace.
I'll cook you guys something nice.
I'll take your offer for that.
Don't bail on us,
or I'll have to eat everything.
I'll take my mom home, then.
Thank you.
Na.
Excuse me.
Mr. Saen?
-You are…
-I'm Sitha.
Have some coffee.
Thank you.
Long time no see.
It must be eight or nine years
since Sibmeun passed away.
I don't come around this way very often.
Just once in a while.
I had some business today.
I just saw Nut and Na.
Is Na sick?
Well, it's her old condition.
It has come back?
I've heard she got better.
She is better, but she's still sick.
Nut just found out
that she stopped taking her pills,
so her condition got worse.
But she's seeing a doctor now.
That should help.
Nut found someone to look after her.
If you're worried about her,
go visit her sometime.
She would be happy to see you.
Are you hungry, Mom?
I'll order you something.
You can eat and take your pills.
Mom.
I have to get back to work.
Call me if you need anything.
Your mom
may have some scars
that she can't bear to face right now.
Give her some time, Nut.
Have you told Nut about this?
He wouldn't want to hear it.
You know when I talk about Saen,
Nut always gets angry.
I wonder if he's angry
because he doesn't believe me…
or that he doesn't like me.
Everything I do seems to be wrong.
Mom.
I'm sorry…
Although she isn't ready
to see the picture,
I still think you should keep it.
She might want to see it someday.
Before you worry about me,
worry about yourself first.
I know what happened
between your mom and Mr. Saen.
Jan told me everything.
Didn't I tell you
not to talk to her
as long as you're living here?
I know that.
But she's telling the truth, isn't she?
Your mom has the wrong idea about Saen.
That's why you try to make her forget him.
But I can't do it.
Now, my mom is in love
with someone else's husband.
It's too bad.
You know about it,
but you can't do anything.
That's worse than not knowing.
You must have been shocked
when you found out.
I was so shocked
that I didn't know what to say.
I don't know what to do about it.
I'm sorry.
What for?
I've always thought
that you were mean to your mom.
But she was mean to you too,
even if she didn't mean it.
I'm sorry too.
Why?
I hurt you,
though you did nothing wrong.
You just didn't know.
Everyone who comes near me gets hurt.
It's all right.
I wasn't hurt or angry with you.
I know how much pain you're in.
It must be a hundred times
worse than this wound.
How come you get me,
even with your amnesia?
Even my friends and family don't get me.
It's all right, Nut.
Even if the world doesn't get you,
I'll always try to understand you.
I will be here for you.
You don't have to be strong all the time.
Don't fake a smile
when you want to cry.
When you're sad,
don't think that no one is there for you.
Although that teddy bear is gone,
you still have me.
I will hold you in its place.
Horrible things happened
to Nut and his mom yesterday,
but at least something good came of it.
Hang on.
It's not what Jan and Nhong
always gossip about.
The good thing that happened
is I got to hug Nut last night,
and he hugged me back.
I hope it cheered him up a little.
That would make me so happy.
Why am I thinking about him?
I'm going crazy.
Come on, son.
Here's some hot shrimp porridge.
Wow.
It looks great, Dad.
Eat up, then. Isn't it your favorite?
It was Neung's favorite.
But…
But I like it too.
If Neung was still here,
there wouldn't be any left for me.
It has been ten years now.
Time flies.
Dad, let's go make merit for Neung.
Sure, choose where we'll do it.
I already have an idea.
What is it?
I want to donate some sports equipment
to a school that needs it.
Neung loved basketball.
How about we donate some basketballs?
Sure, son.
I know a guy
who owns a basketball factory.
He should give us a discount.
That's great, Dad.
We can get a good price.
All right. Eat your food
before it gets cold.
No. You eat up.
Won't you season it?
No need, Dad. Your cooking is the best.
Wow.
It's delicious, Dad.
Whoa.
You just appeared like a ghost.
No ghost is this handsome.
Hey.
What do you want?
I came to see if you were up.
Did you sleep well?
I did.
What about you?
Does your wound still hurt?
Seeing you happy takes my pain away.
If you need someone to hold you again,
just let me know.
I will happily volunteer.
Mom.
I woke up late and got flustered.
I guess we should give him a bath.
What a drag.
I'll help.
I'm ready, Nut.
What are you doing with a toothbrush?
Well…
You told me to brush my teeth
after a bath.
I'm giving Kuenchai a bath, not you.
Put that away and get me the hose.
I'll get back at you later, Kuenchai.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Turn the water on.
Okay.
Stop it, Tofu!
Hose Kuenchai down, not me.
Okay.
Tofu! Stop it!
That's it.
I'll do it myself. You hold Kuenchai.
Go on.
Hold him down.
Nut, Tofu.
What are you guys doing?
It was nothing.
We were giving the dog a bath
and we slipped.
That's all.
Really?
Yes, Nut slipped.
I was going to help him up,
but then he got up.
And then…
And then?
And then what?
And then you walked in.
It's always like this.
Kuenchai won't stay still,
and he's very strong.
Nut and I always fall on our faces
when we give him a bath.
You must have been shocked.
Stay and have dinner with us.
It's my treat.
Okay, Mrs. Na.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Don't tell me you don't have food at home.
Come on. Dinner is just a bonus.
I need you to check my work.
Pribpree.
Why can't we speak inside?
I need to clear things up with you.
I want to know
whether you like Nut or not.
What?
Why are you surprised?
Nut is so irresistibly charming.
No man or woman can resist his charm.
Plus, you've lost your memory.
I don't know if you were into men
or women before this.
I don't trust you.
So, do you want Nut to be your boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
What do you mean?
I only want to be a bear.
A bear?
I guess your memory is still hazy.
Let's put it like this.
Seeing someone romantically…
it's that feeling you get
when you really like someone.
When you're near them
and lock eyes with them,
your heart starts beating fast.
But my heart is beating right now.
Does this mean I like you?
Come on. Everyone has a heartbeat.
Or else you would be dead.
It's another kind of heartbeat.
It's like your heart will beat
through your chest.
You feel like you're floating on air,
and you're the only people in the world.
When I locked eyes with Nut earlier,
-my heart was beating really fast.
-What?
But I think it was from chasing Kuenchai.
I saw a documentary.
When you're tired,
your heart beats a little faster.
I don't think I like Nut like that.
Really?
Really.
If he's not your type,
can you do me a favor?
What favor?
Can you get Nut to like me?
Make him want to be my boyfriend.
Of course.
Really?
You're the sweetest.
Thank you so much.
So tell me,
what's a boyfriend?
Do I have to explain it all over again?
Yes.
Whatever you know about Nut, spit it out.
I'm ready to hear it.
Then let's start.
Nut likes to read.
He likes to read everything.
He likes poems, novels,
history, and travel guides.
He also likes picture books.
I remember there's one book
he really likes.
He once told me
that besides reading books,
you can also read people who read books.
That's cool. It sounds like something
a writer would say.
What else does he like, other than books?
Well…
He likes to watch TV series.
He enjoys watching everything.
He can stay up all night
watching something he likes.
Sometimes he even forgets about his mom.
I see.
That's why he never replies
to my late-night texts.
And things he doesn't like?
He doesn't like vegetables.
He doesn't like anyone
going into his room.
He doesn't like the lady next door.
And…
he doesn't like having me around.
Come on. You're overthinking it.
Who wouldn't want
a cute little guy like you around?
Am I right? Don't be so dramatic.
Let's continue.
Okay.
Do you know any of his secrets?
Something nobody else knows.
Things he does in the bedroom
or what he keeps under his bed.
There's nothing under his bed.
I mean…
I mean that kind of stuff.
You know?
I see. Nut likes to sleep shirtless.
Shirtless?
When he's drunk, he sleeps
with no pants on.
No pants?
He gets hot easily.
He always comes out of the shower naked.
But when I do it, he gives me an earful.
Pribpree.
Do you both take your pants off?
That's right.
Wait a minute.
I thought you didn't remember anything.
You know so much about him.
It's like you've known him for years.
And that shower thing,
how did you see that?
-Well--
-Spit it out.
I…
I heard about it from his mom and Gen.
I haven't been here long.
I don't know him as well as you do.
I don't know what he likes
or how he is when he's at work.
These things take time.
I've worked with him for three months.
But it feels like three years.
Is that so?
So what is Nut like at work?
He's very focused on his work.
When he's working,
he's all cool and serious.
He looks ten times cooler than usual.
But when there's urgent work,
he likes to go off and work by himself.
When he has writer's block,
he likes to make himself strong coffee.
No milk, no sugar.
He made coffee for me once.
That's right. He likes coffee.
I should make him coffee.
Where's the coffee maker, Tofu?
Here's some strong, hot coffee
with a little sweetness
from the maker for you.
Nut.
That's Nut's shirt.
Kuenchai. No.
Don't you think you went too far?
Pribpree bought me that shirt.
I can do whatever I want with it.
She bought you that shirt
because she adores you.
But I'm not into her.
It's my day off and she's at my house.
I sneaked out here to work.
Can you be quiet?
Jeez, Nut.
Whose house are you at? Mind your manners.
It's my house.
Eat up. Let me know if you want more.
-Thank you.
-Gosh, Mom.
I'm your son and you never do this for me.
Is he actually your son,
and I'm just adopted?
Have you worked it out just now?
What?
Gosh. Mr. Sitha.
Don't come crying
when I'm not around anymore.
-Gosh.
-How fierce.
I think I would be glad.
-Dad.
-Hey.
You should start looking
for your real parents.
Have you found your parents yet?
Stop it, Dad. You too, Mom.
-You're adopted.
-Stop.
I opened the door one day
and found you in a box.
Come on, Mom.
Nut and I have chosen our actor.
I want to do the fitting today.
Here, Pribpree. Pitch this to the clients.
This actor is the best.
Ask for a lot of money.
This actor is extraordinary.
Tell them to pay up front as well.
-All right.
-Right on.
Juea.
Are you really going
with this little punk?
What's wrong?
Juea.
You can pick anyone you want.
You can pick this one, this one,
or this one.
But you can't pick this guy.
-Why not?
-Yes, why not?
He's male, aged 17 to 18.
He's friendly, he plays basketball,
he plays instruments,
and he can ride a motorbike.
-He's perfect.
-That's true.
What's the problem?
-Shut up.
-What's wrong with him?
Listen. He's just a kid.
And he has no experience.
Can we really trust him?
Haven't you heard people say
that you should never work with kids?
If you don't trust me…
you could try going out with me.
Hey!
What is he doing here?
-Surprise!
-Juea.
I'm just kidding. You're way too serious.
-Hello, everyone.
-Hi.
Hello.
-Hello, Juea.
-Long time no see.
This is my guy.
Prepare the set. Get the costumes.
Get the cameras ready.
I want everything ready. Go.
Let's go.
-Juea, no.
-Knock it off.
-No, Juea.
-Stop it.
-Juea, please.
-Calm down, Gen.
Gen, calm down.
You should keep work
and your private life separate.
Keep that in mind.
Can you even do that, Pribpree?
Sure, I can.
Honey, can you hand me the shovel?
Thank you.
Okay.
Isn't it pretty?
It's like the one
in my grandmother's house.
Honey.
Where should I put this?
Honey!
Mrs. Na, what's wrong?
Little Prince.
I can't find Saen.
Did you see him?
Did he say where he went?
Do you know where he is?
If Mom takes her medication,
the doctor said
she will gradually stop hallucinating.
She might be frightened sometimes.
Please look after her for me.
If she mentions my dad,
just listen to her
and then change the subject.
Take her mind off him.
I haven't seen him.
It's almost noon. No wonder I'm so hungry.
Can you make me something delicious?
Is that the time?
-I'll see what we have in the fridge.
-Okay.
Next one.
Good job.
Hey…
Song, are you good at basketball?
-I'm pretty good.
-Okay.
Give the script a read.
We'll continue next week.
-Okay.
-Listen.
Study the script.
Immerse yourself in the character.
Also, you need to work on your skills.
You've got to look cool
while you're dribbling.
It will be awesome.
-Okay.
-Show me what you can do.
Thank you, guys.
I'll go get changed and take off, then.
-Goodbye.
-Thank you for today.
Goodbye.
I'll borrow your partner to train.
What partner?
Did he mean my wife?
Do you miss Neung?
I think of him all the time.
He passed away so suddenly.
Who would have known
that I would never get to hug him again?
Why did you love him so much?
Is it because he was always there for you
to help you with things?
Love is not about just being around
or doing things for your partner.
When you love someone,
you do things for them
because you care about them.
Saen has always cared for me.
You're just like him, Little Prince.
You really care for me.
Thank you.
Someone else cares about you.
He may not always be around,
but he always cares about you.
Who's that?
Nut.
He might not show it,
but he loves you very much.
He always looks after you when you sleep.
When he hears you scream,
he's the first one to run and see you.
When you cry,
he secretly cries with you.
When you smile,
I think it makes him smile too.
That's not right.
You only need one.
Mrs. Na.
It's good to think about someone
who's far away.
But you should also think of those
who are close by.
If someone is far away,
all you can do is think about them.
It's those who are close by
that you can do things for.
It's time to take your medicine.
Who's at the door?
I'll go check.
Song.
Who is it, Tofu?
-Hello, Mrs. Na.
-Hello.
This is Song.
He's Neung's brother.
Neung was at school with Nut.
Are you here to see Nut?
No, I came to see Tofu.
Are you busy? I need your help.
You said you've never played before.
I don't remember playing before.
My hands moved on their own.
You're quite good.
Let me ask you something.
Sure.
Did Neung ever buy
a teddy bear for anyone?
Neung's girlfriend
didn't like teddy bears.
She liked flowers.
Flowers?
Nut doesn't like flowers.
Nut?
Do you mean Donut?
No. Neung's girlfriend was Nhing.
She's Donut's best friend.
Nhing was really pretty.
-Nhing?
-Yes.
I can't really remember
what she looked like.
I only remember that she was gorgeous.
I was in second grade back then.
If you want to know more,
you'll have to ask my dad.
Let's play some more.
This is Tofu, a friend of mine.
You look just like him.
Hello.
Dad.
Come on. Let's play.
-Here.
-Okay.
Come on.
Bring it on.
Are you tired, Dad?
I'm a police officer.
-This is nothing.
-No.
I mean are you tired from smiling?
You son of a gun. Are you teasing me?
It has been a while
since I heard you laugh this loudly.
Gosh. Are you mocking me?
I'll teach you a lesson.
-Mom.
-Yes?
-Where's Tofu?
-He went to his friend's house.
-His friend?
-Yes.
What friend?
His name is Song.
He asked Tofu to play basketball with him.
Tofu said he would text you.
Don't bother if it's too much trouble.
What was that?
It's nothing.
Take a shower and then come eat.
Okay.
The bulb is gone again.
Come on.
Go on, shoot!
Hey!
-Yes!
-Oh, wow!
Wow!
You're good.
You don't look sick
like Song told me you were.
I just do what Song taught me.
Tofu, don't you want
to ask my dad something? Go on.
What is it?
Tofu wants to know
about Neung's girlfriend.
You see, Tofu's living with Nut.
He's the screenwriter
for the series I'm going to be in.
He was also Neung's junior at school.
I know Tofu through Nut.
Tofu probably wants to know
about Neung's girlfriend,
so he knows how to act
in case they meet each other.
Is that right, Tofu?
That's right.
I met Neung's girlfriend
a couple of times.
She was quite sweet.
She was chatty,
and she was a good influence on him.
They got into the same college.
I was hoping they could help each other
study in college.
It's too bad
that Neung had an accident.
Other than his girlfriend,
did Neung ever bring anyone else here?
Just his friends.
They're all grown up now.
But he never brought
any of his juniors home.
Not even Nut?
He's the guy I just told you about.
I see.
I've never heard of Nut before.
And Neung never mentioned him.
How is that possible?
Neung was the most important person
in Nut's life.
But to him, Nut didn't exist at all.
Could it be
that Neung wasn't the one
who brought me to life?
Tofu.
We're here.
Right.
Thank you.
Please tell your dad that I'm sorry
if I asked anything inappropriate.
He was actually glad to see you.
You should come by again.
My dad would be thrilled
to see your face more often.
Why is the front gate open like that?
Isn't Mrs. Na home alone?
It's very dangerous.
You don't know who might pass by.
No.
Be careful!
Saen.
Na.
It's really you, Saen.
It's me.
I have to go.
Where are you going?
Hey, kid.
Take care of her.
I will.
Wait.
-Where are you going, Saen?
-Mrs. Na.
Please go after him.
Where is he going this late at night?
I'm sure he'll be back soon.
You should go inside.
Nut will be angry if he sees you outside.
Weren't you going to come see your wife?
Come sit down.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Can you go after Saen?
Please.
Please go after him.
All right.
What's wrong, Mom?
I heard you scream.
She fell off a ladder.
Why would you climb a ladder?
The lightbulb burned out.
I thought I could change it, but I fell.
Why didn't you ask me?
You were in your room.
I didn't want to disturb you.
As for you, you jerk.
You were busy flirting outside.
Don't tell him off.
And don't call him that.
What should I call him?
Baby brother Tofu?
That's cute, actually.
Sweet baby brother Tofu.
Has your ass…
Have you eaten yet?
No.
Please cook something for him.
You little shit… I mean…
my dear Tofu.
Help me change the lightbulb.
Let's go.
Please don't be mad at your mom.
It was my fault for leaving her alone.
I thought I wouldn't be gone too long,
but I got carried away
chatting with Mr. Anik and Song.
Mr. Anik?
He's Song's dad.
When he first saw me, he was shocked.
Just like Song was.
Anyway,
aren't you curious
why I look exactly like Neung?
If I weren't,
I wouldn't have let you live here
or taken you to Neung's house.
I used to think
that you might be a relative,
even a sibling.
But Neung's father doesn't know you.
So, you're not their family.
Now that you know
I'm not related to Neung,
you won't kick me out, will you?
If I wanted to,
I would've left you
at the temple that day.
Gosh.
I'm a bear, not a dog.
What did you say?
I said…
I'm a nice guy, not an asshole.
Anyway, Tofu.
When I was upstairs,
I saw a guy rushing out.
Was it Uncle Saen?
Yes, he saved your mom.
But it's strange.
He seemed to be in a hurry.
It was like he was avoiding someone,
but he was also worried about her.
You haven't had dinner, have you?
Go eat something.
Where are you going?
Hey.
The food is cold. I'll warm it up for you.
I'll help.
Is Nut getting his dad to have dinner?
Take your medicine.
You shouldn't drink so much.
You're not young anymore.
You might fall ill.
Are you worried or are you jinxing me?
Think what you will.
I know. You want me dead, right?
So you can go back to her.
You got back and went straight to her
when your wife was right next door.
Are you that worried about her?
Yes.
I came to see a doctor in Bangkok
because I was worried about her.
Are you happy now?
In that case,
the doctor must have told you
that your little angel has gone insane.
Even if I agreed to a divorce,
you couldn't go back to her,
unless you want a lunatic for a wife.
What difference would it make?
I already have a crazy wife.
Saen!
Go back to her, then.
You've already slept with her.
Are you crazy?
Na and I never did that.
If you didn't,
why did your brother get jealous
and lock you out?
Enough with this love affair nonsense.
Stop being paranoid and open your eyes.
Your nephew is in a coma.
Do you ever think about him?
Why should I?
I didn't put him in a coma.
Even if I do think of him, what can I do?
I'm not a doctor.
And your company is taking care
of his medical bills.
In fact,
he's better off dead.
-Then I'll get the money my dad gave him.
-Jan!
I'll pretend that
this is the drink talking.
I'm not drunk.
I meant what I said
about Tarn and your mistress.
You better show me some respect.
We're not divorced yet.
You're still my husband.
Then give me a damn divorce.
How many times have I sent you
the papers? Just sign them.
No. I won't let you be with her.
You can hold on
to that marriage license, then.
Saen, where are you going? Come back here.
Saen, stop!
-Saen.
-Hey.
You can't leave me like this.
You're drunk. Get back inside.
-Have you no shame?
-No!
You're one to talk.
Do you think I don't know?
You love Nut because he's your son.
Isn't that right?
-Jan!
-Ouch!
Nut.
Where are you staying?
I'll give you a ride.
Saen.
Don't go.
We're done here.
Saen.
Saen, don't go!
Get back here, Saen!
-Come back!
-Stop it!
Saen.
Saen!
Nut.
It's late. Where has Nut gone?
I don't know.
I'll go and see if Jan is okay.
Jan.
Mr. Saen.
What's all the commotion about?
Jan is home, but her husband left.
I wasn't prying.
-Hey.
-I just poked my face out and saw her
having a fight with her husband.
Then he left in a car with Nut.
Nut went with Mr. Saen?
That's right. I may be old,
but my eyes are like an eagle's.
Should we go check on Jan?
There's no need for that.
Jan is a strong woman. She's fine.
She probably just threw a tantrum.
Don't be too quick to judge
who's strong or weak.
You're not in their shoes.
So don't judge them, okay?
-Okay.
-All right?
Let's go before they run out
of deep-fried dough sticks and soy milk.
-It's already late. Don't be so nosy.
-Okay.
Stop poking your nose in others' affairs.
-Aren't you sick of soy milk yet?
-Never.
I could have it every day.
I've done so much for you.
Are you really going to leave me?
Thank you, Nut.
It's fine.
I barged into your house today.
I'm sorry about that.
You don't have to be sorry.
You should visit us sometime.
We're family after all.
And my dad is already gone.
I forgot.
Jan doesn't want you to see us.
I don't care what she thinks.
She's mistaken
and she has the wrong idea about things.
But I don't want her
to pick a fight with your mom.
Your mom is a poor soul.
I don't want to cause her
any more trouble.
How is she doing?
Uncle Saen.
Hello.
How's your mom? Is she doing okay?
She's fine.
Do you want to come inside?
Dad is also home.
I've got an errand to run.
-Can you give this to your mom?
-Sure.
Thank you.
Take good care of your mom.
I will.
Who was it?
It was Uncle Saen.
Here's a gift from Chiang Mai.
Do not accept anything
from Saen from now on.
Why did Dad do that, Mom?
Uncle Saen is his brother.
You ask the same question
every time we meet.
You've seen how she is.
I asked Tofu to help look after her,
but he had gone out
when she fell off the ladder.
Thank God you got there in time.
Is that kid a houseboy?
He's a friend of mine, not a houseboy.
He's a little bit goofy.
Don't mind him if he does anything weird.
From what I've seen,
he seems like an innocent,
trustworthy kid.
You work hard.
It's good he's helping you
look after your mom.
It would've been nice
if she had married you.
She would have you to care for her.
If I had a loving father like you,
my mom and I wouldn't have
ended up like this.
If we could see the future,
no one would ever make a mistake.
But once you make a mistake,
you're bound to do it again.
I'm home, Dad.
You were gone a long time.
I stopped by a popular porridge stall
and got you some.
It's near Tofu's house.
The queue was so long I almost gave up.
Thank you, son.
You're welcome.
You're not home very often.
I just wanted you to have a good meal.
I wasn't thanking you for the porridge.
I meant Tofu.
Thank you for introducing him to me.
I know you did it because I miss Neung.
Hey, Dad.
Let me ask you something.
What is it?
Did you have a lovechild
with a secret mistress?
You little devil. Watch your mouth.
Look at me. I'm working my ass off.
Would I have time for a mistress?
It's strange.
Tofu looks exactly like Neung.
Wait a second.
Maybe Neung has been reincarnated.
Dad. You watch too much TV.
Neung has only been dead for ten years.
There's no way he could be reincarnated
as someone my age.
That's true.
Hey, Dad.
Why don't you do some digging into Tofu?
Do you think I have time for that?
Please, Dad.
Aren't you a tiny bit curious?
I'll look into it.
Enough chit-chat. Eat up.
Here.
-Take a spoon.
-Thank you.
I got it.
Eat up. Don't wait for me.
The ones who love each other
aren't together.
And the ones who are together
don't love each other.
Who do you mean, Ms. Left Slipper?
You've been a human for ages,
but you're just as dumb as before.
Why do you have to be mean to Tofu?
Are you jealous that he got to be human?
Why would I be jealous of a teddy bear
who lives a pathetic life
without any vision, ideology,
nor the spirit of a free man.
That's enough.
What I just said…
I was talking about Mrs. Na, Mr. Saen,
and Jan.
Do you mean Mr. Saen loves Mrs. Na,
but he can't be with her?
Does that mean he doesn't love Jan?
You've been married to Mr. Saen
for a long time.
How come I've never seen him here?
My husband works in Chiang Mai.
He rarely flies back home.
But I fly over there quite often.
You must be lonely
since you rarely get to see him.
Why don't you move to Chiang Mai with him?
Well, I guess it's my bad luck.
Soon after we got married,
our company started failing.
My dad had to let other investors
help run the company.
Saen took responsibility by quitting
and he got a new job in Chiang Mai
even though it wasn't his fault.
The economy was just bad.
In the end, we couldn't hold on
and we had to sell our factory.
I heard Sibmeun had invested his money
in a house in this neighborhood.
It was in a good spot
and the price was reasonable,
so I bought one for myself.
I spent all my savings on this house.
How can I leave it?
I never thought that one day,
Nut would move in next door with his mom.
Actually, I feel just as sorry for Jan
as I do for Mrs. Na.
There must be something else
between Mrs. Na, Mr. Saen, and Jan
that I don't know about.
But it goes to show
that everyone has problems to deal with.
And their problems
are way too complicated for me
to understand in such a short time.
About life in high school?
And it's not an odd thing anymore.
But it's still not normal.
If for you, normal means
only thinking the way you do,
then half the world would be abnormal.
That plot of land and your house
should have gone to me,
not a brat like you who has never
contributed to the family business.
If you want it,
wait until I'm dead.
Tofu!
Where did you get a key to my room?
Well…
Well, the best way
to get over your old love
is to find a new one, right?
If you're happy,
those romantic scenes
you're struggling with
will come to you naturally.
Shall I find someone for you?
They're crazy about you.
It's either Prib or Tofu.
Subtitle translation by:
Pannapat Tammasrisawat