PREVIOUSLY
Mister.
Song!
I didn't mean to cause any trouble.
But you chose to get involved.
I hope you can put an end
to this problem soon
without affecting our work.
Mrs. Na!
Are you happy, Nut?
Your lips…
are sweet and soft like jelly.
Why do you sound like…
Who the hell are you?
Why are you doing this?
What do you want from me?
I don't believe you.
Who sent you to mess with me?
Tell me!
-Nut.
-Come here.
Please let go of me.
-Where are we going?
-What's wrong?
Stay out of it, Mom.
-Come.
-Why? Where are you taking him?
This is between me and Tofu.
Stay out of it.
-What did Tofu do?
-Come.
-Come on.
-Nut. Where are you going?
-Mom, let go.
-Tofu.
Let go.
Nut.
Get in.
Get in!
Don't you dare get out!
Where are you taking Tofu?
Let go, Mom.
Where are you going? It's late.
-Please calm down, Nut.
-Nut.
Come out, Tofu.
-Mrs. Na.
-Come out, Tofu.
-Nut.
Nut!
-Get out.
-No.
I said get out!
I won't.
You won't?
Come here!
Can I pick up the slipper first?
Stop stalling.
You'll run away.
Come here.
-Nut.
-Come on!
I won't run away.
That's your mom's slipper.
-Come here.
-Nut.
Tofu.
This is your last chance.
Will you tell me the truth,
or should I get the police to make you?
I…
I am…
I am Tofu.
Fine.
Let's see how stubborn you really are.
Nut.
-Come here.
-Nut.
-Come up here.
Nut.
Officer.
Come here. Sit down!
Calm down, kid.
What's going on?
He's a stranger.
He's living in my house.
Why are you living in this house, then?
He asked me to take care of his mother.
So you know each other?
-Yes.
-No.
So what is it? Do you know each other?
Or not?
We do.
This is Nut. His first name is Peeranut.
He's 27 years old.
His mom is Matana. His dog is Kuenchai.
Tofu!
That's plenty of information.
You say you don't know him.
He just said
you invited him into your house.
Listen to me.
I don't know who he is.
My mom felt sorry for him,
so she brought him in.
And I let her.
But recently,
he has been acting strangely,
as if he's plotting something.
Are you?
I'm not plotting anything.
I just…
want to be with Nut.
I don't know what happened.
Everything was fine…
until we kissed.
You kissed?
Wait a minute.
There's no way he's a stranger.
So what is it?
Will you report him?
How old are you anyway? You look so young.
I'm not sure.
If you report him,
you may be charged with child abduction
and false imprisonment.
Those are two charges.
So, are we filing the report?
-Yes.
-No.
All right.
What do you want to do?
You should discuss it.
Don't confuse the police.
Stop following me.
Go away.
Please don't send me away.
You know I have nowhere to go.
I'm sorry
if I offended you,
but I was telling the truth.
Do you really have amnesia?
What's really wrong with you?
If you're not going to tell me,
then get lost.
I'm Tofu, your teddy bear.
I'm your teddy bear.
I have no idea
how I turned into a human.
I never thought you would be such a liar.
Can I believe anything you've said?
Nut. I'm Tofu.
Nut.
Nut
Don't leave me, Nut.
Nut.
I really am yours.
Nut, open the door.
Nut.
I really am yours.
Nut, wait for me.
Nut!
Nut.
I really am yours.
Nut!
I'm sorry
if I offended you,
but I was telling the truth.
Do you really have amnesia?
What's really wrong with you?
Your lips are sweet
and soft like jelly.
Your lips…
are sweet and soft like jelly.
Who the hell are you?
Why are you doing this?
What do you want from me?
Who sent you to mess with me?
Tell me!
I'm Tofu, your teddy bear.
Why did you have to lie?
What a coward.
Would it hurt
to get your phone out and call Nut?
Do you want him to leave you?
How could someone leave
a person they love?
Can't you see he has already left?
Do you think he'll come back
for you like in a Korean drama?
If you're not going to call Nut,
then get up and find my Little One.
Okay.
I remember she fell off around here.
Little One!
Ms. Left Slipper.
Walk around and look for her.
Little One!
Tofu is safe. He's with me.
He told me that Nut kicked him
out of the house.
I'll let him stay with me tonight.
Let's wait for Nut to calm down.
I'll talk to him.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Tofu.
What did you do to him?
Why is he so mad at you?
I didn't do anything.
I just kissed him.
You kissed him?
He kissed me back too.
Well…
We kissed each other.
That's enough.
I get it now.
They just kissed.
Why would he get mad?
Wait, who's that with Gen?
Is it Song?
It looks like Song.
Is he finally telling us about it?
Hello.
This is Tofu.
The kid from Nut's house
that I told you about.
They had a fight,
so I thought
I would let him stay here tonight.
I'll get the first aid kit.
Have you eaten anything?
Not yet.
Here's some hot porridge.
I made it myself.
Thank you.
Here.
Yours is over there.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
What did you fight about this time?
I…
was just going to kiss…
-Tofu!
-What are you doing, Gen?
You spilled it everywhere.
He said something rude.
Something
that might cause adults to freak out.
It wasn't rude.
Well, maybe a little.
It was just a misunderstanding.
You see,
Nut has always been temperamental.
-You know him.
-That's right.
Do you know Nut well?
I used to see him when he was a kid.
He came to work with his dad.
We barely spoke though.
We only started speaking
when he became friends with Gen.
Did you know Nut's dad?
We were classmates
in the military academy.
What was his dad like?
I want Nut to apply to the academy.
What about your son?
Will he apply next year?
My son doesn't want to.
What?
He's a man and a soldier's son.
It would be a waste
if he doesn't join the military.
Nut has to join the military.
He was a determined, serious man.
He was also a strong leader.
We were just acquaintances though.
We weren't close friends.
It was a shame that he died young.
Nut's mom was very upset.
Sibmeun really loved his family though.
But from what Nut said,
his dad was really strict with him.
I see. That must be why
Nut never talks about his dad.
There aren't any photos
of him at home either.
He probably loved them in his own way.
He wanted a bright future for Nut
as a leader.
So he was trying
to lay a path for Nut in the military,
to follow in his footsteps.
I guess he forgot
that everyone
has to follow their own path.
Dad.
Did you ever want me to be a soldier?
No.
Actually,
I kind of wanted you to be a doctor.
I just thought that
if you wanted to follow in our footsteps,
we would be able to guide you
better than other career paths.
In the end, though, it's up to you.
You have to decide what you want to be.
Every job has its pros and cons.
If you do a job you enjoy,
at least, you will be happy.
Then you will do that job well.
Mom.
-What is it?
-What?
-What's going on?
-I'm touched.
-Touched?
-Gen.
I thought you wanted to wipe your mouth.
-Here.
-Come on.
Our little puppy.
Puppies come from dogs.
-That backfired.
-Look at him.
You're never like this.
-Come on.
-Okay, you're touched.
I love you too.
-Can I hug you?
-Come here.
You little puppy.
Had Nut had a warm
and understanding family,
he would've grown up to be
a happy young man like Gen.
THE LITTLE PRINCE
You're home.
What's wrong?
Can you tell me?
SONG: SLEEPING ALONE
MUST BE LONELY, MISTER
I'M NOT LONELY
I HAVE SOMEONE TO SLEEP WITH
Gen.
What?
Will I get to live with Nut again?
I don't know.
You and Nut are the only ones who know.
It's up to your hearts
if you want to get back together.
I really want to.
But…
Nut…
Stop sulking.
Nut is just confused.
It's hard for him to move on
and start over, you know?
He probably had high hopes,
and you must have disappointed him.
Give him time.
I'll talk to him.
SONG: WHO? WHO ARE YOU SLEEPING WITH?
ARE YOU CHEATING ON ME?
MISTER, DON'T
Nut.
I want to be back by your side.
I will not give up.
BE WITH YOU
Wait.
You're not Neung.
Isn't he your friend?
He fell from your balcony
yesterday morning.
Who gave you that pork recipe?
I just followed my gut.
I'm your teddy bear.
But…
I have no idea
how I turned into a human.
Do you really think Tofu is a teddy bear?
Who would be that crazy?
I just thought it might have
something to do with…
Is this about your ex again?
Do you think your ex revolves around you
like a planet orbiting around the sun?
I'm not just imagining it.
I have my reasons.
Tofu reminds me of him all the time.
Nut, there are tens of millions of people
in this country.
Don't you think
some of them talk and think alike?
Tofu could've watched the same movies,
read the same books,
and listened to the same songs as your ex.
That's why he said that.
But what he said was special.
He used the exact same words.
So what?
Did you think he sent Tofu here
to steal your teddy bear,
say those lines,
and love you in his place?
If you can't answer it,
why bother thinking about
impossible questions like that?
You should think about the question
that you can answer.
Do you still want Tofu in your life?
So it's you
who was with him.
Why do you need to borrow my laptop?
To get Nut back.
I'M NOT LONELY WITHOUT YOU
Why did you go to my house?
Where are you taking Tofu?
Here.
I guess that's love.
Even though he kicked you out,
you still look after his mom.
I promised Nut
that I would take care of her.
Even if he's still mad at me,
I need to keep my promise.
True love.
I'm going now.
Okay.
-Look, Tofu is here.
-Tofu.
-Tofu is here.
What a relief.
I was praying for your safety all night.
What about Ms. Left Slipper?
Why did you come back alone?
Mr. Right Slipper,
where's your girlfriend?
I lost Ms. Left Slipper.
What?
My goodness.
Little One shouldn't have helped you.
You always call others ignorant.
Well, your girlfriend
can't ignore you now.
I promise you, Mr. Right Slipper,
I'll find Little One.
I would never lose Mrs. Na's belongings.
Where's Mrs. Na?
Oh…
Thank you.
Let me help.
It wouldn't be as pretty
had I done it myself.
Thank you for helping me.
You're welcome.
This area still seems a bit bare.
Shall we buy some more plants?
Are you free this Saturday?
Let's take a photo
as a memento of the three of us
arranging the garden together.
I'll put the chair away.
Let me help.
I need to research a lot
for the subject I teach,
in order to explain it to the children.
But the more I research,
the more questions I have.
Do you think
Thai people really did migrate
from the Altai Mountains?
And did the villagers of Bang Rachan
really die fighting to protect Ayutthaya?
So,
is it not true?
Well,
I don't know much about this stuff.
You might have to explain it to me
a bit more.
Would you mind
if I asked you to come
and explain it to me every day?
Maybe Thais didn't migrate here
but have always been in this area.
As for Bang Rachan, they didn't fight
for anyone but themselves.
Is that what you think?
History isn't a record
of what actually happened.
It's just distorted recollections
that are retold in a way
that suits whoever is telling them.
Do you agree?
I didn't think…
you would be interested in history.
I like to read.
History, philosophy, and literature.
This one
is my favorite.
THE LITTLE PRINCE
"The Little Prince."
I really like
the illustrations in this book.
But when I was at school,
I didn't really understand it.
They say,
older people perceive
The Little Prince differently
than children.
You should read it again.
You might understand
and perceive it differently this time.
Okay.
Sib.
Mrs. Na.
When did you get here, Tofu?
Just now.
Do you remember Mr. Sibmeun now?
Do you want to tell me anything?
-Thank you.
-It's okay.
You all look happy in this picture.
Why don't you want to think about it?
Sometimes you are happy
at the start of a nightmare, Tofu.
We can't have good dreams all the time.
I have a secret to tell you.
You're the first one to know.
I've just started dreaming recently.
Whenever I have a nightmare,
I would really be glad when I wake up,
because I know it's just a dream.
It has passed.
The monster in my dream
can't hurt me anymore.
Whenever I have a good dream,
I'm happy all day long.
Don't you want
to go back to sleep
to continue the good dream?
No.
In my real life, I have Nut,
you,
and many other friends.
Sometimes I'm happy. Sometimes I'm sad.
But it's reality.
I wouldn't trade it for a dream.
Mrs. Na.
Some nights you have good dreams.
Some nights you have bad dreams.
But in the end,
you have to wake up.
I've decided
to borrow some money
from Sakon to help Na.
Have you thought it through?
She's struggling.
She has to pay for her house
and her grandmother's medical bills.
What can I do?
It's pointless.
You won't hold her grandmother back.
It will just prolong her suffering.
In the end,
the person who will suffer the most is Na.
Is it Na or you who will suffer?
Do you think I don't know
what you're trying to do?
Is it only a soldier with a bright future
like you who deserves Na?
When we were kids, I may not have been
as good as you at anything,
but I won't let you
walk all over me this time.
You know Na loves me.
I'm warning you with good intentions.
Think it through.
The money will cause you trouble.
I have thought it through.
I will show both you and Na
that I can make her happy too.
May I give him a sponge bath?
Go ahead.
The lab results are in.
We found a bloodstain
on the living room floor,
but it had been cleaned.
That means a fight occurred here.
I think Tatarn
could have been injured and moved.
So, it seems like
he was attacked and killed.
That means Saen lied to us.
Should we issue a warrant?
Not yet. Don't alert him.
He went this far to deceive us.
He and his wife must have a solid plan.
Find some solid evidence against him,
then we'll arrest him.
Lieutenant.
Have a look around.
There must be more evidence.
Yes, sir.
Do you remember what I told you?
About someone Tarn liked.
I do.
I would ask permission
to enter Tarn's house
to find clues about this person.
I want to create a miracle.
TO NUT, FROM TOFU
Excuse me, sir.
It's the commander.
Yes.
Roger that.
"Be with you."
BE WITH YOU
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
I'm just arranging your books.
Why this book?
Well?
And this.
You hid the teddy's scarf
in my room, didn't you?
Didn't you?
I didn't.
It had fallen, so I put it away.
Don't lie!
You were going through my personal stuff!
What do you want?
Nut. You said you would talk about it.
Yes. Talk to him nicely.
Right. Calm down.
How can I calm down?
The scarf. The book.
Still think it's unrelated?
He sent you, didn't he?
Who did?
Don't act innocent.
Answer me!
If you think someone sent me,
why don't you ask them?
I want to know
who he is
and why he's so important to you.
Why do you keep insisting I know him?
I've told you everything.
If you still don't believe me,
then I don't know what to do.
I really don't know
how I got here.
It's not some plan.
I just want to stay here with you.
I want to take care of you.
Take care of your mom.
That's all.
If you don't want me anymore,
I'll leave.
You're with Tofu almost all the time.
Do you really not know
what kind of person he is?
So,
you no longer
want him in your life, do you?
Are you really leaving, Tofu?
Nut won't let me stay here.
I don't want you to leave.
If you miss me,
you can call.
Be a good boy, Kuenchai.
Take care of Mrs. Na for me.
Where are you going to stay?
He can stay with me.
I live alone. My dad won't mind.
Don't worry.
You can't stay with Song, can you?
He's Nut's friend after all.
My house would be the best option.
Thank you.
I'll go now.
Goodbye.
I'll sneak back sometime.
Let's go home.
Song.
I need to do something.
Can you help me?
A left slipper?
Yes.
It's pink and fluffy.
I remember I dropped it here.
Can you help me find it?
I'll look over there, then.
You might not know who Tofu is
or where he came from,
but he has never hurt you, has he?
He's a nice kid.
Will you really let him go like that?
Think it through.
If you really don't want him in your life,
I'll take him somewhere else.
But an amnesiac
with no family background like him,
where could he go
but a foster home?
That's what you were going to do before.
I guess it's fine.
Good.
You won't have to see him anymore.
You won't have to worry
when he does something wrong,
or get paranoid about your ex.
Just go back to your old life.
The life you lived before he came along.
Are you okay with that?
Are you?
Just buy some new ones.
I can buy them if you don't have money.
It's not the same.
It belongs to Mrs. Na.
It's more than just a slipper.
It's like a friend.
A friend?
Oh, I meant…
A friend for your foot.
Everything has its value.
Some things can't be replaced.
I see.
Let's find it, then.
Tofu, help me!
Ms. Left Slipper.
Is that it, Tofu?
Yes.
Mr. Dog.
Calm down, Mr. Dog.
May I have Ms. Left Slipper back?
Ms. Left Slipper!
Mr. Dog, stop!
Ms. Left Slipper.
Please stop.
Mr. Dog, stop.
Please let go of Ms. Left Slipper.
-Whoa.
-Oh, my.
Hey. Watch where you're going.
I'm sorry.
You've messed up all my stuff.
Mr. Dog, stop.
Mr. Dog!
Tofu!
Mr. Dog.
You pervert!
My gosh.
I never thought a pretty boy
would be like this.
It's not like that.
I was looking for a dog.
What dog? I didn't see one.
Don't lie to me.
Right. Let's take him to the police.
-Grab him.
-It's not that.
The proof is in your hand.
-Look at that.
-It's right in your hand.
-Please let go.
-I need to take pictures.
-Song, help.
-Look.
Excuse me. That's my friend.
He's not a thief.
You came together? Are you a pervert too?
-I'm not.
-Great.
-No.
-Hey, Oh!
-Those are your bras.
-Miss.
-That's not true.
-I'm not a pervert.
Come here, pervert.
I wasn't doing anything.
I don't believe you.
Tell it to the police.
Such a pretty boy. What a shame.
Come here! Come on, pervert.
I didn't do anything.
It was brand new.
What a pervert. Go inside!
Wait. What happened?
-Well…
What is it? Tell me.
-The thing is…
Song has probably taken him
far away by now.
You kicked him out, now you're worried.
How touching.
Nut.
Tell me what you want to do.
I'll support you.
But I'm warning you,
if you leave this unresolved,
you won't be able to focus on work.
I--
Nut.
Great timing.
Sit!
What's the commotion about?
It's this pervert.
He was stealing my bras.
I caught him red-handed.
-Right.
-I see.
Wait.
Last night, didn't you…
kiss a guy?
-Now,
-What?
you're stealing women's bras?
What are you actually into?
It's not like that.
I was following a dog
and ran into the rack.
I told them that, but no one believed me.
Liar.
We saw with our own eyes
that you grabbed a handful of bras.
Officer, here are the goods.
-I…
-Right.
They got wrapped around my hands
when I was getting up.
There you go. You're a pervert. A thief!
-Such a pretty boy. What a shame.
-Enough.
That's enough. I'll question him.
Wait a minute, Lieutenant.
What is it?
No need to question him. Someone called
to confirm it was a misunderstanding.
-A misunderstanding?
-Gosh.
Who is it?
There. Here he is.
Go in, Nut.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up.
What's the matter?
I'm bailing someone out.
Who?
Someone said our friend got arrested
for stealing bras.
I see.
Wait.
Oh, that's right.
The kid who said
he kissed you last night, right?
Yes.
Someone took him.
What?
Just now.
Who bailed him out?
Thank goodness you came to Bangkok,
or Tofu could've been arrested.
No.
The security camera shows
that he didn't do anything.
Thank you for helping me anyway.
No problem.
Come on. Let's go inside.
We'll decide what to do later.
Don't worry.
If you really can't go back,
I'll find a way to help.
Don't worry. Let's go.
Nut.
Where's Tofu?
Is he in jail?
I can't believe it.
He seemed so innocent.
He was a poor choice.
When you're looking for a boyfriend…
Well,
I mean someone to look after your mom,
you should be more careful.
Thanks for going with me.
Get home safely.
Excuse me.
What?
You seem lonely,
like you have no friends to talk to.
Right. Nut told me you live alone.
Your husband doesn't visit.
You should find something useful
to do with your spare time,
so you don't have to butt in…
I mean bother yourself
with other people's matters.
Thank you for bringing us the news.
I'll be leaving now, Mrs. Sad…
jaree.
You punk! Come out!
You punk! Come back!
Come back!
You seem lonely,
like you have no friends to talk to.
Right. Nut told me you live alone.
Your husband doesn't visit.
Why are you following me?
Who sent you?
Who?
VIEW SATHORN PROPERTY
SAEN
Why are you calling?
I'll visit you at home tomorrow.
WEDDING ANNIVERSARY
To Nut, from Tofu.
Tofu kissed Nut.
He felt so good that he started crying.
Nut asked, "Why are you crying?"
Tofu answered, "I don't know.
I only know that it's sweet.
It's so sweet I'm scared."
Nut smiles sweetly at Tofu.
Nut adores Tofu.
Tofu smiles back at Nut.
Come on. Help me.
You should help your dad.
You do this one.
Nut.
If I were a screenplay writer,
and I could write my own ending,
I would want it to be like this.
I want us not to fight.
I want us to be happy.
Is it that moving?
All right. Come, Tofu. Let's eat.
Then Song can take you upstairs.
Come on. Give me a hand.
Here.
Sure.
I'm full. Let's take a walk.
Since you'll be staying here for a while,
you might as well look around.
Come on. I'll show you my favorite place.
Here.
Do you like basketball that much?
It's Neung's stuff.
It's all old.
Mine is in that box.
I would like you to stay in my room,
but it's small and messy.
Stay in Neung's room instead.
You look the same anyway.
It will be like Neung still lives here.
Yes, it will.
Is the room okay?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Let's play games when you've had a shower.
Okay.
Am I really never
going to see Nut anymore?
TOFU TOFU UPDATED HIS PROFILE PICTURE.
TOFU: I MISS NUT.
Why do I look like you?
Why am I like this?
What happened to me?
I was Nut's teddy bear.
Why did I become your look-alike?
The person Nut loves…
Who did this to me?
Where can I find the answers?
What are you doing, Dad?
What is it?
I saw someone.
They're sneaking around outside.
Is it a burglar?
I don't know.
Dad, wait.
I'll catch the burglar.
What?
It's okay.
Are you leaving?
Did you come to see Tofu?
Come inside.
Thank you.
You're Nut, aren't you?
Song told me.
Yes.
Did you think it through
before coming here?
Although Tofu has lost his memory,
he still has feelings.
You're not just his employer,
and you didn't just save his life.
You're his whole world,
his sanctuary, and something to hang onto.
If you take Tofu back, I only hope
that he will get to stay with you
until his memory returns completely.
Nut!
Let's go home.
Thank you, both of you.
I'll get going now.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Bye.
Did we do the right thing?
I don't know.
But since they miss each other
and they want to stay together,
we have to let them be.
Now, we should go inside
and get some sleep.
Are you sleepy?
-I am.
-Go to bed then.
I thought about the difference
between not having you around,
and having you despite being suspicious.
Did you choose the latter?
No.
I just wanted to follow my heart.
Whatever my heart wants,
I want to let it be.
Right now, I want to be with you.
But I don't know
if I'll get paranoid again.
I don't know what I need to do,
but I want to move forward.
I don't want to leave it hanging.
Please be patient with me.
I promise I'll never kick you out again.
And I'll try not to mention him.
I won't be able to forget him though.
And I won't try to forget him…
because our relationship
is the happiest memory
I have from that time.
But I won't force you to be him,…
because you are you.
He's in the past.
But you're right here
with me.
I promise,
I'll stay with you forever.
Is that all?
What more should I say?
I gave a whole speech,
and that's all you can say?
I must look crazy.
In that case,
I'll try to be good.
I'll be trustworthy,
so that you can trust me,
even though my identity
might not seem so trustworthy.
But everything I've done for you
has always been sincere.
One day,
you'll recognize my sincerity.
I'll prove it.
I promise.
Does that sound good?
Okay. That's good.
You promised.
I'll wait and see.
What now?
This is how we promise.
You're such a baby.
This is how adults make a promise.
Mom is probably asleep.
We can tell her tomorrow.
Welcome home.
Tofu, hurry up.
Okay.
Good night.
Wait.
What is it?
Did you forget something?
What did I forget?
This.
What are you doing?
I'm following your script.
Shall we start?
I'm not really feeling it.
You're so hard to please.
-We can rebuild the mood.
-Sure.
Should we start from the angry part?
Let's skip that.
Then skip to your room.
I'm not in the mood now.
Nut.
I'll skip forward for you.
-Let's start at--
-Go.
I'm going to bed.
You've had him follow me
since we separated.
Are you a psychopath?
Why are you doing this?
I'm doing all this because I love you.
If I can't be happy, then no one will be.
If I wasn't indecisive,
if I had been firm
I wouldn't have made the wrong choice.
She didn't really love him.
I'm just a product of their mistake.
Am I supposed to give up
and be a coward like you?
And behave immorally like you?
-I can't do it.
-Tarn!
I already have plenty of friends.
But now,
I want you.
Subtitle translation by:
Pattranun Bunyanund