I never thought you would be such a liar.
Can I believe anything you've said?
If you can't answer it,
why bother thinking about
impossible questions like that?
You should think about the question
that you can answer.
Do you still want Tofu in your life?
I promised Nut
that I would take care of her.
Even if he's still mad at me,
I need to keep my promise.
True love.
…Even though my identity
might not seem so trustworthy.
But everything I've done for you
has always been sincere.
Kuenchai.
Hey.
Good morning.
I'm back.
Is it really you, Tofu?
You won't leave again, will you?
Stay here from now on.
If Nut still wants me,
I won't go anywhere.
Fine.
I won't send you away.
You might as well stay forever.
Are you serious?
Yes.
I'm leaving, Mom.
Okay.
Nut.
You forgot your lunchbox.
Thank you.
Enjoy the food.
Were you in Chiang Mai or the forest?
How do you not know anything?
You lost out.
I was occupied with Tarn.
Then I saw it on Facebook,
Tofu's post saying he missed Nut.
Gen.
Are Nut and Tofu…
Prib, look over there.
It's written all over his face.
You said that when you come back,
you would claim what's yours.
It's too late. Give it up.
Did I make a mistake stepping away?
Nut, come here.
I knew it.
-What is it?
-All smiles, aren't you?
That's right. So what?
The other day you were so upset.
But today, you're smiling like a lunatic.
If I were to guess,
I would say
you've settled things with Tofu.
Yes. We talked.
You sorted it all out?
Yes.
You picked him up from Song's.
How did you know I had picked him up?
Now, it's my turn. What about you?
You two chat often, right?
Not really.
Just every night?
Hold on. I'm not done with my questions.
Don't try to change the subject.
You're a sly fox.
Hey Nut. Come back here.
We were talking about you. Come back.
How is everyone?
I missed everyone a lot.
You leave home only one night, Beary.
Don't overdo it.
Missing your dual-language complaints
for just one day
made me feel lonely.
Don't be sarcastic.
Be nice, everyone. Tofu just got back.
But my Little One has disappeared.
It's all your fault.
Now, you have the nerve
to behave like this.
You're just like
all the other humans in this country.
Sweeping problems under the rug.
Wow. You're angry about your girl,
but you can still preach your politics.
I really respect you.
Items like you, that represent
middle-class wealth,
surely have no idea
that ideology is driven by anger.
I'm sick of listening to you droning on
about the class gap or whatever.
Instead of mocking me,
why don't you use the time
to educate yourself?
This house is just a bubble.
You're so used to being oppressed
that you're afraid of asking questions
or voicing your views.
All you do is act fierce
and mix Thai and English words
to hide your fear.
Everyone, please calm down.
It's my fault.
I apologize.
I promise you
that I'll bring back Ms. Left Slipper.
Your promise means nothing.
It's in your upper-class blood
to use people then discard them.
What more do you want?
Tofu is trying his best.
You knew it was an accident.
Your girl volunteered,
meaning that she willingly took the risk.
You can't keep blaming him
and ordering him around
like you do with her.
When have I ever made her do anything?
She likes watching dramas,
but you force her
to watch documentaries with you.
Have you ever asked her if she wants to?
You claim you want democracy.
What kind of democracy
won't accept different opinions.
The patriarchy.
A societal system dominated by males.
Prib?
You made Nut fried pork for lunch, right?
Yes. I made it myself.
I knew it.
Normally, Nut doesn't eat
from his lunchbox.
If you didn't make it,
who else could it be?
Can I ask you one more time?
Do you like Nut?
I like him.
I want him to be
more than just a boyfriend.
I want him as my owner.
I want him as my boss.
I want him as my family.
As my everything.
That's enough.
I get it.
Can I ask you one more question?
Do you know what Nut wants
for his birthday?
I once read Mrs. Na's book,
The Little Prince.
I remember this one section
where the fox tells Little Prince
that every Thursday,
the hunters have a dance ritual
with the village girls,
which allows the fox
to take a stroll in the vineyard.
Thursday
is thus a special day.
If the hunters could dance on any day,
Thursday will not hold
any special meaning.
I understand now
why humans value special days.
Since there's no certainty in this world,
relationships may change any day.
On our special day,
we deserve happiness
to make it more special than other days,
don't you think?
You hired someone to follow me.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you mean.
Don't act all innocent.
That guy Chut confessed to me.
You've had him follow me
since we separated.
Are you a psychopath?
Why are you doing this?
Because I am your wife.
The wife you don't live with
and never share anything with.
If I didn't have someone follow you,
how would I know what's going on?
I'm no psychopath.
I'm doing this because I care about you.
You care about me?
You only care about yourself.
You're afraid of losing face,
and being humiliated.
You were afraid I was going to see Na.
So afraid that you bought a house
next to hers.
Even though I keep insisting
that Na and I are over,
you can't help but be paranoid.
How can it be over
when she's the only one you've ever loved?
When we married,
you were in love with her.
When you were with me,
you thought about her.
When you weren't with me,
you went to see her.
I'm no psychopath.
I'm doing all this
because I love you.
Do you hear me? I love you!
But I don't love you.
I married you
because your father pressured me,
and you were the only woman
I was close to.
If I had known
everything was just a scheme,
if I had been more assertive
with you back then,
I wouldn't have been stuck
with a woman I don't love.
I know that you don't love me.
You want to go back to her.
I won't let you.
I won't agree to a divorce.
If I can't be happy, then no one will be.
Where are you going? What are you doing?
Let go of me. Let go.
Let go!
How many times have I told you
not to jump up at the table?
Do you not understand?
Have I already given you food?
Na!
What's the matter?
Look at this!
Look!
Look at it.
Look at it and get it into your thick head
that the guy you think is your husband
is actually my husband.
Do you hear me? He is my husband!
-Jan!
-Look!
-You!
-Jan!
Take a look! These are our wedding photos.
Saen is my husband!
Sibmeun was yours,
and he's dead!
He left a dysfunctional family.
The mother is crazy and the son is gay!
Mrs. Na.
You act like a victim
who was driven to madness.
You used your suffering
to make people feel sorry for you
when you made the wrong choice yourself.
You agreed to marry him!
You were the one who left Saen!
Did you hear that? You left Saen!
Did you hear that?
In the end,
the one who everyone thought was an angel
only cares about herself.
You chose stability over the person
who was devoted to you!
You're just as selfish as me!
Let go of me!
Let go.
Get off her.
Stop fooling yourself!
It's time you accepted the truth!
Do you hear me? Stop fooling yourself!
He is my husband!
He is my husband! Do you hear me?
-Na.
-Do you?
I want to know
why you and Mom didn't get married.
I should…
You probably know
that your mom and I were once in love.
However, our relationship changed
after Jan came along.
You want a loan from my father?
Yes.
Na's grandmother is seriously ill.
Her treatment is expensive.
I would like to help her.
I envy Na.
She is really lucky to have a guy
who loves her so much.
Seeing as you've helped me so much,
I'll talk to my father for you.
Really?
Thank you so much.
No problem.
I know that you need money.
But this is a lot.
It's not a problem.
Please accept it.
I sincerely want to help.
Here.
Thank you.
Try turning it on.
At first, Jan was just my boss,
my colleague.
Once I owed her money,
things started to get worse.
I'm not coming back to Bangkok
this weekend.
Again?
But it's my birthday this Saturday.
Saen?
Did you get cut off?
Saen is in a meeting.
Do you have a message for him?
Please let it be about work only, though,
because he's working right now.
I'm sorry.
I'll call again later.
Kwan said she might be late
and that we should go ahead and order.
Why didn't you tell me?
We didn't have to come so early.
It's no big deal.
Since we had to go out anyway,
we should get something to eat.
Why don't you order?
This dish is really delicious.
What would you like?
Here are their recommended dishes.
Isn't that Na and Sib?
They seem close.
I guess it's not that surprising though.
He's your twin brother.
He probably just helps in taking care
of his busy brother's girlfriend.
How nice of him.
Your mom and I
almost got married.
Here's what I owe you.
This is the first installment.
I'll pay you back
all the money you loaned me.
But I wanted you to have this money.
I don't want it back.
But I must repay you.
Thank you…
for the trouble you went to.
You must be sick of helping me.
You won't have to anymore.
I'm returning this to you.
What do you mean?
It's Sibmeun, isn't it?
It has nothing to do with him.
I made this decision on my own.
The other night,
Grandma's condition got worse.
Sibmeun promised her
he would take care of me.
And I think it makes sense.
We're getting married,
so Grandma won't have to worry.
Here he is.
Please excuse me.
Bye.
I wasn't going to give in that easily.
I asked your mom for another chance.
Jan.
Hey.
-Are you okay?
-Ouch.
Let's go to the hospital.
However, fate wasn't on my side.
-Cheers!
Three years after their wedding,
I married Jan.
It was the worst decision I ever made.
Are you all right?
I don't understand my mom.
Why did she make that decision?
I think there must be more to the story.
Everyone has their own reasons.
If one could choose,
no one would choose heartache.
In fact,
when your mom
got admitted to the hospital,
there was more to it.
I saw that she has been dumping the pills.
So I…
started mixing the pills with apple juice
and gave it to her.
I think her memory was getting better.
Then Jan tried to make her remember.
As she started to remember,
she must have struggled with it
and ended up this way.
I'm sorry.
If you're angry with me, you can hit me.
I don't mind.
How could I hit you?
You did it
because you want the best for me
and my mother.
Thank you
for staying by my side through all this.
I'm glad to have you.
Likewise. I'm glad…
to be here for you.
Get home safely.
Make sure to lock up
and feed Kuenchai.
I will.
Didn't I once say there's nothing good
about being human?
I'm taking back what I said.
Being someone who can hug Nut
and hold his hand
is amazing.
I'm sorry I put the medicine
in your drink.
The meds must have affected you.
But I only did it
because I want you to get better.
I want you to be happy.
I'm the one
who should apologize
for making everyone worry.
What you said is right.
The path to happiness
might start with a nightmare.
But we have to wake up eventually.
We might miss a person who's far away,
but we shouldn't overlook
the people close to us.
In the past,
I kept avoiding reality.
I was selfish.
Until yesterday.
I came to realize
that my family's happiness
is more important than anything else.
Bad memories might cause suffering,
but they make us realize
we are still alive.
And I want to keep on living.
I think
it's time I wake up from the nightmare
for the people I love.
I've already settled the bill, Mom.
Let's go home.
There's somewhere I want to go.
Can you take me there?
Don't worry about your mom.
She's strong enough to face the truth now.
It might be difficult and intimidating,
but now is the time.
If Na has to keep waiting,
when will she ever find happiness?
Hello.
It's me, Saen.
I'll pick you up at your house.
The usual time.
Okay. See you then.
I bet he's not coming.
He never keeps his word.
He might be tied up at work.
Work or something else?
You don't know, do you?
The money Saen gave you
for your grandmother's treatment
was a loan from that woman named Jan.
What did you say?
He took out a loan without asking you.
You could see it as
an act of love and protection.
But if you think about it,
how close must they be
for that woman to loan Saen so much money?
It's not too late for you
to change your mind.
There's someone who loves you
just as much as Saen.
Sib has always been there for you.
His career is stable
and has a clear path forward.
When he gets old and retires,
he'll receive government pension.
If you marry Sib, you won't regret it.
Don't worry about me.
I promise I'll take good care of myself.
Na,
you are a woman.
You will have to get married one day.
That way your life will be fulfilled.
You shouldn't be alone.
Who would help protect you then?
People
will talk about you behind your back
saying you couldn't find a good man
to be your husband.
I want to see you happy.
Love someone who loves you.
Trust me.
Thank you…
for the trouble you went to.
You paid my mortgage
and my grandmother's medical bills.
You must be sick of helping me.
You won't have to anymore.
I'm returning this to you.
I'm doing all this because I love you.
Do you hear me? I love you!
I married you
because your father pressured me,
and you were the only woman
I was close to.
If I had known
everything was just a scheme,
if I had been more assertive
with you back then,
I wouldn't have been stuck
with a woman I don't love.
Thank you.
I never thought that you would miss
an important appointment for me.
You knew?
Yes, I knew.
That's why I did this.
Jan.
Na and Sib are happy now.
You should accept
that you can't make her happy.
You put yourself in this predicament.
Sib actually knows you very well.
I guess it's a twin thing.
Since when?
How long have you and Sib been scheming?
It doesn't matter how long.
It would always lead to this anyway.
Why are you doing this?
I merely presented the opportunity.
You took it yourself.
You were prepared to take on debt
just to beat your brother.
You gave Sib the chance
of winning Na's heart.
You must have thought
that what you did would win her heart.
But you didn't realize
you can't buy love like that.
What you said is right.
Your money can't buy my love either.
I might not be a big shot
who can take out a big loan for you,
but as a soldier, I have a stable career
that will ensure a comfortable life.
I love you, Na.
You won't regret it.
Give me a chance to take care of you
for the rest of your life.
Here we go.
You're ready.
There.
Done.
Hello, boy.
Come here.
Quiet.
Did you think you could run away?
Don't.
Please.
Nut! Open up!
Open up!
Nut, open up!
How dare you raise your voice at me.
How dare you raise your voice
at your own dad.
Nut!
A little pervert like you
will never achieve anything.
It's my fault.
If I wasn't indecisive,
if I had been firm
and not easily swayed by others,
I wouldn't have made the wrong choice.
If I had thought it through,
things would have turned out better.
Be careful.
Mrs. Na.
Nut.
Are you okay?
I'm just tired.
Your mom is regaining her memory.
Things will get better soon.
What will get better?
I think your mom must have loved your dad,
or she wouldn't have chosen to marry him.
When he died,
it must have been a huge blow.
If he were still alive,
I'm sure she would be happier.
You know nothing.
If that's what upset her,
why is it Uncle Saen that she misses?
She should miss Dad.
Nut.
She chose the path
that everyone thought was right.
Maybe it was just the safest.
Mom chose Dad
as a substitute for Uncle Saen.
She didn't really love him.
I'm just a product of their mistake.
Love should make people happy.
Why, then, is everyone so sad?
Whichever path you choose,
someone would always be disappointed.
If disappointment is inevitable,
why do humans seek love?
You still don't know humans that well.
You've learned about humans
based on theory
and from your experience here.
There's still much more you need to learn
about humans and love.
Love between humans is complicated,
just like humans themselves.
Humans are even more complicated.
It's not just about love.
There are other things
you might not even think of.
Some people appear pitiful,
but they are really terrifying.
Some people might seem decent,
but they may not necessarily be
good people.
Aren't you going to help at all?
Why should I help?
You don't need help
pouring alcohol down your throat.
If you just came to lecture me, get lost.
Leave.
I want to know about the guy
you hired to follow me.
He has been following me for a while.
You know what happened that day, right?
Are you admitting you went there that day?
You wanted to get rid of him,
just like I did.
We're in the same boat here.
Do you still plan to abandon me?
Stay out of this.
Also, tell your guy to stop following me.
You wanted to get rid of him,
just like I did.
Please, Tarn. I don't want anything
to happen to you.
Are you threatening me?
I'm just trying to warn you.
Stop trying.
I won't back down.
What do you hope to gain?
You know full well
that you don't have enough influence.
It's not going to bring about any change.
Things might not change today,
but they will in the future.
Time is on our side.
We have time to win, to fight, to lose.
Winning might take time,
but that day will come.
But power is on their side.
We have to get that power on our side.
The people should have the power,
so that problems can be solved.
Am I supposed to give up
and be a coward like you?
Should I give in to power,
abandon my principles,
and behave immorally like you?
-I can't do it.
-Tarn!
What is it, Lieutenant?
I searched the house
and the surrounding area.
I didn't find any weapons.
We checked the car again,
but we didn't find
the perpetrator's blood or fingerprints.
This means
that we have no other suspects.
All the evidence we have
points to Saen as the perpetrator.
The wife
might have hired someone to use
Tarn's grandfather as a diversion.
It's my fault.
If I wasn't indecisive,
if I had been firm
and not easily swayed by others,
I wouldn't have made the wrong choice.
If I had thought it through,
things would have turned out better.
Mom chose Dad because she saw him
as a substitute for Uncle Saen.
She didn't really love him.
I'm just a product of their mistake.
Nut.
Yes?
What?
Why did you come in?
I brought you coffee.
Did you get your phone fixed?
I did.
What's on your mind?
I'm working.
Working or daydreaming?
You were in a trance.
My brain is not working.
Shall I give you a massage?
It might help.
What does a massage have to do with this?
I can't focus with you massaging me.
Let me help you.
Focus, Nut.
When you're so close,
I can't focus.
I'm sorry.
I'll go then.
If you go, I'll still be stuck.
What should I do then?
You made me lose my focus.
You must take responsibility.
No problem.
I know what to do.
-Hurry up.
-But why?
Is this taking responsibility?
They say running is good for dogs.
But I'm not a dog.
-Come on.
-Damn it.
Humans are the same.
All you do is work.
How can you have energy
if you sit inside all day?
I guarantee running a few laps
will kick your brain into gear.
I am busy.
But…
you're getting fat.
Your butt is big.
Your thighs are big.
You're getting a belly.
Come on. Don't complain.
Give me a sec.
See?
You're busy now.
I'm busy, Song.
I'm tending to Nut's heart at the moment.
Is it that serious?
If you're busy, you're busy.
Speak to you later.
Who's busy, son?
Dad.
Do I really have to run?
Two laps will be fine.
I'll do one.
How about three and a half?
Come on.
Hurry up, Nut.
-I'm already tired.
-We are only just starting.
I'm catching up.
Hurry up, Nut.
How come you're so fit?
That's obvious. Since I turned human,
I've been running regularly.
What?
What I meant to say was,
since we got to know each other.
Don't you remember we had a chase
the first time we met?
Did you bring me out to reminisce?
I'm giving you a second shot.
I wonder if you'll lose again today?
I won't lose to you today.
I'm sorry, Song. I really am busy.
It's important to look after
your loved ones' hearts.
Right now,
I think Nut is in desperate need
of someone to look after him.
Kuenchai.
What are you training for?
Next week,
we're shooting a basketball scene.
That's why I called Tofu
to practice with me, but he's busy.
Speaking of Tofu,
we barely had a chance to talk
before Nut came to pick him up.
It's a shame.
He had to go home, Dad.
Why, do you miss him?
What?
Between Tofu and me, who do you miss more?
You, of course.
What's up?
You're acting like a neglected puppy.
I don't know. You just seem
more interested in other people's lives.
What part of your life
don't I take an interest in?
There's a lot.
You don't remember the food I like.
You don't even remember my birthday.
I wasn't the one who gave birth to you.
But you always remember Neung's birthday.
Even after he passed away,
you still remember.
Thanks for offering to train with me, Dad,
but I forgot I arranged to meet a friend.
I better get going.
What's wrong with you?
When I called, you sounded upset.
Did you trick me into watching you play?
You're quick. Not bad.
I didn't ask you to come just to watch.
Will you help me with my lines?
What lines?
A proposal.
I have to play basketball
and pour my heart out at the same time.
What about this? If I score,
you agree to be my boyfriend?
I'm not playing.
Don't fool me. I've read the script.
There's no such scene.
What about this, if you can't score,
you have to be my boyfriend?
Fine. Remember, this is your challenge.
How was that?
That's that.
How come you're so good?
Damn.
Are you okay?
Song,
take this.
Thank you.
Aren't you going to ask anything?
Are you not worried about me?
Tell me if you want to.
If you don't want to, don't tell me.
I'll just sit here, okay?
It's just tiring
when you try your best to please someone,
but they don't even notice.
So now you're sulking, are you?
Look at you.
You may seem like an adult,
but you are not really one.
What? I am an adult.
I'm not a kid anymore.
I'm also very good at making money.
I know that.
I've seen you running yourself
into the ground
trying to make that someone proud of you.
There might be a reason
they haven't noticed.
If you want them to notice you,
why don't you say something?
Just tell them. It's not that hard.
What are you doing?
Come on.
Just let me recharge for five minutes.
Fine.
Anything over five minutes,
I'll charge you.
Aren't you stingy?
It's fine. I'll pay.
I don't remember
the last time I came running here.
Let's come again sometime.
When I'm not busy.
Where's Kuenchai?
Kuenchai.
Hey.
I'm sorry for letting him loose.
Come here, Kuenchai. Let's go.
Is his name Kuenchai?
Please don't be angry with him.
He just wanted to play.
Today is my daughter's birthday.
I made her a cake.
She found him adorable
and wanted to share her cake with him.
But she dropped it.
Didn't you?
Thank you.
What decoration do you want
on your cake this year?
I want a rainbow.
With these colors please, Mom.
Let me see.
Your birthday is in a few days.
Is there anything you want?
I'll surprise you with it.
You're so stupid.
If you ask me what I want,
how will it be a surprise?
I want to give you a special gift.
Birthdays are special days.
Everyone celebrates, don't they?
My birthday is just another normal day.
It has never been special.
I've never wanted anything before.
But this year…
What is it?
Forget it.
Nut.
What do you want?
Tell me.
I don't know.
Listen, Prib.
I had to eat that burnt pork you made,
and now you want me
to help you think of a gift for Nut.
You're the worst niece of all time.
Your heart is blacker
than your burnt pork.
You can talk, Uncle. Your skin is black,
and you have a black heart.
We're family but you won't help me.
You've worked with Nut for ages.
How come you know nothing about him?
You're a useless uncle
and the worst boss.
Listen. Nut and I just work together.
I'm not his father. I don't know
everything about him.
This is a waste of time.
Yes, you're wasting your time.
Wasting time is still better
than wasting my chance.
You'll surely waste your chance.
No matter how precious the gift is,
no matter how expensive it might be,
Nut will never accept your love.
A precious gift?
-Uncle Juea!
-What is it?
Thank you. You are the best uncle ever.
-Whatever. I've warned you.
-Hey.
Give me your paw.
The other one.
Well done.
Here.
Here's some water.
Thank you.
What brings you here?
I would like your help with something.
I've figured out what I'm going
to give Nut for his birthday.
Did you tell her
what Nut's teddy bear looked like?
Yes.
Was that a good idea?
What if she manages to find
an identical teddy bear,
and Nut replaces you with it?
The best she'll find is something similar.
Nothing can replace me, right?
Well, I guess
it won't hurt to be optimistic.
I know that Prib likes Nut.
She just wants him to be happy.
If her gift makes him happy,
I am happy too.
How naive.
Of course, you and Nut
are getting on well.
Even better than before, I may say.
When he is being nice to me,
I want to be even nicer to him.
But…
I haven't figured out what to give him.
When I asked him,
he wouldn't say what he wants.
Should I get him a new bolster cushion?
Tofu, you evil teddy bear!
You are very close to him.
You must know what he wants.
It shouldn't be that hard.
Nut was a cute kid.
He was.
He was such a cute child.
He was lively and he always smiled.
Lately, he hardly ever smiles though.
It must be because of me.
He seems to have a lot on his mind.
There's his work and his research.
He works really hard.
That's why he looks so serious.
Is that a rainbow?
When he was young,
he wanted a rainbow on his cake.
He asked me to make it for him.
That year, he must have been very happy.
No.
I didn't make it for him.
We never made
another birthday cake together again.
In that case,
for his birthday this year,
shall we make him a cake?
ALARM
Nut.
Are you awake, Nut? It's getting late.
All right. I know.
Happy birthday.
What are you doing with that?
Hey.
Go put it away.
Take this.
I'm leaving, Mom.
I already opened the gate for you.
Are you nearly here, Song?
Sure.
Song.
Here's everything.
Thank you.
Sure. I'm going now.
Drive safely.
Here you go, Prib.
Thank you, Nut.
LOOKING FOR A TEDDY BEAR
IDENTICAL TO THIS
ANYONE WITH INFO, PLEASE DM ME
-I'm going.
-See you.
Haven't you finished yet?
It's all right.
I have someone to delay him.
-Look.
-Yes?
I've been editing this for hours.
It's fine as it is.
You say good.
I say not good enough.
A bit more. Go on.
Fine, a bit more.
Why do you sound so irritated?
It's okay now. You can let him go home.
Wait, let me see.
Not bad. This dialogue here is good.
What?
That dialogue was in the first draft.
That's what I'm saying. The dialogue
is exactly where it should be.
All right. You may leave now.
Good job.
-I'm going then.
-Hold on.
What is it now, Juea?
You remembered?
Nut,
how long have we worked together?
How could I not remember?
Thank you.
You're like a father to me.
I'm more handsome than him.
I'm kidding. Don't crush my hopes.
I would like to be handsome too.
Thank you.
Even though you didn't raise me
as a parent,
you've guided my career in this industry.
Well said.
If you didn't have talent,
I wouldn't be able to help you.
Whatever problems you faced last year,
let them go.
I'm sure this year will be your year.
Because your series
is going to be a big hit.
You would like that, right?
It's a win-win situation.
Go on. Go home.
-Thank you.
-Don't mention it.
Drive safely.
You?
Gen.
Yes, it's me.
Who else would it be?
Happy birthday.
I wish you all the happiness in the world.
You buy yourself a cake every year,
so I bought you one.
Although this year,
you might not really want any cake.
All right. Thank you.
I'm leaving.
Got you, Nut.
Hey, you.
Is that all you got for him?
What should I give him?
A car? A house?
Nut doesn't want anything.
Every year,
I wish him a happy birthday
and offer my support.
That's adorable.
I would like someone
to offer me support
like that.
Wait.
Find a good friend like me then.
I already have plenty of friends.
But now, I want you.
This is for the cake.
Thanks for buying it for me.
Right, I…
better get going.
You can buy a cake like that
from loads of places around here.
You can just tell me
if you want to see me.
Stay by my side…
and don't go anywhere.
Your mom said,
love isn't about doing
something for someone.
It's about putting your heart into it.
How are you involved with what happened
to Nut and his mother?
You're nosy
because you're jealous
of Nut's mother, right?
Why would I be jealous?
Well, everybody loves her.
This includes Mr. Saen too.
Have you heard of the phrase
"Pity is the foundation of love"?
No. I've only heard of sympathy.
Subtitle translation by:
Supanida Piyayotai