I think you like Nut, Tofu.
You didn't use your experience
as material, right?
If for you, normal means
only thinking the way you do,
then half the world would be abnormal.
If I remember who I am,
I have to leave.
I want to record my time with you,
so it can be my memory.
That plot of land and your house
should have gone to me,
not a brat like you who has never
contributed to the family business.
If you want it,
wait until I'm dead.
When will you understand
that going into someone's room
without permission
is an invasion of privacy?
If you're happy,
those romantic scenes
you're struggling with
will come to you naturally.
Mister.
Song.
What's that smell?
Song!
Song.
Song, wake up.
Song, get up.
Get up.
What happened?
I can't…
Don't fall asleep.
You can't die on me.
Come on.
One, two…
Let's go.
You can't die on me, Song.
Come on.
Song.
Are you okay? Come on.
I need a stretcher.
-This person is hurt.
-This way.
Bring the stretcher.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
Gen.
What's happening?
Mom.
The guy who went inside is my friend.
Go park your car. It's blocking the way.
I'll take care of this end.
Dad.
Why are you here?
I'm here to pick your mom up.
Who's that?
Well…
He's an actor in Nut's series.
I found him
-in bad shape
-I see.
so I brought him here.
Were you on the set?
No.
Wait.
Where did you find him?
At his house.
I went
to talk to him.
-Oh, my…
-Our son went to a man's house.
-I know.
Mom.
It was necessary.
Why are you investigating me?
You seem to care about him,
but he's not your friend.
-That's why I asked.
-Yes.
I'm worried the series
will be affected.
If you're short of an actor,
it's a big deal, Dad.
Nut is fixing the drafts all by himself.
He's got enough on his plate.
I don't want to make it worse.
I see.
You worry about Nut.
Who else am I supposed to worry about?
-My goodness.
-Well…
Him, maybe.
He's fine. He has diarrhea, that's all.
We call it non-stop shitting.
He's a shitting dog.
So it's just
-diarrhea?
-Yes.
-It's diarrhea.
-He's a friend?
Gosh.
-Yes.
-I see.
A friend and a brother.
Is that so?
Are you all right?
Tell us.
I'm fine, Dad. I'm usually like this.
I see.
He's sweating.
Bring it on.
Catch me.
No.
I love you, mister.
Fuck.
I died.
I know you heard me.
What?
I was
playing a game.
You know what?
I'll call a nurse for you.
I love you, mister.
-I love you, mister.
-Stop.
A nurse
might hear you.
I love you, mister.
-I love you, mister.
-Stop.
I said, be quiet.
They might hear you.
Okay?
But I really love you.
Give me your hand.
My hand?
I don't want your phone.
I need support from you.
-Please.
-Just be quiet.
Kuenchai.
You came to play inside this room again.
Go away. Get out.
Gosh.
This dog.
All right.
-What?
-Do you love him?
-Do you?
-No.
-You love him, don't you?
No!
Sib.
Mrs. Na.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I accidentally dropped those.
Do you like history books?
Yes.
I used to teach social science.
That's why I have history books.
Is history fun?
Of course.
You study important events from the past
to understand the present
and use them to guide the future,
so history doesn't repeat itself.
In that case,
if we realize
that we are unhappy
because of our bitter past,
can we create new history?
So we might end up happy in the future.
She was suffering.
That's why she created a new world.
And Nut is suffering
because he locked the old world up.
He can't make use
of those old memories.
Well, the best way
to get over your old love
is to find a new one, right?
If you're happy,
those romantic scenes
you're struggling with
will come to you naturally.
I gave you a ladder, but why don't you
have the courage to climb it?
Go back
and think about
what your problem is and fix it.
I don't want to see a wall
in front of you your whole life.
Humans are so complicated.
Humans are like that, Teddy.
You might become
more complicated yourself.
I feel so sorry for Nut.
I'm going to help him.
Prib said
Nut can't write romantic scenes
because he has a bitter past.
I might not be able to change his past,
but I will help him get over it.
What are you doing in my room?
We need to talk.
Stop.
Let me get dressed.
I talked to your mom about history.
Why don't you create new history
if your past was bad?
What are you saying?
Let's create new history together, Nut.
I want to make you happy.
With good memories,
you will have stories to tell.
Look ahead,
look around you,
and open up your heart.
Wait.
Is your name Tofu?
I'll let you stay here.
Nut.
Why are you being quiet?
All right then.
Let's try it.
But since it's your idea,
you must take responsibility.
Let's go on a date.
We are here.
CAN TOSS
Tofu.
Is this where you wanted to take me?
Yes.
Do you like it?
I do.
Let's go.
RING TOSS
Take that.
Nut.
Look.
It's switched off.
Tell me next time.
Drink some juice, Nut.
Nut.
Tofu.
This isn't juice. It's herbal liquor.
-It's juice.
-Oh, my god.
It's fermented juice.
Come take a look.
Welcome.
-I'm back.
-Welcome back.
-She sells many types of juice.
-That's right.
I see Trembling Girl,
-Elephant Power…
-Trumpet.
And Tiger Power.
-I have everything.
-Tofu.
Welcome.
-Is this it?
-Yes.
-This is it.
-I've tried them all.
This is the best one.
Take your pick.
-Can I take this home?
-No.
-Tofu, stop. Put it down.
-Sure.
-I'll give you a special price.
-That's all right.
Put it down.
We also have a set.
A set?
Do you want some?
It's pickled fruit.
Please have a taste.
-It's good for your circulation.
-Tofu.
-Try it.
-How much have you had?
-Just ten shots.
-What?
Nut, can you bike in a straight line?
You are so drunk.
-I'm not drunk.
-Careful.
Not drunk, my ass.
I've been going in circles.
I don't want to go home yet.
You don't want to go home,
but I do.
Really?
Tofu.
-I can walk home.
-Oh, my god.
You're a weird drunk.
I'm not drunk.
I can walk ten more laps.
One.
Two.
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Tofu.
Are you okay?
Get on. We're going home.
You want to go home?
You asked me out.
Why did we have to come here?
How is it romantic?
I don't know.
I wanted to come.
Did you not want to come?
Do I look like I wanted to come?
Where should we go for our date?
The market is good enough for you.
Give me somewhere more meaningful.
Does anyone know
where Nut wants to go?
Yes, I know a place.
Nut wrote how he wanted to go there
and drew a picture of it long ago.
Where is it?
Follow me, Nut.
Where are you going?
Answer me first, Tofu.
Tofu.
What made you think I wanted to come?
Does it matter?
I just want you to be happy,
smile
and laugh like you did today.
You need to remember
this moment to write the script.
I like seeing you happy.
Tofu.
Let's find a place to hide.
Why?
I've never played in the rain.
Woo-hoo.
You've gone crazy.
Let's go or you'll get sick.
The rain is so cooling, Nut.
It's as cooling as a shower.
You will be dry later
when the rain stops.
Don't be scared.
Come.
Are you happy, Nut?
Woo-hoo!
I made coffee for you.
You haven't showered.
I'll help you.
Do you know
how things will end
if you're too good to me?
What did you say?
I said,
do you know how things will end
if you're too good?
I'm kidding.
Go away. I need to work.
Go.
Go take a shower.
What's wrong with me?
Is it because of Nut?
My heart is racing
and my face
feels hot.
It's hotter than usual.
Why is my body so hot?
My whole body feels hot.
But I'm happy.
Is this
what they call…
This is for you.
Tofu.
You are so gross.
Go take a shower.
Tofu.
Oh, my god.
You're burning up.
It ends with me caring for you.
Look.
-You're mine.
-Wow.
-How was that?
-You're good, Nut.
Watch me.
Oh, no.
Nut.
You go first.
BALLOON POP
Watch me.
Yes.
-Oh, my god. Watch me.
-Oh, no. Nut.
Oh, what?
-Oh, god.
Come on.
I have to win.
So close, Tofu.
Go.
Tofu.
Let's go.
What the hell?
It's hard.
Tofu, throw it.
What's wrong?
If I throw this ring,
I won't have one for you.
How lame.
Nut.
If you want me to propose,
buy me more rings.
Nut.
Thank you.
Yours is bigger.
Do you like this place?
That's great. I'm happy
to take you to a better place.
You make it sound like I'm dead.
How do you know my likes and dislikes?
I always pay attention to you.
Let's take a selfie.
I want to capture our day together
to remember it by.
Nut, look.
You can see the candy.
No.
That trick is getting old.
Tofu.
Where are you going?
I'm going behind the hut.
Thank you.
You're frying pork in the office?
I can do anything for love.
I worked on the recipe all night.
Juea approved it.
I hope he doesn't get cancer.
The pork is way too burnt
to eat.
Nut eats it like this.
Do you think he eats it
because it's burned?
It's about the person who makes it.
If he were to fall for you,
this pork wouldn't be the reason.
He would love you for you.
Do you understand?
Who made it for him?
Only his mom and Tofu live with him.
Do you think that person…
What?
Don't be sad. I'm here.
I knew you would come,
so I waited for you.
Thank you for watching me all night
and taking me home.
I'm taking responsibility
for giving you diarrhea.
Did you tell your dad?
He's busy.
He'll just worry.
If he worries,
take good care of yourself.
My parent isn't a doctor like yours.
I don't take good care of myself.
I'm looking for someone
to take care of me.
I'm here, am I not?
What is it, mister?
I…
washed them for you.
Wait.
Are you opening up to me?
Opening up?
What are you talking about?
I'm just afraid
the series will go under
if you die.
That's all.
I won't die easily
because
-I will stay alive to hug you.
-Hey.
Song, what are you doing?
Song.
-I love you, mister.
-Song.
What's your problem?
-Oh my.
-Let me go.
-My god.
-What are you doing?
Dad. Mom.
Why are you here?
We came to visit him.
The doctor approved his discharge.
He must have gotten a great caretaker.
Mom.
Be careful of what you eat next time.
Yes.
-Thank you guys so much
-You're welcome.
-for taking care of me last night.
-Sure.
You look better in real life.
I was the one who accepted
your friend request.
He was playing hard to get.
Dad!
You're being way too loud.
People will think I've died.
What?
If you don't like yelling.
you should leave.
I'm going to drop him off
and go to work.
Go already.
Let's go.
Gosh, judging from what
you were doing on the bed,
he's definitely more than a friend.
Mom.
This kid gets on my nerves.
Be glad I'm your friend.
Not every kid is like that.
There are many good kids out there.
Come on.
-What?
-Let's go.
Look at him.
Who did he get his stubbornness from?
You, I guess.
-Really? Not from you?
-No.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to wake you.
The thing is
you had a fever last night,
so I wiped your body down.
You said you were cold
so I…
Thank you.
It got much warmer
with you next to me.
Having fever for the first time sucks.
But I got a lot better…
when you hugged me.
Human bodies work in a strange way.
You can go back to sleep.
I'll go check on your mom.
Mrs. Na.
Here's your apple juice.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I woke up late because I was sick.
I almost forgot your apple juice.
That's it?
I was worried.
It's my job to take care of her.
I need to do my best.
Are you going to work today?
I didn't have time to prepare anything.
Can you wait?
I'll help you get it ready in no time.
What brings you
all the way here?
I hear you talked to a doctor in Bangkok.
Are you sending Tarn there?
I've got connections.
I'm aware that the chance
of Tarn waking up is slim to none.
But I want to do my best.
He doesn't deserve any of this.
It's too cruel.
He's unfortunate.
I still stand by what I said.
I agree with you
and I'm willing to cover
all of the expenses
if it will get us out of trouble.
Trouble?
We don't know who attacked your nephew
but people think it's TRD.
Investors are putting
their investments on hold
because it's too risky.
It's starting to upset the executives.
If this project is terminated,
you, the project manager,
might be in trouble.
I didn't mean to cause any trouble.
But you chose to get involved.
Your wife too.
Or they wouldn't have
asked you to give a testimony.
You know?
That's all I know.
I'm not going to meddle
in your family's business.
I hope you can put an end
to this problem soon
without affecting our work.
If you can't,
I'll have to step in.
I thought you went back.
Didn't you want me
to do my job as his aunt?
Here I am.
It looks like
you're worried about him more than I am.
You must be extremely afraid of him dying.
That's why you are here all day.
Why?
Do you feel guilty?
Guilt about what?
Don't get upset.
I meant
you feel guilty…
for neglecting your nephew.
Someone almost beat him to death.
That's all.
Or are there other reasons
that make you feel guilty?
I have only one regret in my life.
It's marrying you.
Saen.
Don't worry about him.
As his uncle-in-law,
I won't let his attackers walk.
A wound from a blunt object,
3cm wide and 7cm long,
was found at the back of his neck.
His X-ray shows
a fracture in the skull
and a cerebral hemorrhage.
He needs more than 21 days to recover.
He was hit from the back.
No other wounds were found.
This means there's no sign of struggle.
Is it possible
that the attackers
lured him out of the car
and hit him with an object?
Sir.
Since he's smart enough to lead a protest,
he must be quite a thorough person.
Maybe someone lured him outside,
so he took the car.
Once he arrived,
he carelessly got out of the car.
According to Saen,
he has evidence proving
it was an accident.
A security camera
in Tatarn's neighborhood
recorded his car driving past at 7:06 p.m.
One minute later, Saen's car drove past
in the same direction.
Fifteen minutes later,
Tatarn's car was spotted
near Sarapee Temple
with Saen's car not far behind.
Then, his car hit a motorcycle
that was riding
on the wrong side of the road.
Looking at the time,
there's no way Saen got there
in time to attack Tatarn.
Could Sajjaree
be behind it?
Is that you, Tarn?
Can we meet?
I need to talk to you.
Sajjaree
may have lured her nephew out
to the meeting spot.
Then she flew back to Bangkok right away
to avoid suspicion.
Yes.
As for Tatarn's car,
a security camera in Chiang Mai
caught it on the road
along the railway track.
I've asked the officers
both in Lamphun and Lampang
to check the route Tatarn took
before the attack.
No one has found anything.
Why did he take the longer route
to get to Lampang?
It's like he avoided the cameras.
I agree.
Something isn't right.
Set it up around the house.
The hard disk
of the security cameras is missing.
Search the house.
Yes, sir.
-All done.
-Thank you.
Excuse me.
I thought you went back.
Why do you care?
Who did you meet with?
I saw you talking to a man.
Who?
There are lots of men.
Which one do you mean?
Are you jealous?
Don't worry.
Even though you don't care about me,
I would never cheat, unlike you.
If you don't want me to cheat,
then agree to the divorce,
so I can date her
without going behind your back.
-What? You drugged her?
I had to.
Or she would have thrown
her medicine away again.
Why didn't you tell Nut the truth?
He'll get mad
if he finds out about it later.
He might even kick you out, who knows.
I don't want Nut to fight with his mom.
He's already stressed with work.
What Tofu is doing might be good
for both Nut and his mom.
That's true.
Saying only what is necessary
is better than making things worse.
You are doing the right thing.
I won't hide it for long.
Once his mom gets better,
I'll tell everyone the truth.
Kuenchai.
Have you seen my book?
Did you take it again?
"The Little Prince."
They say,
older people perceive
The Little Prince differently
than children.
You should read it again.
You might understand
and perceive it differently this time.
Dad.
-No.
-Be careful!
Saen.
Na.
It's really you, Saen.
Mrs. Na.
Mrs. Na!
No.
Let's move.
What's going on?
-What?
-Are you hurt anywhere?
How careless of you.
Do you have a death wish?
Jan.
It's…
-Well…
-Saen.
Do you see other men
as your husband again?
-When will you stop being crazy?
-Jan.
Saen is my husband.
-Can you hear me? Mine.
-Jan.
-He's mine.
-Stop or I'll call the police.
-Get off her.
-Stay out.
Make sure she takes her medicine.
She shouldn't talk to anyone's man.
Weren't you the one
who left Saen for Sib?
What a lunatic.
Gosh.
-Move.
-My goodness.
What the…
My goodness.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
-Gosh.
-What?
I feel sorry for Na.
And what is Jan's problem?
She has been with Saen for 20 years.
But she still can't let it go.
She knows Na is sick.
What does she want from Na?
Listen to me.
You shouldn't judge people.
All right?
People have
different limitations.
We are not her.
We don't know
what she has been through.
Do you understand?
People who seem weak
might have a really strong heart.
And people who seem strong
might have wept more tears
than we could imagine.
Keep an eye on him
and keep me updated.
Weren't you the one who left Saen for Sib?
Na.
Yes, Grandma.
I…
I don't know how much time I have left.
I'm worried about you.
You are a woman.
You need
a husband
to take care of you.
Trust me.
You won't have to anymore.
I'm returning this to you.
See? Do you see what Sib does for you?
He's a man who's nice and consistent.
What are you waiting for?
A good man doesn't come by easily, Na.
Mrs. Na.
It's apple juice.
Is it a headache?
I'm just a bit confused.
Is it about what Jan said?
That and…
what I saw.
The guy who looks like Mr. Saen?
It's okay.
When you remember it,
you can talk to me.
You should rest.
There's still a lot
I don't know
about what happened
between Mrs. Na, Mr. Saen,
Mr. Sibmeun, and Jan.
It's still bothering her.
It's the reason
she's refusing to get treated.
I hope
what I'm doing
will help her
get over it one day.
Mrs. Na and Nut
will finally be happy.
Come in.
Nut, take a seat.
Nut, you've managed
to climb over the wall.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much, Juea.
I don't regret
giving you the ladder.
Or is it possible
that you are in love?
Song said I had to have a Facebook first
before I can add you as my boyfriend.
HE LOOKS CONFUSED AND SO ADORABLE
THAT I HAVE TO TAKE A PICTURE
I want to record my time with you,
so it can be my memory.
You even have a photo of a dog.
I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT IT
BUT I WANT TO GIVE IT TO YOU ANYWAY
PLEASE ACCEPT MY BOYFRIEND REQUEST,
I MEAN, FRIEND REQUEST
You try too hard.
I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT IT
BUT I WANT TO GIVE IT TO YOU ANYWAY
PLEASE ACCEPT MY BOYFRIEND REQUEST,
I MEAN, FRIEND REQUEST
PEERANUT HAS ACCEPTED
YOUR FRIEND REQUEST
Nut accepted my boyfriend…
I mean, friend request.
Kuenchai, Nut has accepted
my friend request.
HE LOOKS CONFUSED AND SO ADORABLE
THAT I HAVE TO TAKE A PICTURE
Holy shit.
Has Prib seen this?
Excuse me, where's Prib?
I don't know, but I saw her leave.
PRIB, WHERE ARE YOU? HAVE YOU SEEN IT?
Are you dead?
No.
Almost though.
You rubbing it in will do the job.
I saw it when Nut posted it.
Nut accepted Tofu's friend request,
but not mine.
You should make peace with it.
Really?
Stop it. Do you still
consider me as a friend?
Seriously.
I'm being honest with you
because you're a friend.
Stop running from the truth.
I'm not running.
Really? Where are you then?
Did you go drinking?
No, I didn't.
I'm getting my stuff together.
Getting your stuff together? Where?
Somewhere far away.
But don't worry.
I'll be back in two days.
I'm going to take back what's mine.
Two days? Are you…
Are you becoming a nun or a witch?
MY BELOVED BROTHER
I came as promised.
Do you remember?
We promised each other
that we would meet up this day every year.
We can't be lovers.
But you can be my sister.
Fine.
I'll be your sister.
But you have to promise
that you won't forget me.
You are
one of a kind.
I won't forget you.
Is that a compliment?
Yes.
How about this?
You must make it up to me
by celebrating the day we met
and our bond.
Promise me
that we will meet every year
and you will buy me a meal.
I promise.
I will buy you a meal every year.
Okay?
Let's take a picture
as proof of our promise.
Don't keep me waiting for too long.
Wake up and buy me a meal already.
I think I'm about to be heartbroken again.
Please wake up. I need your support.
I came to visit Tarn.
It has been a month.
Are there any signs of recovery?
His condition has been stable.
Why don't you take Tarn to Bangkok?
My friend's mother is a doctor.
I can talk to her.
I already talked with a doctor.
He said the same thing.
Someone said,
with enough moral support
from their loved ones,
comatose patients
might get better.
But Tarn has no one.
You are his only visitor.
We can't do anything,
except wait for a miracle.
Why hasn't Nut uploaded other photos
besides the one from the fair?
Come here.
Nut said
Facebook is a diary full of memories.
How come his diary is empty?
That's because some memories are kept
deep inside the heart.
There's no need to archive them.
You know?
You can never erase them from your heart.
Do you understand?
Thank you.
We went to the market.
We bought snacks for you and Na.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
-Yes.
-Which are harder to erase,
good memories
or bad memories?
Well…
-Nhong, tell him what you think.
-Yes.
-I think
-Tell him.
-Go ahead.
-bad memories stay in your heart
-Yes.
-longer than good memories.
Yes, that's right.
Do you understand?
Do you really like him?
What are you talking about?
I told you to find someone new,
so you went out with Tofu.
Are you a couple?
What's with you?
Listen.
We've only been on one date.
Do I look that easy to you?
Is that so?
I can tell from Mars that you are happy.
Look.
You've never been like this before.
If you like him,
go for it.
You're a grown-up now.
You don't need to listen
to anyone anymore.
But he's a stranger.
He will leave one day.
That day isn't today.
Why worry about it now?
If you want to be happy
and Tofu makes you happy,
why wait?
Someone might take him first.
Which one?
I don't know.
What?
Nut was looking
at this photo at the shoot.
I thought maybe
he was thinking of an old friend.
Why do you want to know about this person?
Well…
I want to help Nut with his work.
I hear Nut is inspired by his own past.
If he meets an old friend
he misses,
he might have fun stories to tell.
You care a lot
about Nut.
He's my special someone.
Without him,
I wouldn't be here.
If I were Nut,
my ears would turn red.
Why?
You're confessing your love.
Love?
Yes.
Nut is always your priority.
Nut was even the first person
you added on Facebook.
I'm the second, right?
Right?
Oh, my god.
You are blushing.
Your cheeks are red.
Look.
Both cheeks are red.
Does Nut make you shy?
Tell me the truth.
You're back.
I came back a while ago.
Are you deaf and blind?
Why are you here?
I came to invite Tofu over for dinner.
My dad asked me to bring food.
After that,
Tofu can sleep over at my place.
I bought a new game.
Let's play it together.
Sure, I want to play it.
Really?
I was going to invite you
to watch a short film
produced by my senior.
Do you prefer games?
You have to choose
who you want to go with.
You chose a short film over a game.
I chose you over Song.
Nut.
Joi, hello.
Hello, how's it going? Long time no see.
I'm good.
-I would never miss
-Welcome.
your event.
Thank you so much.
I ran into Juea.
He said you were working on a series.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
-I'm looking forward to it.
-Thank you.
Let's watch the film.
Why are you smiling?
I'm glad to see you happy.
You must love your job.
You've been smiling nonstop.
My job is what
I'm most proud of
in my life.
When I work,
it feels like I can be myself.
I can think and do anything
I want to do.
Your hard work
will make the new series very successful.
You are behind
the success too.
You were right.
I wanted to do it.
I want to tell the world
about many things in my life.
I don't know why I was afraid.
Thanks to you,
I got through a hard scene.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Nut.
You're here.
Hurry.
Bow. Joy.
Tofu, scoot over.
What?
Scoot over quickly.
-Hurry up.
-Okay.
Gosh.
-Juea.
-Yes.
-You came too?
-Joi, my junior, directed this film.
He's a great director.
You know?
All right.
Just wait.
I was there during the first edit.
It was amazing.
He put a love scene at the start.
It's starting.
What's happening?
What the hell?
Joi, what happened?
Why did you cut out the love scene?
It was great.
You ruined the whole film.
You know?
Gosh.
-Nut.
-Tofu.
I…
I'm going to the toilet.
Okay.
Wait here. Don't go anywhere.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I'll be right back.
Why does my heart keep racing today?
During the film,
I couldn't focus
because I was looking at Nut.
What's happening to me?
You're confessing your love.
Is it possible
that I really love Nut?
If you want to be happy
and Tofu makes you happy,
why wait?
Excuse me.
Me?
Yes.
I think you're cute.
Can we take a selfie?
Can I have your contact info?
I'll send you the photo.
Tofu!
We're going home.
Nut.
How did it go?
-How was the film?
-It was good, Mom.
Nut.
Nut, why are you mad at me?
You said you would wait by the toilet.
Where did you go?
Well, while I was waiting for you,
he asked to take a selfie.
That's all.
You went with him just like that?
You should have told me.
I thought you got lost.
There's no need to be upset.
I wasn't just worried about you.
I was jealous.
Forget what I said.
I'm your boss.
I'm talking crazy.
But that was before.
Things are different now.
I don't know what these feelings are.
But I want you to be more than my boss.
I want to be by your side…
hold your hand…
and hug you.
That's all?
I'm sorry.
You're such a kid.
Why are you crying?
Your lips…
are sweet and soft like jelly.
I'm afraid…
What did you say?
I said,
your lips
are sweet and soft like jelly.
Why do you sound like…
Who the hell are you?
Why are you doing this?
What do you want from me?
What did I do?
What you said just now…
Why did you say that after I kissed you?
It's how I felt.
I don't believe you.
Who sent you here?
Tell me.
Tell me now.
This is Nut. His first name is Peeranut.
He's 27 years old.
His mom is Matana. His dog is Kuenchai.
Tofu!
That's plenty of information.
You say you don't know him.
I'm Tofu, your teddy bear.
I never thought you would be such a liar.
Excuse me.
You seem lonely,
like you have no friends to talk to.
Right. Nut told me you live alone.
Your husband doesn't visit.
Is the room okay?
Yes.
I was Nut's teddy bear.
Why did I become your look-alike?
What are you doing, Dad?
Subtitle translation by:
Pet-chompoo Sa-ngarmangkang