The Jaturungkabart...
were sworn to protect
the mighty royal elephants.
Why, Dad?
Elephants are so big, who could hurt them?
The king sits on top of them.
So they must beware of things from below.
Beware of what, Dad?
If they lost their swords,
they would use their bodies as weapons.
Throw, Crush, Grab and Break.
What do they need to be careful of?
I cannot tell you yet.
But I'm going to be a Jaturungkabart,
I have to know.
Not yet, Kham. One day you will know.
-Hello.
Bye.
Hello.
Splash him, son, splash him.
Come on, splash him.
Splash him all over, son.
Splash him, son, splash him.
Por Yai, you're so naughty!
Dad, look at him.
How was it?
Was Por Yai up to his old tricks again?
Why did you do that to him?
Splash him.
Come on.
Dad, I'm here.
Dad, Dad, Dad. Where's Por Yai going?
Let him go, son.
Pull! Pull it tight. Lasso it.
Come on, pull. Pull it.
Holy crap!
If I ever had the chance
to present Por Yai to the King,
it would be biggest honor of my life.
At the very least it would mean that
I upheld the name of the Jaturungkabart.
Korn,
I have something to show you.
Is it nice?
I reckon this Songkran Water Festival
is going to be fun.
Mr. Suthep is taking care of everything.
He's throwing a huge party.
Well, his son's now a member
of government.
Hopefully,
he can give us back some of our profits.
Koi, I heard they are going to check
the elephants for royal status.
Aren't you going to take your elephants,
to see if they're in with a chance?
Say goodbye to Por Yai, Kham.
After Por Yai has been checked,
we might not have the chance
to see him again.
This could be a great opportunity for you.
There's no reason to worry.
ANNUAL SONGKRAN WATER FESTIVAL
Mr. Koi, this way, please. Hello.
Welcome.
Dad. They're here.
Hello, Mr. Koi.
-Please, come inside.
-Yes, sir.
Everything's ready. Come in.
-Go on, Korn.
-You wait outside for a while.
Your father should go in alone.
It's gonna be okay.
This is Supoj, a friend of mine.
Hello, sir.
He takes care of this place.
He will take care of everything for you.
Young man,
would you like a bell for your elephant?
Do you want a bell?
Would you like a bell for your elephant?
-Do you want one?
-It's for good luck.
Do you want one for your elephant?
-How much is this one?
-That one is 40 Baht.
It's not expensive.
Buy a bell for your elephant
and get good luck.
Thank you, sir.
Let me take a look.
That's lovely.
Let's go.
Alright, Jungo. Jungo threw a left punch!
Hit Precisely. Be alert, be alert.
Be careful,
the referee has been knocked down.
It's coming.
Thank you.
Come on.
Bring it here.
Wait! Are you taking him away today?
Yes, today, Uncle.
You can go back home and wait there.
I will let you know what happens later.
Come on. Quickly.
Come on, move it.
Come on. Go.
You can't take him. Not yet.
I won't let you.
-What are you doing?
-You can't.
-You can't. You can't take him.
-Let go.
Force it to go.
-I said you can't take him.
-You old fart. I told you.
Move it. Quickly.
Look! Elephants.
Didn't you see the truck?
Dad.
Dad. What happened, Dad?
-Dad.
-Kham.
Check on Por Yai.
Move!
Go!
Move it. I said move!
Baby, we belong together
Enjoying the forest with a joyful heart
The waterfall pours down
As if heaven was before our eyes
Birds coo like my loving words for you
Hey!
Who the hell are you?
Do you want my foot in your mouth?
Go on. Get him.
What are you waiting for? Go get him!
Boss, my teeth! My teeth!
Boss! Wait for me! Boss!
Where are Por Yai and Korn?
-Where are they?
-I don't know. I don't know.
You don't know? You don't know?
Johnny took them.
They are in Sydney.
Where is he?
Dad! Shoot! Shoot him!
Enough.
My arm!
-Hey, you.
-Come on. Quickly.
Move it.
WITH LIFE THE SKY HAS NO LIMIT
BOAT NOODLES
Hey!
And this is the main Asian market
in downtown Sydney.
Most of the people here are Asian,
you know?
Chinese, Thai, Vietnam...
and Laos.
So officers here
need to understand Asian's way,
like me, for instance.
This is how I do my job.
It's important
to stay mates with the people.
-What beautiful mangoes.
-Hello. How are you?
They look lovely.
-How much is it?
-Do you want some? It's okay.
-Take some. Take them. It's no problem.
-That's enough.
-How much?
-Forget it.
-Are you sure?
-Just take them.
-Well, okay then. Can I take two more?
-Take them. Go on.
-Thank you very much.
-Not at all.
This just the way we do things here.
Being Asian in foreign place,
need to stick together, like a family.
Sure thing, love.
I'll be there in two shakes. Why?
Do you miss me?
Woah, woah, woah, woah, woah.
Take it easy, baby.
I give you a kiss first, okay?
I love you, bye.
Hey! Just in time.
This is my new partner Rick.
He's just a young energetic kind of bloke.
A little less hard working than I am.
Hey, lighten up, mate.
There's no work right now.
Using public services
is part of our job as police officer.
You know? To serve and protect.
You look like you're constipated.
Why did you call the police?
-What am I supposed to do?
-Calm down...
-Hey, take it easy! Easy!
-Call the police.
Don't come in.
-Hey, Take it easy.
-I'll blow their guts out!
-Call the police!
-Calm down.
Rick, Rick, Rick. No, no, no.
Leave him to me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Take it easy.
Let's talk, okay?
Hey, Tui. You stupid prick.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
How did you know, Sarge?
You idiot. With a face like that,
who wouldn't be able to spot you?
Put the damn gun down.
-Put it down!
-Stay away.
-If you come any closer, I'll shoot.
-Shoot me if you want.
But don't forget about your mother.
When she gets here, you're in deep shit.
Don't lie to me.
-My mom isn't here.
-She is. Look behind you!
-You silly twit!
-No, no, no, no.
-Stop! Stop! Hey! Hey!
-Show me your face.
Hey! Stop! Stop! Please.
Come on. Imbecile.
It's been just another day.
Anyway, enough fun for now, okay? bye.
Go on, run.
Don't be such a wimp. You idiot.
It's no use
arresting a young junkie, mate.
Put a sock in it!
Don't you know?
Cut some slack!
Stunned, you're stunned.
Go! Go! Go! Let's go.
Shit! When did that happen?
Why didn't anyone tell me?
Why aren't you working?
When are you gonna pay
your boyfriend's debt?
Wittaya? Remember him?
Or you wanna die like him?
I know. I can pay.
You know you can pay?
How the hell are you gonna pay?
Thai students are only allowed
two jobs here.
One, you can be a waitress
or you can be a call girl.
What can you do?
You've got two weeks. That's it!
If the NGOs truly understood
the elephant situation here,
then they wouldn't be so against us.
From all the exits to the meeting room,
guards have been placed
at every ten meters.
Uncle, I have arranged everything for you.
I've hired Sydney's top chef
to make Abalone soup.
I made it for all of you.
I hope everyone will enjoy it.
Especially you, Uncle.
You should have some more of it.
This is good for your health.
It will keep you strong.
With good health,
you'll be able to look after
the family business forever.
Are you sure this is Abalone?
It's bland.
There's no aroma and no sweetness.
It tastes like earthworms.
You know earthworms, right?
Slithering insects...
which have two genders
without being either.
So what about it, Rose?
If you can't even provide
proper food for me,
how do you expect to protect me?
For security,
it's better to let Cheng handle it.
I think this is better.
When your father was alive,
Cheng was in charge.
What you do shows no respect
to our clients.
We are negotiating
with representatives of the government.
If we unite with them,
our business will grow rapidly.
Concentrate on the restaurant I gave you.
That's enough
responsibility for you, Rose.
That stupid old man
made me lose face in front of everyone.
You don't need to be angry; or impatient.
You already have this, don't you?
I think this new fate of mine
will finally rid me of that old man.
A tricycle is faster than this.
Stop here!
Is that the best you can do?
God, you drive like a pensioner.
Hey! Jimmy.
Calm down. Calm down.
Let's talk. Okay?
Hey, hey. Stop!
What the hell are you doing?
He was a hostage!
I didn't do anything wrong.
I will handle this.
Jimmy was no ordinary thief.
I know him well.
And this guy was not with him.
I don't, I just have a hunch.
What are you doing here?
Are you Thai?
I'm speaking Thai.
Do you think I'm Burmese?
Did you come to Sydney to break the law?
No, sir. I've come here
to find Por Yai and my little brother.
-Are you looking for your relatives?
-Yes.
-What do they look like?
-Like elephants.
Elephants?
Who's like an elephant in Thaitown?
Come on.
Let's talk about this back at my office.
Mark.
-Hello.
-How's it going, Goong?
-Are your clients keeping you busy?
-Not really.
It's your fault.
You never visit my restaurant.
I'm really busy now.
-There's a new promotion on.
-Yeah?
Special price at lunchtime.
-I will go if I have time.
-Okay.
It's a Thai Restaurant.
Tom-Yum-Goong is Thai food.
So, why did they hire
a Vietnamese guy like Johnny,
to be the general manager?
Johnny, Johnny.
-Okay. See you later.
-See you.
-Work hard.
-You too.
Follow them quickly.
Hurry up!
-Don't start any trouble.
-Follow that car! Quickly!
Quiet down! Quiet down!
Those are the people
that took Por Yai and Korn.
Don't say that. You can't accuse someone
without any evidence.
I have a photo. But it's in the taxi.
Don't waste my time.
We'll talk at the station.
Hey!
Let him go.
Johnny, where are my elephants?
Where are my elephants?
Johnny! Give me back my elephants.
We are both Thais. So, I'll warn you.
Don't get involved with them.
Where is Jimmy's body?
And the evidence?
I know.
You're an ugly son of a bitch.
Okay. Thanks.
MAMA CUP TOM YUM GOONG FLAVOR
Kings sit upon the elephants.
Vital areas are underneath.
Enemies aim for those areas.
Soldiers protect the four most vital areas
of the elephants.
What are the vital areas, Dad?
One day you will know, Kham.
Come on out!
What are you doing?
Tui.
What the hell are you doing?
He forced me to do it, Sarge. I...
Rick.
-Hello.
-Mark. This is Goong.
Where are you?
I just watched the news
and I'm worried about you.
Don't say anything.
Someone might be listening.
Can we meet?
Pla has just called me.
She has evidence
which can prove that you're innocent.
She won't see me unless I see you first.
No problem. Where?
Mark.
I'm sorry.
You.
Ever since Johnny and his men came here,
it has been hell for everyone.
Everyone from the waitresses
to the manager.
I don't know what to do.
They built a secret entrance
at the back of the restaurant...
for their VIP clients.
Everyone wants to know
what goes on up there.
Maybe the relative you are looking for
is up there.
Where's Johnny?
Don't let him in.
Hey, bro!
Where are my elephants?
What is he saying?
Korn!
Hey. Hey.
-What are you doing? Hey, Johnny!
-Don't touch me. Let me go.
-Johnny!
-Mark!
-Johnny.
-Johnny. Let her go, Johnny.
-Let me go.
Let her go, Johnny.
Korn!
Have you found your brother?
Korn! Korn!
Korn!
Shit!
An elephant! A real elephant!
How did you get here?
Korn!
Rose, the heir to the business
should be Sim's Son.
But Chao is only 13. He's still a child.
He doesn't yet have the ability
to run the family business.
Then, the most suitable person
should be Kang.
He is the son of Third Aunt,
who is the younger sister
of Sim and your father.
That should be good. Kang has just
graduated in Management from England.
He should be able
to take good care of the business.
Why don't any of you
think about how I feel?
I am also my father's child.
I have devoted everything to this family.
I would always help Uncle
when he was still alive.
Take a good look at yourself.
You're neither a man nor a woman.
How do you expect us
to let you run the family business?
We wouldn't be able
to show our faces in public.
Kang! What's wrong with you?
Please don't scare me. Help! Help!
Help! Help!
You! Why did you have to do this?
The most suitable person is dead.
What's wrong? Tell me, Chao!
-And the second is dying.
-Chao! What's wrong? Chao!
Is there anyone suitable left?
In that case, I accept the responsibility.
I promise you all...
I will make the family business
better than ever.
I won't let you down.
I won't let my father down.
And I hope for the utmost cooperation
from you all.
Be patient, Korn.
We'll find Por Yai together.
Hey, Kham. We can't stay here anymore!
I think we've disturbed you enough,
father.
Thank you very much
for your gracious assistance.
Once you have stepped on fire,
no matter how far you run,
your feet will still burn.
At least, we won't cause you any problems.
I must go now, father.
Come on, Kham.
-What are you going to do now?
-I must find Por Yai.
I think that transsexual knows something.
Maybe we should go back
to the temple for now.
Father!
-Someone, help!
-Father!
Get out quickly. Go on.
Damn it!
Kham!
You should take the elephant
back to Bangkok.
I have connections at the port.
It would be easy for you to go back.
What about you, Sarge?
Don't worry about me.
Where's my elephant?
Where is he?
Vincent.
Asshole!
You piece of shit!
Korn!
You're scum!
You son of a bitch.
Your mother's a dirty whore.
Get up! Get up!
Get up!
Johnny! Put the gun down.
This majestic elephant...
will enhance your dominion.
All will bow to you
and the power which you hold.
Korn! Korn!
Korn! Korn! Korn!
Stupid!
Watch out! What have you done?
Be careful. My elephant.
Bring him down. Get up! Move!
An elephant is most vulnerable
at its tendons.
If its tendons are severed, it will fall.
Wait.
-Come on, come on. Quickly.
-Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Lower it down! Lower it down!
Lower it down!
-Come on, come on. Quickly, quickly.
-Up! Up!
Are you okay, Goong?
Name?
Somsak, Sir.
-God, are you Thai?
-Aren't I speaking clear enough?
You sarcastic piece of shit!
Elephants have represented Thailand
for many years.
We respect them
as if they were our own brothers,
our family.
Thai people don't appreciate it
if anyone tries to hurt an elephant.
Actually, Thai people like peace.
Peace, peace, you know?
But we don't like it
when people take our liberties.
Translated by: Patchara Laeka