This program is suitable for viewers above 18 years of age.
It may contain violence, intense sexual situations, and use of rude language.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Parental guidance is suggested for children under the age of 18.
Characters, behaviors, places, agencies, occupations, and events in the series are fictional and for entertainment purposes only.
It is not intended to encourage any actions shown in the series. Viewer discretion is advised.
What do you want from me?
I want you to live at my house.
Can't we just forget about what happened last night?
You're the one I want to be with.
I'll give you some time to think about it.
He acts like a mafia.
Send someone to look after Kim.
Don't let him out of your sight.
Yes, sir.
I have to go abroad for work.
When I return, I'll pick you up at your place.
Let's go. It's time for Omakase.
Kim, you're the best!
He hasn't said that he will treat us to Omakase yet.
Omakase please.
Anything is fine for me because I'm so hungry.
Kim!
Hello.
How are you? I came here yesterday, but May said that you were sick.
Actually, I really wanted to go visit you.
I told him that you didn't want anyone to disturb you.
I'm much better now. Please take a seat, Mr. Karan.
I would definitely have gone to visit you if I knew where your house is.
Here. I've brought this for you. At first, I was going to ask May to give it to you.
Thank you. But you don't have to give me all of this.
Kim.
You're on lunch break now, right?
Well...
Do you want to have lunch with me?
Please?
I...
Mr. Kamol.
You have a guest?
What are you doing here?
I already told you that I'll treat you to a meal after my work is done.
Kim, who is this guy?
It's none of your business.
I'm taking Kim out for lunch.
You guys can't threaten me like this.
Please leave.
Don't touch me!
Please leave now.
Kim.
When...
are you going to shut up?
It's annoying.
Stop bothering someone who belongs to me.
Who belongs to you?
I mean...
My soon-to-be person.
It's all in your head.
Please leave.
Kim, are you going to have lunch with him?
I'll owe you guys a meal, then. I have to take care of something first.
Let's go.
How do you feel?
We haven't seen each other for a couple of days.
I feel good.
Are you happy now?
Are you saying that you don't miss me at all?
It was just a one-night stand. Why would I miss you?
But I miss you.
♪ I don't know if you're going to believe it or not ♪
♪ I just knew what love was the day I met you ♪
♪ The first time our eyes met ♪
♪ When we're close, only a breath apart ♪
♪ You're the one I'm looking for ♪
Why are you not getting out?
You said you're taking me out to lunch. But why are we at the hotel?
Are you getting out of the car by yourself? Or do you want me to carry you out? You decide.
Move. I'll get out of the car by myself.
I remember this hotel. It was where we first met.
What's your intention?
What do you think?
I'm bringing you here for lunch. You don't trust me?
You like Japanese food, don't you?
You know me so well.
If you have something to say, just say it.
We can talk while we eat. I'm not in a hurry.
But I am! What do you want from me?
It was just one night.
Let's forget about it.
Have you packed your belongings yet?
I'm not going anywhere. Are you trying to get on my nerves?
I didn't intend to make you feel that way.
This is the last time that we meet.
I won't go anywhere with you anymore because we don't know each other.
But I'm giving you a chance to get to know me.
I told you before that I don't want to get to know you. Who would want to get to know a guy like you?
You have people following you around and calling you "boss."
There are only a handful of jobs that have people act that way.
And I don't want to know anyone who has those kinds of jobs.
But it seems like
you want to know what kind of job I have.
I don't want to know that.
I'm a business owner.
I guess it's a shady business. You're a mafia, aren't you?
What's your definition of "mafia"?
Someone like you.
If you want me to be a mafia,
I can be that for you.
But if you want me to be a business owner,
I can be that as well.
I can be whatever you want me to be.
Am I that important to you?
I want to know... why does it have to be me?
You're the first person that I'm interested in.
Then you might be interested in other people as well.
Let go of me.
Can you give me some time to explain
why you're the only one that I want?
Let's begin plan B.
Plan B?
I really want to know you better, Kim.
Why don't we take some time to get to know each other more?
Or to make things easier, we can be boyfriends.
Tonight...
You will stay with me, right?
No. I will go back home.
If you want to go back,
you have to let me drop you off.
I can go back by myself.
I'm sorry, boss. There's an urgent call from a Korean investor.
Wait for me here.
Don't try to run away.
Do whatever you want.
Even if I run away from you, you can find me anyway.
Gosh! He's such a control freak!
Hello, is there something urgent?
I have something to tell you.
That's why I have to call you now. Sorry about that.
No worries.
Mr. Danai contacted me regarding the casino concession.
He has offered me 300 million baht for investment.
But you have offered me only 100 million baht. So, I think...
We will reconsider it and get back to you soon.
Well, if you're too slow...
I won't. I'll get back to you within two hours.
Give me some time to sort this out.
Mr. Hyung-sik, do you still trust me?
All right. We'll wait for you.
Thank you for your trust.
Danai is trying to hinder me from getting this project.
Send me the details of the entire budget.
And let's begin plan B.
There will be a lot of losses if we go with plan B but end up not winning at the auction.
A man like me
never loses.
Kom.
Send someone to check on Danai.
Find out if he has contacted any of our partners.
Yes, sir.
Kit.
Tell Lop to call someone at Kim's office
and let them know that Kim will arrive home safely.
Yes, sir.
Why do I like you so much?
What time is it now?
It's 11 p.m.
11 p.m.? Why didn't you wake me up?
My phone is dead.
May is probably worried about me now.
Don't worry. I already told her.
Also,
I didn't want to wake you up because you were sleeping so soundly.
You called May?
Wouldn't that make her question the fact that I--
That you're here with me?
I told my subordinate to call her
and tell her you're safe.
Don't worry.
You can trust me.
I'll go back now.
Okay.
If you want to go back, I'll drop you off.
Get up, then.
What do I have to do
if I want to see you every day?
Will you come live at my house?
I'll give you the same answer, which is no.
I'm not rushing you.
I'll give you a couple of days to think about it.
Once you have the answer,
I'll go pick you up by myself.
I want you to come and live with me.
Okay?
If that's the case,
I can go back home by myself.
I hope we'll never meet again.
Kim.
I've told you before.
I want to get to know you.
Kit.
Yes, sir.
Give me the car keys and get the car ready.
Let me wash my face first, and we'll go back together.
Why are you not answering my call, Kim?
There are a lot of men in black suits in front of our office. What should we do?
Have a good rest.
Thank you for dropping me off. You can leave now.
Do you know that you look like a cat trying to threaten me?
I'm human.
Okay.
I'll leave then.
I hope that you'll reconsider what I said.
Just leave. I want to sleep now.
Hello, May.
Hello, Kim. Are you all right? They didn't try to kill you, right? You're safe, right?
I'm sorry for making you worried. I'm back at my condo now.
That's good. I'm glad to hear that. I don't want to say this, but his subordinates are so rude.
I'm fine. Thank you for worrying about me. You should get some rest.
Okay. It's good to hear that you're still okay. You should get a lot of rest. I'll see you at the office.
Okay, see you later.
It's all because of you, Mr. Kamol.
I haven't thought about Day at all today.
You can really make me forget his embrace, huh.
Mr. Kamol.
Hello, Ms. Cherry.
I want the full treatment today since I'm going to meet my special someone.
Of course. Please wait.
Here you go.
Thank you.
May.
Please sit.
Alright.
Well... I need some advice.
It's about my friend.
Sure.
My friend told me that...
someone asked him to live together.
Like, they had a one-night stand.
But then that person suddenly asked my friend to move in with him.
Do you think I--
What do you think I should tell my friend?
I think it's too fast. You don't know his personality and how he lives his life.
It's not like you'll live in his house for free, right?
You're right.
But I think you can tell him that it's better to get to know each other more before moving in together.
There are a lot of men in black suits in front of our office. What should we do?
What's going on?
Hello, Kim. We're sorry for alarming you. We're here for your safety.
That's right. Don't mind us. You can live life as usual.
How can you call this "usual"?
Do you miss me that much to the point where you have to call me?
Quit imagining things!
Tell your subordinates to leave and give me back my normal life!
He's quite stubborn.
Sir.
We can identify those who committed the arson now.
We've found out that these two belong to Danai.
That's what I thought.
Get ready.
Since he wants to play with us,
Show him that we are not the ones he should be messing with.
Yes, sir.
Kamol is here, right?
He's not available for guests at the moment. Please go back first.
I'm not a guest.
Kamol, look at Kom. He won't let me go in to see you.
I'm getting angry now.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to ask you to eat out together. Let's find something to eat.
I'm not free.
Please excuse me.
You've changed.
You're not like this before.
You used to be kinder.
I'm not a kind person.
If you were not kind, you wouldn't have helped me on the first day we met.
You would've probably let me get hit by a car.
If that wasn't an act of kindness, then what was it?
If I've done something to make you misunderstand my intention,
I'm sorry about that.
Kom, please send off the guest.
All guests are not welcome.
Kamol!
Please leave.
(2 days later)
I want you two to take care of the financial statements of the Siam Tech company.
Siam Tech is going to be listed on the stock exchange soon.
I want you guys to have a look--
(Mr. Kamol)
Whoever is calling is so persistent. Kim is not answering his calls, but he keeps calling anyway.
Kim, are you okay? Do you need our help?
I just want you to help with the financial statements.
Not about that. You can tell us if you're having personal problems.
I'm fine. Thank you so much.
Why don't you take a vacation?
Take a break from everything for a little while.
That's right. You don't have to worry about work. I'll take care of it.
It's okay. You guys should get back to work now. Thank you so much.
Don't forget what I asked you to do.
Are you sure that you're okay?
Yes.
Why are you not answering my calls, Kim?
I want to talk to you.
Should I hang out with my friends?
My only friend is Day.
Should I do that?
Hey, dude. You've disappeared!
Well, I'm calling you right now.
Are you free?
When? If now, no. I have a meeting.
Really? I was going to ask you to hang out with me.
Why don't you ask Day? He's a freelancer.
I gotta go now. Bye!
Should I call Day?
Hello, Day. Are you free? Can I talk to you?
Sure. What's wrong?
Where are you? Can I come to see you?
I'm out of town right now. Is something the matter?
It's nothing.
I can wait until you come back.
Wait until I go back to Bangkok then. I'll call you.
Hey, Itt. Why don't you dry hair after getting in the water? You'll get sick.
I know. My towel is with you.
I gotta go. I have to deal with something.
Come here. I'll dry it for you.
Why don't you dry your hair?
Did I make the right decision to call Day?
I'll find out if I can forget about him yet or not.
Hello, Day.
What's wrong?
Can I come over to your house and have a talk?
Our people is still keeping an eye on Kim, right?
Yes, sir.
Good. Don't let him out of your sight.
What's going on?
Are we going to die?
I don't know.
Who did this?
(DIE)
Move!
Damn it!
He dares to do this to me?
Everyone in his company is scared now.
A rabid dog like him
should be scared too.
Also, those people who spied on us have disappeared.
Good.
Now they'll know that they shouldn't mess with me.
You dumbass!
You're all useless!
How could you let him do this?
Maybe it's not Kamol's doing this time.
Are you serious?
If it's not him, then who?
You're fucking stupid!
Listen to me. From now on, keep an eye on him.
He will try to get back at us again.
Yes, sir.
How's Kim?
He goes to work as usual.
He loses his temper because of Lop sometimes.
Nothing's changed. Everything is as usual.
Does he think that he can continue to not pick up my calls?
Hello.
You're finally picking up the phone.
Hey, you!
I miss you, Kim.
Why aren't you answering any of my calls?
When will you stop bothering me? This is my office number.
It's been three days. Get ready.
I'll pick you up this evening.
He's so stubborn, just the way I like.
Our people is still keeping an eye on Kim, right?
Yes, sir. Lop's team is still watching him.
Good. Don't let him out of your sight.
Yes, sir.
Hello, Day.
I'm back in Bangkok.
What's the matter?
Can I come over to your house and talk to you?
What's wrong?
Can I tell you in person?
Okay, I'll wait for you at home then.
Thank you so much.
May and Jin, can you get Mr. Pakorn's document for me?
Kim, is something the matter?
I'm going on a vacation.
My friend asked me to go out of town with him.
But if I go out now,
those people will follow me.
Are you going to run away?
I've got to go now.
I'm off.
What's that sound?
What happened?
Miss, what's wrong?
I have a stomach ache.
Are you all right, Miss?
Have a safe trip, Kim!
Thank you so much, May. You can contact me via e-mail. Please don't let anyone know where I'm going.
Sure.
How can I help you?
It's okay. Thanks!
What's wrong with her?
It's a pleasure to work with you all.
I hope that we will win this time.
A man like me doesn't know how to lose.
Please, sir.
Hello, Lop.
What?
What did you just say?
Okay. I'll let him know.
Sir, I have something to report to you.
Er... Mr. Kim has escaped.
This is why I want him to be my lover.
I'll handle this myself.
He couldn't have gone far. He's probably still in Bangkok.
Also,
don't bother anyone from his office.
Kim will be mad at me if he knows.
Yes, sir.
Who are you talking about?
Who is Kim?
The hands that I've wished would hold mine someday.
I have something to discuss with Kim.
Move out of the way.
No.