NETFLIX PRESENTS
[birds chirping]
[church bells ringing]
[music playing on record]
[children shouting]
[townsfolk chattering]
[camera clanking]
[vehicles approaching]
[ominous music playing]
[ominous music continues]
SCHNAPPS
Oh…
[speaking German]
[swallowing]
[gasps]
[coughing]
[snickering]
[all laughing]
[speaking German]
[mournful music playing]
[gun clanking]
[gas hissing]
[ominous music playing]
Come on guys, seriously.
Who was it?
Who told you about my birthday?
If I catch the bastard
who spilled the beans, I'll kill him.
[man] Ready!
No, no, no, guys, seriously now.
For real.
Let's drop this already, okay?
Talk to my uncle, General Lozano.
Get him now.
This is a misunderstanding.
[man] And… aim!
No, I'm the General's nephew!
Let me go now!
If anyone dares to pull the trigger
you'll be in fucking trouble!
Stop!
[sighing]
Stop, assholes!
[gasps]
I'm very happy to see you here, Uncle.
You and I need to talk.
Release him!
Take him to my office as soon as possible.
Well, then…
didn't you hear him?
Let me fucking go already,
you bunch of hicks!
Uncle, I gotta admit that you had me
doubting there for a sec today.
Obviously, it was just for a split second,
but I swear,
I thought that was it for me.
I got there in time to stop them
from shooting you, Jan.
But they still want you dead.
Well, here I am, right?
[sighs]
Not for much longer.
It's the third time I've saved your life,
but it'll be the last time.
I convinced them not to execute you,
but in return,
they want something similar.
They want you to take this envelope
to Colonel Alarcos.
-Alarcos? But he commands the Sixth.
-Tell me something I don't know.
The Sixth is on the other side
of the Sierra.
I'd have to skirt no man's land.
It's impossible.
I told you it was almost an execution.
You can't do this to me. That's like…
You head-butted a judge!
For the record, I hurt myself too.
It seems that doesn't matter.
You and your typical little jokes,
right, nephew?
Well, as it turns out, that judge
is a lifelong friend of Franco.
They're almost cousins, you idiot!
Look, I had no clue he was Franco's
almost cousin. I'll keep it to myself.
Those powerful men have had
their eye on you for ages, Jan.
You've drawn too much attention saving
those Reds from death with your trials.
"Private Decruz, accused of desertion
and cowardice on the national front."
You insisted on
freeing him from execution.
He's not a coward, he's just
a 17-year-old boy who's scared to die.
I've done everything I can, Jan,
I wish you'd used your head better.
Yeah, well, Franco's almost cousin
doesn't think the same.
The judge sentenced you for treason.
The only way they'll overturn the sentence
is proving that you're a good soldier.
And you'll prove that
by delivering this envelope to Alarcos
and coming back before dawn.
-Maybe execution would've been better.
-Watch that mouth, Jan.
That fucking mouth.
If your father were alive today…
Get out of here and be careful.
I've already lost too much family
to this war.
Let me remind you,
my brother's still alive.
Well, not for me.
[sighs]
[keys rattling]
-What's this?
-There's a vehicle outside.
You know I don't know how to drive.
Don't worry,
we've also thought of that.
[door squeaking]
[Jan] Private Decruz.
-Are they gonna shoot me already?
-[Jan] No.
Today's your lucky day.
[Decruz] Thank you, Captain,
but I didn't do anything.
[Jan] You were supposed to be
fighting at Ebro,
but they arrested you
20 minutes away from Boiro.
Meaning you were scared shitless
and you ran to your mother.
-So there's a sentence already?
-Yeah, you're a coward.
-You can drive, right?
-Sure, in Boiro, when we were kids…
-I only asked if you can drive.
-Sorry, Captain. Yes, I can drive.
Very good, you'll drive me to the Sixth.
-To the Sixth?
-Mm-hmm.
But that's impossible, Captain.
There's no way to get back alive.
-Would you rather be executed?
-It's kind of the same thing.
You have a girlfriend?
I've got friends. A few friends, actually.
There's one in Boiro and one in Cambados,
but the one in Boiro is a better friend.
So you're a virgin?
In Boiro we're all virgins, Captain, sir.
-Are you good with weapons?
-It's not my forte.
And what's your forte, soldier?
I don't have any fortes, Captain, sir.
Mother of God…
Considering you're a coward
and I'm a lawyer,
together we're a dangerous duo, huh?
[man] Captain!
Lozano! Hey, stop!
Montoya, what happened to you?
Uh, you see, shrapnel from a Red mine,
I barely survived.
These Germans say they can
make me a prosthesis, or whatever.
Yeah, can't wait to be able
to jerk off again, huh?
[chuckles]
Uh, Captain, could I get a cigarette?
That old crow won't even let me
take a drag.
-Sure.
-Oh.
Mmm, thank you. Mmm!
[woman] What's going on?
Smoking is bad for your health.
So is the war, right?
Do you think those little stars
mean anything to me?
I'm in charge here, not you.
But what is this?
Was this sloppy job done by Laura?
When I get back from Garabandal
I'll show her.
Why are you standing there?
Let's go, I don't have all day! Let's go!
That's the old crow?
If she's going to Garabandal
she won't be back till tomorrow.
[man shouting in German]
[speaking German]
Wait, wait a minute. I said wait. Halt!
Fuck!
Thank you, Captain.
[ominous music playing]
[door clanking]
[Decruz] In Boiro I worked at
my uncle Chete's repair shop.
My thing is motorcycles,
but there's no engine that can resist me.
Cars, tractors…
If it has screws, I'm your man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can't we go a little faster, private?
Yes, we sure can, but I prefer to go slow,
that way maybe we'll live
a little bit longer.
-Although maybe we could…
-No, no. I'm telling you right now.
-But I didn't even say anything.
-I'm not going to Boiro with you.
How did you know I would ask that?
Turn right, Private.
We'll cut through the valley.
-Are you sure about that, Captain?
-Mmm-hmm.
That's no man's land.
Our men aren't there, right?
Just relax, kiddo.
I promise nothing will happen to us.
Sure. And are you just saying that
or do you really believe it?
Fuck.
[subtle music playing]
[Jan snoring loudly]
Oh, shit!
-Captain, wake up!
-Are we there yet?
[speaking German]
-Do what they say.
-What the fuck did they say?
[gasps] I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[Jan] Easy, Decruz,
these guys are like dogs.
If they smell fear, you're dead.
We have to pretend
we couldn't care less, got it?
[in English] What are you doing here?
What a coincidence,
I asked myself the same thing.
-Do you have papers?
-I'm Captain Lozano, from the Fifth--
Papers!
[sighs]
What's all this?
You can't pass through.
Please turn around.
Well, I'm in a hurry. You can start
moving all that out of the way.
Yeah, out of the way.
Where are you going?
-That is confidential.
-I asked where.
Confidential means you know exactly
where you to shove your questions.
Up your ass.
You can shove 'em up your ass.
-Let us pass, if you don't want problems.
-That's right.
-Get the fuck out of our way!
-[honking horn]
Decruz. Decruz. Decruz, hold on.
Hold on, because this gentleman…
is going to let us pass.
Isn't that right?
-[speaking German]
-[jeep engine revving]
How the hell did you do that, Captain?
Alright. When we can, let's stop, okay?
I'm about to puke.
Private, can I ask you something?
Well, you already asked if I'm a virgin.
How'd you end up in this war?
-The truth is, I don't really know.
-What do you mean?
Had to take a side, you know?
In my town, everyone sided
with the puff pastries.
"Puff pastries"?
The nuns add something
that makes different.
And if you ask them, they won't tell you.
So, of course, with the war,
our first thought
was that if the Reds captured the nuns
the Puff Pastries would be gone forever.
We could never allow that.
You're telling me that puff pastries
put you in this war?
If you put it like that.
-Oh, do you have a better motive, sir?
-Any motive is better.
You say that 'cause
you haven't tried those pastries.
[airplane passing overhead]
That's a Polikarpov.
A Rat.
[imitating clattering engine]
[second plane passing overhead]
That's a Fiat.
[imitating smooth engine]
[machine guns firing]
The Russians have no fucking idea.
The Germans and the wops,
they are incomparable.
[machine guns firing]
Really? Well, it looks like the wops
don't have such great aim.
Pull over, soldier.
[engine sputtering]
[explosion in distance]
Let's go help him, he's one of ours.
One of ours?
What do I have to do with an Italian?
Decruz, it's too soon to be a coward
and this is just the beginning.
But, Captain, sir,  I'm sure he's alright.
And you've seen
his friends are out there too.
Private, move your ass,
we're not going to leave him there.
Oh, fuck!
[Decruz] Why don't we give up already?
It's gonna be really hard to find him.
-Maybe if we--
-You always talk this much?
-In Boiro, Grandma always said…
-Shut up, Decruz, please.
Okay.
[branches snapping]
Come on.
[ominous music playing]
Is he dead?
What do you think?
[man] Show your hands!
And turn around nice and slow!
[Decruz] Oh, God.
You see, Captain? Not a good idea.
I told you so, we're screwed.
Easy, kid, if they wanted us dead
we would have been shot.
[man] Did you hear me? Turn around.
Nice and slow.
Don't do anything stupid, Private, got it?
[man] Who would've thought?
We come to hunt a Pava
and we run into a fascist captain.
No, sir, we're Republican soldiers.
We're dressed like this because
we've infiltrated between enemy lines.
Do you think we're stupid, kid?
No, no.
Get their weapons.
-What are you looking at?
-Oh, nothing.
[camera shutter clicking]
[man] Will you cut that out?
All these photos.
What are you doing here?
That information is confidential,
I'll only be able to tell you.
And why's that?
You'll understand when I tell you.
Start saying goodbye to your fucking life.
Priest-killer! Fuck! Don't kill him!
-"Priest-killer"?
-You got something to say, fascist?
No, it's just a beautiful name,
that's all.
We clearly caught a big fish.
You don't send a captain to sniff around.
I won't forget this.
Don't you worry about it.
Be a smart-ass again and you won't live
to tell the tale, that clear?
Oh, fuck. Crystal clear, dude.
We need to search him,
he could be from intelligence.
See if he's got anything we can use.
[man 2] They were coming from
or going to Las Águilas
and decided to take a shortcut.
[scoffs]
[sighs]
"A War is won by having balls"?
What does it mean?
[scoffs] Son of a bitch.
Is this a joke?
-Maybe the message is encrypted.
-Encrypted, my ass.
You better start explaining this.
Alright.
Match, kill the kid.
It'll be my pleasure.
-[cocking pistol]
-What?
No, no, no! Fuck!
You can't just murder me like this.
'Cause I'm a virgin! I'm a virgin!
Tell him, Captain, sir!
That's a lie.
He's married and has two kids.
Don't be assholes,
it's not worth it to kill him.
-[urinating]
-Oh, man.
-Oh, shit.
-For fuck's sake, that's gross.
-I can't go on, Sergeant, sir.
-Damn it, Match, again?
Fuck, if it were up to you we'd resolve
this war by playing cards.
[drawing pistol]
Isn't he a bit young to have two kids?
-He's a bit young for you to kill him.
-I'll do it if you want.
Will you shut up, Brodsky?
Two kids?
Son of a bitch.
We'll take them.
Who's the softy now, huh?
Match, don't fuck with me!
We've got orders to take no prisoners.
Will you shut up already?
Fuck, man. Everyone's got an opinion.
Is this a town hall meeting?
Listen…
The kid's of no use to you.
Look at him.
Let him go already.
-You can take me.
-Oh, is that so?
Seems to me you're not
in a position to negotiate anything.
For now, we're taking both of you
to the camp and we'll see how it goes.
You caught me on a good day…
but don't push your luck.
Let's go.
Move it!
[Match] Walk!
Pulitzer, here I come.
[shutter clicking]
Fuck! He's alive!
[snarling]
Ahh!
[screaming] Get him off of me!
Get him off of me!
-Jesus!
-Get out of the way!
[zombie snarling]
[screaming]
[flesh tearing]
[grunts]
Oh, shit.
What the fuck is this?
[choking]
[growling]
Brodsky…
[snarling]
[growling]
[gun clicking]
[snarling]
[gunshot]
Can someone tell me
what the fuck that was?
[Decruz] He was possessed.
Decruz, shut up!
[Brodsky] He's right.
Back in Mother Russia they say
that when those that passed away…
Brodsky, now isn't a good
a good time for your stories.
What stories?
I've told you a thousand times,
I'm Russian!
I was brought here as a child,
goddamn it!
You do have a taste for vodka.
Okay, that's enough.
Stop acting like children.
Match, how's the American?
There's nothing we can do.
He's pretty dead.
Let's get out of here.
Wait. Hold on, hold on.
You're gonna leave them like that?
-What do you want, a Christian burial?
-Sergeant, the fascist is right.
The American was an idiot,
but leaving him is wrong.
Fuck, man, don't you know
how to check if someone's dead?
Ah, shit!
What the…
[snarling]
[gnashing]
[bones crunching]
Brodsky, please.
You know he was one of us.
I'm not so sure about that.
I can't believe it.
Sergeant…
[gnashing]
He's suffering.
[gunshot]
Okay, now we can go.
[planes droning overhead]
Now what?
Messerschmitt 109s.
No, these are Pablos.
The one that fell wasn't a Pava.
-Who asked you anything, fascist?
-The fascist is right, they're Junkers.
Where are they going?
[grunts]
Starting now, you'll only speak
when I tell you, understand?
[gasping]
Try anything and I'll drop you
in your tracks.
Fascist, what's going on here?
I know as much as you.
We'll see when I leave you alone
with the Nail Clipper.
"Nail Clipper"?
What the hell, none of you
have normal names here?
It's an appropriate name.
You'll see.
He's our man for extracting information
and he's the best at it.
That's 'cause you don't know
my aunt Charo from Tudela.
I doubt you'll be so funny
when you meet him.
[explosions in distance]
[gunfire]
That's at the encampment.
Let's go.
Fucking fascists.
Looks like my interview with
the Nail Clipper has been canceled.
Well, he was our only reason
to keep you alive.
Move, fascist!
[Sergeant] Ochoa!
Manolo!
Hey! Anyone still alive?
Fucking goddamn it!
I had a CS1 like this,
when they brought it to the garage…
It's an ES1.
And it was mine…
Of course, it's an ES1, whatever you say.
It's the same dust
the pilot was covered in.
That's enough.
You talk right now
or I'll blow your head off.
What's that fucking crap that you dumped?
-I swear to God I have no idea!
-[Priest-killer] Sergeant!
It's Ochoa!
Kill them already
and let's get to the checkpoint.
Why the fuck would I do that?
[exhales]
What the hell did they do to you, Ochoa?
[flesh gurgling]
Oh, shit!
We need to get our asses
out of here right now, guys.
[growling]
What the fuck's happening?
Same thing as with the pilot
and the American.
There's only one thing we can do.
Don't even think about it!
It's Ochoa! She needs help!
I'm not getting near her, Sergeant.
[snarling softly]
Please, come on.
Could someone just untie us?
[zombies moaning]
[snarling]
Mary Mother of God!
Could you please untie us,
like right about now?
What the fuck is happening?
Are they alive or what?
Father?
No! No, no, no! Kid!
-Father!
-He's no longer your father.
-[growling]
-[screaming]
She's right, we have to get out of here!
-Shut the fuck up!
-[Jan] This doesn't look good, Sergeant.
No! They're fucking comrades,
we have to help them!
[snarling]
Sorry, Sergeant,
but as we say in Mother Russia…
[screeching]
kiss my ass, fucker!
[screaming]
Motherfucker.
[Sergeant] No! Cease fire!
-Cease fire, they're our people!
-[Brodsky] We can't stop!
In the head!
You have to shoot them in the head!
We have to get out of here!
We can't do anything for them!
Let's get the fuck out!
-[Jaime] Come on!
-[Sergeant] Fuck, let's go!
Run, Decruz!
Come on! Come on! Push!
Get off, fascist!
Priest-killer, release the kid!
Help us, you imbecile!
What about me? I can help you guys.
I don't trust you at all! Come on!
[straining]
Come on, push!
[Jan] Get in!
[gunshots]
[snarling]
[Priest-killer] Get in!
[Sergeant] Let's go!
Gutiérrez, the Gardner,
and that kid from Manresa.
Massip.
The dead are walking.
Their blood is dry.
The kid was right, they're possessed.
Stop with the nonsense, damn it.
That's not possible.
Well, you guys shot the shit
out of the Italian pilot
and your comrades too, by the way.
Don't remind me, son of a bitch!
They weren't dead, they were walking!
You guys fucking saw it!
-They wanted to eat us.
-Will you shut up, Brodsky?
Well, yeah, it's true,
you saw what they did to Carlos.
Come on, fascist,
you must know what's going on.
You guys believe in nuns and all that!
I don't have to believe in nuns,
they exist.
You understood, asshole!
Nuns, priests, God and all that nonsense.
Look, in the Bible doesn't it say that God
rose up three days later in Bethlehem,
like those demons?
Let's see, first of all,
it wasn't God, it was Jesus.
Second, it wasn't in Bethlehem,
it was in Jerusalem.
Third, when Jesus rose the third day
he didn't start eating fucking people!
We know the same as you about that.
It bothers you,
but we're on the same side.
No, that's not true. In this war,
we're on the side of the Republicans,
and you guys on the side
of the fucking sons of bitches.
How nice.
Hey, untie him.
Mmm.
Hold on…
I've got something to say.
[grunts]
Now we're at peace. Yeah.
Careful, careful.
"You can't die twice
if you don't escape death once."
What are you saying?
What-- What does that phrase mean?
It's not a phrase,
it's a Russian proverb.
Bunch of ignorants.
Brodsky isn't only Russian,
he's also a poet.
Yeah, exactly like Machado, right?
Maybe they came back to life!
My uncle from Cambados
had a catalepsy attack
from drinking two bottles of moonshine.
They thought he died. Two days.
Until he woke up.
He vomited for three hours.
But three days later,
he was drinking moonshine again.
It doesn't sound like
the same thing to me, kid.
All that doomsday shit is just a bunch
of tales to scare the people.
If they were walking,
they weren't all that dead.
They didn't attack each other.
What they wanted was us.
What do we do now?
We go to a hiding place we have near here.
Why, to meet more comrades of yours?
No, no, don't worry.
There's only weapons, ammunition
and food. Well, and a radio.
Let's see if we can find out
what the fuck is going on.
Does the Captain agree?
I don't know. Any other options?
Yes…
We shoot you two
and throw you into the river.
Then it seems like a great plan.
[snarling]
If we hurry,
we'll get there before it's dark.
[bushes rustling]
What the…
What, here too?
[zombies snarling]
Fuck!
Shit!
I told you they were possessed!
Wait, wait, wait!
Give me a gun, I can help!
Don't try anything stupid
or you'll meet the Virgin, Jesus
or whoever the fuck you pray to!
This doesn't change a thing, fascist!
[Jan] Did I say anything?
-Come on, kid, move it!
-Whoa!
[growling]
Get the fuck out of here!
[snarling]
[flesh tearing]
[screaming]
Brodsky!
[screeching]
[yelling]
-Brodsky!
-Hold on! Hold on!
Let me go!
-We can't do anything!
-Let me go! Brodsky!
Clear out! Get out of here, come on!
[Brodsky] Get out of here!
[Brodsky screaming]
[grunts]
Don't touch me, fascist!
Come on!
Why are those two still alive?
They're of no use to us!
Let me handle…
Haven't you had enough of this shit today?
What the fuck's wrong with you?
[ominous music playing]
Someone beat us here.
[all cocking weapons]
Just what we needed.
Wait… what's going on here?
It's a long story, actually,
what happened…
Nobody move! Freeze! Nobody move!
No. Hold it, freeze!
I'm Captain Lozano, Requetés Regiment.
Requetés Regiment, my ass!
Drop the weapon, you fascist,
or we'll mow you down!
[man] Drop yours
or I'll blow your head off.
A fucking Arrow and a Muslim!
Hands up now or I'll take out your boss!
-Look at the fucking nun!
-Freeze. Everyone freeze.
Priest-killer, shoot her!
Do it! Soon enough I'll be running
after you trying to eat your guts.
What if I blow your head off?
Well, I guess that changes things.
Rafir, take out the old guy.
I'll take care of this runt.
Be careful with the old guy,
he'll blow your balls off
before you can pull the trigger.
Can we just drop this?
Stop aiming at him or I'll shoot you.
If it's about having balls,
let's solve this now.
-What are you waiting for, asshole.
-Hmm?
Don't aim at my captain,
or I swear you'll taste some lead, huh!
-You should take the safety off first.
-Sorry.
[bullet ricocheting]
Shit!
Shit! Shit, I'm so sorry.
-Are you an idiot?
-Nothing happened, alright?
We can shoot each other
and whoever survives
can deal with the crazy ones outside.
Or… we can lower our weapons
and try to think of a way
to get out of this alive.
I don't trust the Arrow.
Lieutenant, identify yourself.
Lieutenant Jurel. Spanish Phalanx
of the National Syndicalist Offensive.
Good. You?
Private first class Rafir.
Fiftieth division.
-You know what's going on?
-The dead aren't dying!
-What are you doing here?
-We were crossing the Sierra when--
-Rafir! Shut the fuck up!
-You shut up, Lieutenant!
From now on you will follow my orders.
Are we clear?
Alright.
Then answer me.
Why are you here?
The Junkers mistook us and shot at us
as we were crossing the Sierra.
Out of ten, only two survived.
And the next thing we know,
our own comrades were trying to to eat us.
So we ran through the woods
and came across Sister Flor.
And God guided our steps to here.
[scoffing]
Now there's a few more of us here,
so we have to work together.
Yeah, with the Reds
who'll shoot us as soon as they can.
Oh, you better believe it.
Right between the eyes, huh?
-Match!
-Let's cut the crap already!
There's only one way
to get out of this alive.
Together.
So whoever thinks they'll do better
on their own can leave.
So be it.
Decruz, damn it, lower that gun already!
Yeah, sorry.
Are you finished yet?
Great, now that we're all
best friends again, let's eat something.
[Flor] These demons came out
from between the trees
and the vehicle fell down an embankment.
Then the driver was eaten
by those beasts that came from from hell.
-[Jan scoffs]
-I saw it with my own eyes.
May God have mercy on them.
And if I'm still alive, it's a miracle.
Let me take a look at that.
That's not necessary, Mother,
it's nothing.
"Mother" is the Mother Superior,
and if it is or it's nothing,
that's my call.
Jacinto of the Sacred Heart of Jesus?
Yeah, what of it?
I wear it as an amulet.
This needs to be taken care of.
If they attacked the old crow--
I mean, sorry, Sister Flor…
then they're not just at the river.
They can be anywhere.
Decruz!
You, Rafir and Match,
eat something and go upstairs.
-See if you see anything.
-[scoffs]
You heard him, Match, upstairs.
Are you letting a fascist
tell us what we have to do?
He's our best shooter.
Upstairs.
Captain, don't push it,
I give the orders here.
We'll rest here tonight.
We'll split the food and ammunition
in equal parts.
-What are we, communists?
-We're anarchists!
Whatever you say, comrade.
Whatever is happening here isn't…
What do you fascists say?
"Earthly".
What's happening here isn't earthly.
I don't know much about things,
but what I know, I know.
I worked on the railway.
I can explain to you
anything about the tracks.
Why can't you explain
why this is happening.
Don't the priests say that
the dead will rise one day?
Tell us where the bible explains
what to do to save our asses.
This has nothing to do
with the kingdom of heaven.
"When there's no more room in hell,
the dead will walk the Earth."
What the fuck is that?
My grandma used to say it.
I don't believe in that bullshit.
Although it's also true
that in this fucking war
we've all done something we could regret.
Well, in Las Águilas there's a priest.
Just saying, in case you want to
confess before Doomsday.
-Go fuck yourself!
-[Jan chuckles]
This is not Doomsday, sir.
The only thing this has to do with God
is that someone is trying to play God.
So what about this, Captain?
This…
is a family affair.
A WAR IS WON BY HAVING BALLS
[Match] Hey, Muslim.
Oh! I forgot that Allah
doesn't allow you to drink.
To kill, yes, that he does allow.
Seems like your god doesn't care either
if you kill your brothers.
I don't have a god.
I fight for a cause.
So you owned a CS1?
You little snob.
I told you I drove a CS1,
not that I owned it.
Before the war I used to work
at my uncle's garage.
And you?
That ES1 was yours, right?
That's a bike you don't see every day.
Wait a moment.
You're Miguel Andreu?
Miguel Andreu!
Ten years ago I went to La Rabassada
to see you race!
When you passed the curve
you were going so fast…
[exhales]
…I thought you wouldn't make it.
What a race!
You signed an autograph for me,
remember?
I mean, how could you remember?
There were so many people
and I was a child.
Miguel Andreu!
Who could imagine I'd be fighting
with Miguel Andreu?
We are not fighting together.
[can clatters]
And my name isn't Andreu.
Who cares who I was before all this?
Now we're in the war.
Yes, but you can race again,
the war is going to end someday.
"It's going to end," you say.
It's been a full year that
we've been retreating everywhere.
Anyway…
someone had to win.
I'm not an idiot, kid.
I know very well I won't race
on a circuit again in my fucking life.
If you know you've already lost,
why are you fighting then?
I've never abandoned a race.
I don't give a fuck about coming in last,
but if you start a race, you finish it.
[stations crackling]
[jazzy piano music playing]
♪ My prayer ♪
♪ Is to linger with you ♪
♪ At the end of the day ♪
♪ In a dream that's divine ♪
♪ My prayer ♪
♪ Is a rapture in you ♪
♪ With the world far away ♪
♪ And your lips close to mine ♪
♪ Tonight, while our hearts are aglow ♪
♪ Oh, tell me the words ♪
♪ That I'm longing to know ♪
♪ My prayer ♪
♪ And the answer you give ♪
♪ May they still be the same ♪
♪ For as long as we live ♪
♪ That you'll always be there ♪
♪ At the end of ♪
♪ My prayer ♪
[Jan] So they call you
the "Priest-killer"?
[chuckling] You haven't killed a priest
in your life.
I had to say something
to get admitted into the militia.
Will you keep my secret?
I've heard that the only women
who enlist in your ranks
are either whores or dykes.
Some of them are even
both at the same time.
I suspect you're not a dyke.
Don't act tough, the only soldierly thing
about you is you're looking for trouble.
You think I didn't see you
checking me out?
[chuckles] I get it, huh?
An army that sends its women
to war is an army of queers.
I bet you're dying to find
a proper man.
If you find one, send him to me.
[bangs on door frame]
[sighs]
[unzipping pouch]
Look.
This is Father Bustos.
The girl next to him is my little sister.
Lovely, right?
Father Bustos thought she was pretty.
When the war broke out,
I didn't say goodbye to my family,
but I did to Father Bustos.
Want me to tell you another secret?
[whispering]
But you're right about one thing.
Kill him? I didn't kill him.
When I left he was still breathing.
He's just a big mouth.
Well, and a poor idiot too,
but he's just as scared as the rest of us.
For me "the rest of us"
are my comrades.
You could all die right now,
so don't pretend to be Mr. Nice-Guy.
Those things out there don't care
a whole lot what side we're on
and if we want to get out of here,
we'd better put all this shit aside.
-All this shit?
-Mmm-hmm.
Sure, and we can also
hold hands and sing cheerful songs.
All you fascists are the same,
fucking treacherous rats.
And all you Reds are children of Satan,
straight out of hell.
I think I saw your demon tail
poking out earlier.
You were looking at my ass?
No, no, I mean, I…
Where I come from,
all the men have very rough hands.
You've never been to battle, huh?
I'm a lawyer.
-A lawyer.
-Corporate.
What the fuck is a lawyer doing here?
Yeah, you'll be very useful to us.
Well, I broke Franco's friend's nose.
Well, actually, his almost cousin.
So, in reality, I've done more damage
to the Nationals than all of you together.
A lawyer… Well, fuck me.
[ominous music playing]
[dog barking]
-[dog whines]
-What was that?
Shit! There's one coming.
-Muslim, let me try your rifle!
-No way.
Only I touch Leila.
If not, her barakah wears off.
Fucking Muslim!
That one won't be up again.
Motherfuckers!
Shit, shit, shit, shit!
[zombies snarling]
We've got company!
The Muslim shot one
but the others are coming.
[Jan] No time! Come on, let's go!
-[Decruz] Captain, what do we do?
-[Jan] Come on!
-[growling]
-[straining]
Priest-killer!
[grunting]
Holy fuck.
Quick!
[straining]
Come on! Out the back door! Come on!
-[Jan] Let's go!
-[grunting]
-Oh, God…
-Move! Move!
Come on! Come on!
[Sergeant] This way!
Come on!
Match!
[grunts]
Are you hungry, you fuckers?
Then eat this.
Run now!
[explosion echoing]
[Jan shushing]
What the fuck is that?
[zombies moaning]
[Match] What do we do?
[Jan] Hey! Shh! Don't shoot,
we don't know how many there are.
It smells like pig.
How do you know
what a pig smells like, Muslim?
Because I fucked your father once.
Oh, so you're a queer.
No.
It's nothing to worry about.
But if you fucked my father,
you're queer.
Yeah, he's right about that.
Enough, come on.
Are we in fifth grade or what?
[electricity crackling]
What's this?
They fenced off the valley.
Who fenced off the valley?
The Germans. I saw them roll it out.
They fenced off the entire valley.
They're frying.
[electricity crackling]
[electricity zapping]
Sergeant.
[snarling]
We can't leave him like that.
[snarling, moaning]
[pistol fires]
Even though he's a Red,
may God have mercy on his soul
and embrace him in his glory.
Amen.
Fucking bullshit.
Hey!
If the Nazis put this up,
then you guys must know something.
Right now we're all risking our lives,
fascist, don't fuck with us.
[sighs] They're not going to let us out.
Because we're in the middle
of their operations.
You see that? I was right.
Son of a bitch,
you knew from the beginning!
No, wait, I can explain.
It's the same note you saw earlier.
I didn't know it had a hidden map,
It must be invisible ink, who knows?
I discovered it at the house.
What's it mean? It's German?
Yes, here it says something about hours,
minutes, and advance speed…
Look, the dog recognizes
his master's voice.
-Advance of what?
-Advance of troops.
No. What troops?
You seen any troops around here?
No, it's something else.
It's them.
What I know is that whatever's going on,
has its origin here.
You dragged us in with no warning.
No, I didn't drag you anywhere.
I have no idea what these things are
or where they came from.
I am sure they don't care
what side we're on.
At least they don't argue all the time.
They seem more in agreement than we are.
-Sorry, I meant no offense by that, huh?
-[Jan sighs]
Okay, let's see…
The good news is if there's a map,
they aren't at all places, right?
The bad news is that we're in the part
of the map where we shouldn't be.
I don't know, we can keep walking
until they find us,
but the X is here.
There's gotta be a reason.
I say we try to find out
what the fuck's going on.
Are we in a frying pan
jumping into the fire?
Sometimes it's the only way to put it out.
Without setting a precedent,
the fascist might be right.
I vote for investigating it.
Without setting a precedent,
I second the four-eyes.
We've got nothing to lose.
-Decruz?
-Huh?
Oh, yeah, of course.
What are you afraid of, Jacinto?
The Virgin of the Sacred Heart
is with you.
Let's go.
Fucking democracy.
[ominous music playing]
Let's imagine for a moment
that the fascist is right
and there's something making
the dead become alive again.
If we find it,
we gotta do something about it.
What are you saying?
That we could use it for ourselves.
Of course if we find it, we'll have to
get rid of our new traveling companions.
I just want to make sure that
you know where your loyalties lie.
I know exactly what side I'm on.
I hope so.
[Jan] It's not that late,
somebody should be up.
[Sergeant] Maybe they turned off
the lights due to the bombings.
[Match] Or maybe they were all
eaten alive.
What a battle.
No, this definitely wasn't a battle.
Here some were shooting
and others just took the bullets.
-Decruz, go see if it starts.
-Yes, Captain, sir.
[engine cranking]
It's the blue powder again.
Hey, Sergeant!
[suspenseful music playing]
[door creaking]
If you're alive, show yourself.
[creaking continues]
We're going to start shooting in three…
Two…
-One!
-Wait!
I'm out.
I'm out. Don't shoot.
It's okay, sweetie. It's okay.
You aren't dead?
Have you seen any dead people talking?
I've seen them walking.
And your leg?
I got hurt trying to escape.
Escape? From whom?
From the groom, I bet.
[Priest-killer] It's alright.
You're with us now.
[breathing raggedly]
What's your name?
Ana.
And what side are you with?
A little bit of each side.
So the war's over?
Let's say we're in a parenthesis.
What happened here, Ana?
It was the happiest day of my life…
[sighs]
…until the Germans arrived.
[clattering]
[zombie snarling]
[snarling continues]
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
-[tools clattering]
-Fuck!
My fiancé, well… my husband.
He fell on me, that's how
I protected myself from the bullets.
Only one got me in the leg.
Then more soldiers arrived…
and they locked themselves up
in the church with those huge boxes.
I took the chance to hide in the cellar.
And then I heard the noises.
The dead began to move outside
and got up on their feet.
They wandered aimlessly around the plaza.
I wanted to go out,
but that wasn't my family.
That wasn't my husband.
The Germans would watch everything
from the bell tower and laugh.
Now and then they would capture a few
and took them inside the church.
They were doing experiments in there.
And we were their guinea pigs.
Then there was an explosion
in the church…
And that's when they stopped laughing.
Everything was filled
with the blue smoke again
and suddenly they were the ones
running around and devouring each other.
They tried to defend themselves,
but there were too many of them.
They didn't stand a chance.
With nightfall, everything got quiet.
I gained the courage to go out
a few minutes ago.
I was crossing the plaza
when I heard footsteps and…
I thought it was those creatures
coming back for me.
But it was just us.
[ominous music playing]
[Ana] And I hid here,
and that's all I know.
And where are the people now?
Where did they go?
[truck engine starting]
-[Jan] Everyone to the truck. Now!
-You can hold on to me, I'm strong.
What? She's a poor widow!
[Sergeant] Come on, let's go!
Not so fast, comrades.
Huh? What the fuck are you doing?
I found the formula that produces this.
We have the weapon.
Perfect, then we'll take it with us.
Yeah, of course we'll take it with us.
But they stay here.
Fucking Republican son of a bitch!
Next I'll aim for your head.
Jaime, for your mother's sake,
drop the weapon,
-and let's all get out before--
-Shut up!
This isn't a military decision.
It's a political matter.
and as such, I give the orders.
We have to take this information
to headquarters.
The Russians will know what to do with it.
If we dump the powder on their cities,
we'll win the war.
They'll kill each other.
We'll kill all of them.
These people have helped us,
we can't leave them behind.
Not only can we, but we're going to do it.
But, of course, if you prefer, you can
stay here with your new girlfriend.
What, did you think we hadn't noticed?
I won't tell you again, Jaime.
I'm fucking telling you to put it down.
Watch your mouth.
They're coming! We need to--
What's going on here?
You're a damn hick
who doesn't know anything!
You're out of your league here.
The Party gives the orders,
and I'm the Party representative.
And you're all idiots.
[grunts]
I'm giving you a chance to come with me.
It's up to you if you--
-[snarling]
-[screaming]
[screaming]
God embrace him in his glory.
-[snarling]
-[flesh tearing]
We can't go out that way.
I know this church.
It has an underground exit.
[Match] Of course.
Rats always have several escape routes
in case they need to run away.
Are you sure about this, sister?
If those beasts get in
and this tunnel has no way out,
we're pretty much fucked.
Sorry.
-[door smashing]
-[zombies snarling]
[Flor] We've got no choice
but to check it out.
[Sergeant] Come on!
[Jan] Let's go!
Move! Move!
They're here!
[Match] Can they fucking smell us or what?
[Flor] Hurry up! Hurry up! Come on!
[Jan] This way!
Look at those cowards run.
Of course they're not gonna wait.
But don't you worry, trust me,
I won't leave you here alone.
[hissing]
-[snarling]
-Jesus Christ!
-[grunting]
-[snarling]
[yelling] Get off!
Rafir! Rafir! Help!
Get off me!
[Flor] Get off me, you demon!
No! No!
-Get it off me!
-Get off him, fucker!
[Jan] Bitch!
[screaming]
[screeching]
How fucking gross!
And she was so pretty.
She was just a friend,
no need to get so jealous.
Come on.
Hold on! Hold on!
The girl just bit the Muslim.
You know what happens
if you're infected.
No! It's just a scratch!
Fucking bullshit!
There are teeth marks in his boot!
Your barakah just ran out.
-[Match] Sergeant?
-Wait! Look! Look!
-Her teeth didn't go through!
-Bullshit!
Take your sock off.
[panting]
[chuckles]
Her teeth didn't go through! You see!
I was right!
Allahu Akbar, he still protects me!
You and your fucking barakah.
I bet the stench stops them!
-[zombies screeching]
-Let's get the fuck out of here! Come on!
Hang on. This way!
Come on! Don't stop!
[Sergeant] Sister…
What are you doing?
-I'm going back to the church.
-Huh? What?
Someone has to take care
of their poor souls.
Stop with the bullshit and come out now.
They're right behind us!
It is the will of God.
-God! What God?
-Jacinto!
What?
[sighs]
Without setting a precedent,
I'm going to let your lustful eyes
rest on my leg for a moment.
[sighs]
We already know what those demon beasts
do when they bite you.
Oh, damn it, Flor…
Go on, I have work to do.
Wait a moment.
Here's a few consecrated hosts.
[church bells tolling]
Now, if you'll allow me,
I'm going to give communion.
May God be with you.
[cocking shotgun]
"…and the God of peace
brought back from the dead
-the great Shepherd of the sheep…
-[zombies snarling]
…our Lord Jesus through the blood
of the eternal covenant,
to Him whom be glory forever and ever.
Amen!"
It looks like we're all clear,
and the truck's still running.
-Decruz, you know how to drive it?
-Don't offend me, Captain.
Great. What do you want to do?
Listen. In Las Águilas there's a train car
with the same emblem we saw in the church.
I think I know who's behind this.
If we manage to get there--
Stop, stop, stop.
Do you take us for idiots or what?
Why would we want to go
to a camp with fascists?
It's impossible they've unleashed
all this without having an antidote.
-There must be some way to stop it.
-Why do you want to stop it?
We already know it's a weapon.
And it's yours.
We're already fucked in this war, there's
nothing we can do against this. You won.
My brother is fighting with you.
My own brother is fighting with you.
Every time I receive a dispatch
I think I'm going to find out that
he's fallen at the front or that
he's in some prison waiting to be shot.
Whatever happens, I lose.
If we let that out of Las Águilas
this war will never end.
It will go on until none of us are left,
is that what you want?
If we let that weapon get out of here,
we all lose.
Smooth talker.
What did you do before this?
He was a corporate lawyer.
No shit?
I also studied criminal law,
but haven't practiced it until now.
I'm going to Las Águilas
to try and stop this.
You can all come with me or wander around
the valley until you run out of bullets.
If we enter Las Águilas
we'll end up executed or digging ditches.
At least here we can take a chance.
Oh, don't worry,
we'll treat you very warmly.
For us to end up like Brodsky,
we might as well
shoot ourselves right now.
Your little speech wasn't bad.
But that doesn't change anything.
We lost the war.
Fuck that. If we go to Las Águilas
and get--
No, not this one, idiot, the other one.
You won that one.
Even if we stop those bastards,
this country is yours.
Listen, I'm too old.
I don't give a fuck what happens to me.
They can kill me.
But I do have one request,
whatever happens,
my comrades survive, alright?
So let's find whatever we have to find
and make sure they make it back home.
Swear to me.
Hey, wait a minute. Where's Decruz?
-He was here a second ago.
-Damned kid! Where'd he disappear to?
[horn honks]
We're ready to go now!
[sighs]
Well, look at that.
The fascist has some balls after all.
Kid, the line that separates the brave
from the stupid is very thin.
If only you knew, Captain, sir.
[Sergeant] Let's get going!
[Sergeant] So what's your plan?
We get in, we find the antidote
and then we get out.
-And you know where this antidote is?
-Mmm-hmm.
More or less. Yeah.
And you know this place?
Yes.
Well, actually I've only been there once.
And that's the best plan we have?
I don't know if it's the best,
but it's the only one.
Great.
[suspenseful music playing]
That's the rear of Las Águilas.
There are some tunnels
that lead up to the main area.
The train car I saw was there.
I guess it's their lab.
We'll find out soon.
Good luck, lawyer.
This isn't a card game, I don't need luck.
[suspenseful music playing]
[guard] Halt!
Not another step!
I'm Captain Lozano!
I brought a group of survivors!
Do you always not give a shit
about your orders?
I guess I'm like you that way.
-Nice to see you, Uncle.
-Did you bring Alarcos' answer?
As you can see I took a shortcut,
and I ran into a little problem on my way.
But you managed to get yourself here.
You're your father's son.
Let him pass.
Mm-mm-mm-mm.
The orders are that no one enters.
I don't give a shit about the orders.
See how I'm just like you?
I came with three soldiers
and some prisoners.
I sent you to the Sixth
so you could learn how to fight.
And that's exactly what I'm doing,
fighting for my men.
I don't give a shit about your men either.
You can see we're not that much alike.
You want them to enter,
they have information about your weapon.
You think I don't know?
One of them reported your adventure
to the post in Moncayo.
What he didn't know is that
we took over that post ten hours before.
Your prisoners
have no fucking idea about anything!
You don't understand
what's going on out here.
[General] You're the one
who doesn't understand.
The Russians have something similar
to what he have.
They haven't perfected it,
but it's just a matter of time.
Do you really believe
they'll think twice before using it?
You aren't in your city office anymore.
We're in a war
and I'll win it at any cost.
Despite everything,
the test has been a success.
Now we'll be wiping out the valley.
Best for you to come in
before they start bombarding it.
Try to be reasonable, Uncle.
Those men are under my command.
I gave them my word.
I can't leave them behind!
[tense music playing]
Come on, Jan.
Don't fuck around.
I'm not leaving them behind.
-Captain!
-[cocking pistol]
That's an order!
What the hell are you doing?
Follow me, you fucking idiot.
-What happened, Captain, sir?
-Good luck!
-Hey, General--
-[machine gun firing]
Fuck, I'm a fascist!
Motherfuckers, you can't trust anyone
in this country.
[General] Stupid idiot!
We'll have to delay the bombardment.
I'm calling Alarcos.
[scoffs] Forget about that.
You are no longer in charge
of the situation.
Actually, you never were in charge.
What are you saying?
I'm the one in charge around here.
And my orders will be followed.
Fucking German.
[Sergeant] I told you
it was a shitty plan.
They'll get here sooner or later.
And they won't care what uniform
they find in front of them.
[Jan] No.
They're going to bomb the area.
The airplanes are on their way.
This will all become wasteland.
Well, I'm not leaving
without making some noise.
Match.
-Got anything to blow up that den?
-I've got some siphons and dynamite.
It might work.
Where are my explosives?
I've got them.
What are you doing with that?
Turns out you were right, Captain.
I wanted to be brave…
but I guess I'm just stupid.
What are you saying?
The plaza was pretty much clear.
But not the truck.
No… Shit.
Drop that right now, soldier.
Drop…
-They have the antidote in there.
-[Decruz] Captain.
It's… It's all over for me.
But… you're a coward, Decruz.
Plus, you're still a virgin,
did you forget?
You're a good man, Captain.
But I'm not a child.
I only have a favor to ask.
I lied about having girlfriends.
So if you go to Boiro,
look for Teresita.
Tell her that ever since I left,
I never stopped thinking of her.
[sighs] I'll also try those puff pastries.
[somber music playing]
[Match] You're such a liar, kid.
I drove a pretty shitty race
at La Rabassada.
I fell in the middle of it.
When I finished,
everyone was celebrating with the winner.
There was this one brat who wouldn't leave
me alone until I signed an autograph.
-You're lying, you don't remember.
-You had a red journal.
And a blue pencil.
I kept it.
In that notebook I wrote,
"If you start a race,
you gotta finish it."
"Until the end."
"For Pablo."
[pin clicks]
[exhales]
-[guard] Halt! Don't move!
-[rifles firing]
[machine gun firing]
Oh, fuck!
-What a career.
-[Jan sighs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[hissing]
[growling]
[guns firing]
[rifle shot]
[growling]
Come on, kid, you're almost there!
[snarling]
Damn it!
What a career.
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music playing]
[zombies growling in distance]
[growling intensifies]
There's no turning back.
[growling]
[man on speaker]
Special Team, go to the north door.
Once again, to the north door.
[alarm klaxon blaring]
State of emergency has been activated.
Repeat, state of emergency
has been activated.
[men shouting in German]
[man on speaker] Repeat,
state of emergency has been activated.
[zombies snarling]
[soldiers shouting]
-What the fuck do we do?
-Find the antidote, right?
The train car has to be here somewhere.
-You don't know? Somewhere where?
-Who knows, but we gotta stop this.
[Jurel] Captain, sir!
I enlisted 'cause I look good in uniform,
but wasn't born to this world to save it.
So with your permission
I'll try my luck alone.
Don't cry, I swear I'll write you.
Rafir, let's go.
-No.
-Good luck. Salam aleikum.
May God be with you.
[officer] Alright, let's go!
Come on, come on!
Well, your master plan
is working out perfectly, fascist.
[engine revs]
I don't feel too good about this either.
My thing is racing or fighting,
not digging ditches.
Don't fuck with me, Match!
-[soldier] Come on!
-Yep, it's working out perfectly.
[zombies screeching]
Damn it! Fuck, follow me!
Let's go!
[guns firing]
-[growling]
-[screaming]
[Jan] This way! Run!
[suspenseful music playing]
[screaming]
-[growling]
-[screaming]
Wait! Where's Rafir?
Another one scared shitless.
[zombies growling]
[Jan straining]
[straining, yelling]
[gunshots]
Come on! I'll cover you!
[Priest-killer] Run! Come on!
[growling]
Fuck! This way!
-[growling]
-Damn!
[man screaming]
Fuck!
Hey, hey! They're there too!
What… Fuck!
Holy Mother of God… or whatever!
-We have to get to the lab!
-Tell me how.
This way!
[screaming]
[growling]
[pistol clicks]
Fuck it!
[Rafir] Jurel!
Allahu Akbar!
[growling]
-Rafir!
-[screaming]
[panting]
-[yelps]
-[gasps]
-Oh! You scared the shit out of me!
[muffled banging]
[groans angrily]
[sighing]
Alone at last.
What happened, did you miss me?
Ah… I was always a shitty racer.
I fell and your comrades
wouldn't let me leave.
[Jurel sighs]
Girlfriend?
Laura.
We were going to get married in May.
You bastards killed her in Lucena.
[Match] Maria.
The boy's name was Miguel. Like me.
I watched our the house collapse
on top of them during a bombardment.
There's something about them.
-They look alike.
-Fuck that, man. Mine is much prettier.
[chuckles]
Fuck everything.
EXPLOSIVES
I still have a little gift.
Long live Spain!
Wait, wait, wait!
Yours or mine?
Who cares?
The one that's left after this shit!
[both grunting]
It's this one!
Here's the plan.
You two get the antidote.
I'll get us out of here.
And how are you going to do that?
I told you, before the war,
I drove an old heap like this.
Let's go!
Son of a bitch!
What's this?
Is it the antidote?
[chuckles softly]
[in German]
Is this the antidote?
There is no antidote!
[in English] There's no antidote.
[in English] We did try several things.
But they only slow it down.
I think I did my job too well.
I conquered the final frontier.
The gates are open and there's
nothing you can do to stop it.
My work…
My work is immortal.
[SS Officer groaning]
[flesh gurgling]
[moaning]
It's…
It's coming!
Eternal life!
[gun fires]
Didn't last long, bastard.
[banging on door]
[zombies growling]
[screeching]
[screaming]
[yelling]
Damn, it got me! [yelling]
That's it. I'm fucked.
No, no, no!
[pistol fires]
[panting]
No, wait a minute!
Wait! Please! Wait, no! No!
[screaming]
You're crazy!
You cut off my hand!
I think we did it in time.
[flesh gurgling]
Here it is. I knew it.
What little imagination!
[zombies hissing]
[growling]
[steam hissing]
[grunts]
[screeching]
-Come on!
-Fuck!
[both grunting]
Get in! Quick!
[Jan] Shit!
They'll wind up breaking it.
I guess now you've finally
run out of brilliant ideas.
[chuckles] Well, I still have two bullets.
Too bad I don't have a hand anymore
to load my gun.
Are you gonna remind me forever?
You can bet on it.
-Were you thinking of kissing me?
-No! No, not at all.
It's just-- Just not the best timing.
Well, in reality,
we don't have much time left.
[growling]
[engine rumbling]
Flor, if those tales are true
about the afterlife…
then wait for me, I'm coming!
[zombies growling]
-[pistol fires]
-[horn blowing]
[bombs exploding]
[muffled explosions]
[loud explosion]
[train clattering]
[screaming]
[speaking Arabic]
The barakah!
Jan?
-Jan. Jan!
-Huh?
You cut off my hand.
[Priest-killer grunts]
[sighs in relief]
[soft music playing]
Well, here you are.
[sighs]
Where will you go now?
I'll try to cross over to France.
Fuck. I know this is
a pretty shitty country, but France?
Nothing left for me here.
Listen…
On my side, no one knows who you are.
What I'm saying is…
You can come with me.
You'd be safe here.
Jan, we don't have anything in common.
If it wasn't for this war
we would have never met.
Yeah, but the thing is
we did meet each other.
There's nothing that can
get us back together.
Fuck.
[sighs] Can't anything good
come out of this war?
Not out of this war or any other, lawyer.
You should probably get that arm treated.
[motorcycle engine starts]
Hey, wait, wait!
At least tell me your name.
[engine revving]
Seriously?
I can't keep calling you "Priest-killer"!
[dramatic music playing]
[lighter clicks]
[upbeat music playing]
[metal shearing]
[slow music playing]