Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Can you explain what a colorist is to you?
People may think a colorist designs the color scheme for a film.
To me,
it’s the position that brings a film to life.
It emphasizes the moods of the scenes.
Let’s say in sad scenes, the sky doesn’t have to be blue.
It can be moss green.
Or…
If this room is too gloomy,
I can use my magic to make it brighter.
It says here you analyze and categorize people into colors.
Try analyzing us.
Are you sure?
Give it a shot.
Tell us what you think.
All right.
A man on the far left seems lively,
yet he’s having something on his mind.
He reminds me of…
a rotten carrot orange.
As for you,
you seem calm and passive.
You give me…
a pickled cucumber green.
As for you,
you look serious.
You remind me of
a horse manure brown.
Brown like…
Brown like a horse shit. You know?
Brown like a horse shit.
I am sorry.
I talked too much.
Sorry.
Damn it!
I shouldn’t have said that.
My emotion right now is ocean blue.
Here we go again.
Emotions by colors.
Come on.
It all boils down to your skills anyway.
You’ll get it.
True.
Besides, working is stressing out.
Look at me.
I’m an assistant director.
They work my ass off like a slave.
Shoot!
The series is on.
Puen is in it.
Come on, Gyo.
You can watch the rerun.
I can’t.
I must help retweet.
This episode must be trending worldwide.
You’re too much.
Lay,
you won’t forget the gift I asked you to make, will you?
Yeah.
I will do it tonight.
Great.
I need it tomorrow.
Time to watch it now.
Bye.
What is it?
Just hold it and follow me.
Well, come on!
Hold on.
Do we really have to do this?
We do.
If they know we’re fans, we’ll be asked to wait at the exit.
But I’m a VVVVIP fan.
Therefore, I must get to welcome Puen on his first step at the airport.
Ahem!
Guys,
Puen is coming.
What?
That’s not Puen.
Guys, we’re at the wrong gate.
Puen is at a different gate.
Run!
Go!
Wait.
I need to pee.
You go ahead.
Make it quick then.
The gift is with you.
- Catch up with me.
- All right.
Are you Puen?
I am.
My friend is your fan.
She brought you a gift.
Here.
Congratulations on your international film.
Is it against the rules to give a gift to an artist directly?
No.
Just wondering if you washed your hands already.
I’m sorry.
I’ll do it now.
But I think…
It’s too late.
I’ll wash it for you and...
That’s okay.
I should wear it like this, right?
Almost right.
It should be in the center.
Excuse me.
You have a big head.
The alpaca is now in the center.
So it’s supposed to be an alpaca?
Yes.
It doesn’t look like one?
Looks more like a llama.
Did your friend draw it?
Actually…
It’s cute.
I guess the one who drew it is very cute too.
Tell your friend I said thanks.
Puen.
I drew that.
Cute.
Damn it! I forgot to wash my hands.
You were damn lucky to meet Puen up close.
Is he hot?
Yeah.
He is.
But I’m not his fan like you are.
Right now,
I’m just worried about the interview.
Wondering if I pass.
I dragged you to have fun, yet you still think about work.
You should do something else while waiting and put your mind at ease.
By the way, Joe is looking for a movie extra.
I told him you’re available.
What?
Why didn’t you ask me first?
What role?
The hero will walk in from here.
Just be a corpse and lie down.
Why do I have to be a corpse?
You can use anyone.
Stop complaining.
Here he comes.
Shit!
That is Gyo’s sweetheart Puen!
Right.
That’s why she wanted you to join this set.
So you can take lots of his photos for her.
Work first. Talk later.
Hey!
Everyone, get ready.
Sound.
Cameras.
[Mafia: The Movie]
Scene 2, cut 4, take 1.
Set and…
Action!
Hey!
Hey, wake up!
Cut! Cut!
The corpse, why are you smiling?
Are you happy you’re dead?
I’m sorry.
He’s breathing right on my face and it tickled me.
That’s okay.
I’ll be about this close.
Close your eyes.
We’re ready.
You are.
Okay. Let’s focus.
Let’s continue.
A slate, please.
Take 2.
Ready?
Set and…
Action!
Hey!
Wake up!
Cut!
Whose phone is it?
Sorry. It’s mine.
Holy shit!
BFB!
Can I please take this real quick?
Hello.
I’m with a movie set.
What?
I got the job!
Seriously?
Thank you.
Sure.
Yes!
Are you kidding me?
I know you’re a workhorse.
But you can’t bring your work here to celebrate your new job.
Come on.
Let’s go out. Our friends are waiting.
Your feet haven’t touched the sand yet.
Gyo has taken hundreds of photos while waiting for you.
Damn it.
I told you I start the job at BFB next week.
So I must finish my old tasks before that.
You’re this drunk and you can still work?
Yeah, I can.
Guys, you’re still here?
Come on. The sun is gorgeous.
I’m waiting for him.
Look!
Damn! That’s stunning.
Lay, let’s go.
This is stunning?
The sky is too pinky.
Again?
His attitude against pink.
Right.
The only pink he likes is bacon pink.
This is what you call beauty.
Look.
Any color of the sky is beautiful except black.
It’s getting dark here.
Come on, Lay.
You guys go ahead.
I’m working.
Let’s go.
Joe!
I haven’t finished!
I’m not done!
Guys, let’s take a photo.
Photo time.
1, 2, 3.
Yeah!
Lay, don’t go too far. It’s dangerous.
I know.
Let me appreciate these beautiful colors a little longer.
Lay,
get back here.
You’re drunk.
All right.
I’m coming.
Shit!
Cramp.
Help!
Tess!
You’re awake.
I was worried sick.
Your friends said you were in bad shape.
When are you going to quit causing trouble?
Last time, you hit someone with the car.
This time you got yourself into a bar fight.
You’re just--
Wait.
Who are you?
I’m not your son.
You, bastard!
Now you’re pretending to have amnesia?
Stop it. Don’t hit him.
He’s hurt enough.
Hold on a second.
I think there’s a misunderstanding here.
I get it.
This plan doesn’t work.
I…
Shh.
Just cry.
Look at you.
You must be in so much pain.
My son.
My poor son.
Don’t cry, baby.
Let’s go.
Don’t you run away.
What the hell is going on?
Shit!
Who’s that?
Excuse me.
May I take the patient out for an x-ray?
May I ask you something?
Do you believe in reincarnation?
I knew it.
You’re not Tess.
You’re someone else.
So you know?
You had an accident and woke up in a stranger's body
in a world that looks familiar but is not really home.
Am I right?
Help!
There’s a patient running away.
Anybody.
Let me go.
I’m going to find my body.
Let go!
Hello, Tess.
What’s up, my dear friend Tess?
Who are you guys?
Your daddy, maybe.
Don’t bug him.
Well, look at him.
He’s in pain.
So?
Are you feeling better?
When you’re fully recovered, we will deal with those scums who beat you.
Are we friends?
Amnesia, I see.
Your mom already told us you’d pull this shit.
Here.
A special gift from me.
Have a sip when you’re bored.
I hate to see you have alcohol withdrawal syndrome.
No.
I don’t want Dad to chew me out again.
Tess.
When did you become afraid of your dad?
Just now.
Hey!
Don’t be afraid.
We’re never golden sons anyway.
It’s good we don’t finish university in four years.
Otherwise, we’d be taking on family businesses by now.
Damn boring.
Guys.
I have a question.
What is Qooqle?
I can’t find my name there.
And where is Google?
Google, my ass.
Qooqle is the right one.
If you can’t find it on Qooqle, then you can’t anywhere else.
What about Behind the Film Bangkok Company?
Do they exist?
Is it a filmmaking company?
I’ve never heard of it.
The number one filmmaking company in this country.
Never heard of it?
Tess, listen to me.
There’s only one best filmmaking company here
and that is 26 Pictures.
And?
And, my freaking ass!
It’s your father’s company.
Are you okay, man?
Huh?
Excuse me.
May I take the patient out for an x-ray?
I asked the radiologist about you.
He said you’re speedily recovering.
Really?
I feel like I’m going crazy.
You seem to have fun with your friends.
I look like I’m having fun?
Wait.
May I ask you something?
Do you believe in reincarnation?
Absolutely.
Why?
What about dying and switching bodies with other people?
I knew it.
I was right.
You’re laughing.
You must be thinking I’ve lost it.
No. It’s the opposite, actually.
It’s just that my theory is right.
You’re not Tess.
You’re someone else.
You had an accident and woke up in a stranger's body
in a world that looks familiar but is not really home.
Am I right?
So you know?
It’s not just you who is having this fate.
Remember one thing.
This isn’t only body switching.
But you traveled between universes to be in a new body.
Before we continue,
what’s your name in the other universe?
It’s Talay.
You don’t have to speak with me so politely.
Okay, Talay.
My name is Phuwadol.
I was a male nurse in that universe.
Then I got hit by a car and my soul traveled to this universe and now resides in the female nurse’s body.
For real?
Are there a lot of people who travel between universes?
From what I’ve seen in this hospital, not more than two people a year.
But those who I haven’t found,
I think it’s a lot.
Can any of them travel back to the old universe?
I’m in a rush.
I just got a new job.
Calm down, brother.
What’s your job?
I’m a colorist.
Colorist?
Like a color mixer?
Do you make house paints?
No.
I adjust colors for films.
Pretty much like editing photo colors in applications.
So…
Will you tell me now if we can travel back home?
Can we? Well, we can.
But it’s gonna be a long story.
I will take you to a place and explain it to you there.
TWO WEEKS LATER
This is my place?
Don’t play dumb.
You have class this afternoon, don’t you?
But if you can’t, you can skip and rest.
Keep pampering him. That’s how he became a spoiled brat.
Get to class this afternoon.
Then I’ll send someone to take you to CT Scan.
You seem out of your mind.
We will leave now.
Take care, okay?
Come on, honey.
Yes?
Hey.
My dad said the CT scan is tomorrow.
Why did you come so soon?
What CT scan?
I’m just taking you to a place you should know if you are to live here.
Wow!
They’re going so slow.
Can you honk the horn?
Relax. Let them.
They’re having a good time.
Wow!
Our country in this universe allows men to get married?
Of course.
Don’t tell me they still can’t in our universe.
No.
How has our country changed then?
Nothing has.
Sidewalks are crappy just the same.
Buses are as old as dinosaurs.
But the gas is now more costly.
What we have more are the SkyTrain lines.
That’s good.
No more traffic jams then?
The traffic is still bad.
The SkyTrain tickets are so pricey.
Who would use it?
I’ve been here for eight years.
I can’t believe nothing is better.
Come on.
(Keep looking at me like that…)
And I’ll kiss till you drop.
What is this?
Our password.
People who can access this building must know the password only folks from our universe know.
But you’ve been here for eight years.
That series was only a few years ago.
I update it every year asking from those who newly join.
Come.
Come on.
[Association of Thai Citizens in the Alternate World]
Come on, Talay.
Hi, Tess.
No.
Um…
Talay!
Welcome to…
Association of Thai Citizens in the Alternate World.
How do I start?
To return to the old universe, you must first
find someone who has traveled between universes like us.
We call the person we’re looking for ‘the portkey.’
You might start with something simple like I did.
My name is Joobjang.
I’m the head of the association.
I’ve only heard of an Association of Thai Citizens in a Different Country.
Didn’t think there was one in a different universe.
Can your association take me home?
Easy there.
This is where people who have traveled between universes gather.
In case we can help each other.
Did Phuwadol give you an intro to this universe?
Yes.
According to Phuwadol, this is a parallel universe.
There are certain things that are not like those in our universe.
And I traveled between universes to live in a body of a guy named Tess.
And Tess traveled between universes to live in your body.
You two just switched universes.
What?
Then my life will be so f*cked up.
As for the question of how you travel back,
let me explain it to you.
To return to the old universe, you must first
find someone who has traveled between universes like us.
There will be something of that person that matches you.
Once you find that person, you will dream.
Dream?
Right.
Have you noticed that you haven't dreamed since you came here?
Universal travelers don’t dream.
People who usually live here can dream as usual.
If we dream,
what will it be about?
It will be a place.
When you dream about a place, you must go there as soon as you wake up.
There’s a chance for you to return home.
And…
How do we know if that person matches us?
There will be a sign.
When you found one, you will feel it.
For example, you two may share the same interest.
You may both have moles or marks in the same area on your body.
You two might also have a brief memory together but you can’t remember it.
That means
if I come to this association,
I might find that person here.
Possibly.
But there’s a 99.99% chance that the person we’re looking for is close to the owner of the body we’re in.
Even more difficult.
What if I can’t find that person?
Do I die here in this universe?
Not always.
You might be lucky the person in your body dreams and can come back.
Then you can go back too.
But if he dies,
you die too.
Come on.
Don’t make a long face.
We will help each other.
How do I start?
We call the person we’re looking for ‘the portkey.’
To find the portkey, you might start with something simple like I did.
But it will a little embarrassing.
How?
[If you know me, come say hi.]
Doesn’t seem to work at all.
Tess.
Hey.
How have you been? Long time no see.
Hi.
How are you?
Good.
But I will go to England to study by the end of this year.
I heard you haven’t graduated yet.
Well, you don’t need to hurry anyway.
Your dad is loaded.
I have a question.
Have you experienced death before?
Tess,
if I said something that offended you,
I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean to. I love you, man.
See you.
Hey! I didn’t mean it that way.
(Hello.)
(I don’t think your idea works.)
(I will try looking through Tess’s yearbook instead.)
(Talk to you later.)
Pakorn?
Hi, Pakorn.
It’s me, Tess.
You--
What the heck?
My friend, I need help.
How did you get in?
You told us the combination.
Let’s drink.
Fuse just got himself an ex.
Right.
Can we do that another time?
I’m busy today.
Bullshit!
Someone like you is busy?
Right.
We haven’t celebrated since you were discharged.
You love being in the crowd, don’t you?
Right.
Be in the crowd.
I might find my portkey.
I mean
my friends.
Are you serious?
It’s the bar where Tess got beaten up, isn’t it?
That’s the reason we’re here.
We might see them again here and finish them off.
Guys.
I got beaten up here?
Damn right.
Can’t you remember anything?
You flirted with a girl here not knowing she wasn’t available.
Her boyfriend brought his friends to beat the crap out of you.
Lucky you.
Someone nice called an ambulance for you.
And that person was nice enough to wait until the ambulance came.
Who was it?
Go away.
I can’t let you check the video.
What?
It’s just for a second.
My friend wants to know who helped him.
Relax, man.
Let me handle this.
Hey!
I’m begging you.
Please help us.
Please.
Be kind to other human beings.
Just go.
Please.
Here.
Will you help?
It’s all I have.
All right.
You have 10 minutes.
Make it quick.
Chop-chop.
Damn. I’m broke.
Look here.
There!
Hello.
Can you please call an ambulance here?
Please hurry. It’s bad.
Tess.
You’re curious about Tun. Right?
Do you know where he is or what he’s doing?
He shouldn’t be anywhere else.
There is Tun.
Hi, Tun!
Right here.
Joe!
Easy there.
Who is Joe?
I’m Pramote.
Same old Pramote.
Only he’s hotter now.
Not funny.
I’m just not wearing glasses and have long hair.
You don’t remember me now?
You asked me here because you’re curious about Tun. Right?
What is it?
Who is Tun?
What?
Tun.
Tun, aka Pakorn.
Student number 18 in class.
So Tun is Pakorn?
Right.
You normally call him Tun.
Actually, whatever questions you have, you can call him.
I did but he hung up on me.
I don’t know why.
Do you know where he is or what he’s doing?
I guess I do.
These are...
his business cards.
Hold on.
Just Pakorn’s contact.
These are all his.
What?
Yes.
Did you forget he’s a screenwriter?
So he switches jobs all the time
to get inspiration to write his script.
That’s what he told me.
Do you have any idea where he is working today?
It’s Saturday.
He shouldn’t be anywhere else.
Here.
At his older friend’s bar.
[Pakorn Aue-aungkul]
You should take them all.
Since I’ve brought them.
Here.
Tun?
He should be coming later tonight.
He won’t come now.
Look.
It’s deserted here.
Life sucks!
Relax.
Can I get a beer?
Wow.
Luxurious choice!
Beer is luxurious?
It costs several times more than wine.
A poor guy like me drinks only wine.
Beer is once in a blue moon for me.
Beer in my universe is so damn cheap.
How many cans?
Hey!
You will drink two all by yourself?
A heavyweight, huh?
This is one.
That’s two.
This is one. This is two.
So this is one. This is two…
There is Tun.
Hi, Tun!
I’m gonna go play.
What’s the hurry?
Don’t you come talk to your friend?
What’s with him?
Bartender, give me a beer.
Here.
Pay attention.
He’s the best.
♪ Just when you lay eyes on me ♪
♪ I can’t feel my heart ♪
♪ Because I already gave all my heart to you ♪
♪ I have no idea how I can live ♪
Bro.
You sure he’s the best?
The best at singing off-key.
If there’s a show searching for the most off-key singer, he wins.
Thank you.
I knew you’d run away.
Can we talk for a sec?
Hey!
Pakorn!
I don’t want to talk to you.
Damn you!
Why did you run away?
Hot-headed as always.
Who?
How did you get in here?
Enough with that amnesia joke.
I’m Thanin, your big brother.
A guy who cleans after your shit.
Why are you here then?
Dad is furious you skipped class and the CT scan.
He sent me to scold you.
Sorry about that.
I got something to deal with.
Tess.
I don’t want to order you around.
But please at least show up at the company.
Work sometimes so that Dad won’t get mad.
At the filmmaking company?
Hell yeah.
I know you don’t want to.
- But I…
- I’ll go.
Does our family really own this?
Of course.
How can I help?
Lots of people are coming to sell their movie projects.
I can only handle a few as I need to go see the editing process.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
If you’re ready, let’s get started.
You.
You two know each other?
Should be easy then.
Something like that.
Actually, you can go to the editing.
I’ll listen to his presentation.
You think?
All right, then.
Take care of it.
I’ll be right back.
What are you doing?
Preventing you from running away.
I have questions for you, Pakorn.
First,
why are you avoiding me?
Second, when I got beaten up at the bar,
you helped me, didn’t you?
If we’re not talking about the screenplay, I’ll leave.
Wait.
Answer me.
I have nothing to say to you.
Damn it.
Let go.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I said let go!
Stay away from me.
I hate you.
Shit.
This is harder than I thought.
Directed by Nuttapong Mongkolsawas
I’ll do anything to go back as soon as possible.
Have you found anyone who seems right?
There he is.
Is he the real Tun?
I think Pakorn is the one I’m looking for.
Check again if he traveled between universes like you.
Shit!
What happened last night?
To be my wife, you must endure.