Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
To return to the old universe, you must find your portkey.
Pakorn!
Stay away from me.
I hate you.
Talay.
Like to share your story?
You’ve never shared it with us.
Me?
Sure.
How do I start?
I woke up in a rich boy’s body.
His family runs a huge filmmaking company.
It matches my career.
That sounds pretty nice.
It does.
But…
They are not my family.
I have my own family,
friends,
and a dream to be a colorist waiting for me.
I’ll go to any length to get home as soon as possible.
Everyone here shares the same hope.
Have you found anyone who seems right?
There is one.
But there’s one problem.
He’s always avoiding me.
Let’s put it this way.
It’s the same as hitting on someone.
You must keep pushing and pushing.
Come on, guys.
Let’s transfer our energy to Talay.
We hope the person is your portkey.
Stop following me.
I told you I don’t want to talk to you.
But I do.
I will keep following you around until you agree to talk to me.
Oops! Amateur.
I thought you were good.
You missed.
What are you talking about?
You hit the outermost ring, you get the full score.
Look.
Hit the edge and get 10 points?
Rules in this universe are too easy.
What’s wrong with you?
Hitting the center is easy. Anyone can do that.
But if you miss the edge just a little, you get zero point.
I’ll show you how easy it is.
Give it here.
Move. I need space.
There!
If I competed under this rule, I’d be an Olympic gold medalist.
Shit!
When did he leave?
Hi, Pakorn.
You’re a cameraman today?
I’m working. I don’t want to talk.
Wait.
Shoot my photos.
Do your job.
Yes?
Hey. Hold on.
Hey!
You’re here too.
Didn’t expect to see you here. Amm said you weren’t coming.
I changed my mind.
Have you talked to Tun?
Not yet.
Don’t know what the hell is wrong.
He won't talk to me.
Surely, he is still mad at you.
I’m not surprised.
What you did to him was shitty.
Huh?
Me?
What did I do?
Whoa.
How dare you forget?
You hit on someone he liked.
Not just that.
You even dated her.
If I were him, I wouldn’t speak with you ever again.
What can I serve you today?
An iced latte, please.
Hi, Pakorn.
Wait.
You can’t run from me today.
I’m your customer.
Customer,
I’m working here.
I don’t discuss anything personal while working.
Just one question then.
Do you believe in reincarnation?
I do.
Why?
I’m a screenwriter. I must believe in anything.
Do you…
have any other reason to?
Not telling.
Come on.
We’re alone here.
No one can hear us.
Anything you’d like to tell me?
A secret you can’t tell other people.
I’m all ears.
Actually, there is.
Go ahead and tell, my friend.
This is my first day here. The coffee should taste like shit.
Damn you, Pakorn.
What’s taking him so long?
Hey!
It took you forever to come.
I’m starving.
Sorry.
There’s a guy messing with me a little but…
Forget it.
Let’s order.
Hold on.
What about the screenplay you offered to 26 Pictures?
What did they say?
I…
Well…
Um…
He sold it.
You.
Don’t be confused.
Your screenplay is bought.
I talked to my brother for you.
Wait a minute.
I’m so lost here.
Tun,
when are you friends with someone from 26 Pictures?
Sorry, I didn’t introduce myself.
My name is Tess.
A son of 26 Pictures owner.
Also a friend of Tun from high school.
Huh?
Wait.
You have a big connection.
Why didn’t you tell us?
No.
We’re not close.
Not at all.
Come on.
We are close.
Freakin’ close.
Hey.
My name is Up.
First name Preeda.
Friends call me Up-Pree.
I have expertise in writing comedy plays.
If you want comedy, let me know.
I’m the master.
And my name is Aou.
I write every genre or style.
How did you three become a team?
It’s a very long story.
Let’s make it short.
We ran into each other when trying to sell our screenplays at your father’s company in our freshman year.
We became a group since then.
Right.
We tried selling our plays to 26 Pictures.
But we never made it.
This is the first time they are interested.
Right?
Damn!
I just wanna cry.
Let’s cheers.
To our first project accepted!
Yes!
Come on.
You get the whole jar.
Cheers!
Why not raise your glass?
Come on.
Looking forward to working with you, screenwriter.
Get in. I’ll drive you home.
It’s too late to get a taxi.
Hey.
I’m sorry.
Sorry I did a horrible thing to you.
What do you mean?
Pakorn.
Pramote told me everything.
About me stealing someone you liked.
Stop following me.
I’m trying to apologize here.
I said stop following me.
You just don’t know a damn thing.
Take that stupidity to your grave.
Hey.
I’m sure Pakorn is the one I’m looking for.
I’m sensing
he’s traveled between universes like us.
He’s just afraid to tell the truth.
The best thing to do.
You check if he’s traveled between universes like us or not.
If not, you can move on
and search for someone else.
Trust me.
Hey.
Can you make the light pinker?
You got it.
Awesome.
Hey, bro!
Have a seat.
Are you here to appreciate the pink lighting I just put up?
It’s gorgeous.
No.
I’m here to see Tun.
Will he come?
No.
He said his screenplay was sold.
So he’s taking a time off to develop it with his team.
Where are they?
Do you know?
No idea.
I think they went out of town. Some place quiet.
They do this often.
And don’t bother to call them.
Because their phones…
are all with me.
They are being artists.
They said they didn’t want anything to distract them from their screenplay.
And do you happen to know how long they spend time in their hideaway?
Shouldn’t be that long.
Around a month.
A month?
ONE MONTH LATER
You keep checking your phone?
Whose call are you expecting?
I’ve been through a lot, man.
You’re being dumped.
Come on. Let’s drink.
Guys!
Right there.
Who is picking a fight?
No.
That’s your history, Tess.
Who?
You can’t remember Anna?
The ex-girlfriend you bragged to us that you stole from someone in high school.
That girl?
That’s Anna.
The one.
How dare you forget?
You hit on someone he liked.
I did?
Tess.
Hey, Anna.
How are you doing?
Doing okay.
Uh…
Tess.
I talked to Tun.
About what?
The reason I broke up with you.
The truth is I was being selfish.
Anna, it wasn’t your fault.
It’s me.
I knew Tun liked you yet I still did it.
Huh?
No?
No.
Tun didn’t like me.
He likes you, Tess.
What?
This is the reason I broke up with you.
Not only that we couldn’t get along,
but I also felt bad for Tun.
Here.
It’s on me.
You’ve been making a sad face all alone.
Heartbroken?
Not really.
I’m just shocked to learn something.
I thought he avoided me because we’re both universal travelers.
But it turns out…
he just likes Tess.
Hey.
Are you drunk?
What are you saying?
I’m all confused.
Exactly.
I’m sorry.
That’s fine.
Shit!
Holy shit!!
Let’s request a song.
It might make you feel better.
Here.
Write down.
(Dear everyone,)
(My name is Talay.)
(If you’re reading this letter,)
(that means I lost my hope to go back to my universe.)
(Farewell to all beings.)
This is a song title?
Why so long?
Pong, hello!
Hi, guys.
You’re back.
Keep walking.
Take a look at your friend here.
Comfort him.
He is falling apart here.
Comfort what?
Look.
Leave the job to Tun.
There he comes.
Is that really Tun?
Of course, he is.
I don’t know what’s happened to him lately.
The guy just keeps cool all the time.
Right?
Right. Look.
I see you’re finally back.
The stage is not taken.
And your guitar is left in the same spot.
Go ahead.
Yes!
You’re gone for a month.
You have no idea how much I missed your off-key singing.
Go on.
♪ There are millions of people in this world ♪
♪ Millions of hearts out there ♪
♪ And I’m nobody, I’m just one guy ♪
♪ Our world seems enormous ♪
When did he become such a good singer?
Let’s leave that question for later.
I’m just wondering whose song it is.
I’ve never heard of it.
Did he write it?
♪ Did it actually happen, or am I dreaming? ♪
♪ Us meeting each other in this world ♪
♪ Don’t know how to put it ♪
♪ But with all my heart ♪
♪ I believe this is… ♪
♪ A miracle that we met ♪
♪ It’s a miracle that I love you ♪
♪ It’s the greatest miracle I’ve ever witnessed ♪
♪ Oh, you are the miracle ♪
You’re not Tun, are you?
To our universal-traveling friendship.
Cheers!
Shit.
What happened here?
What?
You guys didn’t finish the screenwriting
because Tun had a car accident?
Yes.
He was driving to buy things.
A cat cut him off.
He loved that cat more than his life, apparently.
So he turned the steering wheel right to the utility post.
He was in a hospital for days.
He’s blessed to be alive.
Right, my friend?
Yeah.
After he recovered, we headed back to Bangkok asap.
We’re afraid his parents would be worried.
Yeah.
Sorry to interrupt.
I’m making a new cocktail here.
I need lab rats.
Anyone interested?
- Me.
I’ll go first.
You’re not Tun, are you?
What are you talking about?
The song Miracle you just played doesn’t exist here.
It’s from our universe.
You know.
I’m like you.
I died and traveled between universes too.
Damn! You don’t say!
You traveled between universes too?
Yes.
Shit! I’m freakin’ happy.
I’m Talay by the way.
How did you die?
I was drunk and had a car crash.
Then I woke up in this body.
I was so stunned.
I don’t even know how to go back to our universe.
Yeah. I get you.
There is a way
with conditions.
I’ll explain it to you when I have time.
Hey,
what did you do for living in that universe?
I was an actor.
For real?
Which company?
GGN.
Damn!!
That’s so dope.
What’s your name?
I might know you.
I’m not telling you.
I don’t want a die-hard fan.
Oh, please.
Being secretive for what?
Like you’re so famous.
I’m pretty famous.
Let’s do this. You call me Tun.
And call this guy Pakorn so we don’t get confused.
Fine.
Oh.
How long have you been in this universe?
Over a month.
It might not be that long, but you can ask me if you have questions.
I might have answers.
I’ll just ask you now.
Shoot.
If I want to search for something, which search engine should I use?
Judging from what you asked,
you couldn’t find Google, could you?
In this universe, they use Qooqle.
What if I want to be an actor?
Don’t go to the GGN building.
Because here,
GGN is a company that makes toys.
Yes.
If you want to be an actor, come to my dad’s company.
26 Pictures.
Which doesn’t really belong to my real dad.
It belongs to this guy’s dad.
And…
what if I have problems one day?
Who should I go to?
Me.
Fine.
I’m glad it’s you.
Let’s celebrate then.
To our universal-traveling friendship.
Drink!
Cheers.
Shit!
What happened here?
What a relief.
He still has pants on.
Why are you looking at my pants?
What happened last night?
Why did you crash here?
You drank like a fish last night.
So I took you home.
Why are we leaving?
I can drink more.
More, my ass.
Come on. I’ll take you home.
No.
I’ll stay and celebrate with you.
To be honest,
I’m so happy I met you.
Ouch!
It hurts.
Stand on your feet.
I’m taking you home.
Yes.
Home.
Let’s go back to our universe.
But how do we do that?
Can we go back if we kiss?
What?
It doesn’t work.
Let me try again.
What?
Damn it.
We’re still here.
Hey.
Talay.
I have visions of many bad things.
But can’t remember exactly.
It’s good you can’t remember.
Why?
Did I hurt you in any way?
No.
But me hurting you sounds more like it.
Stop it.
You’re giving me goosebumps.
Why did you mention it in the first place then?
I’m hungry.
Any food here?
This room was so hot last night.
Wow.
It’s weird they have cone bread here.
Oh,
but it’s pretty convenient to eat.
Tun.
Seriously.
What’s your real name?
Take a guess.
I can’t even guess what happens in my life.
I can’t guess yours.
Let me give you a clue.
My mom named me after a character in a movie.
It’s the movie that came out the year I was born.
Which is the same as yours, right?
Right.
1998.
Oh!
Are you Jack?
Titanic was a hit that year.
Wrong.
Rose then.
No.
Maybe you’re refusing to tell me because your mom likes this movie.
2499. (Dang Bireley's and Young Gangsters)
Your name is Dang.
Dang, my ass.
Besides, 2499 didn’t come out in 1998.
But I think Dang Bireley is cool.
Don’t you know the famous quote from the movie?
‘To be my wife, you must endure.’
I know.
You could’ve just said it normally.
No need to poke your face so close.
You bugged me first.
I just got a little payback.
Like I felt anything.
Do you know what the first thing I'll say to you if we meet in our universe?
What?
Dang!
Shut your mouth and eat.
They said I could get a taxi here.
Where is the taxi?
There’s none.
Come on.
You live in a fancy condo.
Don’t you have a car?
I do.
It’s in the garage.
Tess, the owner of this body, didn’t go soft on his car.
Need a tuk-tuk ride?
It’s budget-friendly.
How much to Charoen Krung Road?
Free of charge
if this man agrees to have a meal with me.
I like you.
Uh.
I’m good.
I’m already taken.
Oh, come on.
The excuse I’ve used a million times.
If you’re really taken, then where is the lucky one?
Here he is, my boyfriend.
What are you freakin’ doing, Tun?
No need to hide.
We are boyfriends.
We’ve been together forever.
Holding hands? Anyone can do that.
I dare you to kiss your boyfriend’s cheek.
Don’t do it.
Don’t.
Stay put.
- Don’t.
- Don’t move.
Okay!
I believe you.
Come on. I’ll give you a special discount.
- Thank you.
- Come on.
See?
Trust me and things will be fine.
Well, well.
I already believe you. No more sweetness shown.
Get in.
Hold tight.
My ride is fast.
If you’re scared, hug each other. I don’t mind.
Sure.
You fill in your info in this form.
It might help you find the portkey faster.
I hope they find your match soon.
Me too.
(If I can make you my wife…)
Your gear badge is also mine.
Damn!
There’s a password too?
What is this, a spy movie?
Shut up.
Get in.
Why so grumpy?
Ah, I get it now.
I need to dream about a place and go to that place.
Then I’ll be able to go back home, right?
That’s correct.
You’re right, handsome.
I just want the matching system we just built matches you and me.
Wait.
What matching system?
This.
Here.
You fill in your info in this form and it will match people with similarities.
It might help you find the portkey faster.
I will go prepare it for you.
As for me,
anything questions at all, feel free to ask.
Ask away.
Show your face.
Shit.
It asks about your favorite movie director.
Who should I input?
Just answer.
Pick the one who directed your favorite movie.
Do you like Wes Anderson?
I do.
Really?
Which of his films is your favorite?
The Grand Budapest Hotel.
Like you read my mind.
Why do you like it?
I just like it.
Have you seen Her by Spike Jonze?
I have.
I like it too.
We also match here.
Do you like the song Love by Paradox?
Does it sing…
♪ Oh dear love ♪
♪ Please look at me ♪
♪ Sometimes we meet on a heartbreaking day ♪
Am I right?
Precisely.
♪ You come in and embrace me softly ♪
Yeah.
I like it too.
Shit!!
Do you seriously like everything I like?
No.
I just said what you wanted to hear.
You seem so happy when you know we share the same interests.
It’s like you truly believe I’m your portkey.
Asshole.
I was happy for nothing.
Once the system completes,
we should know who has the potential to be your portkey.
We will meet again then.
Okay. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
We should go live our lives then.
I hope they find your match soon.
Me too.
I hope you find the right one.
See you.
Good luck.
Tess.
What are you standing there for?
Come down here and study.
Yes.
Quickly.
Why does he look confused?
Hey.
I’ve been meaning to ask.
Why is nobody wearing a university uniform?
Where on earth have you been?
Uniforms were canceled ages ago.
Why?
It doesn’t have anything to do with study, does it?
It’s good they were canceled.
Guys!
The mid-term exam result just came out.
How is it?
Kita and I pass by a whisker.
And me?
Let me check.
Wow, Tess.
You’re awesome.
Number one of the class?
2 out of 30 scores.
Damn you, Tess.
Why are you so dumb?
Just realized that?
Do your best on the final exam.
You might still have a chance.
Though it’s very small.
Yes, Dol?
What?
The matching is done?
(Wait at the stairs in the middle.)
(Your match will come see you.)
Hey.
Are you sure your system works?
I don’t feel like we match at all.
Stay put.
Eyes on me.
What’s the matter with you?
The bees.
Be still.
Stay put.
I don’t want to get stung.
Eyes on me.
Don’t look at them.
See?
They’re gone.
Right.
How about a thank you?
Thank you, Mr. Smart.
Next time, stay still when you’re surrounded by bees.
The more you move, the bigger chance you’ll be stung.
Yeah.
Here.
For you.
Hey.
Just what I want.
I’ll drink it now.
That’s it?
You said you wanted it.
I don’t want Tess’s body to get fat.
Worried about your look, huh?
Don’t use Tess’s body as an excuse.
Worried about my health.
Besides, Tess only has a small size of clothes.
This drink has no sugar.
Don’t be afraid he’ll get fat.
Seriously?
Yes.
You can drink it all.
Do it.
I bought it for you.
That’s it.
Drink it. Gulp.
Good job.
Stop that.
No.
I’ll keep knocking.
It’s annoying.
Bye. I’m leaving.
Hey!
Wait for me.
Hi, Dol.
So is Tun my match?
(Where are you guys?)
(Your matches can’t find you.)
Huh?
Our matches?
I thought Tun was my match.
(No! You have your own match.)
(I just told you guys to meet at the same place.)
So no?
No.
I bet you’re happy you’re not my match.
Who told you?
I think…
- Hello.
- Hi.
My name is Som.
I’m Tun’s match.
Which one of you is Tun?
That’s me.
Don’t use formal language with me.
We’re friends.
Just call me Som.
I’ve been here for two months already.
I’m so lonely.
Lucky us they have the matching system
that brought me to meet a hot guy like you, Tun.
Should we go?
Come on. Let’s go.
Good luck to you.
And you…
Prae.
What?
Still can’t hear you.
Forget it.
I’m Talay.
Nice to meet you.
Sure.
Okay.
Well?
I saw you have fun talking to her.
She’s the only one having fun.
She didn’t give me the chance to speak.
But my match didn’t even say a word.
I don’t think the matching system works.
Let me check.
Hello, Dol.
Are you sure your system works?
I don’t feel like I match her at all.
(Hey, it should work.)
(I was the one who submitted the data into the system.)
But I have a weird feeling.
I don’t think it works.
(If you’re not sure, there is a way to check.)
How?
(People in the association have this rumor.)
(If you and your match enter the maze from a different entrance)
(and wind up meeting inside, you might be each other’s portkey.)
Sounds like a fantasy.
Is it reliable?
(Better than not trying at all.)
This is exciting.
The walk to find the true match.
Tun.
I hope to see you inside.
Um.
So…
Should we start from different entrances?
Sure.
I’ll use this entrance.
Bye, guys.
I’ll go that way.
I’ll go in from here.
Good luck.
Directed by Nuttapong Mongkolsawas
I'm starting to lose hope of ever finding the portkey.
It's extremely difficult to match someone.
When he comes,
he comes.
Don’t tell me after spending time together,
we turn out to be each other’s portkey.
That’s not a problem.
If it’s you,
I’m okay.