It was clear that I was the first one to come.
But Linh got him, and now is Phuc.
Why not me?
Come in.
From now on, this is your house.
Yes.
Thach!
You're coming over?
Uhm.
This is Nu. She is a year younger than you.
Yes, hello Mister.
I just bought this book.
Seems so thick! Can you finish it?
As you read it with me, it won't take long.
Nu? What's the matter?
No, I'm okay.
Your leg is dislocated, isn't it?
Get on!
No way, I can go by myself.
Or you want me to carry you in my arms?
Always wait for compulsion?
Well... No girls would get on with your first ask.
Besides, I was a bit afraid.
Afraid of what?
You're very famous at school.
If any of your fangirls sees this, they'll beat me to death.
But I've got an apple in my eyes.
Huh? You have a crush on someone?
Who is she? Do I know her?
You surely do.
Who?
Never tell you!
If you love Thach,
should you be glad for his happiness?
No.
Thach belongs to me in the very first place!
Nu...
How can one-month feeling equal years of emotion?
Nu..
Calm down and listen to me.
Love is not for competition.
How could you force someone to love you?
It's your weakness.
In love, as long as you want, you'll obviously get it.
You only need the desire.
I want to have a word with you.
Has Thach proposed to you?
What are you talking about?
Not yet, then.
Thach and I are nothing to each other.
I saw you kissing him.
But so far, we're still nothing.
So just leave!
Quit your job.
Why?
Don't you see that Thach has enough of misery?
He's blind, infertile, and now getting in love with a man.
What's wrong with loving a man?
It's stupid, my boy.
He wasn't like this before.
But since the day you came, he's become that stupid.
Do you love him?
Sure.
And I'll never stop chasing him.
You love him, but you can say those bad words?
Don't you think Thach will be upset if he hears?
Let's learn for your own a way to love!
Phuc!
This is how you can call me.
You touch here,
then you dial number one.
Is it Thach calling you?
Yes.
Hello?
Hello, where are you now?
Who is that?
It's Thach.
The house's owner?
Where are you?
Where am I?
I have no idea!
You and your belongings must come to my house, now.
You're being nonsense! Coming to your house for what?
You have 30 minutes to take all your stuff and clothes here.
I have so many clothes.
You're that drunk?
Being able to recognize you means I'm not drunk.
I don't wanna say anymore.
Take your things to my house, right now.
Who the hell he thinks he is?
I think you should go there quickly.
He asked me to take all my belongings there.
Being that romantic, he must want to be under the same roof with you.
I think this thing is a bit uncertain.
He still has his job, family,
and you two's father was a politician.
He is dead but his reputation is not.
I don't know where this can go to.
Alright. Let me take you home.
Thank you.
Ah. Maybe I should go there anyway.
He gave me only 30 minutes. He'll scold at me.
OK.
Go now?
Heyy! Our motorbike is over here.
That's so?
Go!
You told me here, then where will I sleep?
Who came with you?
No one.
I heard someone else's steps.
Mine.
Come here.
Uh?
Just come here.
I also want to drink beer.
Order on Shopee, then.
I feel sleepy.
You should go back in and sleep.
Then just come in.
Fire! Fire! The house is on fire! Run, people!
Gosh, Thach! The house is on fire!
Leave here now!
Wait a minute! I can't smell anything!
How can you? People are rushing out there.
Run now! Hurry, please!
A minute!
I can't find Phuc.
He may be in the bedroom, let me call him.
Phuc is out. He has left before.
Come on! Quick, man! Quick!
Be careful!
Come on, man!
The house is burning down!
The house is on fire!
Be quick please!
Over! Thank you for participating this fire-drill of the village.
It's a fire-drill. Now let's back to our homes!
Thank you all.
Brother, what happened that everyone gets bewildered?
Our area was taking a fire-drill.
Wait!
Where is Phuc?
Come on...
Nu?
Yah?
Do you see Phuc around here?
Phuc is not here.
When I left, did you see me turning off the gas cooker?
This one... I have no idea.
Take me inside!
But...
I say take me back in the house!
Let me take you in.
Thach!
Phuc! Where are you?
Phuc!
Hi, you call me...
Why is it so smoky?
Just leave here. It's so smoky over here.
The room is filled with smoke. We should leave.
Why did you tell me Phuc had left?
I didn't know it clearly,
I just thought that he might be out.
How could you tell me without checking carefully?
What if bad thing happened to him?
Who is he that I need to care for?
I only thought of you at that moment.
You're so strange.
You're being selfish.
I have the rights to save who I want.
Why is it considered selfish?
Only not saving him can make me a selfish one?
Let's go out.
Leave me alone!
It's time to make everything clear.
Come on!
Let go of me!
Can you just stop it?
Are you okay?
There was a fake alarm.
People were flocking out.
That explains why you forgot our dish.
I'm good. It's real.
It hurts.
Tell me.
Tell what?
You didn't call Phuc out on purpose, did you?
You don't need to ask what you've already known.
You're the most stubborn person I've ever seen.
So?
You said that you had no feelings with him.
If you like him now, take him away from Thach for me, please.
Are you insane?
How many times do I have to tell you? I'm straight.
The line between straight and gay is dim.
You piss me off!
If you're straight, you must know how Thach feels more.
He was in very good condition, but then fell for a guy.
Don't you see it so nonsense?
How could you say that?
Don't take your gender as an excuse to say what you want!
There are only 2 kinds of people: good or evil.
Boy or girls is considered the same. We're equal!
I don't know and I don't even give a f*ck!
The only one occupying my mind is Thach.
Don't waste time giving me advice. It's useless.
I'm nothing to her.
Hello?
I'm listening.
Have you left the school?
If not, please buy me two ham sandwiches at the school gate.
Oh! I'm not. Let me buy for you.
But you can eat two of them by your own?
No way! See you later?
Sure.
Duy?
My god!
I forgot and asked Thach to buy for me.
You also bought the same?
Earlier, I asked him to buy for you and me.
Nu called me and luckily I was around there. So I rode there to buy.
You stay here and eat with us.
It's okay, you two can enjoy.
I'm sorry!
Don't bother me.
Come on.
It will never happen again.
You should move to leave with your mom.
She has moved to the South for years. It's quite near my parents' house.
I and mom can take care of you when you're there.
I really can't know how to live if that case really happens to you.
You're still in contact with my mom?
Because... I adore her.
Then you mean...
That thing can happen to Phuc?
No. It’s not what I mean.
I mean if you move home, we can take care of you and make sure nothing will happen.
And... Phuc will be safe.
Actually, this is also because of me.