Phuc!
I boiled some water in the kitchen.
Get me a glass of water, please!
Yes!
Ouch! It's too hot!
What's wrong with you?
I got burned by boiling water!
Why are you suddenly scalded like that?
Ouch! It hurts me so bad!
Phuc!
Bring me some ice!
Let me see your wound!
It's so painful!
Put your hands in there! It keeps you not blistering.
Does it still hurt?
It hurts so much!
So painful!
Please try a little more!
Where does the smell of medicine come from?
Is anyone sick?
No, it is!
What's the matter with you?
I got nothing!
I feel your hand is hot.
I'm fine!
You thought I could see nothing,
so you ignored my concern.
Give me your hand!
It's hurt!
Why did you say you got nothing?
But now you suddenly show it to me!
Is it so painful?
Does it still hurt?
Yes, it does!
Phuc!
You think when loving someone, what will they be like?
How do you know I'm here?
Because of your fragrance.
Too aromatic is also an inconvenience.
You still don't answer my question.
Well...
They will want to talk, stick by their lover,
and want to see them.
I've always felt something strange inside of me.
I got angry easily!
Every time I knew that person was with me,
I became irritated.
Bit of a mixed blessing.
You might have late puberty.
It's successful puberty.
Hey, you...
I have no boyfriend.
I also don't put salt in your pasta.
So don't be mad at me!
Who got mad at you?
There!
It's exactly that face and that voice.
If these expressions aren't anger, what could they be?
You've fallen in love with someone, haven't you?
Do you think who I can love?
Well, if your lover is a girl, she is Nu.
If your lover is a boy, it's none other than me.
How confident you are!
I'm not pretty, but I'm very confident.
Do you want me to help you?
With my current situation,
hearing that person's voice makes me happy.
If we can do that, it's great!
Give me the phone number! I will call!
No need!
Why not?
I'm hearing...
Don't joke with me!
It's an important matter of a lifetime.
Let you be! I don't lie to you!
Can you walk alone?
I got there!
Hey!
Uh? Duy?
Do you want to get a ride?
No, I don't! I wanna take a walk and go home later.
Well, let me go with you!
Yes!
Does your hand still hurt?
It's much better!
Nu didn't do it on purpose! Don't take it to heart.
Did Nu and you grow up together?
It's a kind of childhood sweetheart , isn't it?
I'm the son of a concubine.
That's why Thach speaks with a northern accent,
but I speak with a southern one.
So you don't live with your father, right?
Previously, my dad came here for a business trip.
Then he met my mom and fell in love with each other.
Boom! After 9 months and 10 days, I was born.
He is a politician.
It's not good when having a concubine and stepchild,
so they didn't register their marriage.
After a while, my mom passed away,
so I came here to live with Thach.
After that, I studied abroad,
and my dad also passed away.
Mr.Thach is so good!
Since the day our dad died, he took care of everything.
He shouldered our relatives.
But when getting into an accident, no one visited him.
How long has he been in an accident?
It's been two years.
At that time, there was also our sister in the car.
She's the same age as Nu.
It was an extremely difficult time for Thach.
He can't see anything and can't walk.
That changed all his life.
I was still in the US at that time
so I couldn't care for him.
Fortunately, it has been for Nu.
But things don't seem to get any better!
How about Thach's mom?
I have never met her before.
She broke off with Thach
because he was dating Linh.
She didn't want to accept him as her son anymore.
Since his accident, hasn't she come back here yet?
Yes, she has!
But Thach didn't know it!
Anyway, he is still her son.
Yes!
She couldn't abandon her son!
Nu returned home to care for him for 2- 3 months.
When he got better,
she came back to continue studying.
How about Linh? Has she come back here?
Yes!
But she came back here for money.
When Thach was hospitalized,
she took care of him until he woke up.
She disappeared after 2 -3 months at home.
Then she ran out of money and returned here.
She used the excuse of
caring about him to ask for money.
Thach is only 30 years old,
but he's very talented.
What?
That face and body belong to a 30-year-old?
You react as if it's the first time you know it!
What time do you start your work?
Just a little more!
But now, I have to go to the park to see Nu.
What does she see you for?
I don't know!
So let me take you there!
No, I can go by myself.
Get in! Let me bring you there!
Yes!
Phuc! I'm here!
I'm so sorry!
The teacher let me leave too late.
No problem! Just sit here!
Yep!
What did you call me here for?
Uhm...
I hope what I'm about to say won't make you sad.
Just tell it to me!
Could you quit your job?
I also stayed here, so let me care for Thach.
But did he allow me to do that?
Yes, he did!
I told him already, and he agreed!
Thank you for caring for him for the past 1 month!
It's my duty!
Ah? Are you going to leave right now?
Nope! I'll come to his house to get my stuff.
Get your things?
Well, just go home! I'll have the deliverer give it to you.
I can go by myself.
Ah... Let me go with you.
Yes!
Uhm! Let's go!
How about the restaurant?
Why did you suddenly ask that?
Want to shave your head? Let me do it for you!
Why did you ask me to do that?
Uhm... Because lately, I felt the weather's too hot.
I wanna shave my head first,
but I'm scared of being ugly.
That's why I shave your head for a trial.
Have you just come, Phuc?
It's me, Nu!
Ah! I just think it's Phuc!
Let's clean up your stuff! Go!
Thach!
Is it Phuc?
I'm getting in there to take some CDs.
But you just lent them to me?
- But now...
- I also want to borrow it!
It's an introductory linguistics document.
What do you borrow it for?
I'll take it and leave immediately!
Where are you going?
Nu said that you let me quit my job.
I've said that when?
Would you say that because I came back here,
you didn't need a carer anymore?
Did I say that?
Yes, you did!
Ah! That day, Duy also heard it, right?
Did I say that, Duy?
I don't remember it!
So do I!
I remember that day, I was not drunk.
That night, we drank up the bottle of wine.
Maybe I said nonsense things.
Don't take it to heart! Just keep doing your job!
Yep!
So let me come in there to clean up!
One day, I'll treat you
the way people pluck a bird's feathers.
No matter what you're mad at, don't take it out on plants.
I think throwing rocks into the water
seems to make you happier.
Then I will jump down there, right?
Why did you let Phuc quit his job?
I feel threatened!
Phuc does nothing with you!
He's just like Linh,
the poor living on others.
How can you say that?
What? You love him, huh?
No, I don't!
Brother!
Did you say that when I was in trouble, you'd help me?
Is it right?
Yes!
Please love Phuc for me!
Then flirt with him!
You will flirt with him
and keep him away from Thach for me,
is it okay?
You think what my feelings are
that anyone can get it easily?
It's not what I mean!
Don't mind who my brother loves and wants to go with.
How can you stop two people from falling in love?
But I love Thach!
I don't know what to do now!
It seems that Thach fell in love with Phuc!
I don't know what to do! Please help me!
Please help me, bro!
Thach is still in love with girls, right?
He likes Phuc just because
he wants to try something fresh.
Is it right?
I won't leave you at peace if you say any words.
Suddenly, I think that
Linh's departure is related to you, right?
I have my own eyes,
so I can see who he is.
I have a heart,
so I can sense for myself
who is good and bad for my brother.
I'm sorry! I can't help you with this!
His face is still as obnoxious as
when I first met him.
It's okay! He'll get angry if you keep asking like that.
God! If he says he had a boyfriend, I'll laugh to death.
Okay! Let's meet at the coffee shop!
Thank you!
It's yours!
Thanks a lot!
Do you know the Rio coffee shop?
Yep?
I'm going there too!
I didn't say I'd go with you.
Hey, bro! Can I ask you this question?
You say your dish is only for high-class guests, huh?
And people like us can't try it?
Oh! You are right!
We have no money,
but dishes you cook
are just the food of poor people.
Stop being arrogant! You're not better than anyone!
You are just the one who cooks food.
There is no such thing as art here.
Who do you say is arrogant?
It sure is! If you've taken the interview,
please cooperate with me!
One day, I'll force you to cook for me!
Leave me out!