You should move to leave with your mom.
She has moved to the South for years. It's quite near my parents' house.
I and mom can take care of you when you're there.
I really can't know how to live if that case really happens to you.
You're still in contact with my mom?
Because... I adore her.
Then you mean...
That thing can happen to Phuc?
No. It’s not what I mean.
I mean if you move home, we can take care of you and make sure nothing will happen.
And... Phuc will be safe.
Actually, this is also because of me.
Let me do it.
Where's Duy?
He's at the restaurant. He's coming home at late night.
And Nu?
She went back to her parents' home.
She'll be back the day after tomorrow.
You can take rest early today.
Me... How about...
D*mn it! Even you want to laugh at me?
Why are you still here? I told you to leave early.
Or do you want to stay and see how miserable I can be?
You told me to move in here.
I've ended my rental contract with the landlord.
Where else could I go when you say that?
Pick up those books.
Yes.
What time is it?
It's 5 P.M.
Let me hold it for you.
Are you laughing at me?
I'm not!
What clothes did I just take?
You took a shirt and a pair of pants.
You're lying.
I'm not lying!
Here.
The weather's cool now, so I changed other pants for you.
Is that your phone?
Yes. I put it on the table in the living room. I'll go get it.
Let me get it. You should eat.
I think the caller has canceled it.
Give me the phone.
They're calling again.
I've tapped "Answer".
Hello?
Why are you calling me?
Leave.
We have no...
I'll go out and talk to Linh for a while.
Let me lead you.
No need. I can go on my own.
Hello, bae!
Let me open the gate for you.
Phuc forgot to lock it again!
My darling!
Let go!
Leaving you made me realized that your embrace is my safest place.
Linh!
You don't love me anymore?
What do you want?
I want us to be together again.
This is your last chance.
If you want this to be the last, you wouldn't be out here to see me.
Drop your act!
Delete all of our photos.
You came out here just to want me to delete them?
Yeah.
You really don't love me anymore?
I want us to get back together.
I and you have no love for each other anymore.
Thach.
Delete the photos.
Linh!
Why are you here?
Get back inside.
How long do you think you can bear him?
A normal person spends his life taking care of a blind man.
He even needs help when he urinates or takes a bath!
Human all wants a normal love life.
We want to kiss, hug and hold hands.
Do you intend to do everything by your own?
Look at him!
He can't even tell where you're standing!
How could he find you lips to kiss you?
About what you feel, whether you're happy or sad,
even God can't help him to see it!
Just shut up! That's enough!
I don't lie
I just wanted to give you an advice
and to torment this selfish man, also.
I heard it enough. You should leave now.
Can I ask you this, Phuc?
Have you ever wondered that
one would love you more or less if he sees who you truly are?
Are you done causing troubles?
We used to love each other so much.
You chased me away whenever you liked.
You could scold or hit me. You didn't respect me!
How could I feel safe when I was around you?
Don't think that I didn't know about your affairs.
Don't you ever show up in front of me again!
Leave me alone!
Where are you two goi ng? Stop!
You... Stop!
You're a blind and broken man!
You will never be happy!
Phuc will leave you soon!
No one can love you like I do! Thach!
I'll wait and see how long can you and Phuc be happy together!
Don't keep her words in mind.
I don't think much about it.
Eat your food.
Thach.
Do you have feelings for Nu?
But... You said she was very important to you.
You grew up together.
How can't you have feelings for each other?
I told you that I had a close sister.
Sleep more. It's still early.
Can I ask you this?
I know what you are going to ask.
My answer is "Go back to sleep".
I've thought so much about it.
Nu came to you first.
And I'm... just someone who came latter.
Me, you haven't even seen my face yet.
Can just feelings make you love me enough?
Have you ever loved a boy?
Have you ever loved someone without seeing their face?
After all, maybe, sexuality and appearance are two most important things.
It feels so vague to me.
Like, there are people who were in love for years still broke up.
Let alone that you have never seen my face.
But, when you called me to come your place,
all my questions just disappeared.
Dear.
Do you really have feelings for me?
You said you used to  really love Linh, too.
How's it going between you and Thach?
It's been okay.
Hey. Yours is really big!
Yes?
It's so much bigger than mine!
Yours is big, too.
Should we use a ruler to measure them?
It's faster to measure by our hands.
Measure what?
What are you doing in front of me?
Nothing
I'm blind, not deaf.
Why are you angry?
The person I like is doing something shady with someone else.
Can you like that?
We we talking about our calves, mister!
Your calves?
What did you think we were doing?
I didn't think about anything.
Do we have any fruits?
I want to eat.
We do.
Duy.
Yes?
Help me delete the photos.
Put it there. I'll do it later.
Right now, please.
Okay.
Thank you.
How long did you study abroad?
I started since my second year.
It's been 4 years til now.
Three-second rule! It's safe!
Yeah, it is!
When I was a kid, I dropped a whole rice pot!
But my dad didn't scold me.
Where's Duy?
He has a business at the restaurant.
Come sit next to me. Let's watch a movie together.
Yes.
Sit here to watch and tell me.
Okay.
Let's watch movies on my phone.
What movie do you want to watch?
"It".
"It"?
Sounds strange to me.
Let me search.
A horror movie?
Yes. It's horror.
You should watch it alone. I still have homework to do.
Who will tell me the plot if you leave?
I'm afraid of ghosts!
Try it! I haven't watched a movie for so long.
Okay...
Oof! He jumped off the building!
Who jumped off?
The zombie!
But he's alive!
How... What is jumping off a building then alive?
Uh... This guy is immune!
You said we'd watch a romance.
But, I love watching zombies!
Can we watch something lighter?
The characters just stand still and talk.
Just keep quiet so I can watch the movie.
Today we had chicken livers, not tiger livers.
How dare you raise your voice at me?
Keep silent and let me watch this movie.
Don't you care about me?
Nah!