- Come back and work for me.
- About going back and being your chef,
I don't think so.
So I have a new job vacancy for you.
And it's only for you.
(Partner Application Form)
Tan, I have changed.
I don't love you anymore.
This is all I can do for you.
Please take good care of yourself.
Stay with me a little longer.
I want to talk to you.
Let me compose myself first.
What are you going to talk to me about?
Because I don't want to mix
my feelings right now
if you're going to talk about work.
Oh, come on.
What I said the other day
that I don't have feelings for you,
Actually,
I didn't mean it.
I was just afraid
people will think that
I had to break up with him
because I cheated on him.
You don't have to care about
what people say.
And in fact,
it's just my unrequited love.
If there is anyone to blame,
the person should be me.
Why are you still waiting?
I don't think
I have given you any hope.
Because I care about you.
And it's frustrating to see you upset
because of him,
when I can treat you better.
I appreciate that.
You have made me realize
that my relationship with him is toxic,
and no matter how hard I try
to hold onto it,
I have to let it go eventually.
But I haven't done anything.
Yes, you have.
Oh, there's one more thing
I want to tell you.
I don't love him anymore.
The relationship between him
and me is over now.
Does that mean you are available?
And I can start hoping
for you to love me, right?
Hey, answer me.
Gosh, I'm so sleepy.
- I can barely open my eyes.
- Teng!
I think I need a rest.
Let's talk later.
The restaurant is closed tomorrow,
and you can rest as much as you want.
Teng! Wake up and talk to me!
Fine, I'll be leaving then.
I'll ask you again
when I'm back to work.
If you don't have a plan for tomorrow,
Let's go on a trip together.
Let me know what time
you want me to pick you up.
Eh?
He's gone?
Gosh!
- What are you angling at?
- No, but you deserve this.
For pretending to be sleepy!
Now, answer me.
- Why pretend to be sleepy?
- I was really sleepy.
- No, you pretended so.
- But you also startled me.
How childish you are!
Hey!
Why do you come back here?
Didn't you have to rest?
I come to see you.
And I have something to show you.
Wait here.
What are these? Your collection?
I constantly bought new watches
because I thought I had lost them.
But I found each of them later.
So you have kept them all in here.
Your are quite forgetful, though.
Sometimes I'm too busy with work,
forgetting where I put things.
So this box is like
a Lost and Found department
where we store
the guest's left behind items.
Because they will look for it
until the find it if it means for them.
Seems like you are good
at finding things.
I thought I'd lost you, Poon.
Don't disappear from my life.
I don't think I can find
someone like you again.
I'm really sorry,
but I didn't know what to do.
I didn't have a job.
I didn't have money.
I didn't have a place to stay,
and you also pushed me away.
Actually,
I wanted to ask for your help,
but I acted opposingly
to what I thought.
I'm sorry too.
That I wasn't there for you
on your hardest day.
I've been through a lot
and I'm stronger now.
It's okay.
You will always have me by your side.
I will take care of you.
Hey, tell me.
Why are we at the joss house?
Well, you have had
a lot of tough recently.
And I want you to get some good things.
I make a wish for you too.
- You wish for me?
- Yeah.
What do you wish?
I wish for you to find someone
who sincerely and genuinely loves you.
Someone who will take care of you
and cherish you.
And most importantly,
he must be able to cook you food.
Oh...
With such qualifications,
I don't think he would exist.
Don't knock it till you try it.
If you find him, love him,
and he loves you back,
I will, let's see...
I will let you cut my topknot.
You said it yourself.
- I will cut it with my own hands.
- Not right now!
- You can't cut it right now!
- But you said it.
Yes, but not now. Can't you just wait?
What are you doing?
Don't tell me you can read a palm.
Yeah, I have studied some of it.
Fine, since we are here
relying on some supernatural,
Tell me about my future.
This is the line of life.
This is the line of heart.
And this is the line of relationship.
Your ex-boyfriend isn't your soulmate.
See? the line tears apart.
Hey, are you just saying it randomly?
No, I'm serious!
The line tells me
you have just met your soulmate.
Who?
I don't think I have met anyone.
Are you sure?
Yes, you have met him.
Only you just haven't realized.
You don't have to stand
this close to me.
Are you shortsighted?
Do you want to get eyeglasses?
I stand this close
because I want you to see me
and how frank I am.
Stop it. Let's go home.
Wait, can I borrow your pen?
The one you always have with you.
Why do you want it for?
Here.
Eh?
Beautiful, eh?
Seriously?
I think from now I have to call you
Mayom, the sorcerer.
I'll wait and see
if it will be as you said.
Of course.
I just recited the incantation on you.
You and I will be inseparable for life.
I don't know when Mr. Athip will find
a new head chef.
Tian, ​​I already know
who is going to be the head chef.
- Hey, is the soup ready?
- Yes, right away.
- Can I have some chilli?
- I'm working on it.
- Put in the carrots first.
- Please.
- Just a moment.
- Wait. I'm doing it as fast as I can.
Oh, but I didn't rush you at all.
Hello everyone.
- Hey, Poon
- Hello, Poon.
I miss you so much, Poon.
We have been waiting for you every day.
- I want you to come back.
- Yeah.
I miss you guys too.
Today I have a day off,
so I'm dropping by.
How are you doing?
You sacrificed yourself to protect us,
but we couldn't do anything for you.
Mr. Athip told me about how you guys
confessed to him,
so he understand me now.
Poon, tell us everything.
Because I heard that
you are working with Mayom now.
- How come you ended up working there?
- Right, tell us.
Firstly, I planned to sell Papaya Salad
at the stall in front of my house.
- But I...
- Hold on, Poon.
I have to check on the ingredients.
- But what?
- But the landlady,
- she has already sold...
- Oh gosh!
My goodness, Ping!
I'll be right back.
Hey, what happened?
What she did?
Apparently, task delegations
didn't help at all, right?
I know.
At this point, we only take
each problem as it comes.
We really need a head chef,
and I don't know
when Mr Athip can find a new head chef.
- Pan, come over here.
- Alright.
What is it?
A new head chef?
Who should it be?
Peekaboo!
Welcome back, Poon!
Even if I know it's just a visiting.
- Hello, Taywich.
- Hello, Poon.
Are you jealous? Oh my, really?
I still remember how you guys
disliked each other, though.
By the way, I heard he even needed
to go to the hospital.
Oh, uh, it's my bad.
No, not yours, Poon. It's his.
I mean, was that the only way
you have come up with?
You didn't care about
your stomach at all.
Enough about us. How about you and Amy?
Hey, I'm rooting for you.
How come the topic is suddenly changed?
I'll pick her up from the airport
after this.
I think I almost win her heart,
though she plays hard to get.
- Hey Pong, isn't it ready?
- Wait. It's boiling now.
- Can I pass me a fish sauce?
- Put the pounded chilli in first.
Oh my, your kitchen is so chaotic.
Still can't find a head chef?
Hey, taste it.
- Is it good?
- You haven't added sugar, right?
- Ouch...
- Oh, my.
Oh my god, you tripped over again.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Thank you so much for picking me up
from the airport
and taking me to my favourite
restaurant.
It's my pleasure, Amy.
How long will you stay in Bangkok
this time?
Why do you ask?
Because I will book a flight
and go to Chiang Mai with you.
Goofy.
Menu's here, Amy.
Oh, I didn't know
they serve Papaya Salad now.
It looks appetizing.
Well, that's an old menu.
I'm sorry for that,
but we don't serve it anymore.
Oh, what a pity. It's actually
our favourite dish, you know.
- Yeah.
- Well, it's because...
we still can't find a replacement
for the old chef.
I know it has never been easy
to find a skilful chef.
But you are also skilful!
Otherwise, you wouldn't own
a restaurant.
It's just that I want to try
something new.
would you care for today's
recommended menu?
We have Fish Paneang Curry
and Scallop Spicy Salad.
- No, thank you.
- Alright.
I'd like to have
your all-time recommended menu.
Great!
- I'll cook it for you.
- Thanks, chef.
Here they come. Thank you.
- They look so good
- I know.
Hang on!
Let me help you.
I didn't take care of you at all
while you were there.
I must say I feel bad for him.
If only the competition rules
benefited his expertise a bit more,
I'm sure it would be more exciting.
Eh?
Tay, what are you doing over there?
How come I have overlooked him?
Tian is going to have to pay us
some referral fee.
What do you mean?
You made me lunch?
Well, I'm hungry just right.
Hey, what are you doing?
What if other people see us?
So if we are somewhere more private,
I can do it, right?
You can't neither way.
You have made me forget
what I wanted to say.
Take your time to recall it.
I won't be going anywhere.
Whoa.
Let's eat lunch, Athip.
Let me feed you.
Why does it take so long?
Because it's very hot.
Second thought, no.
I think it needs more flavours here.
I'll season it for you.
Have a taste.
Is it spicy?
- Isn't it spicy?
- No.
Okay, if you find it delicious,
eat more.
I thought you said it isn't spicy.
It'd be great if you could cook for me
every day.
You know I can't.
I have to work at Teng Nueng's.
Aren't you going to change your mind?
I'd rather want you
to work here for me.
I already have my plan.
After working with Teng Nueng,
I realize that
it isn't only about skills
but I have to gain
extensive experience too
if I want to own a restaurant.
You want to own a restaurant?
I've been dreaming about it
since I was a child.
It has to be original and represent me.
A place where I can create
my own recipes and menus
that I can make a profit from.
I'm sure you can do it.
Oh, I remember now.
I was about to recommend
a new head chef to you.
Hey, Tian!
I know who is suitable to be your chef.
I mean the head chef.
Who?
- Chef Pipob!
Chef Pipob?
Do you want to talk to me?
Do you aware that I'm looking
for a new head chef?
I will ask my chef friends to see
if anyone wants the job.
Let's cut to the chest,
The person I'm interested in is you.
I have checked with my friends
whom you have worked for,
they all felt regret when you resigned.
I didn't get a promotion
after being a head chef for many years.
And my job was stuck like that.
So I decided to start my own business.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm going to offer you a food
and beverage executive position.
But I have one caveat here.
You will have to train my chefs to be
a new head chef within a half year.
An Executive, you say?
Yes, and it's a critical position
for the hotel.
But I believe that you can do it.
How about this restaurant?
I mean I built it from scratch.
To be honest,
I kind of regret abandoning it.
I also have a solution
for your restaurant.
Hello, I have arrived.
Excuse me, are you looking for someone?
I have an appointment with Mr. Athip.
- Hello, Pipob.
- Hello, Mr. Athip.
Pirada, this is Pipob.
Acting executive of the food
and beverage department.
Please come in, Pipob
Yes, Ping, I have to tell her.
Ping!
Really?
What?
Seriously?
Everyone, here is Chef Pipob,
Acting Executive of the Food
and Beverage Department.
He will start working with us
as the Head Chef of Thai Kitchen.
I'm pleased to meet
and work with you guys.
Next week, I will hold a welcome party
for chef Pipob.
And you guys will be responsible
for the food at the party.
This is the first task you will work on
as a team.
- Acknowledged.
So do your best.
See that box? Have a look at it
and tell me what's inside.
Thank you very much.
It's just a document from Tankhun.
He remains a restaurant partner,
and I still need his signature
for financial purposes.
You don't have to explain it to me.
I trust you.
Well, I just want you to know.
So you can be sure
I have nothing hidden from you.
Well,
did you miss me this morning?
- Go on with your chilli paste there.
- Hey, come on!
Didn't you just say that...
Jeez.
Hey.
Are you here only to win his heart?
If I don't start now, then when?
Right, I hope you success soon.
Mayom.
Hey!
Listen to me!
There will be a welcome party
for the new head chef.
So is it Chef Pipob you mentioned?
Yeah, I think it fits him.
By the way, will you join the party?
I don't think so.
I mean, I don't work there anymore.
Mr Athip wants to thank you
and Teng Nueng for helping me.
So he asked me to invite you.
Hey...
Are you going or not?
Here I find you a reason
to invite Teng Nueng.
Just ask him.
Fine, I will ask him then.
Good, man.
Take it to Chef Mayom.
You are so adorable today.
Thank you.
Oh, everybody is here.
Yeah!
So Tian really approached him,
and he agreed to take the position.
Amy, give me credit too.
I was the one who recommended
Chef Phipop to him.
Alright.
You are good at everything, Tay,
except for your own stuff.
I don't see you making any move.
Are you giving me a hint about us?
- I...
- Chef Phipop!
- Hello.
- Hi.
Congratulations.
- Do you remember me?
- Of course,
you are my regular customer.
So you won't be
at the restaurant anymore, right?
Well, kind of.
But isn't your restaurant on the rise?
So who's going to take care of it?
You have to ask Mr. Athip
regarding the matter.
If you don't mind,
I'll go take care of my guests.
- We don't mind.
- Please enjoy the party.
Sure, see you around.
- Hang on.
- Eh?
- Why ask Tian?
- Well, I don't know either.
- Don't you think it's weird?
- Of course, it is.
He didn't tell me anything.
- You don't know anything?
- No, I don't.
- Amy, watch out!
- Ouch!
Hey, don't, Amy, don't.
- Oh, does it hurt?
Yes, it hurts.
They just didn't look at
where they were going.
You are dress-up,
so don't get cranky and ruin it.
- It hurts so bad.
- Let's go, Amy.
Let have a seat over there.
- Ouch.
- Does it still hurt?
- Yes.
- Be careful.
- Ouch!
- Oh, easy.
- Oh, no, Amy
Why don't you wear comfortable shoes?
Well, this pair of shoes are beautiful.
Ouch...
Damn, it's hard to walk in the heels,
and now it's pinching my feet.
Hey.
What are you doing, Tay?
I'm embarrased.
Why are you embarrassed, Amy?
They all are our friends.
Abracadabra!
Thank you, Tay.
- I'll do it.
- Here's the reason.
Your shoes are too big for you.
That's why you always trip over.
High heels will pinch your feet badly
if they are too fit,
but they complement your feet more
when sizing up.
I will buy you some shoes
that fit and make you beautiful.
Speaking of being more beautiful,
I always take you as I find you.
Moerover,
you are already beautiful for me.
Hey, Tay.
What are you going to do?
Isn't it too fast for us?
- Here.
- Aw.
An ankle bracelet?
- Wow, it's so cute.
- Do you like it?
I know it fits you.
Thank you very much.
Don't kneel down next time.
Come here and sit properly.
Well, I bought you an anklet.
So I have to put it on your ankle.
Do you want me to put it on your wrist?
or around a finger?
Are there anything
that is put on a finger?
Yes, of course.
Think about it, Amy.
Oh, you mean earrings?
How about this?
I will tell you if you
agree to be my girlfriend.
Hey, Tay.
Why do you squeeze in?
There is a lot of space there.
Will you be my girlfriend?
You acted so straightforwardly earlier,
but now you seem so crafty.
Move over. There is a lot of space.
I don't see why you have to squeeze in.
Please.
Come on, move over. Go over there, go!
Isn't the party is held at the pool?
Why are you here? It's about to start.
An urgent work comes up,
so I have to check the clip first.
Can you check it for me?
I need to check the file too.
I'll leave it to you then.
Hello! Welcome to the special episode
of Kin Kub Teng.
I'm not going to review any food today.
But I'm going to give a review
on a person.
Without further ado,
This is the meaning of his name
Tadah!
Star Gooseberry.
And it also implies his personality
because the first time I met him,
he was so harsh and astringent.
But he also has sweetness hidden.
This guy is very commitment
and doesn't easily give up.
even if he knows how things
will not be possible for him.
And he literally showed me that
if a person puts an effort
into doing something,
people will see it eventually.
Or at least, I can see
all of his efforts.
Usually, I'd give a star rating
when I do a food review, right?
It applies for him too.
Let's see how many stars
he will receive.
I must say every time I was in danger,
or when I felt sad and crying,
he was always there for me,
accompanying me and taking care of me.
I think you better keep your mouth
to do something else.
Haven't you said you want stars
from me?
I'll teach you how to make it...
- I'll get even with you!
- Hey!
What are you doing?
Can you stop enchanting people?
It's him again?
He aggrieved you again, right?
I'll make sure you will never
get a chance to reconcile with him.
Thank you
for giving a newcomer a chance.
He has been dedicating himself to me
but he never asks for anything
in return.
I can't believe such a person
really existed.
Judging from what he's done for me,
I'm sure that he is made for me.
Does it mean a full-star rating
reviewing me like this?
Just listen to it.
I hear it now.
What do you hear?
Will you be my partner?
Oh, the weather is refreshing.
Let's try this.
I want to be with you like this forever.
How about the party?
Don't you have to welcome guests?
Yes, but before that...
- Can you do something for me?
- Do what?
Do you see that box?
Have a look at it
and tell me what is inside.
Don't entice me, I'm not a kid anymore.
Don't be stubborn, boy.
Come on.
What is this?
Didn't you say you wish
to own a restaurant?
Please let me fulfill your wish here.
What are you playing at?
Don't joke around like this.
I already bought it from Pipob.
We can go check it out
and redecorate it together.
Hey,
isn't it a little bit too much?
I thought you said you aren't a kid.
Why are you crying now?
Athip.
Let's make it
the first step of our life together.
From now on,
I'll always be by your side.
and take care of you.
I will never forget today
when you show me how much you love me.
Thank you, Athip.
For being everything to me.
And next, let's meet...
Our Thai chefs gang!
Chef Pipob,
we bring you a new chef suit.
- Put it on.
- Yes, put it on.
Put it on!
Okay, put your arm in.
Way to go!
Put it on, man.
Cool!
Yeah, that's way to go.
Let me see how cool you are.
Oh, wow! You are super cool!
How about we take a picture together?
Of course! Where shall we stand?
Come on, everyone.
Here's the spot for the beauty.
- Let me check the picture!
- Here.
Oh my god!
Look, it's Mayom!
Oh, man. I mean, your friend is a stud.
Not a friend, he is my partner.
Wait, let's not forget
Poon and Mr Athip too.
Don't be too friendly
because I'm very possessive of you.
I can't be friendly at the party too?
What's with you?
Go ahead.
I have nothing to hide from you anyway.
What are you doing?
Hello, everyone.
Thank you so much for watching,
and thank you for your support
on the channel.
Today I want to let everyone know
that Teng Nueng and I
are officially partners.
- You can't be any sweeter, Mayom.
- Seriously?
I don't see any reason to hide it.
Well, well, what's going on here?
Hey, Tian.
So how about you guys?
Oh, I'm delighted to tell you that
Amy and I are in relationship now.
Oh, no, you just broke my heart.
Don't worry, I still go
and see you like always
- She takes it serious, you know?
- How about us?
(I'm just kidding.)
The food is really delicious.
Let's go eat, everyone.
Enjoyt it.
- Do you know what is it called?
- Tell me.
...and thank you for your support
on the channel.
Today I want to let everyone know
that Teng Nueng and I
are officially partners.
And  I will make sure
you will never get
to reconcile with him.
Now, it's time.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
After the redecoration,
my restaurant,
The Spiciest by Chef Poon,
is ready for business.
The guests I have invited today
have contributed a lot
to the restaurant.
Wow!
I have promised to buy you some shoes.
If it wasn't for Taywich's
recommendation,
I probably wouldn't have a chance
to be a chef at the PK Hotel.
And without Amy,
I wouldn't even know
how I actually feel about Athip.
So cute!
- Yes, you are so cute.
- I mean the shoes.
(Share Transfer Contract -
This is what I can do for you.)
From a no-name Papaya Salad merchant,
I have gained reputations
because of Teng Nueng.
Mayom is a supportive friend
and adviser to me.
He lends a helping hand
every time I'm in trouble.
Chef Pipob, Ping, Pan, and Pong.
I have learned a lot from them,
including some great recipes
and cooking tips.
And the most important thing
is the friendship between us.
Thank you for making me the chef
I am today.
I really can't figure out if Pirada isn't around,
how Athip and I will end up.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Oh, my, I forgot to introduce myself.
How is the cash register?
- Does it work?
- Yes, Poon.
- I have tested it three times already.
- Good.
Don't worry, Poon.
I will help him here.
Alright then,
I'll go take care of the guests.
Welcome to The Spiciest.
Sure.
They ordered Papaya Salad and...
What are you angling at?
- Giving you a flower.
- It's not yours to give.
Thank you, everyone,
for being here today.
I'm looking forward to eating
your Papaya Salad, Poon.
And don't forget to make
a Mixed Fruit Spicy Salad for me.
And the restaurant looks stunning too.
Oh, I'm not going
to disappoint you for sure.
Wow, look at the menu!
You serve Soy Sauce Pickled Prawns
and Crab Roe too.
You also put my assorted omelette
on the menu.
Hey! Look at this!
My on demand instant noodles too!
Because you guys are my inspirations.
Oh, my god, I'm crying.
I will do the reviews for all dishes
you serve here.
Oh, thank you very much.
I'm going to order Shrimp Chili Dip
to see if yours can compare to mine.
I'm sorry, mate. But I must say
mine is way better than yours.
So please allow me to cook for you.
- Sure.
- Go it, Poon.
My friend wants to reserve
two more tables.
Oh, great!
But I'm afraid of making mistakes.
I'm probably nervous.
Don't be. Now, relax
and take a deep breath.
I believe you can do it.
Oh, right.
What is it?
It's already got a magic kiss on it,
and it will increase
the spiciness in you.
Congratulations, Poon.
Do your best.
If it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't have a restaurant like this.
You are part of it.
No, this restaurant is part of us.
- Now, it's time.  Let's go.
- Okay.
(The Spiciest by Chef Poon)
The first and the last person
I want to thank most is Athip.
You want a fight, huh?
The person I hated
from the very first sight
who have become the only person
I love now
and always.
Thank you for making me
the most fortunate person
who is loved by you.
My Tian.