WHERE GOT GHOST?
GHOST ON THE ROADSIDE
YUNNAN SHANTANG
There are two children outside,
looking at us and wanting to come in.
Who are their parents?
Never mind.
You can't see them anyway.
I think they're the children
from your family.
I don't think so, Master.
Did anyone have an abortion
or miscarriage years ago?
Never mind.
These children will then follow
the unlucky ones.
Master, are they neighboring kids
who've lost their way home?
Will your grandchildren
also go to the wrong doors?
No.
Baby spirits can be terrifying.
If they're not dealt with properly,
these baby spirits
will haunt their parents for life.
-What are we to do then, Master?
-Simple.
Perform a ritual to send them away.
Do it then, Master.
Let them reincarnate.
-Okay, $1,000 each.
-What, $1,000?
Can it be cheaper?
If you're tight on cash,
just do the ritual for one,
and the other will stay here
to follow the unlucky ones.
Okay, then.
-So be it, $2,000.
-Okay.
What toys do you want to burn for them?
Burn toys for them?
This is crucial.
-Show them the catalogue.
-Right away.
We're having a promotion.
You'll be given special discount
if you order today.
Look at this Transformer.
It's the children's favorite.
-Very popular.
-Is it?
There are also DS Lite, Ben 10...
PSP is the best.
There's more...
Yours.
Chief?
Too little?
No.
If we continue with this act, will we
offend the spirits and get retribution?
He's right. I feel uncomfortable,
making money like this.
I get goosebumps every time.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Let me tell you,
there are no ghosts in this world.
They exist only to the guilt-stricken
and weak-hearted,
who'll pay us to perform the ritual.
Aren't we still cheating them
out of money?
We're executing heaven's will.
These people are willing to pay us
to help them feel better.
What's wrong with that?
Chief, what you just said
makes me feel much better now.
Okay. Go buy some supper
and some fruits too.
I've been having problems of late.
Must be constipation.
Whenever I pass by this place,
it gives me the crisps.
Crisps?
I mean "creeps."
Singaporeans can never speak
proper Mandarin. All because of you...
Oh, no!
-What's the matter?
-I forgot to buy fruits!
I'm not going to go alone
to buy them.
I'm fat and tired.
Let's go together then.
What's the difference? It's equally far,
and I'll still be fat and tired.
What shall we do then?
Expect a scolding from the Chief?
I have an idea.
Are you with me?
You want to give the Chief these oranges?
Chief said there were no ghosts
in this world.
If you don't take them,
the foreign workers will,
and they're fine after eating them.
Are you sure?
Have you heard of foreign workers
dying after eating oranges?
-No.
-Then it's okay.
You're right.
Anyway, it's for the Chief.
I'll never touch them.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Spirit.
Our Chief wants to eat these fruits.
Please look for him
if you spirits are unhappy.
His name is "Li Ah Cai."
He's not afraid of you spirits,
but we respect you very much.
Sorry.
I respect you too.
Get the oranges.
May I ask, where did you get this orange?
It's tasteless.
It's inedible.
How dare you give me such rubbish?
It's sugar-free.
Yes. You'll get diabetes
from eating too much sweet stuff.
Go to hell!
If I get diabetes,
I'll drown you with my urine.
Almost forgot.
Prosperity!
Goal!
I worship to the God of Ball.
Are you insane?
God of Ball?
I meant the God of Football,
who can help me win.
You should pray hard not to go insane.
Nuts!
Chief, there's a god in everything.
Worship them,
and you'll be blessed and prosperous.
Hello?
Congratulations to you, sir.
You've won a prize
in our company's lucky draw.
Two first-class round-trip tickets
to America.
Please come collect your prize
from our company.
Go to hell!
You think you can fool me
with these old tricks? Idiots!
Can you believe it? They're still trying
to trick people with such calls.
Can't they be more creative?
Full of shit.
Chief, look at it from another angle.
If she makes 10,000 calls,
all she needs
is ten people to buy into the idea,
and they'll be rich.
Chief, the same goes
with our everyday lottery system.
Out of 10,000 combinations,
there are only 23 possible winners.
You're right.
If a person bets from 0000 to 9999,
they'll win 23 combinations for sure.
We're going to win big!
What is it, Chief?
From tomorrow,
we'll make 10,000 phone calls,
from 0000 to 9999,
giving each of them
a combination of numbers.
There will surely be 23 winners.
From the smallest to the biggest prize,
we will win them all!
Then we'll get a 20% commission fee
from every winner.
That's a brilliant idea, Chief!
What if they don't buy into our idea
or even deny having won?
How do we get a commission then?
We'll tell them it's lucky money
from the God of Wealth.
Then they'll pay up accordingly.
Is there a God of Wealth?
Yes, I'm the God of Wealth!
-You're a God, Chief!
-We're with a deity!
Where can we find 10,000 phone numbers
and addresses?
There's something used to wrap
steamed rice roll and kanchan puti.
I'll use it to "win."
You do A to J, and you do K to T.
Who will make the calls from U to Z?
Who do you think?
Congratulations!
We're calling on behalf
of the God of Wealth. Listen carefully.
Your lucky combination is 1045...
1033...
Make the purchase with these numbers.
If you win...
Please donate
20% of the winnings to our foundation.
The donation will be used to build
a temple for the God of Wealth,
not for our personal use.
Thank you.
We wish you the best of luck.
Win big!
The first prize of the week goes to...
1045.
I've won again!
I made the calls for the top three prizes.
Take a look.
Get lost!
What's the celebration for?
Chief, the calls for the top three prizes
were all made by me. I'm so lucky!
It's only the top three prizes.
I made the calls
for the rest of the combinations.
A total of 20 prizes.
I'm luckier than you.
So great, huh?
-You both made all the winning calls?
-Yes.
Did you win any prize?
No.
What's there to celebrate?
Chief, we may not be the winners,
but we made those calls.
It still feels amazing.
Although I didn't win for a long time,
this feels good too.
Morons. I look at it differently.
I came up with this system,
so I knew all along
that those 23 combinations
would be my winning combinations.
I'm the ultimate winner!
Take down the addresses
and collect our commissions quickly.
I'm such a genius.
Congratulations
on winning the third prize.
I told you,
this money is from the God of Wealth.
You'll need to donate
20% of the prize money to our foundation.
I'll send you the God of Wealth's
account number via SMS.
Thank you.
Win big!
Let me tell you,
Lady Luck will be on your side very often!
Win big!
This is not right!
You didn't bet on
the second-prize combination?
This is the God of Wealth's prize money.
You can lie to us,
but not to the God of Wealth.
Also... Hello? Hello?
He hung up on me.
What shall we do?
Have you been in the army before?
Your size is out of standard anyway.
They have something called
a "contingency plan."
So does our business.
Where does this guy live?
She's the one refusing
to pay us commission!
No worries, I'll call her.
Are you Chen Xiaohua?
Yes, who's this?
Congratulation on winning the lottery.
Our God of Wealth never fails to deliver.
Please donate money
to help us build a temple.
I've told you,
I didn't bet on the combination.
How could I win if I didn't place the bet?
This is the God of Wealth's money.
If you've placed the bet,
you can lie to us, but not to a deity.
I've told you so many times,
how could I win if I didn't place the bet?
-Really?
-Really.
No worries.
Don't blame me
for any misfortune in the future.
So be it. Bye
-Okay?
-Okay
-Remember the target.
-Her head, right?
No, just to scare her.
Missed her head.
Your aim must have been lousy
during your army days.
It's not easy to miss on purpose.
She'll transfer the funds to us tomorrow.
But this won't be feasible
when we have more customers.
We'll seek help from professionals.
Professionals?
Loan sharks.
I see.
I don't owe you any money.
I'm not a loan shark. The God of Wealth
gave you your lucky money.
-Why didn't you make a donation?
-Donation!
Donation! Donation!
-I didn't place the bet.
-Are you certain?
You sure? You sure?
TRANSFER
I can't stop smiling.
Chief, this is easy money.
Our business will be great!
Chief, your idea is brilliant.
We need to copyright it.
If not, there will be copy dogs.
It's "copycat," not "copy dog"!
You're right. I'll need more manpower.
Recruit 100 students
with sweet voices to make the calls.
I'll run the business like an enterprise,
have my company listed.
Then I'll be filthy rich!
I'm a genius, indeed!
GOD OF WEALTH ENTERPRISE
Hello. I'm a representative
of the God of Wealth Enterprise.
Good fortune to you.
Your lucky combination is 2305.
...6111.
However, if you win a prize...
Please donate 20% of your prize money
to us to build temples.
-Thank you.
-May you prosper!
Wow!
What's up?
If we continue making money like this,
We can afford the largest plasma TV
for next year's World Cup Live!
Are you okay?
If this continues,
we won't be watching TV,
but flying first class
to South Africa
to watch the match live!
You're right.
From 0000 to 9999,
there are 10,000 combinations.
Place a bet on one combination,
and you'll stand a chance to win a prize.
This is called "Four-Digit Lottery"
or "4D."
This lottery has been in Singapore
for decades.
It's a brilliant idea,
because anyone who bets
will feel a strong sense of victory.
It's very popular among citizens,
and also very good business
for the organization.
That's why even our government
is actively involved.
If you're interested,
I can make arrangements
for you to meet our officials.
Get back to me quickly.
Time for lunch, Chief.
Chief, the Taiwanese are also interested?
Not only Taiwan!
My targets also include Hong Kong, Korea,
Japan, the US, England, Australia, Africa,
and all the countries in the world!
Everyone will buy my lottery,
including Westerners!
I'm a genius, indeed!
Congratulations. I'm here
to bring you good fortune.
Please take down this combination,
6-6-6-6.
Damn it! Someone is using our idea,
and they're telling me
to place a bet on 6666!
Really?
-Hello?
-If you win,
please donate 18% of the prize money
to our charity.
Go to hell!
They're even cutting commissions
to compete with us!
Yes, I told you to get the idea
copyrighted. Did you do it?
I did. They said you need
to wait five years.
Five years?
I'll starve to death!
Chief, want to place the bet on 6666?
My foot!
What if it wins the lottery?
It could be one
of the 23 winning combinations.
I hate both of you!
-Bet a little then.
-How much?
$200!
Get going, before it's too late!
-Bet a little then?
-$200?
...8-9-0-1.
The numbers are
1-1-5-5.
-Did the numbers win?
-Nope.
I knew it.
That guy cannot be trusted.
The third-prize combination is
6-6-6-7.
Didn't I tell you? I knew it all along.
It's utter rubbish.
The second-prize combination is
6-6-6-6.
Hurray!
It's a windfall!
The first-prize combination is
6-6-6-6.
It's spot on!
This guy is a deity!
-He's so spot on with his prediction!
-What did you say is a deity?
I meant the table is dirty.
Dirty?
You're such an idiot!
Our Chief is the most formidable.
Cheers to our Chief!
Cheers!
-Hello?
-Congratulations.
You've won the first and second prizes.
I told you.
Please make your donation soon.
This is my idea.
You've stolen my idea,
and you expect a commission from me?
You're a moron!
Come and collect the money if you dare.
You haven't even paid me royalties.
You're such a loser!
Hope you get H1N1!
What's wrong?
He wants an 18% commission?
Who cares? Let's toast!
You guys deserve a treat.
Tonight, you can order
whatever you want. Go ahead!
Let's drink!
$800,000 is so heavy!
-Let me help you, Chief.
-No need.
-I can lend you a hand.
-That won't be necessary.
We need to be discreet.
Hurry up.
You're old and skinny.
The money is safer with me.
Not required!
You have arthritis, Chief.
The weight is bad for your bones.
I said not required.
-I'm big. I can protect the money.
-Not required!
Chief...
Say no more.
Let me carry it for a while.
I've never felt the weight of $800,000!
No!
Chief, let me have it for a while.
I'm willing to break my leg for it.
Over my dead body!
I beg of you. Let's play
rock-paper-scissors to decide.
Say no more!
-What's up?
-Who are you looking for?
You won the prize.
Why didn't you make the donation?
So you're that H1N1 loser!
You stole my idea!
How dare you demand a commission from me?
Your winning combination was given
by the Granny of Wealth behind me.
The prize-money donation
will be given to her.
Granny?
What Granny?
Look at him, copying all our ideas!
Don't you have better tricks?
Your brain must be rusty.
She's right behind me.
Didn't you see her?
Yes!
-And I can even see Grandpa too!
-Right!
Grandpa is cooking it salty
Granny wants it less salty
Granny brought you such fortune,
you ungrateful bastards!
You'll be knocked down by a car.
Loser, trying to frighten me?
I'm so scared, my limbs are trembling.
I'm peeing in my pants.
I'll cross the road now.
Let's see if cars knock me down.
Come on, run me over!
-Come back, Chief!
-Run me over!
It's dangerous!
Did you see that?
I'm perfectly okay!
-Come back, Chief!
-Get the cars to knock me down!
I'm invincible!
Look up! Run for your life!
Chief!
Next time, don't eat my oranges.
Ghost!
I'm so sorry, Mr. Spirit.
Our Chief wants to eat these fruits.
Please look for him
if you spirits are unhappy.
His name is "Li Ah Cai."
He's not afraid of you spirits,
but we respect you very much.
Sorry.
I respect you too.
Get the oranges.
It's inedible.
How dare you give me such rubbish?
DISASTERS IN LIFE
START WITH IGNORING DETAILS.
THERE ARE GHOSTS IN THE WOODS
Faster!
Yes, Master Sergeant!
Don't take this lightly!
Don't take shortcuts!
Don't be lazy!
Don't be a smartass!
Yes, Warrant Officer.
No, Warrant Officer.
Put on your helmet on.
Move out.
Sir, can we be the last detail?
Can, come back next Sunday.
Report to the Master Sergeant.
I heard that this forest is cursed.
-So?
-Many Japanese soldiers died here.
-What are you afraid of?
-Ghosts.
You look like a ghost yourself,
and you're scared?
Buddy, slow down.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
My reasons for trying
to take off are all valid!
What are you trying to say?
I've seen five masters.
They all told me the same thing,
that I'm cursed
with a "blood encounter" this year.
"Blood encounter" curse?
Don't get me into trouble. I'm your buddy.
-How's your luck been this year?
-Extremely good, man.
That'll do. You can save me.
But what if I'm cursed
by your bad luck instead?
No.
No? I must complain
to the Ministry of Defense.
They'll need to consult my masters
before assigning me
a buddy from now on.
Right.
Stop. Don't move.
See? I've lifted
your "blood encounter" curse for you!
-Thank you.
-Don't move.
Blood encounter.
Stop!
B-L-O-O-D E-N-C-O-U-N-T-E-R!
Are you trying to get back to me?
These mosquitoes are formidable.
Just can't seem to hit any of them!
Buddy!
I think we're lost.
Says who? See?
We came this way, and we're here!
No, we came that way, and we're here!
No, we're there.
Don't argue with me.
We're at this point.
-Take that thing out.
-That "thing" is called a compass.
See?
I think it's broken.
The compass points to this direction.
When you turn around,
it still points to the same direction.
If you turn back,
It's definitely broken!
Don't you know?
This is how a compass works.
It always point in the same direction.
It's always pointing to "Nan,"
meaning South.
How do you know?
-Do you see an "N" on it?
-Yes.
What about the "S"?
"S" is "See," meaning West.
What about the "W"?
"W" stands for...
There are women over there.
It's dangerous.
Rubbish!
So "E" stands for "Elephant"?
Don't fool me.
You think I don't know topography?
In fact, I really know nothing
about it! I used to be a military driver.
There's always someone
to tell me directions.
I know nothing about topography really.
I used to be in the military police.
I arrested people every day,
so I don't know topography either.
I always lazed around in my army days.
I used to be second sergeant.
Then I got demoted to third sergeant.
Can you be worse than me?
I went from first sergeant to corporal,
then back to third sergeant.
I was locked in the detention barracks
three times!
Three times?
No big deal.
My record was five times.
Listen carefully.
I was locked for 40 days every time.
You win!
Let's take a look.
If we follow the instructions,
we'll be here forever.
What shall we do then?
Do you dare?
-What are you talking about?
-Shortcut.
Buddy!
Why do we need to prowl like this?
We're taking a shortcut.
This tactical movement
will keep us from officers' view.
-This is the shortcut?
-Yes.
This is the Pan Island Expressway.
Idiot, we'll take a cab
from here straight to the end point.
Go to hell!
Pass me the map and follow me closely.
Learn from me, kiddo.
Let's see what you can do.
Why is there a tombstone
in the military training area?
Let's go.
Is there a lucky number on it?
-Cut the crap. Let's go.
-She is so pretty.
-Don't say "pretty."
-Okay, she's ugly.
Stop uttering rubbish! Let's go!
What's wrong with saying
"ugly" or "pretty"?
LU-YIN
What's the matter?
Do you smell something?
Nope.
Take a deep breath.
Yes, a scent of flower,
but I can't tell the name of the flower.
What is it?
I just farted.
Go to hell! Childish!
I was in front of you
when I farted along the way.
Didn't you smell anything?
Is there something wrong with your nose?
You're so childish!
My tummy aches. I need to poo.
It's getting dark.
You want to poo in the forest?
I can't help it. It's coming out.
If you take off your pants, squat down,
and see a cobra, what will you do?
I'll remain still.
If it bites your private parts?
I hit it with a stick.
-It'll be too late.
-What should I do then?
You take off the co-bra's "bra,"
give it a tight slap, and it'll fall.
Cut the crap!
I can't hold it anymore.
That's what you get
for playing pranks on me!
Wait for me.
I want to poo too.
-Buddy.
-What?
Do you smell something?
I just used this trick.
Can you be more creative?
It's true.
Take a deep breath.
Trying to fool me?
Use other tricks, please.
I'm not joking.
I smell something nice.
You're a weirdo.
You couldn't smell a thing
when I farted earlier.
Now you're saying
my waste smells nice to you.
Your nose is really not working.
-Did you see that?
-I saw it.
-Is it...
-Sure!
Do you dare?
What is it?
Ask her for lottery numbers.
Why not?
Come on!
One, two, three...
Run!
Ghost!
Help!
What about our rifles?
Are you nuts?
We almost died.
Forget the rifles.
We'll be charged under military law.
Let it be!
Buddy...
Do you have a tissue?
What for?
I forgot to wipe my butt.
Me too.
Don't you feel dirty?
It can't be worse than that thing.
Then say no more!
I have a request.
Please don't laugh at me.
What request?
My hands are cold.
Can I hold your hands?
Okay.
Buddies, hand in hand.
Buddies, poo in hands.
Give me a hand.
Will you fall in love with me?
-Go to hell!
-Just joking!
Our rifles!
The officers said if we see the canal,
we're on the wrong route.
The canal is the shortcut.
Be careful.
Look around carefully.
Don't let the officers see us.
Be careful of the canal.
We seem to be on a much better path,
thanks to you!
Of course, I drew the Singapore map.
Yeah, as if I'll believe you!
On the count of three,
-we'll run over to that bush.
-Okay.
Look out for officers.
Let's go.
This forest is divine!
I didn't know Singapore
could be so beautiful!
Where's this place?
I don't know.
But you drew the map, right?
I didn't finish drawing.
What the heck!
Be careful.
Look out for officers.
No more water.
It'll never be enough
if you keep drinking like a cow.
Look over there!
Miss...
Handsome.
It's tough to be a soldier.
Do you need water?
This is a deserted forest,
yet someone is selling water.
Get me a bottle.
Has to be cold.
-Here.
-Thank you.
So cooling.
You're lost, right?
How do you know?
I've been selling water here
for many years.
The soldiers I meet,
all get lost while taking a shortcut.
It's always the same.
Nothing has changed.
You' had an unforgettable night yesterday?
Last night, we saw a ghost.
She had long hair, red clothes,
but no face.
This is normal.
This ghost is very popular.
All the soldiers who had taken
a shortcut met her.
Glad we're not the only ones to see her!
$2 for a bottle.
Pay her $4.
Miss!
Do you know a shortcut to the end point?
You're asking the right person,
but I don't think you would be able to
understand my instructions.
Don't worry. I'm a university graduate.
I'll understand. Is there a problem?
Okay, listen carefully.
Go straight ahead. Turn left.
Turn right and straight--
Enough, Miss! We'll find our way.
-Thank you.
Why is the sky so dark suddenly?
Seems like it's going to rain.
Why the sudden change in weather?
This is the kind of rain
that will last a long time.
As it gets heavier,
the forest will soon be flooded.
Be careful.
Miss, is there a shelter nearby?
Yes, my house.
-What shall we do?
-Let's follow her.
Miss, wait for us!
Here we are.
This is my house.
What happened to your trees?
The branches hit my roof
whenever it rains, so I tied them up.
Come in. This is my home.
Why do you live in such a big house?
It's my father's.
I'm drenched.
I need a bath.
Buddy, it's good we found shelter.
Buddy...
Don't you think it's strange a girl
would live in such a deserted place?
Many girls stay in the forest
in Lim Chu Kang, Woodlands, and Yishun.
Who are these girls?
Prostitutes!
You're wrong.
Those prostitutes are young and pretty
with gorgeous figures.
This fat one is called a "boar."
So boring. It's a downpour.
My noodle stall can fetch me $500 a day,
yet I'm doing nothing now.
You can tell the Ministry of Defense
you earn $50,000 a month,
and be excused,
but the tax office will come after you.
Have you ever seen a pig shower?
No, I've seen farmers bathe pigs.
But have you seen a pig
taking bath on its own?
I'm curious. Don't stop me.
Buddy...
You're a sergeant.
Sergeants have desires too.
I meant you're a sergeant.
You should proceed with tactical movement.
You're right. Good one.
Are you for real?
Hope you get into big trouble.
Ghost!
Ghost! Ghost! Ghost!
LU-YIN
I didn't peep,
but he did!
Sorry, I won't do it again.
Why are you both running away?
Because you're a ghost.
I'm not a ghost.
She's my twin sister.
She died months ago.
I saw your mouth spilling blood.
I was brushing my teeth
and accidentally hurt my gums.
The blood is from my gums.
Right. It happens to me too.
So you're really not a ghost?
If you don't believe me, try feeling me.
No, no, no!
No? So do you both want to follow me home?
No, no!
Well, you can either stay drenched here
or go into the woods to meet with
those hundreds of ghosts in there.
I'm leaving.
My leg is stuck!
My leg!
Stuck?
Simply lift it from the log.
What's happening here?
It was stuck earlier.
What do you think?
There may be
hundreds of ghosts in the woods,
but only two ghosts in the house,
and both are female.
I think it's safer to follow her.
Let's go.
-Wait for us!
-Wait!
Come in.
You can stay outside then.
There's a ghost in your room, I swear.
She has long hair and scary fingernails.
You must be seeing things.
See?
My gums are bleeding again.
You must be seeing things.
Let's check it out.
-Come on.
-No.
-Come on!
Are you men or not? Wimps!
She's calling you a wimp.
Prove her wrong.
No way!
Weren't you a medium before?
That was an excuse for getting a day off.
This is for real.
Don't get me into trouble.
-You check it out, and I'll run.
-What?
You'll have to follow me closely
to be safe.
Sound good? Good.
-Watch out for me.
-Okay!
Come and see.
No!
Come here.
We've been fooled.
So cowardly. Come on!
What are these things for?
They are my dad's.
He was a magician.
The renowned American magician
David Footballfield was his student.
You mean David Copperfield?
It was Footballfield then.
He changed his name when he became famous.
Without my dad,
he wouldn't be David Copperfield today.
I didn't know Singaporeans
were good at tooting their horns.
I'm tooting a horn?
I'll be performing David Footballfield's
most formidable magic stunt,
the Great Escape.
Prove it to us.
It's empty?
There are no flowers or rabbits.
Not even pigeons.
Here she comes.
-Tie up.
-Not me. Tie him up.
Tie you up!
Are you nuts?
I meant, tie me up.
You?
For real?
Just do it!
Come on!
Don't let me move around.
Come on.
One two, three, pull!
Lock up!
She's really a giant!
Wait a minute!
Remember, tie me up tightly.
-Will you die?
-It can be dangerous!
Piece of cake.
So arrogant!
Tie her tightly so she can never escape.
Just like wrapping a dumpling.
Be careful!
Careful!
You're not supposed to drop her!
Do you know how heavy she is?
Why don't you do it? It's not easy!
I'll get you when I'm out.
-Sorry.
It's my fault.
-I will close it
-Close the chest.
Lock it up.
For real?
Count to ten, and I'll be out.
-So arrogant.
-Come on.
Lock up the chest.
I have the key.
She can never escape.
Are you okay, Fatso? Fatso!
There's not a sound in there.
Will she die in the chest?
So strange.
Fatso!
Will she die in the chest?
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one!
Fatso! Fatso! Fatso!
Aren't you inside the chest?
I'm holding the key.
How did you escape?
It's magic!
Look inside the chest.
Is she really that good?
It's true!
Amazing!
If I learned this magic, I could stop
frying noodles and perform on stage.
I'd perform in Las Vegas.
And it'd be at least $10,000
for each performance!
-Jackpot! Tie me up first, okay?
-Tie me up first!
You'll get your chance.
Tie me up first.
I'm fed up of giving in to you.
-Give in already!
-Don't be such a bully!
Buddy, you cannot imagine
how tight Master has tied me.
I'll give a better performance than you.
Nonsense!
Master has tied me much tighter,
so I can perform better than you.
Just wait and see.
Bring it on!
Master! Master!
Teach us the Great Escape trick, quick!
Relax.
I'll teach you something better
than the David Footballfield's stunt.
It's a new magic trick!
More tricks!
Tighter?
Tighter, Master!
A bit more!
Okay.
Did you see that?
I want mine to be
tighter than his, Master.
I want to perform better.
Let's see. Tighter, Master!
A bit more. A bit more...
Why are you holding knives?
It's part of the magic trick.
Are you going to kill us?
Be careful with it.
It's dangerous.
All magic stunts are dangerous. Scared?
Then forget about learning the trick.
I want to learn.
Aunt, I've found
the two substitute ghosts for you.
Can you let me go?
ONE YEAR LATER
Take your sweet time.
Want me to come hold your hands?
Check your equipment
and report to the Master Sergeant!
Who's not taking the shortcut?
Ridiculous!
If we get caught,
we'll be in deep trouble.
Have you heard
of Code of Conduct Number 7?
What?
You're still at Rule 7?
The latest is Rule 8!
-What?
-You are not a soldier if you don't cheat!
Gentlemen!
Say that one more time!
-Yes, Master Sergeant!
-Go!
THERE IS A PRICE TO PAY
FOR EVERY SHORTCUT YOU TAKE.
GHOST IN THE HOUSE
Mother, it's been a year,
and still no lottery blessing from you,
no starter prize, no consolation prize.
Nothing at all, not even a lucky draw.
Please remember
to let them win some lottery.
Thank you.
Mother, you're staying with us.
I pray to you every day.
You must remember
to give us some lucky "4D" numbers,
not give your granddaughters
all "D's" in exams.
Bless us, Mother.
Come pray to Grandma.
Mother, you must remember,
"4D" numbers and getting
four "D's" in exams are different.
Don't mess up again.
Bless us!
Mother, Lehman Brothers in America
is such a big company.
As a deity up there,
you must've known it would go under.
If you knew,
why didn't you inform me in advance?
My friend's father
tipped him off in his dream.
He managed to avoid heavy losses.
But I didn't.
I suffered a huge losses.
You must bless me.
Mother, are you still mad at us?
Please don't be angry.
We've apologized
and paid for all your medical bills.
Look at Stella.
She's so obedient now.
Stella, pray to Grandma.
Mother, please bless us all.
Mother, thank you for blessing us.
I'm finally pregnant.
Mother, you blessed me with a child,
but did not bless me with any earnings.
How will I feed my child?
Our business is getting worse every day.
Please open your eyes and look after us.
Please give us your blessing.
Take a break.
-Have a drink.
-Thank you.
Our business is getting worse.
What shall we do?
The market is so bad.
What can we do, right?
Amid the economic downturn,
the government has launched a new scheme
to help small and medium businesses.
Let's apply for it.
Lots of incentives up for grabs.
Don't be naive, Second Brother.
Normally, you can apply,
but it doesn't mean you'll get approval.
"Apply" and "approve"
are two different words.
Many conditions apply.
It's never easy getting money
from the government,
but it's so much easier
in the private sector.
Private sector? How?
I have a friend who's a Datuk.
Datuk?
-Where?
-Kuala Lumpur.
He's loaded.
If he invests in our business,
we'll be rich.
Are you sure?
Okay!
You have to be careful.
There are cheats everywhere.
Rest assured, Big Brother, he wants
to see me. Here's my suggestion.
Next week, why don't we, as directors
of our company, meet him in Kuala Lumpur?
-Okay, we'll go where the riches are.
-Lovely!
Mother, this is our last chance.
You've been up there for a year.
You should have friends.
Please get them to bless us too.
Otherwise, your sons' future is doomed.
Please give us your blessing.
Win big!
Bless us.
Since Mother died,
we've not had dinner together.
Too bad.
We're all busy with our business.
Luckily, we made some profits initially.
Not anymore.
Too bad. No blessing from Mother.
What can we do, right?
Sometimes, I miss Mother.
Enough talk. Let's eat.
Who put a chair over there?
What is it for? Mother is no longer here.
I didn't do it.
Did you girls put the chair here?
Stella, mind your words
on the Seventh Month.
Sorry!
Take the chair away, hubby.
I'll do it.
She's our mother, nothing to be afraid of.
Don't be afraid.
Come sit closer.
More room for us.
This pig's trotter tastes great!
Sister-in-law, you've finally mastered
Mother's cooking.
This tastes exactly like Mother's cooking!
Congratulation! It's delicious. Eat more.
I didn't cook that dish.
Didn't you bring it here?
Don't look at me. It wasn't me.
I didn't bring it either.
I bought it.
You almost scared us to death.
Dear, I bought it
from the coffee shop near our place.
It tastes exactly like Mother's cooking.
Why didn't you mention it before?
Come on, let's eat.
Why is there another chair?
No, the chair was here all along.
The chair was never here.
Ask you wife.
He's right.
See?
Big Brother, that chair is gone!
I remember placing the chair over there.
Why is it here?
Is it grandma?
She wants to join us for dinner.
Mind your words. Just eat!
Tell me, did anyone talk nonsense
at the altar earlier?
-No!
-Someone must have done it!
Mother! Mother!
Ong, have you seen my bra?
Damn!
I saw Mother!
Darling! Darling!
What's up, dear?
I saw Mother!
Mother?
Where?
Here, she was here,
asking me for her bra.
I'm not kidding!
Were you dreaming?
Impossible!
It's true. She was sitting over here,
right at this spot.
I'm not lying!
Ong, have you seen my bra?
The red one with Mickey Mouse prints.
I'll buy you another one.
Get it in Singapore.
Boss, you're selling green tea too?
Yes. The trend follows
the dead to the underworld.
They'll still prefer
their favorite drinks down there.
-"Down there"?
-Of course!
How can I help you?
Do you sell bras?
Bras? You came here to buy a bra?
Are you serious?
I've no choice.
My mother haunts me every day,
asking me for her bra.
You're the first customer
to make such a request.
-Do you have?
-Okay, I'll have them tailor-made for you.
Good. Give me two pairs.
-Color?
-Black and red.
I'll take it down.
Can you add Mickey Mouse stickers to them?
Mickey Mouse?
-Your mother likes Mickey Mouse?
-There's nothing I can do!
She keeps demanding
Mickey Mouse on her bra.
If you can do it,
I can burn it for her.
Burn Mickey Mouse?
Can't do it. Copyright infringement.
You're right. This is such a pain!
I have a suggestion.
Can you make it so that
the Chinese know it's Mickey Mouse,
but Westerners can't tell.
You're so hilarious!
I'll try my best.
-It's settled. I'll collect them tomorrow.
-Okay, okay.
What's her cup size?
She's been gone for a year,
but has never told me.
What shall I do?
We play safe, give her a large cup size.
Large? Large one?
Yes, the larger, the better.
Okay. Okay.
Hui, have you eaten?
Yes.
Darling!
Did you ask me if I've eaten?
You're insane.
You've been asking me
the same question for days.
And will you please
get the television repaired?
It's been broken for days.
I think the wires are loose.
I've missed my favorite drama series.
So annoying.
Look at this television.
Must be a loose wire.
Mother! She's inside the TV!
No! Where is she?
You're insane!
Loose wire...
Mother is in the television!
She's inside!
Don't scare me!
You! It's not the television.
You're the one with a loose wire!
You do the adjustment.
I'll watch from here.
Look. Look carefully.
See anything?
This is a nice show.
What a bad daughter-in-law!
I dreamed of Mother!
Hui, have you eaten?
What a bad daughter-in-law!
I can't take it anymore.
Mother sits on my bed every night,
asking for her Mickey Mouse bra.
I can't stand it anymore.
I bought her a large Mickey Mouse bra,
but she's still not happy
and continues to haunt me.
It's worse for me.
How?
She only haunts you at night,
but she haunts me all day.
-That's bad.
-I hear her words every minute,
but see nobody around me.
Now, she has a new trick.
What is it?
She hides in the television
and scares me.
Which channel?
Every channel.
She kept repeating the same words
until my head almost cracked.
Second Brother, you look very relaxed.
Mother didn't harass you?
Nope.
Impossible!
Maybe she thinks I'm a good son.
You must be joking.
I'll tell you honestly,
if not for that packet of blood you took,
Mother would still be alive.
-You're wrong.
-Why?
Mother willingly volunteered
to save Stella.
In danger, who would you save?
Mother or daughter?
I asked for your opinions,
but both of you just avoided the question!
She's our only Mother, the one and only.
Even if she pulled the oxygen tube,
I would've plugged it back.
Now you're saying this!
Isn't it too late?
Your daughter isn't born yet--
Don't you mention my daughter.
You did it too.
Stop fighting.
It's been over a year, for goodness sake.
But I don't understand,
why didn't Mother look for you?
Big Brother,
how could you say such things?
Mother must have tried haunting him,
but in vain.
You've moved twice in a year,
hiding from Mother?
-Nonsense!
-There's no use hiding.
She'll find you one day.
I'm not afraid of her!
Why should I be?
She may even help me win the lottery!
Don't be so mean to your own brother!
I'm not afraid!
You gave me a fright!
Don't pat on my shoulder from behind.
It's the Seventh Month!
You're so cowardly!
Let me tell you something.
They've seen Mother around.
I think we're next!
Let's go.
Are you sure?
Hubby! Hubby!
Give me a tissue.
Hurry. My eyes are hurting.
Hurry up!
Your tissue.
You gave it to me, right?
No, I just got here.
Then what's in my hand?
But I just entered the room.
Trying to scare me?
I've wet my pants,
I'm so scared. Childish!
Says who?
I'm not that easy-going.
Darling, tell me honestly,
did you help me wash my face earlier?
No.
Come on.
-Don't lie to me, please.
-No!
-Can you lie to me? Say yes.
-What's wrong with you?
I'll feel better this way.
You're becoming more cowardly
as you grow older.
I'm getting the feeling
that Mother is already in here.
Why are you so afraid?
She lived with us before.
Don't worry. Just sleep.
We'll burn some incense for her tomorrow.
Okay.
Kiong...
Did you hear Mother calling me?
No!
Kiong...
This time, I did!
Don't scare us, Mother.
I admit I'm not a good son.
I'll burn some incense
for you tomorrow. Please!
-Don't scare us!
-Let's sleep.
Kiong...
Don't trouble yourself over where I sleep.
I can sleep anywhere.
You saw Mother too?
That was your wish, wasn't it?
Now that it's has come true,
aren't you two delighted?
-What are you talking about?
-Why would we want it to happen?
Stop playing dumb!
Both of you were here last night,
jealous of Mother not haunting me,
so you cursed me, and now she did
come haunt me. Are you two satisfied?
-But we went to Johor yesterday.
-Exactly.
Stop denying it!
If you don't believe me,
I'll show you my passport.
Yes, we were in Johor.
Stop denying it!
I'm not a fool!
Are you dreaming, Second Brother?
Dreaming?
But I remember we meeting here!
You're saying
even our meeting here was a dream?
And I continued to dream of Mother.
She almost scared me to death.
-I also dreamed of Mother.
-Me too.
Both of you?
Mother appeared in all our dreams.
What's her motive?
Right.
Big Brother,
did you perform the prayers correctly?
Do you know the proper procedures?
What are you trying to say?
I don't need you juniors to teach me.
In fact, I should've told you earlier,
I'm not Mother's only son.
Each of us should take turns monthly
to offer her prayers.
I can't do it.
Her tablet doesn't suit
the avant-garde design of my house.
Same here.
You know that I'm busy.
"Can't"? "Busy"?
I don't care! We take turns praying.
Isn't that your friend?
Wow, looks like he's having a good time.
-Hey, buddy!
-Both of you, wait for me over there.
Lucky you, driving a Mercedes!
Mine broke down.
This is my maid's errand car.
You must be earning a lot.
What's you job?
I don't need to work.
My mother's blessing me
with such good fortune.
I keep asking her not to let me
win the lottery again, but in vain.
I even won first prize
with unlucky numbers like 4444.
I just keep winning.
Even the bookies shun me.
Your mother is that powerful?
Didn't you know? When an elder dies,
the timing is important.
If she dies at midnight,
she takes away all fortune
and leaves nothing for the descendants.
But if the time is in the morning
such as 7:00 a.m.,
the descendants will prosper,
leaving nothing for the deceased.
And if she dies at noon,
both parties will split the luck.
Get it? I doubt you do!
So your mother died in the morning?
It was supposed to be at midnight.
The doctor tried to revive her
with injections and a defibrillator,
and shook her through the night.
She struggled all the way until daybreak,
thereby blessing us with good fortune.
That's what I call a great mother.
I need to go.
Forty thousand.
Let's go have some fun!
You'll be fined for illegal parking!
What's the big deal?
I'm loaded!
Jealous of me?
This is the life!
Our mother died at night.
She left us with nothing.
After hearing what he said,
I realize Mother cannot bless us anymore.
So all the prayers are a waste of time.
Forget it then.
How can you say that?
We're her sons, for goodness sake!
Big Brother, if you try too hard,
the situation may backfire.
Our luck may turn from bad to worse.
Now I know
why Mother appeared in our dreams.
Why?
She's trying to tell us
she can't bless us anymore.
So, by scaring us,
she hopes we'll stay away from her.
Therefore, we should stop all the prayers.
Sounds logical.
What do we do with the tablet?
Listen, I know someone from a temple.
The temple is quite remote,
but we can house the tablet there
at discount rates. What do you think?
-I'm good!
-Good?
How about you, Big Brother?
When Mother was alive,
you sent her to an old folks home.
Now that she's dead,
you're sending her to an old temple?
Have you no humanity?
There's nothing we can do.
There's no point continuing the prayers.
My mind is made up.
Me too.
What about you?
Big Brother, if you insist,
do it at your own risk.
-Don't say we didn't warn you.
-Think about it.
Who will bring Mother to the temple?
Mother, don't get the wrong idea.
We're not bad sons.
We've found a nice place for you.
It's divine.
See? Beautiful scenery on your left,
and your old buddies on your right.
They're all staying here with you.
They'll keep you happy.
You can chat with them,
play games, talk about the old days...
The air is very fresh.
Butterflies, birds...
Look! And even parrots!
Mind your step.
Be careful. Slowly.
Up the stairs.
Mother, here's your mansion.
Hello?
I'll tell you something very frightening.
Come here quickly.
Hurry!
Big Brother, why didn't you bring
Mother's tablet into the temple?
-I did.
-Then?
I sent her in,
but she flew back here.
Flew back here?
Are you sure you weren't daydreaming?
Or was it that you made a mistake?
Why won't the two of you believe me?
I brought Mother in personally,
but when I came out,
she was already inside,
even before I opened the car door!
-Don't cry.
-Stop crying.
I'm not crying.
Do you know how frightened I am?
Listen, don't try to be funny,
Big Brother.
Tablets don't fly out on their own.
You must be joking, right?
-Is this a prank?
-Why are you both so stubborn?
Why won't the two of you just believe me?
Why would I need to lie?
Why are you doubting me?
-Why?
-Okay, we believe you.
I think Mother wants us
to send her in together.
Here we are.
Here we come, Mother.
All right, let's send her in together.
He's doing all this
because he's unwilling to do it alone.
Big Brother, we need to go.
Time is running out.
I feel weird.
Can we cancel the appointment
with the Datuk today?
No, the Datuk is a busy man.
We need to make an appointment
three months in advance.
We have no other choice.
Maybe Mother will bless us with success.
If we don't go,
how can she bless us?
Exactly. Let's go.
What's up?
I'm looking for Mother's flying tablet.
Don't be superstitious.
Did you actually forget--
Here you go again!
Enough talk. Let's get going.
Come on, there's a traffic jam
at the causeway!
Let me remind you, don't visit Mother
only on her anniversary.
You should do it every now and then.
If Mother blesses us
with success this time,
I'll buy the whole temple
for her to stay in.
Actually, I don't understand Mother.
Take your friend's mother for example,
always blessing your friend
with good luck.
But our mother? Nothing.
Not only are we not winning
any money in the lottery,
even our business
is being left in the cold,
making us struggle like hell.
Exactly.
How can you say that?
Why are you
always complaining about Mother?
She's our mother!
We still have to respect her,
even if she's dead.
Okay, enough talk.
What's that sound?
Must be those falling branches.
Drive slowly.
Our children are still young.
In fact, I'm more concerned than you are.
I have a pregnant wife.
Just slow down.
I'm only going 74 miles an hour.
Says who?
It's 100 miles an hour.
The meter's faulty.
Remember, three lives are at stake here.
Slow down. The rain is getting heavier.
I'm driving. You're such a nag.
Mother!
Be careful, Big Brother!
It's very slippery.
Watch your step!
I know. You be careful too!
Be careful!
Don't look back. Just move!
The car is sinking!
Hurry! Don't look back. Hurry up!
-Did you see Mother?
-Yes, I did.
-Yes.
Why is she trying to scare us?
And there goes our car!
Mother.
Look, Second Brother.
Brother.
Look, Big Brother.
Let's go. Be careful, Mother.
Mind your step.
Be careful, Mother.
It's your friend again.
What happened to you?
Down on my luck.
Didn't your mother
bless you in everything?
Yes, she blesses me in everything.
She gave me luck in the lottery,
in Big Sweep,
in Toto,
even at illegal gambling.
And now, she even gave me cancer.
You have cancer?
Damn the doctor.
He said I was okay
after months of check-ups.
I checked with another doctor
to confirm the results,
and he told me
I've only three months left to live.
I'm doomed!
So what if I'm rich?
My mother didn't bless me well.
I've decided not to offer her
prayers anymore.
Heed my advice.
Nothing is more important
than our health and safety.
Don't let me fall.
If I fall, I may be left
with only one week to live.
Let's go bring Mother home.
WHEN YOU HAVE HEALTH AND PEACE,
DO YOU THINK IT'S A COINCIDENCE?
This is the money that
the God of Fortune gave to you.
God of Wealth. Not God of Fortune.
This is...
This is God of Fortune...
This is the money that
the God of Fortune gave to you.
God of Wealth!
Cheesy.
-I want to learn.
Sit.
It did hit.
-160...
-The meter doesn't work.
Don't forget.
We all want...
We are all together.
When we are all together
This is in the beginning.
-Eh...
-Mother!
Mother! Ah!
Eh, mother! Ah!
Nice job.
If I see marble, all of a sudden...
-Marble?
If I see bubble...
-Marble.
-Mother don't sit too close.
-Our super crazy friends...
Why did you...
Bless us rich!