♪
Shit!
-(humming)
-Molly?
Molly?
Molly?!
Hey, I was listening to that.
Earth calling sisterling.
Have you forgotten today's
the day Rosemary moves in?
Like you'd let me forget?
Please tell me you're not
gonna do anything crazy.
Look, you know
I love you Mollster,
but are some things you're just
way too young to understand.
I know what
I'm doing, though, okay?
-Trust me.
-Poppy!
All right, guys, let's give
my dad's girlfriend
the perfect Malibu welcome.
Everyone, help yourself!
(all cheer)
You can keep it
or you can throw it away.
You can keep that.
(chattering)
Oh, Poppy, you've really
done it this time.
Ugh!
Hey, girls, watch this.
(all laughing)
(all gasping)
(screaming)
Where did she go?
-Is she okay?
-Is she still down there?
-She's still under.
-There might be sharks.
Welcome to Malibu, biatch!
Get up here right now!
Get up here!
Please go home. Home, home.
(chattering)
Go on, out. Out.
Out, out, out.
Let's go. Come on, out.
Out, out.
That is the final straw, Poppy!
You are going to England.
-Let's go.
-Yawn!
The boarding school
threat again!
I don't even
recognize you anymore.
All this is gonna
stop right now!
So, what? Big deal!
You can just replace me
with a newer, trashier version,
like you did with Mom.
You are going
to boarding school in England,
and that's final.
What, you think
just because Mom went
to boarding school in England,
it's gonna magically
straighten me out?
Do you even remember Mom?
(sighs)
Hi, Molly.
I think you might've
pushed him too far this time.
I know.
But England's so far away.
Well, at least they speak
American there, right?
But who's gonna cut
the crusts of my sandwiches?
You're gonna be fine, Mol.
I promise.
Oh, in England, it rains
200 days out of the year.
You will definitely get S.A.D.
She is sad.
Seasonal Affected Disorder.
Depression due
to lack of sunlight,
resulting in acne
and weight gain.
What?
What? I saw it on Dr. 90210.
(groaning)
(gasps) Not those shoes.
They don't do rain.
Just take them.
Hey, you promise
we'll talk every day?
Swear on your life?
Dude, who loves ya?
Everything's gonna suck
without you.
Oh, Ruby, you're my best friend.
I'm gonna miss you so much.
I know, let's check out
their website.
(door closes)
(both) Oh, my God!
"Abbey Mount School is
an independent boarding school
"for girls age 11 to 17?
Founded in 1797!
The school is one of England's
top institutions
for young ladies?"
-It's all brick!
-Ew.
Please tell me that's not
in the countryside.
Ugh!
(chattering)
Excuse me.
Hello, how are you?
All right, Kate. Yes?
Mr. Moore, I'm Mrs. Kingsley.
Oh, please call me Gerry.
Thank you, I am so grateful
I'm happy we could help out.
She's going through
rather a difficult stage.
Just leave it to me, Mr. Moore.
I have a double first
in difficult.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Good holiday?
-Yeah.
Good.
Hello, Poppy,
welcome to Abbey Mount.
I'm Mrs. Kingsley,
your headmistress.
Look, I understand you're just--
Uh-uh uh-uh.
Lesson number one, Poppy.
To me, negotiation
is like a nightclub...
not something I tend
to enter into.
Now, come along.
-Hello.
-Hi.
♪
Wow.
-Who's she?
-Is she new?
-Wow.
-Look at those shoes.
Poppy, this is Kate.
She'll be your big sister
at Abbey Mount.
You'll soon settle in.
-Hi, how do you do?
-I already have a sister.
It's just school lingo.
I'll be your friend,
a helping hand, that's all.
Okay, but, um,
I choose my friends.
And FYI, you don't make the cut.
I'm sure that comment would
sting a lot more
if I knew what "FYI" meant.
But, for the moment,
let's just pretend
it's had the desired effect,
shall we?
Saddle up, girls,
we've got ourselves a bronco.
Mrs. Kingsley, a gift.
One for you and one for Freddie.
Oh, thank you.
I shot them myself.
Oh, I don't doubt that you did.
Well, perhaps you'd like
to keep hold of them
while I welcome back
the first years.
Nice thought, though.
Salve, puella novella.
Harriet.
Head girl.
Hmm.
You shake the hand
of the head girl
out of respect.
When the head girl
has earned my respect,
then I'll shake her hand,
biatch.
-I'm sorry.
-Apology accepted.
Oh!
Stunningly horridious ego
desperately seeks
a good bashing.
Can we oblige?
Me thinks so.
(together) We think so, too.
I'll call you tomorrow morning
as soon as I'm back in L.A.
I hope your flight
gets seriously delayed.
(chuckles)
And I hope your bags end up
in Kazakhstan.
I'll come back for you
at the end of the semester,
all right?
Sweetheart,
you know I love you.
(engine starts)
Bye.
♪
(thundering)
Oh.
(sighs)
♪
I have to find this CD
to play for you guys.
♪ I gave a slap ♪
♪ You smashed a plate
over my head ♪
♪ Then I set fire to our bed ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ My black eye
casts no shadow ♪
♪ Your red eye sees no blame ♪
♪ Your slaps don't stick, ♪
your kicks don't hit ♪
Excuse me.
Huh?
Hi, um, I've been
assigned this room.
You need to leave.
(all laughing)
Oh... wow, communal.
Well, it's bed number five
or the corridor.
Your choice, mate.
Move your stinking socks,
Drippy.
(girls continue chattering)
Ugh.
Gross.
You lock away your chocolate?
Key information,
if it's the Wagon Wheel
versus the Rolex,
the Wagon Wheel is going
to trounce it every time.
What's a Wagon Wheel?
Jesu Christi,
you have not lived.
Ew.
That's carbs and sugar.
What a revelation.
I had no idea.
Mm.
(cell phone beeping)
What the bleep is that?
None of your bleeping business.
It's an iPhone.
Good luck getting a signal.
We only have two hot spots
that work 'round here.
Maybe you should try entering
the 21st Century, Buck Rogers.
This place is medieval.
It's imperative
that I make my phone calls.
It's pointless anyway.
Only allowed mobiles
on weekends.
How am I supposed
to call my therapist.
(scoffs)
She's joking, right?
Oh, sweetheart, this is not
Beverly Hills 90210.
Just put it away
before Matron catches you.
Where's your trunk.
It hasn't been delivered yet.
♪
No...
Ah!
No!
Ew.
No, no, no.
Not the new season Gucci.
The Choos! No!
This is all only hand-washable.
This is ridiculous.
Uh, why?
What? I might get thirsty.
You know, in the U.K.,
we have this amazing thing--
It's called a tap.
Oh.
Welcome back, girls.
Oh, good, staff.
How quickly can you
get all this stuff cleaned?
-Is she...
-Mm-hmm. American.
Oh, yes.
We had one of those in 1997.
Not good.
Oh. Accustom her to my rules,
and she should be in the correct
uniform for a start.
Mobile phones, please, girls.
Thank you, Kiki.
Thank you, Josie.
Thank you, Kate.
Whoa! Hands off, mama!
I said hands off!
Habla Espanol?
Po si to Italiano?
I am Scottish, not remedial.
Good, then you understand.
Line-dry, press.
No starch, and no creases.
How dare you.
No mufti for a week?
Fine. Mufti might be
your thing, lady,
but it sure ain't mine.
She means no home clothes
for a week.
Like I give a shit.
-Huh?
-I'll be gone by then.
Language!
Two Sundays detention
for the whole dorm.
(all groan)
I'll deal with this.
-Look, hey, hey.
-Huh?
Here's a Ben Franklin.
Why don't you go out and buy
yourself-Well, anything.
Whatever you get will be
a serious improvement.
Three Sundays for everyone.
(all moan)
Thanks a lot for that,
you utter moron.
-What, are you mental?
-What?
She was a grade one A-hole with
a severe attitudinal problem.
The bell's gonna go in a minute.
Just put your uniform on.
(scoffs)
(bell rings)
(all) Now!
You will never get away with
that uniform for start,
and FYI, no drinking,
no smoking, no alcohol,
no fireworks,
no dangerous weapons,
no illegal drugs.
If you have a problem
with someone,
no random bitching.
Structure your point.
No Web-surfing, no bullying.
So, if you behave like
an asshole, we all suffer.
So do not get us in your shit,
or we will break you.
Oh, I'm scared.
-Hi, Kate!
-Hello.
What are you, like, prom queen
or something?
Kate's got
a terrible affliction.
You're actually lucky
that you don't have it.
It's called "popularity".
Hey, get up.
Wait for Mrs. Kingsley
and the prefects.
Screw them.
That is physical abuse!
I'm calling my lawyer!
With what?
Well, hello, Freddie.
How kind of you to grace us
with your gorgeous presence.
And cue Harriet
in three, two, one.
Subject's moved in on target.
And we have contact.
(both) Walk, Annabelle.
(bell chimes)
I love that Freddie's always
here at the beginning of term.
It's such a perfect
welcome back.
So, who is Freddie?
Mrs. Kingley's son.
Devastating heartthrob.
Won't look at any of us
since he got caught
playing doctors and nurses
with a girl in the third grade
when he was 11.
Massive hoo-hah.
They're not together now,
though.
Because of her massive hoo-hah?
(all laughing)
No. Fraternizing is forbidden.
Here you go.
I can't eat this.
Anorexia or bulimia.
Because if it's bulimia,
I'd rather you didn't
eat other people's birthday cake
on their birthdays.
It's such a waste.
Actually, I'm a pescetarian
Monday through Wednesday,
fruitarian Thursday
through Sunday,
and vegetarian always.
Oh.
(bell chimes)
(all) For what we're about
to receive...
Nam ring-eye kie.
Nam ringee kee.
(all) Amen.
Namaste.
Get out of my way.
Hey, watch the 'shmere,
girlfriend.
Two hundred goats died for this.
We meet again. How sublime.
Learn the rules.
When it comes to right-of-way,
there is a hierarchy.
Teachers, prefects, scholars,
dogs, vermin, Americans.
Kate, see to it
she falls in line.
What is this place, Hogwarts?
Bedtime, girls.
Night.
The correct school uniform.
Wear it. Bed.
Poppy Moore, bed, now!
♪
Bonjour!
(all) Bonjour,
Monsieur  Nellist.
Right.
Translation today, everyone.
So, uh, PDF,
pretty damn straightforward.
Uh, ergo,  uh, which means?
Anyone?
Ergo.
Oh, Mr. Nellist?
Yes, Drippy?
Uh, leave.
Luddite.
No, it means "therefore",
Drippy.
Therefore, you'll
probably finish early,
which means that, uh,
you'll have lots of time
to ask me questions about
my trip to Champagne
with my girlfriend.
Who's now suddenly
my-my ex-girlfriend.
Though she was my girlfriend
at the time.
(girls giggling)
(whispers) Embarrassing.
Put your headphones on.
♪
Hi, guys.
You don't happen to have
any eyebrow tint, do you?
(all) No.
You guys have any eyebrow tint?
(music playing
through headphones)
Apparently, California girls
wax their bums.
What? Why?
To look Brazilian.
Makes it look more attractive.
If you say so.
Do you think she's done it?
Hundred percent.
She's definitely done
the missionary
and almost certainly
the Lebanese fulcrum.
I can tell.
How?
From the angle of her hips.
Can I help you?
Is there a problem?
How many boys have you shagged?
Well, there was Brandon,
Eight-pack. Uh, Chase, Jock.
Tyler, Bajillionaire. Derek...
He was Kelly Slater's cousin...
and, um, oh, Jack.
He was all-around sick.
Christ.
I mean, sick body, sick mind.
(gasps) Shit! Kate!
Sorry, Drip,
it looked lighter on the box.
Oh!
(groaning)
That is butters!
Better not stop me
pulling at the social.
Honey, eyebrows are the least
of your worries.
Lights out, girls.
Everyone into bed.
-Night, Matron.
-Night.
Oh!
Hey, switch that off.
No wireless. Should've known.
Internet is only allowed
in the computer room.
Whoa! We are not allowed
out of bed after lights out.
-Oh, look.
-Hey!
-They're not out.
-What are you doing?
Get back into bed!
"Dear Ruby, oh, my God.
Two weeks in this place,
and I'm going out of my mind.
These girls
are all ugly losers,
who think a mani-pedi is
some kind of Latin greeting."
Oh.
Mmm.
Ew.
(alarm rings)
Come on! Fire practice!
Shit!
Remove yourselves
to the quad immediately!
Come on, you know the drill,
for goodness sakes.
Come on, stop being so slovenly.
Hurry up, Kiki.
Ew.
Come on, girls, hurry up!
What if it was a real fire?
You'd all be burned to a crisp!
(water splashes)
Hey, who's there?
Uh, Poppy.
Last name.
Moore. Poppy Moore, sir.
Well, Moore, Poppy Moore,
this is a fire practice.
Sorry. I'm-I'm new here.
Yes, that's obvious.
But weren't you listening
in physics class?
Fire tends to be hot
and the point is to avoid it.
Okay. Where do I go?
Out the door, turn left,
and down the stairs.
Run towards the bright orange,
uh, flickery thing, right?
Oh, and, uh,
try not to get caught.
Excellent point, sir.
♪
Lovely, Harriet.
Hi, Poppy.
♪ Check my coat in
and I paid a dollar ♪
♪ Side-Kick rings,
what's up? holla! ♪
♪ Text the address,
I'll see you later ♪
♪ Baby come down ♪
Ew!
♪ Come down,
come down, come down ♪
♪ Run down, run down,
run down ♪
♪ Run, duck and run,
duck and run, duck and run ♪
♪ Duck and run down ♪
Crack on, team!
Lovely stick work, Harriet.
(shoes squeaking)
Hey!
Mr. Nellist.
Finito.
Well, super, super effort.
We may not win the championship,
but we'll win a lot
of friends, yeah?
So bloody English.
Ha ha ah! Really?
And you could do better?
Laugh it up.
But I could whip all
of your asses blindfolded.
This I'd love to see.
Oh, it's on like Donkey Kong.
Do your worst, horse face.
(hisses)
(cat shrieks)
(breathing loudly)
(whistle blows)
(screams)
Foul! Body check! Body check!
Aah!
-Please!
-(whistle blows)
(horn honks)
Totally illegal.
Shouldn't you guys
be in bikinis for that?
Hi, Fredster. Dig the car.
(engine revs)
Hello, Moore. Poppy Moore.
Hi. Uh... hey!
Bye.
Oh, do you love Fredster?
Do you wanna kiss Fredster
on the lips?
Don't be so immature.
Don't try and hide it, honey.
We've got ourselves a SULA.
Sweaty Upper Lip Alert.
(girls giggle)
Oh!
How on earth did Freddie
know her name?!
You may depart.
But, um, I still have
to turn down your bed.
-Get out!
-(sobs)
Oh!
I don't understand.
Freddie's got a crush on me.
Why was he looking at her?
He was looking at her
so he didn't come across
as looking at you.
He needs to be careful.
He can't get caught.
Yeah, and if he
looked at you too much,
he wouldn't be able
to control himself.
Like, when I have to look sad,
I think about...
...horses being slaughtered.
So, to Freddie,
Poppy's the equivalent
to a slaughtered horse.
You're probably right.
But we're going to have
to do something
about little Miss U.S.A.
She needs a lesson in exactly
who's boss, me thinks.
(both) We think so, too.
I didn't start it,
it wasn't my fault.
-Go out and close the door.
-But you asked to see me!
Yes. Well, you have
to knock before you enter.
I can't believe it.
This is all horse face's fault.
(knocking)
Who is it?
-Jesus Christ.
-Oh, dear.
We were led to believe
you had a beard and sandals.
Now we'll have to change
that stained glass window
in the school chapel.
Look, I didn't start it,
it wasn't my fault,
and if this were America,
I would sue.
That girl is a grade one A-hole,
with severe attitudinal
problems.
I know perfectly well
what happened, Poppy.
Then why isn't
Harriet here, too.
Because, unsurprisingly,
it's you I want to talk to.
Look, I know it's very difficult
being the only new girl
in your year.
You mean the only normal girl.
What do you like to read, Poppy?
"OK Magazine," "People,"
"US Weekly."
Well, might you be able to
tackle such a thing as a book?
I prefer movies.
Well, my personal library
seems to be missing
the book version
of "Freaky Friday."
(scoffs)
So perhaps you might try this.
Oh, my uncle's producing
the film version.
"Alice in Wonderland"
was originally a book.
You might surprise yourself
and actually enjoy it.
This is my punishment?
(scoffs)
This school is so weird.
What do you want to get
out of this school, Poppy?
To get "out" of this school.
You know, this school
has produced
absolutely nobody of note.
Our leading light was the girl
who was
Princess Diana's foot doctor.
So, if your aim
is to make pages of "Us Weekly",
then isn't the place for you.
What we do produce is smart,
independent, free-thinking,
good-hearted girls,
who remain friends for life.
The kind of girl that,
behind all your wisecracks,
I know you are.
Run along now, I must get on.
My in-tray is piling up.
(cat purrs)
♪
Not brown enough.
More coffee.
Ugh. More elbow grease.
You're aging these clothes,
not stirring your tea.
I need complete authenticity.
(sighs)
Charlotte heard Freddie say
I looked exactly like
Keira Knightly.
Right. That's done.
Empty the water.
Not that way, fool.
You'll spill it. Out the window.
-Out the window?
-Just get on with it.
Are you sure?
(screams)
-(gasps)
-So sorry.
Just can't trust
the help these days.
Do you have a pass to be out
during lessons?
Oh, yeah, I do.
It's-it's right here!
Well, don't walk on the grass!
♪
(sighs)
For the tenth time,
you need to make your bed.
Jesus, what's so bloody hard?
Pick up, put down.
It's not rocket science.
Sit down, I'll do that.
Thanks.
You're freezing,
you need a jumper.
Whatever that is,
I don't think I have one.
I don't think I have anything
thicker than prosciutto.
Thanks.
I didn't really come prepared.
Didn't figure
I'd be here this long.
Nothing worse than
the only message you get
all day being from
the phone company.
But Matron took all the phones.
No. She took all your phones.
She took our decoys.
She has no idea
that none of them work.
We keep our real phones hidden.
(cell phone beeps)
Here.
Call your parents,
call your therapist.
Knock yourself out.
But why would you
do this for me?
I mean, you think
I'm a total asshole.
No. You behave like an asshole.
There's a difference.
Look, I know that
I'm not some Malibu therapist,
but I can guess that you're
feeling scared
and a little bit homesick.
Which, in my experience,
doesn't actually make you
a bad person.
Just a normal one.
Sweet photo.
Is it your mum?
Is she gonna come out and visit?
She died in a car accident
when I was 11.
Oh.
Poppy, I'm so sorry.
I know you're not some
Malibu therapist, but, um...
Listen, are you serious about
getting out of here?
Yeah.
Then you're gonna have
to get yourself expelled.
Okay.
"Anybody disporting themselves
in an improper manner
will be proposed for expulsion
before the Honor Court."
Wait, Honor Court?
It's like a trial,
in front of the whole school,
by your peers, your teachers,
the head girl,
and Mrs. Kingsley.
But, I'm telling you,
it hardly ever happens.
If you really wanna
get expelled,
you can't just rock the boat.
You have to drive it up
onto the rocks,
set fire to the galley,
and dance on the burning deck.
You have to take it all the way.
Aye, aye, Captain.
Make your calls.
Oh, tip for best reception.
On top of the cupboard.
Hi, Ruby, I miss you.
I'm gonna escape, though,
I promise you.
You have no idea
what it's like here.
Ew! Who is she?
Zero lip-gloss upkeep
and what's with the sweater
from Target?
I wish you could
come and rescue me.
Oh, she is such
a romantic, Roddy.
Take care of Roddy for me.
(phone beeps)
You already have.
Let's hit the pool.
(creaking)
(cat meows)
(gasps)
(screams)
Watch it, Wee Willie Winkie,
you'll set us all alight.
I've had a word with the girls.
True, some of them took a little
more convincing than others,
but it's decided.
We're gonna help you.
We're your very own crack unit.
Operation Freedom.
Kiki, please explain.
Right. We'll commence with
an entry-level basic favorite,
just to get warmed up.
It smells like pee in here.
Does not smell like--
Bonjour, les filles.
(all) Bonjour,
Monsieur  Nellist.
(Kiki)
But it's not good just playing
the same old tricks.
Try to be
as imaginative as possible.
Only do things that will
get you noticed.
Vary your targets
as much as you can.
And although we'll
all be helping you,
the important thing
to remember...
(phone rings) Harriet?
...is that you have to get
the blame for everything.
Run along.
Speaking.
Headphones on, girls.
Come on, everybody.
Don't run too fast
in your flip-flops.
We'll just jump in,
have a quick paddle about,
warm up, then have tea
and crumpets, yes?
Yes, I'm in school right now.
Regulation uniform?
Skirt just below the knee.
(scoffs)
Of course.
They are simple polyester,
sturdy and practical.
No, I have certainly
not been naughty.
My disciplinary record
is exemplary.
Are you okay?
(phone clanks)
-Get out!
(chattering)
(whistle blowing)
(all repeating in French)
(gasps)
(stammers)
Uh, yes, thank-thank you
very much.
That's it, thank you.
(Kiki) If you make enough
of a nuisance of yourself...
Poppy... Moore!
...she will eventually bow
to pressure,
and she'll have
to call your father.
Naturally, I'll call her father,
but she's had a difficult time.
No, Sara, please,
it's all right.
-Mr. Nellist.
-Oh, uh, sorry.
(Kiki) And then with any luck,
she'll recommend you
to the Honor Court.
Unbe-bloody-lievable!
She's got more lives
than a Buddhist cat.
Kingley's not even mentioned
Honor Court.
I think people
are starting to like her.
People?
People can learn to get used
to rotting pig's vomit,
if they live with it
for long enough.
I believe she's trying to leave.
It'd be a nightmare
if she stayed.
She makes
a mockery of the system.
She's not staying,
take it from me.
Five generations of my family
have made the school great.
The school motto is
"scholarship,
fellowship, loyalty,"
not "be a slutty, whorey,
shit-brain."
(both) So brillianté, Harriet.
(sobbing)
I'm only sorry it can't be
something stronger.
Cup of tea.
(giggling)
Quick, give me the tape.
Give me the tape.
Pull the button off.
Oh, my God, there's a car.
-Get out.
-Quick.
(car approaches)
Whoa. It's all right,
Cerberus, it's only me.
Who's Cerberus?
The dog that guards
the gates of hell.
(whispering)
Hurry up,
or you'll disturb my girls.
(girls wooing)
-(sneezes)
-Huh?
(sneezes)
Sorry, terrible allergies.
(groaning)
(mimics farting sound)
Uh, sorry.
Better an empty house
than an angry tenant, right?
Hmph.
I don't get it.
It's like you've got immunity.
Your dad's a mafia guy
or something.
Yep, I'm the "goddaughter."
Whatever it is, she's cutting
you a lot of slack.
We need to up the ante.
In fact, we need to focus on
her big weakness.
Oh, my God,
you have to snog Freddie.
Snog? That sounds disgusting.
What is that?
It's English for make out.
Mrs. Kingsley will go ballistic.
And Harriet would have
an absolute fit.
Well, that's a definite bonus.
And he'll be at the social.
Cool.
Just remember,
the point is to get caught.
All right, so what's the deal
with the social?
It's the school dance
on Saturday night.
Traditionally, it's fancy dress.
This year it's movie magic.
But the only ones who
bother to dress up are teachers,
morons, and Harriet.
I say we dress up fancy.
Real fancy.
This mission needs to be
planned precisely.
Kiki?
Okay. Operation Freedom,
part two, step one.
Attract Freddie.
Step one, subsection "A",
look the part.
Kiki, you're actually making
something quite exciting
sound like physics homework.
Basically, we're going
into town,
and we're gonna get
some killer outfits.
I want something
that says elegant,
but at the same time
incredibly slutty and available.
In fact, I'm not that bothered
about elegance.
(all laughing)
♪
"So, apparently,
the key is to hook up
with the headmistress' son.
I'll do your trick, Rubes,
swing my hips and giggle."
Oh, come on, Poppy,
we're gonna miss the bus.
Don't forget to log off now,
you ninny.
Everyone, sign out.
Remember you are representatives
of the school.
Sign your own name, come on.
Poppy Moore,
what are you wearing?
You are going to town,
not appearing in a window
in Amsterdam.
Change immediately.
I don't have anything else.
I thought you might
be quite concerned
by that attire, Matron.
So we had a little look-see
in lost property
on our way here, didn't we?
(both) We did.
It'll suit you,
promise.
Arf, arf, arf.
(girls giggling) That's cute.
My grandma used to have a dog
just like it.
Poppy, I think your jumper
is the cat's pajamas.
Come on, girls, in you go,
hurry up.
Upstairs to the seats.
Don't push. Don't push.
Plenty of room.
Come on, here we go.
-Poppy!
-Come on, Poppy!
-Poppy, jump!
-I can't find my sanitizer!
I can't find my sanitizer!
You left it in the dorm!
Oh, my God, no!
Oh, my God!
(all) Run!
(all laughing)
Ew!
(all) Ew!
(all laughing)
(all talking at once)
(heavy metal music playing)
Oh, my God, look.
(dog barking)
-Oh.
-Hi!
Ew. Gross.
Where are we going?
To our favorite shop.
Cancer research?
Girls, I'm all about
finding a cure,
but considering
I flunked chemistry,
I don't know how much help
I'm gonna be.
And BTW, which FYI means
"by the way,"
this is supposed
to be shopping time.
We're not gonna be
doing  the research.
This is a charity shop.
The money goes to charity.
Oh, I just had
a heart palpitation.
You guys are so adorable,
but we need to look
really hot for the social.
So let's go hit Oxford Street.
I take it
you flunked geography, too.
Oxford Street is in London,
my friend.
This is your lot.
(giggling)
(chattering)
Hey, Kate,
what about this for Ascot?
Magnificent.
Is this too workaday?
(sighs)
Come on now, girls,
this is a serious mission.
Get a move on.
Now, Poppy, how about
something like this?
Fifty pence.
It looks like
someone died in it.
I'd rather stay
the Yorkshire Terrier freak.
You're a Buddhist, right?
Think of it as
clothing reincarnation.
Honey, even Buddha wouldn't be
caught dead in half this stuff.
Still, I guess
anything's possible.
Come on, let's do this.
♪ It was so easy that night ♪
♪ Should've been strong,
yeah, I lied ♪
♪ Nobody gets me like you ♪
♪ I know everything changes ♪
♪ For the city and faces ♪
♪ But I know
how I feel about you ♪
♪ Can we bring
yesterday back around? ♪
♪ 'Cause I know how I feel
about you now ♪
♪ I was dumb, I was wrong,
I let you down ♪
♪ But I know how
I feel about you now ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
Unbelievable, this season Marni.
It's sophisticated,
it's elegant.
-Hot to trot.
-Check.
If we could just
call this stuff vintage
and add like three zeroes
to the price tag,
I could totally get into it.
Perfection.
Operation Freddie is well
and truly underway.
Malibu moment!
Remember what I taught you guys?
(all) Who are we?
(camera shutter clicks)
I think he's down a penny black.
Yes, dated prewar.
(chattering)
Oh, my God! It's Tom Cruise.
Would you like
to say any louder?
I need your help.
And I need a back wax
and a night with Michael Bublé,
but we don't always
get what we want.
Trudy, attend to the brows.
Mmm. Yorkie fan.
It's a nice dog, Yorkie.
I used to have one once.
Wee Phillippe.
Got savaged to death
by a badger.
Ow!
Mm.
Aren't you the soufflé
that didn't arise?
Tell me about it.
Okay, I need these
extensions taken out,
a serious deep conditioning.
I'm thinking side bangs
with some buttery highlights,
and maybe a few honey tones.
Oh! And I'd like a night
on Fireman Island,
but I'm afraid
I'm whistling Dixie, okay?
So, here's what's
on offer for you.
A tight perm.
-No.
-How about this?
A wee bob. That's fun, isn't it?
-No.
-Okay.
What about this?
Oh, a pineapple.
Oh, Hawaii.
No.
What about something
a little bit more natural?
Natural?
Aye. The real you.
Hmm.
Natural it is.
Radical.
Okay, ladies, let's do this.
♪
All right,
I'll need that, that, that.
Mm.
(motor hums)
Oh, oh! Oh, no.
Look it. Mmm.
That's not mine. Hmm, nope.
Hey, Mommy,
two strong teas, please.
Bella pronto.
Don't you look at me like that.
(scissors clipping)
Nix that.
You ready, hen?
-Um-hm.
-Okay.
-Et voila.
-Wow.
Thank you.
Oh, you're welcome, darling.
I'm cream-crackered.
I'll lay down
and have a wee Satsuma.
-You look so--
-English.
I look like my mom.
Is she beautiful, too?
She was... very.
Sorry. Foot-in-mouth disease.
(giggling)
Okay, time for the juice.
Any bright ideas?
Leave it to me, I've got a plan.
(bell chimes)
So, Susan, do you like
your new office?
I don't know what's worse,
my job or that husband of mine.
Keith from accounts
is driving me crazy.
He wants that report
on his desk by Thursday.
What's the report about?
Oh, um, business.
(whispers) What?
Do you want to buy
a carpet tomorrow?
Yes, after I've dropped
the kids off at the pool...
...in my saloon car.
Two bottles of Grizinksy
and one of Donmatsa, please.
Oh, and two crème eggs, please.
(groans)
Why did you order
the crème eggs, you idiot?
Why did you only get two,
Drippy?
Now we've got to quarter them?
He believed us till then.
Oh, yeah, right.
Maybe if you hadn't asked me
what Keith's report was about.
Where's Poppy?
-Are you okay?
-I'm furious.
Stupid Drippy.
I know. Never mind, let's go.
♪ Oh, heaven's
a place on earth ♪
♪
Would you boys like a drink?
Now, anybody here.
Come on.
Hi.
Name's Nellist. Roger Nellist.
Licensed to DJ.
Gosh, you look like James Bond.
I thought you might like
a fruit punch.
Oh, I'll have it shaken
and not stirred.
Oh, right.
Why aren't you dancing?
They're all dressed up,
waiting for you over there.
-Mr. Nellis--
-Harriet's coming.
Right. Yes, yes.
(feedback)
(classical music plays)
Mr. Darcy?
What undue pleasure it is to be
afforded your company.
Hi.
You may only call me Mrs. Darcy
when you're completely,
perfectly, incandescently happy.
Okay. Cool.
Freddie...
...it's me.
Of course, Harriet.
♪
Okay, Poppy, let's get Freddie.
♪ Let me think about it ♪
♪ You saying baby,
I'll take you for a ride ♪
♪ Let's get together
work it all night ♪
♪ I'll be your love,
you sexy look fine ♪
♪ I'll make you feel like
heaven is near ♪
Lips, hips, hips, and butt.
Whoo!
-Hi.
-Hello, trouble.
I like your hair.
What are you doing?
This is a themed costume party,
not a dwarf prostitutes'
convention.
I'm so sorry.
I must say that
you look incredible.
You make an excellent Shrek.
This is my favorite song,
come on.
♪ You don't mean
nothing at all to me ♪
♪ No, you don't mean
(feedback)
♪ Shake you tambourine go
and get yourself a whistling ♪
♪ E.V.E. come through
with a Maseratti ♪
♪ On it big like
I'm living in Taj Mahal ♪
♪ Talk, I don't get
and that blah dee blah ♪
♪ Ha! That's what
they lovin' now ♪
♪ That's real and the chicks
that they talk about ♪
♪ Damn is the words
that come out they mouth ♪
♪ She looks good always
without a doubt ♪
♪ Ask for her
is she back and caking out ♪
♪ Shake you tambourine go
and get yourself a whistling ♪
♪ And, yo, yo ♪
♪ They be watching
while we wiggle around ♪
♪ Look at 'em drooling ♪
♪ They ain't use to the sound,
I keep 'em moving ♪
Go, girlfriend!
That is entirely wicked.
♪ Put you up on your feet
the whole night now ♪
♪ Pop them bottles
and drink that up, man ♪
♪ Got you feeling crazy,
well that was the plan ♪
Oh!
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, you're awesome.
She okay?
Shall I call an ambulance?
You can be sick in my hands
if you'd like.
She's acting like she's drunk.
She should be taken to bed.
Freddie can do the honors.
You really are a horridious
piece of work.
Mr. Darcy don't think so.
She's just a little concussed.
She just needs some air.
-Great idea.
-Come on.
Ugh!
She's up to something.
Follow them. Report back to me.
So, explain yourself,
Miss Moore.
(mimics English accent)
I'm afraid I can't
explain myself, sir...
(in normal voice) ...because I'm
not myself right now you see.
Said Alice to the caterpillar.
You're right, how'd you know?
I was Alice in the school play.
All boys before
you look at me weirdly.
Hey.
You so don't need
to play hard to get.
I'm totally into you.
Hey, come on.
Calm down.
Okay, leading lady,
all-boys school,
awkward with intimacy.
Cards on the table.
-Are you gay?
-(chuckles)
Uh, just English.
And I am sober and sensible.
And you, my sweet friend,
are overexcited and concussed.
I go back to school tomorrow,
but I'll be back on the 18th.
How about I see you then?
Okay.
I'll make a deal.
No more head-fry behavior.
I sense that might be
your forte.
I won't fry your head,
if you don't poach my heart.
Deal.
(Jane clears throat)
Oh, crap.
Tweedledum and Tweedledee.
Fraternizing with the girls,
Freddy Kingsley,
as you are well aware,
is not allowed.
Poppy Moore, get back inside.
Immediately.
Tell Harriet.
She won't just
shoot the messenger,
she'll skin us alive first.
Me think not.
We think not.
Oh.
Nice work, Kate.
So, is Operation Freddie
well and truly underway?
God knows? Harriet didn't come.
So it just depends on whether
Tweedledum or Tweedledee
decide to tell her.
There's nothing to worry about.
-Clearly not.
-Right.
We're gonna have to come up
with an addendum to Plan B.
Isn't it ironic how
my ticket out of here
just might be the reason
I wanna stay?
I mean,
one of the reasons, anyways.
Someone call Al Gore.
I think the ice queen
is melting.
What an excellent night.
Eight boys have actually come up
and directly spoken to me.
Now, for all you
lovers out there.
It's your final chance.
It's the last dance.
Come on!
(chattering)
There's something
I have to tell you.
Oh, we already know.
You wax your bum.
No.
Not quite, but similar ballpark.
You haven't done it, have you?
No. I mean, I couldn't
admit it back home,
so I kind of lied,
but I'm a total nun.
Welcome to the nunnery.
(singing together)
♪ I'm loving angels instead ♪
(all laughing)
Come on, girls.
If we lose today, we're out
of the championship again.
(groaning)
Perhaps you'd like
to explain last night to me.
Kate?
I'm sorry.
We just got a little bit
carried away.
Well, as I understand it,
Drippy got totally carried away
by Mr. Nellist
and Miss ReesWithers,
after she lay in a pool
of her own vomit.
Actually, it was Kate's vomit,
Mrs. Kingsley.
I was just lying in it.
I expect better of you two.
You know the values we stand for
at Abbey Mount.
And as for you, Poppy,
I don't know whether
to be pleased
that you've finally
made some friends here
or furious that you've
led them astray.
Dismissed.
Not you, Miss Moore.
I gave your father my word
that I'd try and help you,
but I'll be honest,
you're making it
awfully difficult.
You're cleverer and better
than this, Poppy.
Why don't you
give yourself a chance?
Try.
Try at something.
Show him that you can rise
to the occasion.
Because, judging by the outfits
you created last night,
when you put your mind
to something you can do it.
Don't give up on yourself.
Because I haven't
and neither has your father.
Now off you go.
Ugh, I really do feel sick.
-What did she want?
-Oh, nothing.
Just a good spa destination.
Come on, guys!
Come on!
Oh, God, I feel really vile.
I think I'm gonna puke.
Seriously, Poppy, you're gonna
have to take my place.
There's only seven minutes left.
(wretches)
Oh, cripes!
Um...
Poppy can take my place.
Don't worry, Miss Rees-Withers,
we'll play one man down.
We don't want
to carry dead weight.
No offense.
Oh, none taken.
But seeing as how you don't
want me playing on your team,
well, I'm friggin' playing.
Ugh!
-Into the bucket.
-(wretches)
Josie, on the wing!
Poppy, go long!
All right. Wow, okay.
Let's just pretend the ball
is the last size five pair
of Manolos at Barney's.
Okay.
Let's pull it out the bag.
Offense, yeah!
Eyes on the prize.
Aah, Josie!
Eye on the prize. Oh, my God!
Josie, help!
Poppy, roll over it
or pick it up!
-Yeah!
-You go, girlfriend.
Dunk that bitch.
You see the goal, Josie.
Focus, focus.
Do you see the goal?
(cheering)
And, finally,
in news that's shocking
as the fall of the Berlin wall,
our under-18 Lacrosse team
has gone through
to the second round
of the county championships
for the first time since 1976.
(cheering)
To sign up for extra practice,
please see Harriet B--
Oh, my apologies.
No, it seems you should see
Poppy Moore.
(whispering)
All right, people,
choose a goal buddy.
From now on, each sentence
starts with "I will,"
not "I want to."
"I will" want to saliva vomit
if we have to call
each other "buddy".
Shut up. Hit it.
I'm giving us
an aggression makeover.
♪
Go, go, go! Crawl, crawl, crawl!
Who is that? Kiki?
Kiki, get it, get it.
Oh, that's okay. Pick it up.
Scoop it. Pass it, pass it.
Come on, faster, faster, faster!
This is ridiculous.
Come on, play like
you mean it, baby, try.
Call the ball.
"Mine." "I got it." "Your ball."
Come on, Josie.
Pass the ball.
Congratulations, once again,
to our under-18 Lacrosse team
who beat Bodley Girls
on Saturday, five-two.
Well done.
(cheering)
(whistle blows)
Come on, you guys!
Come on, up and together!
Come on, shake it, Kiki.
Come on, come on!
What is this?
(growls)
Whoo!
Good, come on.
Quicker, quicker,
quicker, quicker.
Josie, come on! Josie, yes!
Kiki, go!
Shoot, Kiki, shoot!
And the groundbreaking news
is that Abbey Mount
is through to the lacrosse
championship finals.
"Dear Ruby,
today is my big date with
the headmistress' son, Freddie.
Wish me luck.
I may be out of here
before you know it.
Lover boy's waiting
outside for you.
(giggling)
But, remember, you want
someone to catch you out.
So stay near school
and good luck.
Thanks. Fingers crossed.
Ah, Freddie Kingsley.
Nice to finally see you
when I'm not delirious
-or, uh, half-naked.
-Don't speak too soon.
And is it wrong for me
to say that I'm just
a tiny bit disappointed?
Come on, trouble,
let's hit the road.
Hey, I thought maybe
we could take a romantic stroll
around the school grounds.
(laughs)
And get caught?
Are you out of your mind?
Call me old-fashioned,
but I actually do
quite like living.
I thought you said
you could drive.
It's not my fault
your stupid car doesn't work.
Have you ever thought
of changing gears?
That's the car's job.
Turn right here.
We drive on the left
in this country.
Whatever.
♪ Putting on a front
you might like that ♪
♪ But will you like me
when I'm real ♪
♪ It seems like a long way ♪
♪ A long way to go from here ♪
♪ You think I don't care
but I do ♪
♪ Yeah I do ♪
♪ When you leave me ♪
And so I threw the whole lot
over the cliff.
My dad went mental,
as Drippy would say.
Drippy said I was crazy,
but Kate said she would have
done exactly the same
in my position.
Sorry, chattering away
like this.
Feel free to shut me up.
Well, remind me to never
to get on your bad side.
But the thing is...
I'm pretty sure
you don't have one.
♪ You think I don't care
but I do ♪
♪ Yeah I do ♪
♪ You think I don't care
but I do ♪
Here you go, trouble.
Bread and fries,
that's my treat?
If I affect your life
in no other way,
allow this honor,
The humble chip butty.
Here we go.
Kinda gross, but, um, I like it.
Here.
You know this is
one of the dates...
The best date I've ever had.
There's something
about you Poppy Moore.
Every moment I'm with you,
I catch my breath.
♪ Should I give up ♪
♪ Or should I just
keep chasing pavements? ♪
♪ Even if it leads nowhere ♪
♪ Or would it be a waste
even if I knew my place ♪
♪ Should I leave it there ♪
♪ Should I give up ♪
♪ Or should I just
keep chasing pavements? ♪
Guys, guess what?
You'll never believe it.
What happened?
"Dear Ruby,
you cannot imagine
how retarded these idiots are.
They're a bunch of ugly losers
who think a mani-pedi
is a Latin greeting.
I despise these village idiots,
but I have to pretend
to like them so they'll help me
get out of this hell hole.
I tried doing it on my own,
and it was impossible.
Still they're so sick,
they'll never realize
I'll be out of this asylum
by the end of term."
I didn't write that.
I mean hardly any of it...
just the loser part.
But that was weeks ago.
Well, it's dated today
and it's from
your e-mail address.
Where did you get it?
It was taped to the door.
You're a seriously
horridious cow.
Come on, guys,
you have to believe me.
Just forget it, okay?
Why would you do that?
You can't believe
I actually wrote this.
All we did was try to make
your life here happier, Poppy.
I thought we were friends.
(door closes)
"So, all I have to do
is hook up
with the headmistress' son,
and it's sure thing
that they expel me.
He's a total English dweeb.
Pretty gross,
but an easy target.
Give me a week tops."
(knocking)
I can explain.
Please, I really need
to talk to you.
I can't right now.
You know the limo's
coming in five,
and I have nada to wear.
-Where are you going?
-Nick's house.
Oh, not the Jimmy Choos.
They don't match,
for Christ's sake.
Rubes, I just need some advice.
Something really
bad has happened.
Oh, crap, fashion emergency.
Gotta go, see you soon as.
I love you.
I love you more.
(phone beeps)
Sorry, Roddy,
couldn't get rid of her.
What was I saying?
Roddy? Babe?
No, Ruby, still me, babe.
(phone beeps)
(scoffs)
(dial tone)
(sighs)
Shit!
(screams)
Kate, Kate, quick!
-Wake up, wake up!
-What's wrong now?
I didn't mean to do it,
It was an accident.
I thought I put it out.
I-I thought I'd stopped it.
I don't know what happened.
I didn't want to hurt anybody.
Jesus, Poppy,
you're a proper psycho.
Help me get everyone out
before it spreads.
Josie. Josie, get up.
Josie, there's a fire! Get up!
(fire bell)
Fire, fire! Everyone get up!
Fire! It's a real fire!
Get out of bed!
It's a fire!
This isn't a practice!
Guys, get up!
Come on, darling get up.
It's a fire, it's not a drill.
(sirens)
-Joise!
-No, I'm not getting up.
Get up! On fire!
It's a real fire!
Please, everybody get up!
-Phoebe Faircloff.
-Here.
-Susan Casey.
(Drippy) Let me out! Let me out!
(siren)
-Daisy Bevin?
-Here.
-Can't hear you. Daisy?
Jennifer Logan?
Jennifer?
Has anyone seen Drippy?
Come on, girls.
Who was the last person
to see Drippy?
The freezer.
Drippy's in the freezer!
Hey, stop her!
Drippy! Drippy!
Drippy!
What's going on?
(coughing)
What do you think happened?
Don't know yet.
We're lucky,
could've been a lot worse.
Well done, Poppy, you saved us.
You're brilliant.
Hey. I believe this is yours.
Thank you.
Do you realize
you could've killed her?
Well done, thanks, Poppy.
You could've killed all of us.
I didn't mean to.
I thought I'd stopped it,
I swear.
I don't understand, okay?
I heard footsteps,
and then I put it out.
I was just so upset
at everything,
and I wish
I hadn't have done it.
I really wish you hadn't
done it, too.
Someone here knows exactly
what happened last night.
What we're clear on is
that this fire was no accident.
If you have the sense to own up,
no legal charges will be filed.
If not, it will be passed on
to the local authorities.
You have until the end
of the day to come forward.
"Dear Freddie,
How can I begin
to say I'm sorry?
You are good and honest
and true.
And, well, I'm the opposite.
But I'm learning.
So, now, I'm going
to do the right thing.
And if it means
I have to leave here,
I just want you to know
I promise you
I never wrote that e-mail.
For a moment, there, yeah,
you were my ticket out of here,
but then I got to know you.
I have never felt this way
before about anyone,
and I really need you
to know that."
(sighs)
Come in.
Oh, what can I
do for you, Poppy?
It's what I used to start it.
It was an accident, and,
uh, I thought I put it out.
But I guess not.
Obviously not.
Oh, Poppy.
You realize what this means,
don't you?
Will I be expelled?
The Honor Court will decide,
but I suspect you'll understand
that it's just a formality
at this point.
The weird thing is I really
did try to turn it around.
I didn't want to disappoint you.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, too, Poppy.
Uh, do you think maybe
you could give this
to Freddie for me?
I told her it was me.
I'm going to the Honor Court
and then I'll be leaving.
So, this is for you.
Well done.
You finally got what you wanted.
You must be overjoyed.
I couldn't be more unhappy.
Oh, please, give it a rest.
Mom?
Hey, I've been looking for you.
Hi.
So, you're backed out
of our deal.
What deal?
That you wouldn't fry my head.
Yeah.
But you poached my heart.
Hey, come on.
What if it doesn't have a moral?
Or says Alice.
I think I just fell down
the rabbit hole and found it.
Look.
She looks exactly like you.
Yeah. She was my mom.
She went to this school.
I didn't even know.
Well, I guess it's time
to face the music now.
(all talking at once)
Josie, I'm never wrong.
When am I ever wrong?
You're wrong when we did
the math challenge.
Hey! She's confessed.
She's going to Honor Court
this afternoon.
That's brave.
And really stupid.
Because guess what
I've discovered.
It is with
great regret and sadness
that we call the Honor Court
to session.
The e-mails were sent
11:40 in the morning.
But, according to Drippy,
Poppy left the computer room
a few minutes after 11:00.
I got my 11:00 Wagon Wheel,
and then I went to tell her
that Freddie was waiting.
She left immediately.
I was able to access
the keystroke order
of the root file
to find out who else
was logged on there then.
And guess who
the only other person was?
Who?
It will henceforth
be our job to objectively
and dispassionately ascertain
what happened
that fateful night.
That will hence to forth
long blight the memory
of this proud institution.
When you think about it,
Poppy would never say "term".
She calls it a bloody samosa
or something.
-Semester.
-Whatever.
Anyway, to check the reality,
I had a sneaky look in her diary
for Friday's entry.
Don't do that.
Shut up and listen.
"I think, deep breath,
I kind of love them
like proper friends
I've known forever.
They've made me say words
like 'horridious' and 'herbal.'
Which is sort of whack,
and I'd probably hate them
if I wasn't one of them.
But I like that
I'm now one of them."
Apart from some
atrocious spelling mistakes,
it's a little bit more kosher,
don't you think?
And now she's
gonna get thrown out.
It is your duty
to understand the dark forces
that drove a seemingly--
Harriet.
May I remind you
that the Honor Court is no place
for your personal grandstanding.
Look, Poppy has a right
to speak in her own defense
before the court, as a whole,
passes judgment.
Thank you, Mrs. Kingsley.
I won't insult everybody
by trying to defend myself
or my actions.
So, uh, I think
it's safe to say that I've...
I've really messed up,
and I apologize profusely.
But I'm also so grateful
to you all.
I tried really hard
to get out of this school.
And, only now, do I realize
just how much I want to stay.
I've learned so much being here,
being with all of you.
And, in some ways,
being with my mom,
who I found out was actually
a student here.
(whisperings)
I've had a hole in my heart
for five years,
and somehow being here,
it slowly started to heal.
I know I may have looked
like a California girl,
but in my heart I've discovered
that I really am
an Abbey Mount girl.
Objection! Sustained.
The court will
heretofore disregard
the previous statement.
And perhaps heretofore we can
begin the real business.
Can you tell us,
in your own words,
where were you on
the aforementioned evening of--
Honestly, Harriet, who else's
words do you expect her to use?
Just leave this to me.
Right.
Sustained.
Poppy, were you in
the cook's sitting room
-on the night of the fire?
-Yes, I was.
Were you there with permission?
No, I was not.
(whispering) Quiet, please.
Silence in court.
Did you intend
on starting a fire?
-Not really.
-Objection!
Does the defendant
mean yes or no?
-Harriet?
-It means no.
I had no intention
of actually doing it.
Was anyone else with you?
Not as far as I know.
I was.
-I was.
(all) I was.
Objection! Stop!
Order!
-I was.
-Stop it!
-Come on.
I was.
This is ridiculous!
What are you all doing?
You're lying.
They're lying, Mrs. Kingsley.
Harriet, you're going down,
biatch.
This is a conspiracy.
You can't expel the whole year,
and they know that.
Be quiet, Harriet!
Sit down, everyone.
It's a black-and-white case.
She has to be expelled.
The girl set fire to the school,
endangering
all our precious lives.
She walked in there,
lighter at the ready,
and tried to burn
the place down.
Lighter?
Not now, Jane.
Have respect for court protocol.
What lighter, Harriet?
Jesus, Charlotte,
how daft can you possibly be?
That ridiculous I heart L.A.
lighter of hers.
She left it behind,
for God's sakes.
Except how do you know that,
Harriet?
No one's mentioned
a lighter before.
(whispers) What?
Yes, they have.
Objection.
Actually, Harriet, they haven't.
I have to second
Jane's question, Harriet.
How did you know about
that lighter?
Well, I-I had--
Freddie found the lighter
before anyone saw it.
How could you
possibly know unless...
unless you were there.
Well, this is absurd.
I refuse to sit here
and listen to these wild--
I had put it out.
And I heard footsteps.
It must've been you.
Oh, my God, you restarted
the fire, didn't you?
Harriet, is this true?
Of course not.
It all makes sense now,
I knew it.
I think I'm innocent.
(both) We think so, too.
You're not, you awful bitch!
You've turned this school
upside down.
You've ruined everything!
You started it.
I only finished
what you started!
Harriet?
My office, now.
Uh...
(whispering)
♪
(cheering)
Okay, suckers, show time.
Let's open a can of whoop-ass.
Come on, Abbey Mount.
You can do it!
Let's go Abbey Mount!
Come on, girls.
Take it! Come on!
(cheering)
(whistle blowing)
Come on, guys,
we can bring it back.
Let's go.
(whistle blows)
You got it!
Mrs. Kingsley?
Oh, Mr. Moore, you made it.
Yes, I did.
Please, please,
come and take a seat.
-Did I miss much?
-Not at all.
Where's Poppy?
She's right there.
She's the spitting image
of her mother, isn't she?
She most certainly is.
Come on, Abbey Mount!
Take it out there!
Come on! Come on, Poppy!
Come on!
(cheering)
Come on, Abbey Mount! Let's go!
(whistle blows)
♪ Two, four, six, eight ♪
♪ Stowe girls
are really great ♪
♪ Two, four, six, eight ♪
♪ Stowe girls
are really great ♪
You're trying really hard.
It's great, great, great.
I know, and...
They've got no possession
whatsoever.
(all laughing)
All right, ladies.
There's only one thing for it.
Let's go.
Who are we?
(all) Abbey Mount!
-(all) Abbey Mount!
-What are we?
A leading single-sex school
admitting boarders at age 11.
Wrong! We're winners!
♪
(all yelling)
♪ Set 'em up, set 'em up ♪
♪ Knock 'em down down ♪
♪ Set 'em up, knock 'em down ♪
♪ Back 'em up off me,
don't even try me ♪
♪ Because I'm the tiger ♪
♪ Stand and drop and sting
like a viper ♪
♪ Manhandle
your whole team like a vandal ♪
Pass it, Poppy!
♪ I made the beat,
we raise the stakes ♪
♪ You're just afraid
we formulatin' ♪
(cheering)
Well done, well done.
♪ Set them, set them up ♪
♪ Abbey Mount! Abbey Mount! ♪
♪ Set them up ♪
♪ Then knock 'em down, down ♪
♪ Then knock 'em down, down, ♪
♪ We set 'em up,
like you can knock 'em down ♪
Come on, Poppy!
(all) Ha!
Ha!
(cheering)
(all yelling)
This is our last chance,
let's make it count!
(whistle blowing)
Kiki!
Drippy!
Why would you pass it to me?
Oh, my God!
Okay, somebody help me!
Where is everyone?
Who do I pass it to?
Jane, Jane!
-Where are you?
-Oops!
(screams)
(cheering)
(whistle blows)
They did it! They did it!
Yes!
I told you you could do it!
I told ya!
Poppy?
Dad?
My dad. My dad!
What are you doing here?
Mrs. Kingsley called.
She told me you found out
about Mom.
Why didn't you
just tell me, Dad?
I'm sorry, Poppy. I thought
it might make you too sad.
I did know that you needed
to breathe a different kind
of air, though.
Did I do the right thing?
You did.
Did you know Mom was captain
of the Lacrosse team?
Yes.
And I also know that
she is incredibly proud
of you right now.
As am I.
Daddy, put your back into it!
(Jane and Charlotte) Harriet,
we think you forgot this.
Me thinks so, too.
Mummy!
♪
♪ Well, I'm just outta school ♪
♪ Acting real, real cool ♪
Who are we?
♪ But the message is
I gotta be a wild one ♪
♪ Oh yeah I'm a wild one ♪
♪ Gonna break it loose ♪
♪ Gonna keep 'em moving wild ♪
♪ Gotta keep it swingin' baby ♪
♪ I'm a real wild child ♪
♪ Me and all my friends
gonna have ourselves a ball ♪
-♪ Gonna tell my friends ♪
-Fire!
♪ Gonna tell 'em all
I'm a wild one ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, I'm a wild one ♪
♪ Girl I'm breakin' loose ♪
♪ Gonna keep 'em moving wild ♪
♪ Gonna keep it swingin' baby ♪
♪ I'm a wild child,
I'm a wild one ♪
♪ I'm a wild one,
♪ I'm a wild, wild one ♪
♪ I'm a wild one, oh yeah ♪
♪ I'm a wild one ♪
♪ Gonna break it loose ♪
♪ Gonna keep 'em moving wild ♪
♪ Gotta keep it swingin' baby ♪
♪ I'm a real wild child ♪
♪ I'm a wild one,
I'm a wild one ♪
Ugh, make it bloody SULA.
♪ I'm a wild one ♪
(cell phone rings)
Who's Ruby?
Huh! Nobody.
Just some horridious cow
I used to know.
♪ I'm a real wild one
and I like the wild fun ♪
♪ In a world gone crazy,
everything seems hazy
♪ I'm a wild one ♪
-Can't do it.
-No way.
You're completely insane.
-Are you guys ready?
-No.
One, two, three!
(all scream)
♪ I'm a real wild child ♪
♪ I'm a wild one,
I'm a wild, wild one ♪
♪ I'm a wild, I'm a wild one ♪
♪ I'm a wild one,
wild, wild one ♪
♪ I'm a wild one I'm one ♪
♪ Gonna break it loose ♪
♪ Gonna keep 'em moving wild ♪
♪ Gotta keep it swingin' baby ♪
♪ I'm a real wild child ♪
♪ I'm a wild one ♪
♪ Gonna break it loose ♪
♪ Gonna keep 'em moving wild ♪
♪ Gotta keep it swingin' baby ♪
♪ I'm a real wild child ♪
♪ I'm a wild one,
a real wild child ♪
I'm a real wild child ♪
♪ I'm a wild one, oh, yeah ♪
♪ I'm a wild one ♪
♪ Gonna break it loose ♪
♪ Gonna keep 'em moving wild ♪
♪ Gotta keep it swingin' baby ♪
♪ I'm a real wild child ♪
♪
♪ Whoa! Whoa! ♪
♪ Set 'em up, whoa! ♪
♪ Whoa! Set 'em up,
then knock 'em down ♪
♪ Whoa! Whoa! ♪
♪ Set 'em up, set 'em up ♪
♪ Then knock 'em down, down ♪
♪ You back up off me,
don't even try me ♪
♪ Because I'm the tiger ♪
♪ Stand and drop
and sting like a viper ♪
♪ Manhandle your whole team
like a vandal ♪
♪ We comin' back and bringin'
the heat just like a vandal ♪
♪ I make the deeds,
we raise the stakes ♪
♪ You're just afraid,
we formulatin' a plan ♪
♪ And then we break,
break, break ♪
♪ Whoa! Whoa! ♪
♪ Set 'em up, set 'em up ♪
♪ Then knock 'em down ♪
♪ Then knock 'em down, down ♪
♪ We set 'em up like skittles
then knock 'em down pound ♪
♪ Down like thunder,
what's your number ♪
♪ Little zero,
don't play the hero ♪
♪ You weigh a kilo plus a ton ♪
♪ You better run son
'cause you're done ♪
♪ Can't relate the beats ♪
♪ ♪Better pump up, wild child ♪
♪ Now feel the draft
as it comes down ♪
♪ You thought
you were winning ♪
♪ But now the table's
turned 'round ♪
♪ Now set 'em on 'em now ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Set 'em up, set 'em up ♪
♪ Then knock 'em down ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Set 'em up, set 'em up ♪
♪ Then knock 'em down ♪
♪ Yo, whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Set 'em up, set 'em up ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Then knock 'em down ♪
♪ Get ready for war,
we're ready for war ♪
♪ We're kickin' the rug,
ripping the place up ♪
♪ Like a cast-iron claw ♪
♪ Now here's a firm example
of what happens ♪
♪ To a convergent person ♪
♪ Lurkin' with a surgeon,
bent on removin' organs ♪
♪ Rippin' them out
and sellin' 'em ♪
♪ To a group that resemble
the Mormons ♪
♪ Or beefed-up doormans ♪
♪ That need
additional sustenance ♪
♪ What's in their food? ♪
♪ Bunch of drunks
with no nuts ♪
♪ Now set 'em up now ♪
♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Then knock 'em down ♪
(repeating) ♪ Set 'em up ♪
♪