(Wish You)
♪I'm breathing heavily♪
♪And running towards you♪
♪To see your eyes
that shined so warmly♪
♪Please don't go far♪
♪Let's follow our memories♪
♪To that place♪
♪Where we used to walk together♪
♪I wish for you♪
♪I won't miss a single moment♪
♪I want you too♪
(Wish You)
(Deposit completed)
The bus is here.
You're acting so strangely today.
Walking me all the way here.
Are you going to ask me
for a favor or something?
See you. Good work today.
- Later.
- Bye.
Excuse me.
Hey, In Su.
Don't forget to check the video
when you get home.
You might be really surprised.
Okay.
- Goodnight.
- See you.
I'm sorry.
(Wish You - The origin mix)
Everyone, you did a great job today.
Let's work hard on our project
that we're preparing right now.
- Okay.
- Got it?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Let's drink.
- Cheers.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
- Bottoms up.
- Please go easy on me.
Alright.
Let's punch in on time tomorrow!
- Come on.
- You're drunk.
I'll have my eyes on you.
Stop drinking so much.
That was a bit harsh.
- Let's just drink.
- Let's go crazy tonight.
Was I outside for too long?
Who is that in the video?
He's pretty good-looking.
His name is Kang In Su.
I'm totally addicted to him lately.
- Do you want to hear it?
- Sure.
- It's not bad.
- I know.
Can you send this to my phone?
Okay, I will.
Sang Yi,
do you want to know a secret?
You're really cute.
Gosh, teasing you is so fun.
I'll go inside now.
Let's go for a second round!
- Let's go!
- Follow me!
Come on, it's this way.
Let's find another place to drink.
Let's go.
- This way.
- Are you okay?
Come on, let's go.
- I think it's this way.
- Let's go.
Sang Yi, do you want to ditch them?
Really?
Why are you so surprised?
I was just kidding.
I'm sorry.
I think you work really hard.
When I worked part-time,
all I did was kill time.
I enjoy my work.
That's why I try harder.
Shall I ask them to hire you
as a regular employee?
Yes, ma'am.
Hey.
- Sang Yi. Sang Yi?
- Yes?
Aren't you going?
Oh, sorry.
Are we going for another drink?
- Sure.
- Come with me.
- Where are we going?
- Which way?
- This way.
- Where is Hyeong Sik?
- One more drink!
- Which way is it?
Ms. Lee.
I'm sorry, but...
The thing is... Well...
You can go.
I'll make up an excuse.
Go and get his autograph
or take a selfie.
It would be better
if you get his number.
Thank you.
Isn't drinking beer the best
when you feel frustrated?
Frustrated? What do you mean?
Hey. Didn't you see
how many views we got?
Don't you ever feel bad or sorry
for your friend...
who's working day and night for you?
Hey, is that my fault?
It's because you make
such lousy videos.
How can you say that to a friend?
You're so mean.
Whatever.
Let's just drink, you jerk.
- Excuse me.
- We'll order later.
I'm sorry, it's not that...
I...
I think I left something here.
Excuse me.
(Wish You)