(Wish You)
What are you doing?
I guess I was mistaken.
I'm sorry.
Sang Yi. Over here.
Oh, okay.
Did everyone go home?
Yes, we called it a night.
So? Did it go well?
Did you take a photo with him?
You're so timid, aren't you?
Hey. Are you working?
I'll send you a video,
so check it now and let's talk.
Yes. I want to hear your opinion.
Okay.
Kang In Su. Do you want to make
music with me?
I like your songs.
Do you want to be friends? Friends.
♪I'm breathing heavily♪
♪I'm breathing...♪
♪And running towards you♪
Let's see. A minor, G.
Right. I think this is the key.
Okay.
I got it.
♪Let's follow our memories♪
♪To that place♪
♪Where we used to walk together♪
♪I wish for you♪
♪I won't miss a single moment♪
♪I want you too♪
♪For us to shine bright and radiantly♪
♪I wish for your name and my name♪
♪To come together as one♪
♪Inside my heart♪
Hey!
Hey, you!
I'm sorry.
Hey, mister.
Do you even know what time it is?
Can you please quiet down
when I ask nicely?
Okay, I'm sorry.
Please be quiet!
Stop!
Ma'am. If you keep
listening to it...
Hey. Do you take me as an amateur?
You used the hook as the intro.
Must I keep listening?
Aren't you guys sick of making
the same songs all the time?
Why don't you take risks
for a change?
- Ma'am.
- What?
- Sang Yi.
- Yes?
Can you play Kang In Su's video?
Okay.
♪I'm breathing heavily♪
♪And running towards you♪
He's still rough around the edges,
but I like him.
I think he has his own unique color.
I think it'll be okay
to try him out.
♪Please don't go far♪
♪Let's follow our memories♪
Yoo Jin. Are you sure
you can make this work?
Ma'am.
Are you sure you can lead
this project on your own...
and take responsibility?
If you give me the opportunity,
I'll try my best.
Tell me if you need anything.
Good luck with your first project.
Let's end today's meeting.
Thank you, ma'am!
- He's so handsome.
- I edited today's video.
- Check it out.
- Is that him?
- He's good-looking.
- I know.
- Go ask for his number.
I'm too shy.
Why don't you ask him?
What are you talking about?
Here.
It's a special coffee
for today's star.
- You can leave it there.
- Come on, you're upsetting me.
Go on and taste it.
Isn't this place nice?
Yes.
I come here sometimes to walk
when I feel frustrated.
It's a hot place that I haven't told
anyone about,
and I'm showing it
especially to you.
Thank you.
There's a reason
why I brought you here.
Sang Yi.
I'm not good at
beating around the bush,
so I'll just say it.
Okay. What is it?
Do you want to do it with me?
Do you even feel thankful to me?
Why are you so cranky today?
Who made my cute Min Seong so angry?
Let go, In Su.
Before I punch you in the face.
Gosh, Min Seong. You're scaring me.
I told you to let go of me.
Excuse me. Can you...
Can you give me your number?
I really mustered up the courage
to come to ask you.
- Do you have a girlfriend?
- He does.
He has a girlfriend,
and he'll get married soon.
Oh... I'm sorry.
Hey. What are you talking about?
What girlfriend?
You're about to become a huge star.
You can't waste your time
dating someone.
No way.
Min Seong.
You really are my manager.
- You little...
- Hey.
Come on, seriously.
This has really become
a habit of yours.
- Hey, let go.
- You punk.
You can't date anyone. Let go.
Go get her back.
You're about to rip my cheeks off.
- I told you to let go.
- Let go.
Excuse me. Are you Mr. Kang In Su?
Surprise.
Sang Yi. I'd like to propose to you
officially.
Sorry?
To become an assistant
of the Planning Team.
You'll be paid twice
your current pay...
for the "Kang In Su Project".
Oh.
Why don't you stop working
part-time...
and work for me
as a regular employee?
Well...
Was the offer too shocking?
Are you saying...
- I've been hired as a regular...
- Oh, wait.
Hello?
Oh, okay. Thank you.
Okay.
Kang In Su, you're mine now!
Shall we go back to the office?
I'll try my best!
Hey. Isn't he pretty good at
playing the piano?
(Wish You)