[woman 1 talking indistinctly on radio]
[woman 2 on radio] Stardust, go ahead.
[woman 1] Activate the V-10 recorder.
[woman 2] Copy.
[man talking indistinctly on radio]
Quarter activation complete.
[man 2] Copy. Thank you.
[Auggie] I know I'm not
an ordinary 10-year-old kid.
I mean, I do ordinary things.
Eat ice cream. Ride my bike.
I'm really good at playing sports.
Well, on my Xbox.
I love Minecraft, science
and dressing up for Halloween.
I love to lightsaber fight with my dad.
And watch Star Wars movies with him.
And drive my big sister crazy.
And dream about
being in outer space,
just like any ordinary kid.
I just don't look ordinary
when I'm doing these things.
Not even my birth was ordinary.
It was hilarious.
Now, how can a birth
be hilarious, you ask?
A teenage doctor helps.
This is my first day.
Nate!
[Auggie] A massive video camera
also aids the situation.
But to really be funny, you need
what all the best jokes have.
A punch line.
[doctor] He's coming!
[baby crying]
[crying fades]
[inaudible]
[baby continues crying]
Where's the baby going? Go with the baby!
-You need to go, sir.
-Oh, the baby.
[Auggie] I've had 27 surgeries since then.
They've helped me to breathe, to see,
to hear without a hearing aid,
and some even helped me look a bit better.
But none of them
have made me look ordinary.
[Nate] He said he doesn't want to go.
-But he's ready.
-[Nate] No, he's not ready.
I cannot homeschool him forever.
Every year that we wait,
it'll just be harder to start.
This is the first year
of middle school for everyone.
He will not be the only new kid.
[Nate] Okay, well, he's gonna be the
only new kid that looks like him.
Look, will you stop folding towels
for just one second and please listen?
It's like leading a lamb to the slaughter.
And you know it.
[Auggie] I know I'll never
just be an ordinary kid.
Ordinary kids don't make other
kids run away from playgrounds.
Ordinary kids don't get stared
at wherever they go.
But it's okay if you wanna stare, too.
My name is Auggie Pullman.
Next week, I start fifth grade.
And since I've never been
to real school before,
I'm pretty much totally
and completely petrified.
[sighs]
Mrs Pullman, so good to see you again.
And you must be Auggie.
What a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Mr Tushman.
You can laugh about that. Tushman.
I've heard 'em all.
Tushy.
-Butt man. Butt face.
-[chuckles] Oh.
Mr Tuchus.
-[Auggie snorts]
-[laughs]
[Mr Tushman] And then
in the spring, we have a science fair.
And from what your homeschool teacher
tells me, you'll get first prize.
You hear that, Auggie?
Then right before graduation,
whole class takes a trip
to a nature reserve in Pennsylvania.
It is the highlight of the year.
-I promise you.
-[kids chattering]
Oh, good, they're here.
Who are they?
Well, I thought
it would be helpful for you
to meet some of our students
before you start school, Auggie.
What do you think?
Other kids now?
[Mr Tushman] They were
in the elementary school
so they know their way around,
and they'll give you a nice tour.
It will be fine.
[Mr Tushman] Auggie, this is Jack Will,
Julian, and Charlotte.
Guys, this is Auggie Pullman.
-Hi.
Hey.
[Auggie] Meeting kids is harder
than meeting adults.
Everyone makes the same face at first.
But kids aren't as good at hiding it.
So I usually look down.
You can learn a lot
about people from their shoes.
I think these three are trust fund kid,
hand-me-down kid...
Uh-oh, crazy kid.
I act in TV commercials.
Really?
Yeah. Tide.
[Mr Tushman] Why don't you guys
take Auggie 'round the school a bit, huh?
Just be back here in, uh, a half hour?
[Charlotte] I started when I was two.
Local spots mostly.
Then when I was three
I booked my first national. Nestlé Quik.
It was hard,
because I'm lactose intolerant.
Anyway, have you ever heard
of a spit bucket?
So this is our homeroom.
We have Mr Browne.
My mom says he's a little weird.
[Charlotte] Then I was in the chorus
of the Radio City Music Hall
Christmas Spectacular.
I auditioned for Annie on Broadway.
I got two callbacks for Molly, but I guess
they went in a different direction.
Hey, Charlotte!
Don't you ever stop talking?
So this is the cafeteria.
The food here is okay for school food.
Or do you eat special food?
Wow! This reminds me
of my guess spot on Law &amp; Order.
So the science elective
is supposably really hard.
So you probably won't be
spending much time here.
No offence, but if you've never
been in a real school before...
Dude, he's been homeschooled.
Okay, I'm just saying.
Science is supposably really hard.
But you're taking it, too, right?
[chuckles] Hey,
maybe you could fail together.
Why don't you get out of the
way, so he can check it out?
Okay.
I mean, there's nothing much to see.
Desks. Chairs.
The incubator. Bunsen burners.
Those are some
really gross science posters.
Oh! And this is an eraser.
[Charlotte] He knows what an eraser is.
How am I supposed to know what he knows?
He doesn't say anything.
You know what an eraser is, right?
[whispers]
Dude, you have to say something.
Yeah, I know what an eraser is.
Is... Is your name Jack or Jackwill?
[giggles] You thought his name
was Jackwill?
Yeah, a lot of people
call me by my first and last name.
I don't know why.
Got any other questions?
Actually, I've got a question for Auggie.
What's the deal with your face?
Dude!
I mean, were you
in a car crash or something?
Julian!
What? Tushman said we could
ask questions if we wanted to.
Not rude questions.
Besides, he was born
like that, Mr Tushman said.
Yeah, I know. I just thought maybe
he was, like, in a fire, too.
Hey, Julian, shut up.
You shut up!
[shouts] Why don't we all shut up?
No, I wasn't in a fire.
And the word's "supposedly."
What?
You said that science
is supposably really hard.
Twice.
The word's "supposedly." With a "D."
Maybe my mom can homeschool you, too.
Do you wanna tell us yet
how you felt about the tour?
Today?
Mr Tushman went out of his way
to tell me how sweet those kids were
and that Julian
is apparently quite the dream.
[sighs] No.
[Isabel] Not a dream?
Is he one of those kids that acts
one way in front of grown-ups
and then another way in front of kids?
Yeah, I guess.
Well, I know it's hard,
but you have to understand that
he probably feels badly about himself.
And when someone acts small, you just
have to be the bigger person, all right?
-Right.
Via, I'll get the pizza.
[whispers] Look at me, Auggie.
That kid sounds like a real jerk.
If someone pushes you, push back.
Don't be afraid of anyone.
[whispers] Why are we whispering?
Because I'm afraid of Mom.
You just gotta be a bigger person
and rise above it. It's that easy.
Auggie, I do believe that this
is the best year for you to start school
because everybody is going to be new.
But if you really don't wanna go...
No. It's okay. I wanna go.
You do?
[Auggie] Mmm-hmm.
[Isabel] What changed your mind?
Well they have a really good
science elective.
And I need a better science teacher.
[Nate chuckles] Oh!
-Oh, wow. There's that.
-[Nate] Whoa! Whoa!
Are you gonna take that, Mom?
Can I get some backup here?
You gonna let him talk
to your wife like this?
[Nate] I'm not gonna let him
talk to my wife like that.
[Auggie] Please!
[Nate] Get him! Come on, Via.
-Get in there. Get in there. Get in there.
-[indistinct conversations]
I'll meet you right here after school.
Okay? Right here.
[whispers] I love you.
[Auggie] Love you, too.
I'll see you later.
Can you hear me?
We're gonna have a little man-to-man.
Now, I gotta stop here, because
past this point is a No Dad Zone
and you don't wanna walk up with
your parents because it's not cool.
[Auggie] But you're cool.
[sighs]
I know I am,
but technically most dads aren't, so...
And neither are these helmets.
Hey.
Two rules. First, only raise
your hand once a class,
no matter how many answers you know.
Except for science. Crush that one.
Check.
Second, you're gonna feel like
you're all alone, Auggie.
But you're not.
Check.
Should we lose this? Come on,
costumes are for Halloween.
Prepare for blastoff.
[kids chattering]
I love you.
Love you, too.
-Have fun.
-[Auggie] Bye.
[woman on radio] Have an
excellent mission and Godspeed.
[man on radio] We are ready
to proceed at this time.
[woman] Ten. Nine. Eight. Seven.
Dear God, please,
make them be nice to him.
[woman] Four. Three. Two. One.
[rocket blasting off]
[Auggie] My mom always said,
"If you don't like where you are,
just picture where you wanna be."
[all chanting] Auggie! Auggie! Auggie!
Auggie! Auggie! Auggie! Auggie! Auggie!
[chanting continues]
[locker slams shut]
[Auggie] I can't wait till Halloween.
[all chattering]
All right, let's settle down.
Everybody settle down.
Uh... Saved.
Sorry.
[Mr Browne] Everybody find your seats?
Yes?
Finding our seats.
Great.
[school bell rings]
All right. Now, some of us are lucky
enough to know each other. Yeah?
And, and others are new. Hi, there.
Okay, my name is Mr Browne
and you're late.
Yeah. I'm so sorry.
I was just helping set up chairs
for the assembly.
Don't worry about it.
Can anybody tell me what this word means?
Anybody? No?
Precepts are rules
for really important things.
Like mottos.
Like mottos. Or like famous quotes.
Or like, um, lines
from a fortune cookie. Right?
Precepts can help motivate us.
They can help guide us when
we have to make decisions
about really important things. Okay?
"So why are you talking to me
about precepts
this early in the morning, Mr Browne?"
Well, let me tell you.
Because precepts also can
tell us a lot about ourselves.
Who is it that I aspire to be?
That is the question that we should
be asking ourselves all the time.
What kind of person am I?
So, this is what we're gonna do.
Um, everyone's gonna come up
with two things
that they think everybody else
should know about them.
All right? I'll go first.
Number one,
I used to work on Wall Street.
For a long time.
And two, I left Wall Street
to pursue my dream and teach.
Boom, who's next?
Yes.
Julian Albans.
And I think it's cool
how you're pursuing your dream.
Thank you very much, Julian.
Let's hear your two things.
Okay.
One, I just got Battleground Mystic
on my Wii and it's totally awesome.
And number two,
we got a ping pong table this summer.
Amazing. Any questions for Julian?
Yes?
Is Battleground Mystic
multiplayer or single player?
Let's not those kinda questions.
-[all laugh]
-Okay, uh...
[sighs]
Hi.
My name's August Pullman.
Auggie.
And, um...
I have a sister named Via
and a dog named Daisy.
I love Star Wars.
And I just said three things. Yeah. Sorry.
That sounds like a bonus to me.
Three things.
Thank you very much, Auggie,
that was perfect. Who's next?
Oh! I actually have a question for Auggie.
What's the deal with the braid
in the back of your hair?
Is it like a Padawan thing?
What's a Padawan thing?
Oh. It's from Star Wars.
Padawan is a Jedi apprentice.
Who's your favourite character, Auggie?
Boba Fett.
What about Darth Sidious? Do you like him?
Ouch.
Okay, can we talk about
Star Wars at recess? Yes?
All right.
Who wants to read this month's precept?
[all] Me! Me! Me!
Me! Me! Me!
What about you? What's your name?
Summer.
Want to give it a shot?
"When given the choice between
being right or being kind,
choose kind."
[school bell rings]
[Julian] Hey, can I sit there?
Sure!
You eat like the sarlacc monster,
my young Padawan.
[chuckling]
Newton's first law of motion.
An object in motion
will stay in motion unless...
It's okay, I didn't expect you
to know that on the first day.
Acted on by another force.
Very good.
Here's how it works.
A moving object will only
change its speed or direction
if something else causes it to do that.
Hey Darth Hideous, did you hear?
Padawan braids were lame 15 years ago.
Supposedly. With a "D."
Dude! More like they were always lame.
[Julian] See you tomorrow.
[Miles] Later, Barf Hideous!
-Hey.
-[Auggie] Hey, Mom.
Auggie, you're supposed to knock.
I'm serious this time.
Wait, did someone make fun of it?
I, for one, had a great day.
[softly] Just trying to lighten the mood.
Right, Daisy? Right. Good girl.
Well, I went to, um, Kinko's today
to see if they could get my thesis
off this.
You're gonna finish your dissertation?
[Via] What is that?
It's a floppy disk.
A what?
Come on! You, it, a floppy...
These kids today.
[stammers] It's basically an iPhone.
You know, it doesn't play music
or, you can't call, but...
They couldn't get the file.
That's okay. You'll find a place.
Well, I think it's great, Mom.
Maybe. Thank you.
So Auggie...
[Auggie] Yeah?
Hi.
How was your first day of school?
Earth to Auggie. We asked you a question.
Come on, how was your day?
Good.
Good how? Good like it was good?
Or good like it was bad and
you just don't wanna tell us?
It was good, okay? I just don't know
what you want me to say? It was good!
Okay, okay, hey! If you're mad at Mom
about going to school,
it was my idea, too.
Why can't I just say "good"
like anybody else?
Batting a thousand today.
Are they gonna ask about my day?
That is not the way we leave the table.
Hey, come on. Talk to me.
Sit down.
Take that off, please.
-[voice breaking] I'm sorry.
-[Isabel] It's okay.
It'll be okay.
Why do I have to be so ugly?
You are not ugly, Auggie.
You just have to say that
because you're my mom.
Oh, because I'm your mom,
it doesn't count?
Yeah.
Because I'm your mom, it counts
the most because I know you the most.
You are not ugly and anyone
who cares to know you will see that.
They won't even talk to me.
It matters that I look different.
I try to pretend that it doesn't,
but it does.
I know.
Is it always gonna matter?
I don't know.
Honey, listen...
Look at me. We all have marks on our face.
I have this wrinkle here
from your first surgery.
I have these wrinkles here
from your last surgery.
This is the map that shows us
where we're going.
And this is the map that
shows us where we've been.
And it's never ever ugly.
But what about your grey hair?
[chuckling softly]
That's compliments of your dad, I think.
[chuckles]
And as though we summoned him.
-[chuckles]
-[Auggie] How was your day?
My day is really good right now.
So they went to Florida,
where Gollum was living in Miami. And...
Oh, you know what it is?
Daddy doesn't have his glasses on.
You're making this up.
[all laughing]
[Via] August is the sun.
My mom and dad and me
are planets orbiting the sun.
But I love my brother and I'm used
to the way this universe works.
My mom says that on my fourth birthday
I wished for a little brother.
And when he was born, it only took me
a few seconds and I was all over him.
Can you hear me?
If they stare, let them stare.
You can't blend in when you
were born to stand out.
I've never asked my mom
for help with my homework.
I never needed my dad to
remind me to study for a test.
I just did most of my studying
in waiting rooms and hospitals.
Mom and Dad would always say I was
the most understanding girl in the world.
I don't know about that.
I just knew my family
couldn't take one more thing.
I know my family loves me,
but ever since my grandma died,
my best friend Miranda
is the only person who knows me.
Miranda!
Wow. Look at you.
Hey, Via.
I've texted you, like, a thousand times.
When'd you get back from camp?
Two weeks ago.
Two weeks?
Sorry, it's been crazy. You know?
Yeah, no, that's okay.
What'd you do to your hair?
Do you like it?
Yeah. Yeah. It looks wild.
Just trying something different, you know.
I'll catch you later.
-Hey, Ella.
-Hey.
[sighs]
Thinking about signing up?
-For what?
-[Justin] The drama club.
They study theatre in the fall
and do a play in the spring.
Um...
No, not really. I'm not a theatre nerd.
[chuckles] Well, that's too bad. I am.
I'm Justin by the way.
Sorry, that was... That was rude. Um...
I'm Via. Olivia.
First days suck, don't they?
[sighs] Yeah. Yeah, they do.
My mom tried to walk me here
from the subway.
I literally had to ditch her
at the traffic light.
My mom still doesn't think
I can use a MetroCard.
You an only child, too?
Yeah. Yeah.
They never listen.
This one time I told my mom
I wanted to take guitar lessons
and play like Jimi Hendrix.
What happened?
[chuckles]
Well, it was nice to meet you,
Via. Olivia.
Yeah. It was nice
to meet you, too, Justin.
Maybe I'll see you around.
Though not onstage, clearly.
[knock on door]
Come in.
[softly] Good night, honey.
Where's Mom?
She fell asleep.
Oh. Okay.
How's Auggie?
[sighs]
There's some bully, you know.
How was your first day?
It was... It was really good.
It was good?
Yeah.
Say hi to Miranda for us.
I will.
Sweet dreams.
Good night.
[door closes]
[sighs]
[Via] My mom put her life
on hold for my brother.
She always wanted to be a children's
book illustrator and teach art.
She was one thesis shy of getting
her master's when Auggie was born.
Then she stopped writing it.
She stopped a lot of things
when Auggie was born.
But she is still great at drawing.
I don't know if she even realizes that
she makes Auggie the centre
of every universe she draws.
Miranda used to joke that
my house was like the Earth.
It revolved around the son.
Not the daughter.
That doesn't change the fact
that my mother has a great eye.
I just wish that one time,
she would use it to look at me.
[Mr Davenport] Yeah, good job, good job.
Miranda?
Via? What are you doing here?
Just trying something new.
You?
Uh, same.
[Mr Davenport]
All right, everybody, let's go!
Time for vocal warm-up.
Bring it in!
Bring it in, people, let's go!
Everybody, hands up! Reach high! And...
[flapping lips]
[all flapping lips]
[Mr Davenport] Guys, can you please...
[indistinct chattering]
Okay. You... You guys, skooch.
Sit. Just be closer.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Stay. Stay, good.
Hey, hey. What's your name?
Auggie.
Nice boots.
Great. Thanks.
Okay, everybody, here we go.
We're skooching and say, "Cheese."
[all] Cheese!
[Auggie] School became...
Well, I got used to it.
Except for dodgeball.
What evil man invented dodgeball?
But my least favourite zone at school
is courtyard.
Because the whole school's there.
No one does anything mean.
Or says anything. Or laughs.
They all just look, then look away,
then look back.
They're just being normal kids.
I kinda wanna tell them,
"Hey, I know I look weird, but it's okay."
I mean, if Chewbacca started
going to school here one day,
I'd probably stare at him a bit, too.
[Chewbacca gurgles throatily]
I'm sorry if my staring
made you feel weird.
[grunting]
In order for any of us to see,
we need light.
So, right now light is bouncing off
this card travelling through the air,
through the glass, to your eye.
But what if we added water?
-[all] Whoa!
-[chuckles]
Whoa, indeed.
Any time light passes from one material
or medium to another, it bends.
This bending of light is also known as...
Refraction.
Very good, Auggie.
Jack, you okay?
-Yeah, yeah, refraction.
-Good.
Clear your desks. Pop quiz.
[all groaning]
[whispers] Hurry.
[kids chattering]
Hey, Jack, come sit here.
In a sec.
Where's he going?
Hey.
Thanks for your help today.
No problem.
And don't worry, I got a couple
wrong so Ms Petosa wouldn't know.
I'm not worried.
The worst they can do is kick me out.
Not loving school either, huh?
Oh, it's great.
[chuckles] I wanted to go to Wayne Middle.
The one with the great sports teams.
Then why'd you come here?
They gave me the scholarship.
Well, if you need help in science,
you can come to my house after school.
You know, if you want.
Great. Thanks!
What's wrong?
I just don't like eating
in front of people.
What do you mean?
It's a long story, but when I eat,
I think I chew
like some prehistoric swamp turtle.
No joke? Me too!
[both laughing]
[Auggie] Now there's tuna on your face.
Yeah! Tuna, man!
No, no, no, let me show you how it's done.
-[chuckles]
-[mimics chomping]
[both chucking]
Dude, that's even more gross.
I'm going as Boba Fett this year.
I like Halloween,
but Christmas is still the best holiday.
[Auggie] No way. Halloween is the best.
A pillowcase of candy
versus two weeks off school.
You're nuts.
-[barks]
-You see?
Even your dog agrees.
Hey, Mom, is it okay if Jack comes over?
Yes!
Thanks, Mrs P.
I mean, you get snow on Christmas.
But you can get snow on Halloween.
-[Jack] How?
-If you live in Alaska
or there's a blizzard.
[exhales] I've got to be cool.
[both grunting]
You ever thought about
having plastic surgery?
No, I've never thought about it. Why?
[chuckles]
Dude, this is after plastic surgery!
It takes a lot of work to look this good.
-[both laughing]
-Oh, my God! Oh, my God.
[Auggie and Jake] One, two,
three, four, I declare a thumb war.
Bow, kiss, begin.
Nate.
Fire.
[inaudible]
Okay, everybody, if you can't see
the camera, the camera can't see you.
Now, let's improv like we know
what we're doing.
Okay, everybody say, "Stella!"
-[all] Stella!
-[camera clicks]
So I can't figure you out.
What?
Um, I can't figure you out.
Oh?
Well, most theatre people won't
stop talking about themselves.
But you don't talk.
I... I listen.
Me too.
I know.
Oh. [chuckles] So you do pay attention.
Okay, that's a start. Uh...
I'm a good listener, so tell me something.
Who are you gonna audition for?
Um, I'm not really the Our Town type.
Oh, come on.
Don't be the "run lights girl."
Should be Emily.
The lead?
Look, your family can't cheer
for you in a booth.
Oh, they're... They're pretty busy.
I don't think they would
cheer for me anyway.
Come on, there's not one person
in your family who would applaud you?
My grandmother.
There you go. Bring her.
I can't.
Well, then I'll applaud you.
Why are you being so nice to me?
Because you're an only child.
We have to stick together.
Think about it. Okay?
And, uh,
your grandmother's still cheering you on.
[grandmother] I know you.
And I love you more
than anything in the world.
What about Auggie?
I love your brother.
But he has a lot of angels
looking out for him.
And you have me.
Yeah.
You are everywhere.
And...
...you are my favourite.
You're my favourite, too, Grams.
Mom, Daisy ruined my Boba Fett costume!
What? Where have you been? It's very late.
-I'm sorry.
-She threw up all over it.
Okay, well, you'll just have
to wear your costume from last year.
But I told Jack
I was going as Boba Fett, not Ghostface.
Well, tomorrow is Halloween.
And all the shops are closed.
And my artistic hands are busy
making meatloaf.
So you do the math.
Fine!
Do you need some help, Mom?
What?
Some help.
Oh, uh, yes, thank you.
Er, mince that rosemary, please.
Where did you say you were?
I, uh... I went to Coney Island.
How about you stay home
from school tomorrow? Hmm?
It's Halloween.
We can make it a three-day weekend.
Spend some time together.
Yeah. Yeah, that would be really nice.
Yeah?
Okay, good.
Peppers? I don't want peppers.
-Peppers give Daddy gas.
-[chuckles]
[Auggie] I don't care what Jack Will
says about Christmas.
[Nate] Hey, Auggie!
[Auggie] For me, Halloween
is the best holiday in the world.
It's so awesome
when I'm wearing the costume!
I usually walk with my head down
to avoid being seen.
But on Halloween,
I walk with my head up high.
I don't even know who that was.
He didn't even know who I was.
It's so cool.
Especially because people
don't like to touch me
because they think I'm contagious.
Oh, yeah, Chewie! Up high!
Boom goes the dynamite!
[kids laughing]
It really does look like him.
-This part right?
-[Amos] Yeah.
[Julian] I mean, he's always reminded me
of, like, the shrunken head, you know?
[Amos] Or an orc.
[Julian] Yeah.
If I looked like him, I'd swear
I'd put a hood over my face every day.
[Jack] If I looked like him,
I think I'd kill myself.
Why do you hang out with him
so much, Jack?
[Miles] Yeah.
[Jack] I don't know.
Tushman asked me to be his welcome buddy
and now
he just follows me around everywhere.
[Julian] Well, that must stink!
That must stink.
[kids laughing]
[Amos] Oh, yeah. Just like him.
[kids continue laughing]
-[growls]
-[laughing]
Nobody puts Baby in the corner.
Always blows my mind how much Daddy
looks like Patrick Swayze in this movie.
-Ew!
-[chuckling]
Ew, no!
Honey, tell me
what's going on with Miranda?
It's not... It's not just the pink hair.
She's just...
She won't even talk to me.
I had a friend in high school.
We went through this exact same thing.
And what I did, which fixed it
almost immediately...
Yeah?
Was, um, to eat an entire
jack-o'-lantern bucket of candy.
-[chuckles]
-[phone ringing]
Mmm. Hello.
Yes, Mr Tushman.
He's nauseous?
Does he have a fever?
What did the nurse say?
I'm so sorry.
All right. Okay. Thank you.
I will be right there.
Honey, I have to go,
your brother just threw up at school.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
[TV turns off]
[clattering]
[sobbing softly]
[Isabel] Nate, do you know
where his helmet is?
He's asking for it
and I've looked everywhere.
I don't know. Something at school.
He won't say.
He won't come out of his room.
And now he says he doesn't even
wanna go trick-or-treating.
I know. Okay. Thank you. Just get here.
[Via] Come on, get ready.
It's almost time for the Halloween parade.
You're supposed to knock!
-[knocks on table]
-Go away!
Mom says you won't say what happened.
Did someone say something?
Someone always says something!
Well, tell me what happened.
It's none of your business!
You took my day with Mom,
so it is my business.
I heard Jack Will talking
about me behind my back.
He said he'd kill himself
if he looked like me.
Jack Will? Isn't he the nice one?
[Auggie] There are no nice ones!
I wish I'd never gone
to school in the first place!
But you were liking school.
I know you were.
I hate it, okay? I hate it!
Auggie, I'm sorry, but you're not
the only one who has bad days.
Bad days? Do people avoid touching you?
When a person accidentally touches you,
do they call it "the plague"?
No.
Jack Will was all I had.
So just don't compare
your bad days at school to mine, okay?
Okay.
Hey.
Did you notice that Miranda
doesn't come around any more?
What?
You didn't. Shocker.
Yeah, she went away to camp this summer
and now she doesn't like me any more.
Why?
Because school sucks.
And people change.
So if you wanna be a normal kid,
Auggie, then those are the rules.
So, let's go trick-or-treating.
Okay?
Because right now
we're each other's best friends.
Really?
Yes.
So, come on.
I'll let you have all my Halloween candy.
[indistinct chatter]
[Auggie] I'll trade you my apples.
[Via] Okay, no.
I know that I said that
you could have all my candy,
but I was really just saying that
to get you out of the house.
[Auggie] What about the chocolate?
-[Via] No.
-And the Smarties?
Gummies, licorice, the Reese's,
the Hersheys.
-No!
-And everything else.
All right, I'll let you have all my candy.
[Mr Davenport] Okay, Via.
You are next, please.
Let's hear it for Via.
[exhales]
Daisy,
do you wanna help me
take back my corner office?
Hey, Auggie! You feeling better?
Are you okay, Auggie?
Yeah.
Sure? 'Cause you're acting really weird.
I'm okay, Jack, okay?
Okay.
[sighs]
They want me to do what?
[sighs] Give a tour through the school.
-But, Mom, it's summer vacation.
-I know.
But your teachers told Mr Tushman
you're known as a good egg.
-No, I'm a bad egg.
-You're a good egg.
And I'm actually really proud
they thought of you for this.
Mom, enough with the guilt.
And you know
they gave you a scholarship, right?
Mom...
Who else is doing it?
Uh, Charlotte and Julian.
-No.
-Why, what's wrong?
Charlotte will just talk about Broadway
the whole time.
And Julian is the biggest
phony on the planet.
So I'm sorry, but no.
Jack, it's for that boy.
Who?
The one from the ice cream shop.
Oh.
Yeah.
So if a nice kid like your little brother
cries when he sees him,
what kind of a chance
do you think he has in middle school?
[sighs] Okay.
Thank you, kiddo.
[Jack] Four things I've learned
about Auggie Pullman.
First of all, you do get used to his face.
Now, it's not like regular ice.
You can't touch it with your hands, okay?
[Jack] Second, he's really smart.
He's ahead of me in everything.
In science,
he's ahead of the whole school.
Everybody watching?
-Whoo!
-[all laugh]
[Jack] Third of all,
he's actually pretty funny.
But fourthly, now that I know him,
I would say I actually
do wanna be friends with Auggie.
At first, I admit it,
I was only friendly to him because
my mom asked me to be nice.
But now I would choose
to hang out with him.
Like, he's a good friend.
Like if all the guys in fifth grade
were lined up against a wall
and I could choose anyone I wanted
to hang out with, I would choose Auggie.
Hey, what's wrong?
Go away.
[Julian] Oh, hey, Jack, come sit with us.
Yeah, come on, man.
I wonder what happened.
[Ximena] Maybe Jack touched Auggie
and couldn't wash his hands in time.
Jack finally got "the plague."
[Charlotte] That's not very nice.
What? We didn't start it.
Where are you going?
Hi. I'm Summer.
I know. We're in the same homeroom.
You don't have to do this.
Do what?
You don't have to be my friend.
I know Tushman talked to you.
I don't know
what you're talking about, Auggie.
I know Tushman talked to some kids
before school started
and told them
they had to be friends with me.
He didn't talk to me.
Yeah, he did.
No, he did not.
No, he didn't, I swear on my life!
[Auggie] Okay, okay.
You don't have to get mad.
I don't like
being accused of things, okay?
Okay. I'm sorry.
You should be.
-He really didn't talk to you?
-Auggie!
Okay, I just...
Why are you sitting here then?
Because I want some nice friends
for a change.
Me too.
Cool beans.
But you'll get "the plague."
Good.
Summer has "the plague."
Shut up!
So what happened with Jack Will?
Promise you won't tell?
I got it! I got the part!
-Congratulations.
-Thank you. [laughs]
[mimicking]
She got it! She got the part! Oh, my God!
Bet she got Emily.
-Yep.
-[sighs]
What'd you get?
Emily's understudy.
I'm not saying poison or anything,
but just a little Benadryl
-to knock Miranda out before the show.
-[laughs]
Okay, enough.
Look, just learn her lines
and it'll give us
an excuse to hang out more.
We can start rehearsing the kissing scene
on Page 110.
Wait. George and Emily?
There is no Page 110.
So I'm thinking,
I really wanna kiss you right now.
But I don't know how you'll respond.
What's wrong?
I'm not an only child.
Mom?
One sec, Via. Auggie, let's go!
I thought you were at the library.
Uh, um...
Yeah, change of plans.
Mmm-hmm.
Hi, I'm Justin.
-I'm Isabel.
-[door opens]
Daisy threw up again. Bucket loads.
[Isabel] Bucket loads.
[Via] Um, Justin, this is
my little brother Auggie.
-Hey, dude!
-[Auggie] Hey.
What's that in your case? A machine gun?
[laughs]
Er, no. It's a fiddle.
You should tell people it's a machine gun.
That's way cooler.
You know what?
That's a great idea, you're right.
We're on our way to the grocery.
-Mom's making-- What's it called?
-Feijoada.
-Mom's making feijoada.
-It's Dad's favourite.
You're welcome to stay
if you want, Justin.
Oh, thank you very much.
It was nice meeting you.
[Isabel] Nice to meet you, too.
Psst. Oy! [snaps fingers]
Bye, Auggie.
Nothing to see here.
[door opens and closes]
It's a gene. Well, it's sort of two genes,
but two genes that are identical.
And the trouble is that both of my parents
carry the gene at the same time,
which is...
Well essentially, he won the lottery.
Backwards or something.
And in another world, I'd look like him.
I'm sorry for telling you
that I was an only child.
Sometimes it's nice to hide a little.
I get it. It's okay.
[Via laughing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[Miranda on phone] Major Tom, is that you?
Miranda!
[Miranda]
It's so great to hear your voice again.
Sorry, Via's not here.
[Miranda] I was actually calling
to say hello to you.
How have you been?
Good. Did you know I'm going
to a regular school now?
[Miranda] No way.
Do you like it?
[Auggie] Yeah, I guess.
It's not as hard as Mom's homeschool.
[chuckles] Yeah, I'll bet.
How are the kids? Are they nice?
[Auggie] No. But I made one friend.
Her name's Summer.
We started a summer names club.
-Summer, August. Get it?
-[chuckles]
Good for you, Auggie. [chuckles]
Um, where's Via, anyway?
[Auggie] She's out with her boyfriend.
Really?
[Auggie] Yeah. We met him last week.
He's super nice.
I've missed you, Major Tom.
[Auggie] I miss you too, Miranda.
And can you tell Via
that I've missed her, too?
[Auggie] Well,
but why don't you just tell her yourself?
Listen, I gotta go,
my mom's calling me, but, um,
you know that you can call me
any time, right?
[Auggie] Yeah.
Okay, so call me any time.
I will.
Merry Christmas, Auggie.
Merry Christmas, Miranda.
[lift dings]
-[Nate] Get after it.
-Open it. Rip it apart.
[Miranda] Via and I have been best friends
since kindergarten.
Oh, my God!
[Miranda] Her family's always been
like my second family.
Auggie's always felt
like my little brother.
-[all laugh]
-How does it feel?
-Awesome.
-Good.
[Miranda] And for a few years even our
family's spent Christmas together.
[Isabel] Everybody say "Merry Christmas"!
[all] Merry Christmas!
[Miranda] But now my dad's busy
with his new wife.
Who was his old boss.
And my mom, well,
she's busy not getting over that.
I got a job at a summer camp.
Just so I'd have somewhere
to go that wasn't home.
One day, and I swear
I didn't plan this, but...
I started playing this little make
believe game with the girls in the camp.
I said I lived in a huge brownstone.
On a nice street.
With my two awesome parents.
And my awesome dog named Daisy.
And my awesome little brother
with a facial deformity.
And, oh, my God, everyone went crazy.
"What do you mean, deformity?
What does he look like?"
Suddenly, everyone wanted to talk to me.
And by the end of summer,
I was the most popular girl in camp.
When I got home, I wanted to call Via.
But she would've asked me about
my parents and about camp.
And then I saw Via audition for the play.
And I remembered how cool she is.
And how I understood why everyone in camp
loved me more when I pretended to be her.
She used to let Auggie
hang out with us all the time.
I was the one who bought him
his astronaut helmet.
He was so into outer space.
And I wanted him to know that
the world was bigger than his room.
And now he's out there.
And I didn't even know.
I could've helped him.
Maybe he could've helped me.
I don't know.
But I could sure use some help right now.
[indistinct conversation and laughter]
[Summer and Auggie whooping]
[laughing]
That was awesome!
[chuckles]
Hey, look, there's Jack Will.
Let's find another hill.
You can't just
keep avoiding him forever, Auggie.
Come on, let's go!
[crowd chanting] Nine. Eight. Seven.
Six. Five. Four.
Three. Two. One. Happy New Year!
[all cheering]
-Happy New Year!
[grunting]
Thanks for the help, Daisy.
Way to put your back into it.
[Miles] What about you?
Christmas was awesome.
We drove up into the mountains
where they had the most
amazing snow I've ever seen.
-It was like powder.
-Nice.
What about you, Jack?
I went up Skeleton Hill. It was the best.
[Amos] Skeleton Hill?
I hate that place!
Should be called Garbage Hill.
I know, right?
I left my old lightning sled there
last time I was up.
It was the crappiest piece of junk.
Went back the next day
and someone had taken it.
[Julian] Hey, maybe a homeless guy
wanted to go sledding.
[Miles and Amos] Yeah.
[Mr Browne] New precept.
Your deeds are your monuments.
Archaeologists found these words inscribed
on the walls of an ancient Egyptian tomb.
Can anybody tell me what they mean?
Summer?
Oh, uh...
I think it means that the things we do
are the things that matter most.
[Mr Browne] Excellent. Anybody else?
Hey, Summer?
Hey. You okay?
Yeah. Fine. Just...
This is gonna sound stupid, but,
do you know why Auggie stopped liking me?
You should ask him.
I have, but ever since Halloween,
he just won't talk to me.
I mean... You know what?
I don't care. Sorry.
Ghostface.
Wait, wait, what?
That's all I can tell you.
Okay.
Now that we've finished our tests,
I want you all to start thinking about
our fifth grade science fair projects.
Which you will need to work on
to have ready after spring break.
Okay? Now, it could be about anything.
[voice fades]
[inaudible]
[Ms Petosa] The point is to create
something you're excited about.
Something you're proud to show.
Mr Will?
Something more important to think about?
No.
So, it'll be teams of two.
Your partner will be your tablemate.
[Julian] Uh, Ms Petosa?
I know we're supposed to be in pairs,
but Jack, Amos and I
had this science fair project idea
that we wanted to work on together.
[Ms Petosa] Okay, maybe we can switch.
Uh, no.
Sorry?
What?
No, um, it's... It's okay.
I'll stay with who I've got.
I'll stick with Auggie.
Hey! What did you do that for?
Dude, I don't want to switch.
Why not? Do you really
wanna be partners with that freak?
[inaudible]
[Jack] Dear Mr Tushman,
I'm very sorry for punching Julian.
It was wrong of me to do that.
I know you may need to expel me,
but I'd still rather not say
why I did what I did.
It might get Julian in trouble, too,
-and that's not fair.
-Stop!
Sincerely, Jack Will.
[Mr Tushman] Dear Mr Will, one thing
I've learned in 20 years in education
is that there are two sides
to every story.
So I think I can imagine
what started the fight.
While nothing justifies
striking another student,
I know good friends are worth defending.
So, after your two-day suspension
your scholarship will be waiting for you.
Just keep up the good work.
And keep being the fine boy
we all know you to be.
Sincerely, Mr Tushman.
[Via] What's so wrong with me
not telling you about a stupid play?
I'm not even in it.
I'm just doing the lights.
Well, your boyfriend is in it.
And don't you think
we would like to see him?
No, I don't!
Look, let's all calm down for a second.
You know, you've been really good
at leaving me alone my whole life.
So why are you suddenly
so interested, huh?
Are... Are you bored
now that Auggie's in school?
Your thesis not going well?
Nate, could you please excuse us?
-Izzy, she doesn't mean it.
-Nate!
[Isabel arguing indistinctly]
What are they saying down there?
[Nate] They, my friend,
are saying a lot of things.
None of which concern us.
Let's see your new Minecraft world.
'Cause we might be moving to it.
So, are we going to see the play?
Um...
I hadn't realized what the play was
and I don't think it will be of
any interest to a kid your age.
Yeah, uh, you'd get totally bored.
[Auggie] Are you and Dad going?
Daddy'll go.
And I'm gonna stay here with you.
What?
So now you're gonna punish me
by not going?
Well, you didn't want me to go
in the first place, remember?
Well, now that you know about it,
of course I want you to come.
What are you talking about?
-Nothing.
-[Via] Nothing.
You're lying.
It's just something to do
with Via's school, honey.
You just don't want your
fancy high school friends
to know your brother's a freak, huh?
-[Isabel] Auggie!
-Auggie, that's not true.
Stop lying to me, I'm not an idiot,
I know what's going on!
[Daisy whimpering]
Daisy girl?
Auggie. Come on.
[Auggie] It's okay, I don't wanna go
to your stupid high school anyway.
I don't care.
Auggie, not everything
in the world is about you.
[Via sniffles]
What's wrong?
[Daisy whimpers]
[Daisy whimpering]
You're gonna be fine, girlie.
Daddy's gonna meet me there.
Take care of your brother.
[Via] Yeah.
Okay. All right.
Did Daisy really bite Mom?
Well, um, she was whimpering.
And then Mom tried to pick her up
and Daisy bit her.
Do you think the vet can fix her?
She was in a lot of pain, Auggie.
She's really old.
Auggie?
I want you to come to my play. Okay?
Really?
Really.
[door opens]
[crying]
[sniffles]
[Auggie] Every time I came home
from the hospital, Daisy was here.
She was a real friend.
And real friends are hard to find.
[beeps]
[laughs]
Excuse me.
Sorry. Thank you.
-This is perfect.
-Here we go. Good seats.
Here. See if you can find
Via's name in there, honey.
Glasses. Oh, no! [gasps]
I think I forgot my glasses.
Auggie, you're missing
a great episode of Hoarders right here.
-Starring your mom's purse.
-[chuckles]
You ready?
Are you supposed to be
in the girls' dressing room?
Just wanted to wish you good luck.
"Break a leg," not "Good luck."
You too.
Anyone cheering you on tonight?
Uh, yeah, my mom invited
-the entire block.
-[chuckles]
It's gonna be really embarrassing.
-[both chuckle]
-You?
Uh, my dad is on his belated honeymoon.
And my mom's in a funk.
But maybe she'll come tomorrow.
Well, um, Via's family will cheer you on.
You'll be great tonight.
-[softly] Honey, just enjoy the play.
-Okay.
All right, go get 'em.
-Mr Davenport...
-Hmm.
I'm really sorry,
but I can't go on tonight.
I don't feel well.
I think I might throw up.
Okay, everybody gets nervous.
You know, when I did my Hamlet,
I threw up every night.
You're gonna be fine.
Just do it. You'll have
all of spring break to recover.
Mr Davenport, you're not listening.
I'm not going on.
Are you kidding me?
I'm really sorry, but Via
knows all the lines. She can do it.
Then go find her, then.
Thank you.
[exhales]
-Hi.
[mellow instrumental music playing]
This play is called Our Town.
It was written by Thornton Wilder.
The name of our town
is Grover's Corners, New Hampshire.
Just across the Massachusetts line.
Is this... Is this really happening?
Yes, you're going on as Emily.
Only you don't have much time.
Well, I don't even know
if I'm gonna remember all of my lines.
You'll be great.
Justin will help you through it.
[Mr Davenport] Where is she?
Via, you're on in two minutes.
Why, why are you doing this?
I told you. I feel sick.
We've got a factory in our town, too.
You hear it?
-Hey, it's okay. Hey, break a leg.
-[Justin] Makes blankets.
Cartwrights own it
and it brung 'em a fortune.
[Mrs Webb] Children, now I won't have it.
Breakfast is just as good
as any other meal.
And I won't have you gobbling like wolves.
It'll stunt your growth. That's a fact.
[whispers] Miranda looks so different.
[whispers] That's not Miranda, it's Via.
-What?
-It's Via.
Oh, great.
[Mrs Webb] As for me, I'd rather have
my children healthy than bright.
I'm both, Mama, you know I am.
I'm the brightest girl
in school for my age.
I have a wonderful memory.
[Mrs Webb] Eat your breakfast.
[play continues indistinctly]
Hmm. Your stomach flu got better fast.
Sorry, sir, just jitters.
I'll be ready by tomorrow night.
She's doing very well.
I can't. I can't go on.
It... it goes so fast.
We don't even have time
to look at one another.
I didn't realize.
So all that was going on
and we never noticed?
Take me back. Up the hill. To my grave.
But first, wait, one more look.
Goodbye. Goodbye, world.
Goodbye, Grover's Corners.
Mama.
And Papa.
Goodbye to clocks ticking.
And food. And coffee.
And hot baths. And sleeping.
And waking up.
Oh, Earth...
You're too wonderful
for anybody to realize you.
[softly] Blow out the candles. Ready?
Take a big breath.
[both inhale]
Ha! We did it. Did you make a wish?
I wished for a brother.
You did?
Mmm. Wow.
-Happy birthday, honey.
-[Nate chuckles]
[all cheering and applauding]
[all cheering louder]
Whoo!
[talking indistinctly]
[Nate] Via!
That was incredible!
-It was just a play.
-It wasn't "just" anything.
-You were amazing!
-[Auggie] You were great, Via!
-Amazing!
-[Via] Oh, Auggie.
[sighs]
[chuckles tearfully]
[Isabel] And then there was the nurse...
[Nate] Yeah.
...who farted, and I don't use
that word a lot, about a hundred times.
-Honey, that was you.
-[all laugh]
To put it delicately.
I don't know how else to say it.
It's not true.
-Busted now!
-[Isabel] No, it's not...
Anyone? Raise your hand
if you wanna change the subject
and save us from this story.
All right, I will. I will.
Um, what is that?
Oh, that is, uh, Jack and Auggie's
science fair project.
Not to be confused with an eyesore
-in the middle of the room.
-[all laugh]
No, but what is it?
Well, I don't know.
I guess it's like a... Yeah.
Follow me, you'll see.
Oh, okay.
[Auggie] Come on!
[Justin] All right.
-Sweet.
-What?
Are you kidding me?
I cannot believe you just did that.
Go, go, go. Okay. But just no kissing.
Seen a lot of horror movies end this way.
We're gonna open
the apertures in three, two, one.
[chuckles] It's a camera obscura.
Yeah. He's 10.
Oh, my God, that was so cool.
Cinema history come to life.
All right, people, single file.
Step right up
for an amazing camera obscura.
Step right up to witness Earth's
greatest mystery, the volcano.
Okay, we're gonna open the apertures in...
[both] Three, two, one!
[kids] Whoa!
[girl] That's awesome!
[beeping]
[beeps]
Jack and Auggie.
[both] Dude!
-See, you have to go...
-No, I did.
[all laughing]
[all continue laughing]
[kids laughing]
[burps]
[all laugh]
-[burps]
-[all laugh]
[Auggie] Okay, now I'll go.
-[burps]
-[all laugh]
[kids chattering]
[Mr Browne] Let's go, let's go.
Everybody get in here.
Find your seats.
We good today?
It's gonna be a good one, guys.
All right. Everybody inside.
Come on. New month, new precept.
-[kids laughing]
-[boy] Look at him.
[Julian] Hey, where's Auggie?
Right there.
Hey, hey, hey.
Why are we running in the hallway?
Auggie, you okay?
Yeah. Everything's fine.
I'm late for class.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Auggie, you know if you need help
you can ask for it.
You're not alone.
I know.
Amos.
You know something about this?
[Mr Tushman] You understand?
We take bullying
very seriously at this school.
There is zero tolerance.
Excuse me, can you explain
what's going on here?
Wasn't Julian the one
who got punched in the mouth?
If there's any bullying going on,
it isn't my son.
[Julian's dad] You wrote that, Julian?
Yes, sir.
That one note was on the back
of a class photo.
Your son photoshopped Auggie out of it.
No. No, he didn't. I did.
Of course, I didn't think that
he would bring it to school.
But when our friends come over
and they see that picture,
I want them to ask about our son.
Not the Pullmans'.
[Mr Tushman] Mrs Albans.
When we pressed Auggie,
he showed us these other notes
that your son left in his locker
and his desk.
Chair.
Okay, look, if no one else is gonna
have the courage to say it,
then I guess I will.
These kids are too young to be
dealing with this sort of thing.
Julian has had nightmares
because of that kid.
-Did you know that?
-Sarah...
We had to take him to a child psychologist
to help him deal with his night terrors.
It's just a two-day suspension.
You'll stay home
from the nature preserve trip.
That's all.
Two days for a couple of notes from a kid?
After all the money that we
have poured into this school?
We have a lot of friends
on the school board, Mr Tushman.
Oh. [sighs]
[exhales] Well, I have more.
[Sarah] So, what would you have us do?
Bend over backwards for every
single person in the world?
Nobody can get their feelings hurt ever?
[chuckles]
You are not doing these kids any favours.
[sighs] Mrs Albans,
Auggie can't change the way he looks.
So, maybe we can change the way we see.
[Sarah] Yes.
I will be sure to tell that
to the real world.
Thank you for this.
We won't be back in the fall.
Mom. I like this school.
-Mom. I have friends, Dad.
-[sighs]
[Julian's dad] Let's go, Julian.
Come on.
[Julian] Mr Tushman.
I'm really sorry.
I know you are, Julian.
[kids chattering excitedly]
-He's not even looking at us.
-Oh. [chuckles]
This is gonna be epic. Race you!
[kids cheering]
-[blows whistle]
-[all cheering]
[people screaming]
[Isabel] The sound of joy!
[Nate] Ah...
All right. I want you to close your eyes,
because I have a surprise for you.
-Do you take requests?
-[laughing]
Not before 9:45.
Okay.
Open your eyes.
No! You... you finished your thesis?
-Let's get drunk.
-[both laugh]
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
Wait a minute.
A double surprise, surprise.
Okay.
-Go ahead.
-Nothing's gonna
-jump out at me, is it?
-No.
Giving me the eyes. [chuckles]
What's in here? I'm kind of scared...
[laughing]
Good, right?
I'm just gonna keep that
in the box for now.
Does that merit a kiss? Come here.
[Isabel] More than a kiss.
Thank you.
[man] All right, kids! Let's give a big
warm welcome to the William Heath School!
The Glover Academy! And Beecher Prep!
Last chance to get popcorn!
-Hello.
-[man] Okay!
Well, welcome to the 23rd annual
Big Movie Saturday in the
Broarwood Nature Reserve!
[all cheering and applauding]
Whoo!
Tonight's movie will be...
The Wizard of Oz!
-Yay!
-[all applaud]
[whispers] Hey, dude.
You wanna go outside?
[whispers] Why?
We can watch this movie anytime.
[movie continues playing]
[Auggie and Jack laughing]
Aw, man, I need to pee.
Wanna go back?
Nah, I'll just go over here.
Like in the subways? That's gross.
No. This is gross.
[inhales and burps]
[both laugh]
Look at that.
What? What are you looking at?
I'm going up there someday.
Well, I'm going down here right now, so...
I gotta go, too, now.
You go there. I'll go here. Don't look.
[kids chattering]
[Eddie] What do we got here?
Couple of losers stinking up the woods.
-[gasps]
-Holy crap! Look at his face!
[boy] He's a freak!
[Eddie] Jesus, I've never seen
anything that ugly in my life.
[boy] Maybe it's an orc.
-Dude, let's go.
-[Eddie] Go where?
Hey, talking to you, Gollum.
This the one mask to rule them all?
My precious.
Hey, what's your problem?
[groans]
[Eddie] Your boyfriend's my problem.
[Auggie] Hey! Leave him alone.
[scoffs] What are you gonna do about it?
-Get outta my way.
-No.
[Eddie] I said get outta my way!
I said no! [grunts]
[Amos] Yo, Jack, what's up, man?
[Eddie] What's this? More little freaks?
What you call us, hick?
Come on, prep boy.
[grunting]
[girl] Guys, stop!
Guys, stop it!
Guys, stop!
Just stop, please! Stop!
-[groans]
-[Amos] Just go!
[Auggie grunts]
Oh, man! Dude! Come on! Let's go!
Let's get out!
[both panting]
-[Auggie] Are you okay?
-Uh...
Dude, you're bleeding.
[rustling]
What was that? Something's coming.
Amos?
[Amos] Jack!
[Jack] Over here!
[Auggie] Amos, come on!
They follow you?
I think we lost 'em.
Whoa!
[all laughing]
[Jack] How did you guys
know we needed help?
We saw them follow you out of the lodge.
I think they were seventh graders.
They were huge.
-[all laugh]
-Thanks, guys.
You totally saved our butts.
Yeah, thanks, guys.
You know, it was cool
how you stood your ground, little dude.
[sniffles]
[crying]
-[fireworks bursting]
-[kids cheering]
[Isabel] Hi!
Oh, my gosh, I missed you so much! Mmm.
-See you later, Auggie!
-[Auggie] Bye!
How are you?
Good. And guess what? I got in a fight.
[gasps] Oh, my God, you're bleeding!
Are you okay?
What happened?
[Isabel] Auggie got in a fight.
[Nate] That's terrible. I'm sorry.
-Did you win?
-Nate!
Well, I'm getting a vibe
like maybe he won.
Did you?
Yeah. And guess what?
They were seventh graders.
-[mimics explosion]
-Yes!
[Miles] See you later, buddy!
Bye!
[Nate] Fighting is bad, Auggie.
-Bye, Mr and Mrs P.
-[Nate] Goodbye.
See you at graduation, Auggie.
Looking sharp.
Thanks, Dad.
I'm talking about me.
Hey! Ah, you look good, too.
I think it's safe to say
the Pullman men are crushing it today.
-You've come a long way, huh?
-Yeah.
Auggie, I am proud of you
for sticking it out.
You didn't think I would, did you?
'Course I did.
Okay, well, come on.
You gotta admit
when you started you were still wearing
the astronaut helmet in public.
I love that helmet.
I wish I knew where it was.
It's in my office.
What? Dad! That was a gift.
You had no right to hide it!
Auggie, Auggie, please, don't be mad.
You gotta understand,
you were wearing it all the time.
I never got to see you any more.
I missed your face.
I know you don't always like it,
but I love it.
It's my son's face.
I wanna see it.
Do you forgive me?
No.
Yes.
Does Mom know?
[whispers] No. God, no, she'd kill me.
But I can maybe find it,
if you need it back.
That's okay.
[choir singing]
Follow the day
Follow the day and reach for the sun!
You don't see me flyin' to the red
One more you're done
Just follow the day and...
-[whispers] Mom.
-[whispers] Yes?
Thank you.
For what?
Making me go to school.
I was so mad at you sometimes.
But I'm really happy to be here.
You really are a wonder, Auggie.
You are a wonder.
Follow the day
Follow the day and reach for the sun!
Whoo! [chuckles]
Thank you, choir.
That was beautiful.
Ladies, gentlemen,
boys and girls, graduates.
Final award this morning
is the Henry Ward Beecher medal
to honour students
who have been notable or exemplary.
Usually, it's a "good works,"
a service award.
But I came upon a passage that he wrote,
which made me realize that good works
come in many forms.
"Greatness," he wrote,
"lies not in being strong
but in the right using of strength.
He or she is the greatest
whose strength carries up the most hearts
by the attraction of his own."
Without further ado, this year,
I am very proud
to award the Henry Ward Beecher medal
to the student whose quiet strength
has carried up the most hearts.
So,
will August Pullman please come
up here to receive this award?
[all cheering and applauding]
Whoo!
You're the best, dude!
[Auggie] Walking up towards
that stage, I felt like I was floating.
My heart was beating so fast.
I didn't really understand
why I was getting a medal.
It's not like I blew up the Death Star.
All I did was get through fifth grade,
just like everyone else here.
Congratulations.
Here you go. That's for you.
[Auggie] Then again,
maybe that's kind of the point.
Maybe the truth is,
I'm really not so ordinary.
Maybe if we knew
what other people were thinking
we'd know that no one's ordinary.
And we all deserve a standing ovation
at least once in our lives.
My friends do.
My teachers do.
My sister does
for always being there for me.
My dad does for always making us laugh.
And my mom does the most.
For never giving up. On anything.
Especially me.
It's like that last precept
Mr Browne gave us.
Be kind,
for everyone is fighting a hard battle.
And if you really wanna see
what people are,
all you have to do... is look.