Why did you get into a fight for love?
I don't know what to say.
You've changed a bit.
So how do you plan to counsel me?
Let's start.
Which class is she in?
The Presidential Order of July 14th, 1987
issued parliament document No. 1641
announce that effective on midnight
of July 15th, 1987,
martial law will be lifted in Taiwan.
President Chiang Ching-kuo,
Premier Yu Kuo-hwa,
Defense Minister Cheng Wei-yuan.
Did you just transfer here?
Class H, Liberal Arts studies.
Class A, 11th Grade,
Science studies.
Lastly, let's train your lung capacity.
Take a deep breath
and immerse your head in the water.
Let's see who can hold
their breath the longest.
Begin.
Later on, I found out
that his name is "Birdy," not "Idiot."
He says that "Birdy"
is the title of a movie.
It's about two good friends.
One is normal
and the other is crazy.
The crazy one's name is Birdy.
Two minutes and four seconds.
I broke my record.
Are you stupid?
What was the craziest thing you did
when you were young?
Dormitory check is a must before bedtime.
Listen, don't you dare hide
any prohibited items.
Hey, haven't I mentioned
that duvets need to be folded neatly?
Mind your personal hygiene, okay?
Don't be too proud of yourself.
Someone hid adult comics
under the mattress once.
When I saw it… Hey!
That's not mine.
Good, there's nothing here.
It's all good.
Don't put your underpants here, okay?
This one's yellowish.
Throw it away, it stinks.
Listen, I'm doing this for your physical
and mental development.
You shouldn't listen
to this superstar concert tape.
I'll keep it for you.
Why are you being sneaky?
Don't think I can't discipline you
since martial law is lifted.
This school's martial law
hasn't been lifted yet.
Tidy up this cabinet later.
A wrongdoer achieves salvation
as soon as he gives up evil.
I'm doing this because I love you.
I'm always watching you.
I'm watching you.
What are you doing?
-What are you doing?
-Go.
Why did you sneak into our dorm?
-Let's get changed.
-Let's go.
What are you doing here?
Do you have a death wish?
I need to borrow soap.
Here you go.
Go.
Fuck.
Are you stupid?
What are you doing?
Where did you go?
He scared the shit out of me.
Goddamn it, let's go.
Hi, everyone. We are…
-The Horn Band.
-I'm Horn.
-I'm Rocky.
I'm Phil.
I'm Jia-han.
Don't let me catch you, naughty girl.
Come on.
You have no idea how hard it is
in a boys' school.
You're like monks who were let out
from a mountain. So horny!
Do you hate straightforward people?
Don't you play musical instruments?
You can treat my body
like a musical instrument.
How do you feel?
It's soft.
Then are you…
I'm sorry.
Treat your musical instrument
as your lover.
Embrace it with love
or it would be like holding a rock
and painful for the audience.
You have to remember,
"Profiter du moment."
"Live in the moment."
It's beautiful to fall in love
at your age.
It will come if it's meant to be.
No one can stop it.
Empty words. How would you know
if you've never been in love, Father?
How do you know I haven't?
-Holy shit, Father. You've been in love?
-Right.
-Tell us.
-Tell us, Father.
Father, one simple question, did you…
Kiss?
That's right, Father.
What did it feel like?
Hey, you guys.
Love is not just physical intimacy.
Was she from Montreal as well?
Yes, Montreal.
I met her at a dance party.
When I looked at her,
she was looking at me too.
Do I need to continue?
Prepare for the flag-raising ceremony.
Father, you haven't finished.
I'll tell you next time, okay?
But my "flag" is already raised.
Supper?
You went out to buy supper?
And drinks too?
You…
What are you looking at?
Do you want to join him?
Those at the back, put your hands up!
Some of you snuck out
in the middle of the night.
Don't think that I don't know.
This is a Christian school.
God is watching all of you.
So you'd better behave yourselves.
Birdy.
This is for you.
It's for the bruises on your butt.
Thank you.
I'll be done in a minute. Wait up.
Aren't you cold having cold showers?
Doesn't it hurt?
Put some newspapers
inside your back pocket next time.
I'm done.
Drag him inside.
Give him a "happy corner."
-Let go of me!
-Phil, pull him farther away.
Are you getting tired?
-Let's have a go again.
-Fucking queer.
-Come on.
-Motherfucker.
Tell me, did you snitch
to the housemaster?
-No.
-You'd better not.
-You didn't?
-I didn't.
Then why is he checking up on us daily?
-If you did, your dick would rot.
-How dare you peek at me in the shower?
Motherfucker, drag him over here!
Fuck, you're still arguing?
Watch it, don't randomly look around.
You're a virus.
Look at yourself. Don't look at me!
I heard that homosexuals
have hairless bodies.
-Take off his pants.
-Take his pants off!
Come here.
No!
Here we come.
Don't move around!
Stop moving!
-You dare to move again?
-Stop!
Dick burning time.
Don't you dare move again. Drag him here.
Who's there?
Whoever you are, come out now.
Come out.
It's me.
Fuck, you scared the shit out of me.
-I just had diarrhea, so I took a shower.
-Come here.
You're pulling up your pants?
Drag him over here.
Beat him up.
-Where are you going?
-No.
-Trying to run?
-What if he tells the housemaster?
-You piece of shit.
-Don't you dare!
Jia-han, hit him.
He peeks at Horn's cock every night.
Isn't that disgusting?
Beat him up.
Come on.
Get him to kneel.
Kneel!
Jia-han.
He'll only do something worse.
He'll force us to be gay too.
Beat him up.
Do it.
You'd better beat me until I bleed,
so the poison in me
would spurt all over you.
Each one of you.
Do it.
How long was he in there?
He must have seen it all.
Chang Jia-han.
Weren't you in the same cubicle?
No, I was in the second one.
What are you doing?
Horn and the others are around us.
Why are you still awake?
You're screwed if you wake them up.
When you came out of the shower,
weren't you scared
they'd give you trouble?
Check this out.
Where did you get these?
From Dirty Head's office.
Dirty Head's office?
Yes.
Have some.
Those sounds
on such a quiet night
sounded like heartbeats.
Heartbeats?
What are you doing?
Hey!
-What are you doing?
-Move.
This is Dirty Head's car.
Wang Po-te.
Fuck.
Shit!
You're fucking nuts.
Are you done yet?
Hurry up, you're taking forever.
Just a few more seconds.
-Would you like to contribute some?
-No!
It's done.
It will definitely stink
when the sun comes up.
With his grades, he can only
be transferred to Liberal Arts.
Don't worry.
We're not giving up on him.
His dad is going to be terribly upset.
He can still make a lot of money
as a lawyer or an accountant.
In compliance with
the Ministry of Education's policy,
our school will start accepting girls
next semester.
With girls joining us, I'm afraid…
Just concentrate on your studies.
Relationships are strictly prohibited
in this school.
Do you understand?
Stop raising it, leave it at half-mast.
Those who watched the news yesterday
are aware
that our most revered President Chiang
passed away yesterday,
on January 13th,
at 3:50 p.m.
So for one month starting from today,
the flag will be at half-mast.
After the final exam,
before winter vacation,
if you want to pay homage in Taipei,
you can take an official leave.
Now, let's observe one minute of silence.
Let's go.
Your attention, please.
We're arriving at Taipei Station.
If this is your stop,
please prepare to disembark.
The next stop is Qidu Station.
We're arriving in Taipei.
OCCUPIED
Thank you.
The left side is for groups.
The right side is for ordinary people.
Queue up properly.
Our beloved
-Mr. Ching-kuo…
-Queue up properly! Maintain order.
-…served his country and his party…
-Move back.
You there!
…with utter devotion throughout his life.
What he did
was a gift to his countrymen.
Your passing is a loss to the whole world…
WITT HIGH SCHOOL'S
MOURNING REPRESENTATIVES
…and we feel deep sorrow in our hearts.
We all love you.
We will follow your example.
You shall remain in our hearts forever.
Almighty Father.
Please take care of President Chiang
just as you take care of us.
-Thank you, President.
-He was a great man.
-May you soon attain Nirvana.
-I may not know the great things he did,
-May you become a god.
-but I think he was great.
-Because everyone liked him a lot.
-Thank you.
May he be free from worry
and sickness in heaven.
Please keep him close to you. Amen.
Check out the clothes here.
Ma'am, I haven't seen you in ages.
Birdy, hurry up!
Look, they sell cassette tapes there.
Open this jar for me.
Would you like to buy it?
Thank you.
-How about a tip?
-Ma'am.
Come and buy some clothes.
They're 50 dollars each.
Why are there so many protest banners?
-No, thank you.
-Thank you. It's fine.
Why are they so angry?
MARRIAGE IS A HUMAN RIGHT!
HOMOSEXUALITY IS NOT A DISEASE!
Look over there.
What is he doing?
I have no idea.
-That's so weird.
-He's over there.
I see him now.
Wang Po-te, it's the Juvenile Police.
Chi Chia-wei, it's you again.
-Are they coming for us?
-No.
You can't protest here.
Chi Chia-wei, are you trying
to revolt here?
-What are they doing?
-Take him!
-Arrest him!
-No.
Wang Po-te.
What are you doing?
Hey, I'll call the police
if you don't stop.
You hooligans! How can you take him away?
-Take him to the station.
-Let him go!
They're plainclothes cops.
The uniformed ones are there.
Will they hurt him?
I don't know.
What would you do if I died?
What do you mean by that?
Stop thinking about those things.
Welcome to Solar System. How many people?
No. Where did they go?
Excuse me, let me clean the table for you.
Okay.
Yes.
Wait for me.
I'll go to the restroom.
Welcome to Solar System.
What were you doing earlier?
Nothing, we were just playing around.
You can't fool around here.
Okay.
Be careful.
Have you read any of Sanmao's books?
Yes.
I like Gone with the Rainy Season
and Stories of the Sahara.
There's a line in one of her books,
"If what you give me is the same
as what you give to others,
then I don't want it."
So you know what love is?
Nobody understands me in this world.
Here.
Let me play a song for you.
Sure.
Who sang this song?
Did he win the College Town
singing contest?
Tsai Lan-chin.
He's dead.
He's dead?
Why was he so hard on himself?
Did you know that by the end of 1987,
the earth's population
had exceeded five billion?
From two people to that many.
God probably didn't expect
such a huge population.
Besides,
the world doesn't need that many people.
Gosh, I can't get up.
Sometimes I feel like
I'm one of those unneeded people.
It's like what my dad says,
"It's useless to raise you.
I should've strangled you
when you were born."
I'll strangle you.
Let's not have any babies in the future,
there are too many people already.
Okay.
You and I can't have babies anyway.
Idiot.
Our Father in heaven.
Thank you for giving us food.
May our food be clean
and keep us healthy.
Jia-han is going into 12th grade soon.
Please help him improve academically
and get into a good university.
As for Chia-ming and Hsiao-ling,
please bestow your blessings on them too.
We thank you before our meal
in the name of Jesus Christ, Amen.
-Amen.
Let's eat.
How long have you been dating?
It's none of your business.
That's your brother's business.
Mind your own.
Once you're in college,
you can date as many girls as you want.
Mr. Chang only made simple dishes,
I hope you don't mind.
They're not simple at all.
Chia-ming, lend me your scooter.
It's about the scooter again.
You talked about it in the kitchen too.
Then buy me one,
so I can have more time to study.
I have no money.
You brought gold back to Chinese mainland,
but you can't afford to get me a scooter.
Damn it. Have I ever starved you?
How much money have you brought back?
How is that your business?
That's my own money.
This is your home too.
-Enough.
-That's right, so I'm in charge!
-Cut it out. We have a guest here.
-Watch your attitude.
It's humiliating
that you're taking Liberal Arts.
You'd better study harder.
Take both Liberal Arts and Science exams,
and see which one you score higher.
Learn from your brother.
Get into a good college
and get a good girlfriend.
Jia-han.
Come inside, your dad wants me
to lock the door.
Are you still upset?
Won't you send money home
when you're working?
Your dad is just trying to prove
that he's doing fine
by bringing money to his hometown.
He wants his family to be proud of him.
Why did you marry him?
If I didn't,
how would I give birth to you?
So you don't love him.
Love? At our age?
We just met each other.
So it was merely procreation.
What do you mean by procreation?
It means having babies.
It shouldn't be like that
if you're in love.
What do you know about love?
It turns to love over time.
Don't think too much.
Just focus on your studies.
Come inside.
Check out some scooters tomorrow.
I'll buy one for you.
I have some savings.
Don't forget to wear a helmet.
Be careful, okay?
Come inside quickly.
Now, we're listening
to the third place
in this week's hits chart,
also last week's fifth place,
"The Crowded Paradise" by Bobby Chen.
Hello, guess who this is.
Mom!
It's Mrs. Chang.
Hello, guess who this is.
What are you up to?
Do you like the color of my scooter?
If you like it, that's all that matters.
Birdy, what are you doing?
I'm collecting posters.
Be careful.
Hurry up.
Are there more posters here?
Are you sure about this?
What if someone comes in?
Until now,
I still remember
what you looked like then.
Stop playing hide and seek with me.
You are…
You are torturing me.
What do you mean?
Only a fool wouldn't understand
what I mean.
I want to be a filmmaker someday.
You really watch a lot of weird movies.
No wonder
you're so weird.
Don't you think things are more fun
in the movies than in real life?
I've never thought about making movies.
It's too difficult.
Fools rush in where angels fear to tread.
Then…
When you make a movie one day,
I'll write the theme song for you.
Deal.
What are you doing here?
Who let you in?
I'll call the police!
Stop!
Will you go to film school with me?
But I don't watch many movies.
Don't worry, I can recommend some.
Let's go to film school in Taipei
and make movies together.
Stop!
Let's make a movie!
Don't you have any desires?
God listed the seven sins
we shouldn't commit.
Pride, greed, envy, lust,
gluttony, wrath, and sloth.
God wants everyone to avoid
the sources of sin,
especially lust.
But I was talking about love, not lust.
Lust is only physical intimacy.
I want him to truly accept me
in his heart.
I still believe in God.
Didn't He say, "Whoever believes
in Him shall have eternal life"?
You should go.
You're misunderstanding God!
Didn't He say,
"Ask and it shall be given to you.
Seek and you shall find.
Knock and the door shall be opened"?
I've been knocking so hard.
Why doesn't He hear it?
Father, you've never
loved anyone like I do,
so you'll never understand!
Good morning, everyone.
It's the beginning of a new semester.
In compliance with
the Ministry of Education's policy,
our school will be accepting girls
and lifting restrictions on hairstyles,
but that doesn't mean you can fool around.
Boys, stay away
from the girls' classrooms.
Tenth grade girls,
if any boy is harassing you,
please report it to the Instructor
at the Student Affairs Office at once.
Is it necessary to have this wire fencing?
Jia-han.
Hello.
-Cool.
-Very impressive.
Did you spend a lot of time on it
to get the girls' attention?
Hey, girls.
Come here, I want to tell you something.
Your face is very pretty.
-Hey, girls. Don't go.
-Girls.
-Girls, talk to us.
How about a scooter ride?
-Hey, girls.
-Girls, come here.
-Do you play musical instruments?
-Which club are you in?
Why does everybody grow their hair longer,
but you cut yours shorter?
Fuck, it's that weirdo again.
Jia-han.
Watch out for that weirdo
when you join Class H.
Hey, everyone with the name "Birdy"
are weirdos.
There was one in my friend's class.
Fuck, there was one
in my class in middle school too.
Watch out in Class H.
If he dares to do anything,
just give us a shout
and we'll be there right away.
What are you looking at?
-Come on.
Let's go.
Jia-han.
-Jia-han, what are you doing?
-Where are you going?
Chang Jia-han!
I'm in the same class as him.
If I don't go with him,
should I go to Class A with you?
Attention.
Take a break.
Boys and girls should practice separately.
Don't think I can't discipline you
in the club.
Instructor, what's going on?
Why do you say that?
Father.
Boys in puberty are very horny.
What if they fail
the college entrance exam?
Dating and studying are different matters.
You can ask them to study hard,
but you shouldn't separate them
like prisoners.
Father, please stay out of this.
God wants you to teach love,
not love between boys and girls.
This is a school rule,
don't make it difficult for me.
I told you to move.
Why are you still sitting together?
-Separate!
-Instructor.
I'm in charge of the band.
I have my way of dealing with this.
Your way of dealing with it
is gathering the students here
and letting them mess around.
Sir, do you have to make it
sound so nasty?
Do you see me talking nastily?
I only heard you.
I didn't want to look at you.
Which class are you in?
How dare you talk to me that way?
-What kind of school do you think this is?
-Instructor, you don't have to be so mean.
I'm just trying to have a discussion.
Why do you make us sound so dirty?
If I weren't mean,
would you take my words seriously?
Would you?
Will separating us prevent us
from messing around?
Wang Po-te.
So after we graduate,
please split the world into two
and return to the era
of concentration camps.
Watch your attitude.
You're in school,
a place that helps you get into college.
So as long as we get into college,
we don't need to learn
about normal social activities?
You're a student.
Students should obey the school rules.
So which rule says
that the seniors can't teach
the juniors in a band?
So what's the point of joining the band?
Fine, I'll remember you two.
You two had better watch out.
Sure, sir.
Class H, 12th Grade, Wang Po-te.
Class A, 10th Grade, Wu Juo-fei.
Instructor, you may leave.
You don't seem to be welcome here.
If anything happens,
you'll be responsible.
Just go.
Goodbye, sir.
-Back to practice.
-Goodbye.
Let's continue.
You should stay away from the girls.
You never know
what the school would do about it.
You sound just like
that annoying instructor.
Finish your food.
We'll rehearse the military song.
Hey.
What's the matter?
How did you get all those wounds?
Did Horn and his friends--
No.
Another class did this.
One of my classmates
hit me here with a brick.
-And this is--
-Hold on.
I actually want to ask you,
when did you start liking boys?
Have you thought of seeing a doctor?
Or have you thought of
getting a girlfriend?
I've known that I like guys
since I was little.
It has never changed
and it never will.
Thank you.
Look at those beside you
and be in unison.
Left, left,
-left, right, left, right, left, right.
-Stop, you motherfucker!
Kill him!
-Where are you going?
-Try to hide!
-Motherfucker.
-Bring that birdman here.
You motherfucker.
-I'll break your wings.
-Get over here!
Let's see if you can still fly.
-Stay away from Jia-han.
-Fuck off!
What are you doing?
-Jia-han, stay out of this.
-Come on!
What are you doing?
-Come down!
-Come here!
Why are you climbing so high?
Come down right now.
Shut up!
-Come down!
You fucking queer, stop running.
-Beat him up!
-Get him!
Kill him!
Hurry.
Birdy!
-Let me go!
-Birdy, what are you doing?
-Don't come near me!
-What are you doing?
Birdy!
I'm sorry. We were just joking.
Birdy, don't jump.
Horn!
We were just kidding, Birdy.
I'm sorry.
Birdy!
-What the hell?
-That scared the hell out of me.
Hey, boys can't be here.
What the fuck were you doing?
Chang Jia-han,
don't hang out with that queer
or people would think that you're gay too!
Birdy, where are you going?
Come on.
-Magnificent, mighty, serious, upright,
-quiet, strong, precise, agile,
-alert, brave.
Halt.
March in place.
Foggy night
Ready, sing.
-Foggy night, stars and moon are dim
-Only the sound of guns echoes all round
-Only shots are flying everywhere
-Toes on the ground, hold your weapons
-Heroic warriors
-Advance into the dark wilderness
-In this world
-Sometimes there's hope
-And disappointment
-That's how I feel
-How I feel
In this world
There's some joy
-There's some sadness, no one can escape
-Hey, he's so handsome.
-No.
-No one can escape it
-I think Birdy is more handsome.
-Our world
-Is not as bad as you think
-Why let it get you down?
-Use your concern…
-Stop!
What are you singing?
This is a military song competition.
What kind of wimpy song are you singing?
Which school are you from?
Who is your advisor?
This is ridiculous!
You're disqualified! Leave!
Come on, let's go.
Next, Taichung First Senior High.
Please get ready.
Wang Po-te.
Go away!
That's enough.
Birdy.
Come on.
You were performing for everyone.
Don't be upset because of him.
They don't understand you, but I do.
Come on.
Don't be mad.
I was going to give this
to you this morning.
It's a throat lozenge.
Fuck!
Hey.
Are you eating the noodles
like they were the judges?
That's right.
Why don't you eat the plate too?
I'm kidding.
Losing isn't a big deal.
Cheers.
I'm not afraid of losing.
We didn't even get to finish the song.
We practiced for over two months.
What's wrong with them?
I thought martial law was lifted.
Do you think the world has changed?
Actually, it hasn't changed a bit.
In my opinion, you've already
won the competition.
Didn't you see the audience's reaction?
I don't know what they were thinking.
It was a lot of fun.
Chang Jia-han, what's wrong?
It was a risky move anyway.
The judges would
either love it or hate it.
Hey, Banban.
Whose songs are you listening to recently?
-Bobby Chen's. Have you heard of him?
-I have.
I like his "The Crowded Paradise."
I like that one too.
Let me play it for you.
Don't move.
Are you two dating?
I thought the world revolved around us.
How did I become an outsider
all of a sudden?
Jealousy is like a snake.
It will eat your heart.
Heavenly Father,
why is it a sin
to love someone?
What are you doing?
Praying.
Heavenly Father,
Chang Jia-han's heart is heavily laden.
He's in 12th grade now.
He doesn't focus on his studies.
He's probably too lonely.
Please use your mighty power
to help him find a girl
whom he truly likes.
Amen.
Do I look funny to you?
You're so lame.
You shouldn't act this way.
What way?
Can you stop hanging out with me alone?
We can be very good friends.
How about I introduce you to a girl?
A girl from Banban's class.
I'm going out with her tonight.
Lend me your scooter.
Come on, give me the key.
The key.
I didn't expect you to call me.
I'm sorry about last time,
I must have scared you.
I was reading Non-no magazine recently.
Do you know how to romanize
the Mandarin word for "good night"?
W-A-N A-N.
Each letter has a meaning.
W means "I."
A means "love."
N means "you."
A-N
means "love you."
You know that if you dial codes
into a pager,
they'll appear in English, right?
This is our secret code now.
Chang Jia-han.
Why did you call me yesterday?
Did you need the scooter?
I went out with Banban last night,
I didn't bring the pager with me.
It was pretty late when I got back.
I was afraid you had gone to bed.
-So I--
-I have something to tell you.
Okay, let's talk tonight.
Listen.
Let's go somewhere at midnight.
I need your assistance.
Shit.
Why are you stealing that?
I'm going to do something big,
don't ask about it yet.
Birdy!
What?
Actually,
I was going to tell you yesterday--
Look at this gigantic balloon!
Teamwork!
Our world
Is not as bad as you think
Why let it get you down?
March, line up properly.
Don't be so lethargic in the morning.
The next class, follow closely.
Boys, what are you looking at?
Don't peep at the girls.
Keep walking.
You're still peeping?
I'm talking about you!
Those at the back, follow closely!
Didn't you eat breakfast?
What's going on?
-"Good night, my love"?
-It's so pretty.
A balloon!
GOOD NIGHT, MY LOVE
That's so nice.
What's going on?
Hey, that's enough.
Is this the big thing
you were talking about?
-Hush, it's a surprise.
-Quiet! Stop it, keep quiet!
So you knew what "good night"
meant when I asked?
Keep quiet!
I'd look it up even if you didn't tell me.
Be quiet!
No more talking!
Try talking one more time!
Who did this?
How dare you!
Does nobody want to admit it?
The school will still find out.
You'd better turn yourself in now.
You'll get worse punishment
if I catch you.
Don't press your luck.
Hello, this is the call center.
Which number are you sending a message to?
Hello?
Hi.
Please leave a message for
178.
Tell him that Jia-han is looking for him
and asking him where he is.
Please ask him
to get back to me.
I often come here.
I spend the whole day here.
I can't help it,
I'm getting old.
What the fuck?
Why do you have to do this?
We're different.
I'm not fucking like you!
Goddamn it!
Fuck off!
You were the one who told me
to live in the moment.
I didn't know you liked boys at that time.
So you can like girls,
but I can't like boys?
Is your love bigger than the love I give?
Tell me.
What's the difference
between your love and mine?
Tell me the difference!
If he doesn't love you,
don't force him to.
That is also living in the moment.
That's impossible!
I can feel that he cares about me too.
"Care" doesn't necessarily mean love.
The bible tells us to control our desires.
Don't cause others to go to hell.
Help me go to hell then.
I'd rather go to hell now.
Don't all homosexuals
deserve to go to hell?
Maybe more people
would understand me in hell.
Make it easy for me
and help me go to hell.
Jia-han.
No! Go back to your heaven!
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I crashed your scooter.
What are you talking about?
What are you apologizing for?
I'll pay for the scooter.
You don't need to pay for it, okay?
What are you saying?
Let me know how much and I'll pay!
I said you don't need to, okay?
Which part don't you understand?
Did you call an ambulance?
I did!
That betelnut stand lady up ahead
called them.
Fuck, she's so nosy.
If you didn't want to call one,
then why did you?
MAINTAIN CLEANLINESS
I'm sorry.
I've called a workshop
to get your scooter.
I'll take care of it.
Don't worry.
I never said that I was worried.
Is that the only thing you care about?
Go away, I can do it myself.
Can you stop being so annoying?
What are you doing?
It hurts!
So how are you going
to do it yourself then?
Spread your legs wider.
Turn around.
Chang Jia-han.
That's enough.
I'm sorry.
Hey, pass the ball here.
-Watch out.
-Thank you.
Hurry up.
I can do it by myself.
Hey.
-Lately--
-I'm done.
Enjoy your lunch.
-He's so cool.
-You can do it, Birdy!
Go!
Dodge him.
Nice one.
-What was it for?
-Disorderly conduct.
They were given major demerits.
-The balloon love confession.
-How can this happen?
-So Wang Po-te did the balloon. So cool.
-Right.
Dating isn't bad.
Why did the boy only get detention
and the girl get expelled?
WANG PO-TE: FOR DISORDERLY CONDUCT,
TWO MAJOR AND TWO MINOR
DEMERITS AND DETENTION.
WU JUO-FEI: FOR DISORDERLY CONDUCT,
THREE MAJOR DEMERITS AND EXPULSION.
-Park the car for me.
-Sir, it's good to see you here.
Where is he?
-Mr. Wang.
-Don't run away!
-Don't beat the kid.
-Come back!
Come back here!
Fuck!
Mr. Wang.
You're the president
of the Parents Association.
It's not good to hit your kid at school.
Mr. Wang, we're at school.
Stop this.
We don't approve of corporal punishment.
-Fuck you.
-Why are you acting this way?
-Please stop.
-I'm teaching my son a lesson.
This is none of your business.
My son is useless.
Don't you dare run away!
Your three older sisters
are nothing like you!
If I had known, I wouldn't have had you.
Then you shouldn't have!
I shouldn't have?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Chang Jia-han, what are you doing here?
Chang Jia-han, why are you here?
-You want to get beaten up?
-Go to class.
What the hell are you doing here?
What?
What are you doing?
If I don't teach you a lesson,
you'll never learn.
Stop beating him up!
Get out of my way, it's not your business!
Don't you dare run.
-You're tough?
-Sir, stop it!
You bastard.
Sir, please stop!
Who are you?
How is he related to you?
I'm disciplining my son,
get out of my way!
Go away!
It's none of your business.
Why is it none of my business?
It's my love affair, not yours.
Instructor.
It's my love affair.
It was me!
What nonsense is this?
When did you have a love affair?
What would you know about my love affair?
Instructor, it was my love affair.
I set up the balloon.
It was me!
What are you two doing?
Why are you treating me this way?
-All right, stop fighting!
-That's enough!
Stop fighting!
-Stop! That's enough.
-Stop!
-Enough!
Jia-han!
Enough!
Leave me alone!
Why?
-That's enough!
-What are you doing?
Wang Po-te.
This is a school, not your home.
Father.
These two are in the band.
I told you,
you must separate the boys and girls.
Look at this.
They're messing around.
-Wang Po-te, what are you doing?
-Don't mind him!
Just let him go to hell!
When I was 18,
I was a rebel just like you.
I was beaten up
by our church's priest every day.
The last time he did it,
he beat the crap out of me,
like you are now.
That's why I decided to leave Montreal.
I wanted to get as far away as possible.
I didn't think my hometown
would change after I left.
When was that?
Almost 30 years ago.
In 1960,
the Quiet Revolution happened in Montreal.
Society broke free from the church.
People could finally follow their hearts
and choose for themselves.
I missed the revolution in Montreal,
but I encountered your revolution here.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
thy will be done on earth
as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread.
Jia-han!
-And forgive our trespasses as we--
-Jia-han!
Father Oliver.
Jia-han's mom called the school
and asked him to go home.
I don't want to go home.
But
your mom said,
Birdy is at your house.
What did you do at school?
What?
Did you try to steal his girlfriend?
What do you want?
Why did you come here?
The college entrance exam is coming up,
I should really concentrate on studying.
And your dad and mom
should know what's going on
with you at school.
I'm the one who has a girlfriend.
Why did you interfere?
Why are you covered in cuts and bruises?
Did you get into a fight?
No.
You're such a loser.
You stole his girl and fought with him.
I didn't steal his girlfriend!
Why is he here then?
Jia-han.
Both of you are best friends.
Don't fight over a love affair.
-You are still young.
-Mr. and Mrs. Chang.
-Don't worry about it. I'll get going.
-Okay.
Tell me,
what do you want from me?
You're best friends, so don't fight.
So are we only best friends?
What do you want then?
I'm doing this for you.
You can have a girlfriend
when you go to college.
What if he doesn't find one in college?
That's okay, he's still young.
What if he never has a girlfriend?
Wang Po-te.
Stop being an asshole.
How is it your business
if I get a girlfriend or not?
So who doesn't have the balls now?
Can you stop bothering me?
Okay.
Dad.
Mom.
I don't like the girl.
-Actually, I like--
-Chang Jia-han!
Can you stop bothering me?
I dare to say who I like.
Do you dare?
Have you lost your mind?
Have you gone crazy?
Chang Jia-han.
Can you stop acting like a queer?
What's wrong with being a queer?
Does it disgust you?
If you find it so disgusting,
say it right to my face.
Say it right to my face!
-Jia-han!
-Where are you going?
Jia-han!
Chang Jia-han, where are you going?
Chang Jia-han!
Let's go back!
Chang Jia-han, where are you going?
-Thank you.
-Attention, passengers.
The ship is ready for boarding now.
One ticket, please.
What time?
Just give me whatever he got.
What are you looking at?
Dear passengers.
We'll be arriving at Magong Harbor
on Penghu Island.
Please follow the instructions
-to proceed to disembark.
-Stupid bird.
-Why do you keep following them?
-Don't forget your belongings.
Chang Jia-han!
Let's go back!
Do you know you're crazier than me?
I won't give a damn anymore
if you don't stop!
I'm serious!
When did you ever give a damn about me?
Tell me, when have you ever
cared about me?
I just want to go
to a place without you, okay?
Go then.
Keep going then.
Let's see how far you can go.
Where exactly do you want to go?
I'll go wherever I want to go.
You can't run away.
You're not going anywhere.
I'll show you how far I can go.
-Fuck!
The tide kept rising.
I really hoped
this would be the end of the world.
After that day,
he said he'd prepare
for the college entrance exam.
And we never
saw each other again.
THE 17TH WITT HIGH SCHOOL
MARCHING BAND REUNION
I remember I once said,
"Live in the moment."
-Live in the moment.
-Cheers!
-To our good health.
How is that possible?
-People become more cowardly as they age.
-That's true.
It's Chang Jia-han.
Horn, go talk to him.
Gosh, look who it is.
-Chang Jia-han.
Where have you been hiding?
Everybody, it's Chang Jia-han's
first time at our reunion.
He's from the Liberal Arts studies.
Let's give it up for him.
Wow, you're still so handsome.
Come on, bottoms up.
Now, I'm giving you a copy
of the contacts first.
I've also sent an electronic copy
to our LINE group.
When you have time,
please update it
since these are very out of date.
Pass them around, thank you.
Is this Birdy?
Birdy.
Long time no see.
How have you been?
I'm fine.
I didn't expect you to page me.
Are you confident
to retake the exam this year?
I don't know.
What do you mean by that?
All the best, you can do it.
Did you change your phone number?
My dad said someone kept calling
and not talking.
It wasn't me.
I know.
You didn't tell me that you moved.
Is everything okay
with you and Banban?
She said
that being with me
is like being in a Chiung Yao movie.
It's not realistic.
Isn't that good?
Everyone's first love
is as great as an epic movie.
Don't you think so?
There's a new song recently.
I…
No, one of my seniors wrote it.
Is it okay
if I play it for you?
Searching for you
Out of everyone, you came into my mind
I've been trying so hard
Not to think of you
But the memories brought me back again
Your name engraved herein
Making time go by without a trace
I've decided to love
Only one for the rest of my life
I hope that the world would stand still
So missing you wouldn't be a luxury
If I have another chance
I'd surely love again
Your name engraved herein
You're buried deep down in the dust
If I didn't do so
I wouldn't be able to live my life
Living in a city
That only reminds me of you
Holding the key to fly into the sky
Continue to fly
I'm always here for you
I didn't expect you to pick up the phone.
How has he been doing recently?
I don't know.
When I'm busy,
I ask him to take care of our child.
I don't bother to ask about other things.
Birdy and I are divorced.
I only understood later on.
Liking boys
is innate.
If I had known,
I wouldn't have tried so hard.
It has ruined my life,
and his.
Fuck this.
This waterfall
separates Canada and America.
America is right across there.
It's said that an ancient Indian tribe
once lived behind it.
The girls there
couldn't choose their own lover.
They had to follow
their parents' arrangements.
Thousands of years ago,
there was a girl just as pretty as me.
She didn't want to marry the old ugly man
her parents had chosen,
so she cried for a day and a night
on top of the waterfall, then jumped off.
She disappeared into the water.
Since then, people noticed a mermaid
in the water.
I heard that the mermaid
looks exactly like that girl.
Hey.
Didn't you leave already?
I was going inside,
but I saw you walking out.
How did you know that I'd be here?
I just came to try my luck.
I saw you sitting there
in the afternoon the other day.
You saw me?
Why didn't you say hello?
Perhaps I didn't expect to bump into you
in such a place.
Did you come to visit Father Oliver too?
Yes, I wanted to thank him.
Because I'd go to him
whenever I was confused.
Back then, Father probably didn't want me
to suffer the pain he'd experienced,
so he kept stopping me from liking you.
But I would've preferred
to experience those things.
We both did a lot of stupid things before.
I thought that by doing so,
you would give up your…
My feelings
for you.
You thought I'd give up
my feelings for you.
How can it be that easy?
Who knew?
Who knew what the world would be like
after 30 years?
If we admitted that we were gay back then,
it would've been the end of us.
How about now?
You can say it out loud.
Can you?
Actually, I really loved you at that time.
The more we hung out,
the more I realized
that it would end badly.
So I asked Banban a favor
to find you a girl to hang out with.
To seduce you.
And to see if you could be corrected.
Did you think I have scoliosis
or crooked teeth
that I needed to be corrected?
But later on,
Banban herself came to seduce me.
I know.
She told me.
I was in stitches.
How is your mom?
She keeps asking how you were doing
and if you were married.
What did you say?
I said, "Who cares?"
-I should go visit her sometimes.
-You should.
I remember you once took
a naked picture of me.
Wasn't it the other way around?
Is that so?
This world
Sometimes there's hope
And disappointment
That's how I feel
Do you really have a naked picture of me?
Take a guess.
Hey! Don't.
My gosh.
-Don't move.
-Hey!
What are you doing?
It's almost dawn
and you're still so hyper.
Give it back.
Give it back to me.
You're so annoying.
Where are you staying tonight?
The Grand Hotel. What about you?
Here?
Yes.
Okay.
Go and get some rest.
The hotel is just ten minutes away
on foot.
Hey.
Would you like to come up
and have a drink?
No.
Maybe next time.
Good night.
What's the matter?
I'll walk with you for a bit.
Let's go.
Birdy, catch.
-You suck.
-Did you screw up in the exam?
Yes, I did terribly. Okay?
Pass me the ball.
The other side.
You're not in a good mood.
Why would I feel bad about my grades?
You're right.
I don't need to know Physics or Chemistry
to make a living in the future anyway.
Fuck, it's too far.
Give it to me.
Catch!
So how will you make a living then?
Me?
-Idiot.
-Forget you
-I've told myself several times
-The more I try to catch the light
-The harder it is
To pull away
I love you
-It only seems memorable to me
-I finally
-Had the courage to give you my heart
-Your silent response is the kindest grace
-Your name engraved herein
-Making time go by without a trace
-One lie was told
-That determined the rest of my life
-I stand defiant to the world
-Even breathing is a luxury
-If I have another chance
-I'll surely love again
-Your name engraved herein
-You're buried deep down in the dust
-If I didn't do so
-I wouldn't be able to live my life
-Living in a city of neon lights
-Holding the address to paradise
-You can soar, but I can only stay here
Hey, Birdy.
It's nothing.
Subtitle translation by:
Yifang Lee, Evan Murray Colbert