It's time, Wonder Boy. Time to shine.
Eyes on your mom.
Hey!
Don't run randomly!
Go to the second floor!
I've already registered,
go to the second floor!
Your grandson has hemolytic jaundice.
Since his mom's blood type
is different from his,
her antibodies cause
his bilirubin level to rise,
resulting in jaundice.
What does that mean?
The jaundice has affected his brain.
The part of his brain which controls
his muscles is permanently damaged.
To put it simply,
it's cerebral palsy.
Even if he survives,
I believe that it would be difficult
for him to walk or use chopsticks.
The only thing we can do now
is an exchange transfusion.
The question is…
-Do you want to go for it?
-Yes!
Do whatever it takes!
Due to his cerebral palsy,
his muscle tone and control
are worse than an ordinary person's.
For instance,
his fingers are showing signs of atrophy.
As for his lower limbs,
since he has very weak muscles,
based on my experience,
if he's still not walking at this age,
I believe that the chances
of him walking is very slim.
We also found
that due to his cerebral palsy,
Wa Wai is left
with 10 to 20% of his hearing,
leading to difficulty in communicating.
He must wear a hearing aid
as soon as possible.
Mr. Shui, one coke, please.
Sure.
There's no need, it's my treat.
Why him?
Why not them?
Here, two dollars.
Jeez, how long will she keep searching?
Hey, don't you have work to do?
Mrs. So said
that her son's hearing aid is gone.
She's searching for it.
Is your son mentally challenged,
or are you?
I'm already letting you bring him to work.
Now, I have to stop the machines for him.
We have a deadline.
You can search for it yourself!
Get back to work, all of you!
-You're all crazy!
-It's no use.
It's better to just buy a new one.
It's worth thousands of dollars.
Wa Wai?
Wa Wai!
Why are you here?
Who moved you here?
You can't walk,
but you can scream!
Why are you smiling?
What's so funny?
You think it's funny?
Walk now,
or let's die together!
Walk.
Walk!
Show me that you can walk, okay?
I'm looking at you.
Walk to me.
No one treats you like an ordinary person.
So just be
an extraordinary person.
Yes, well done.
That's right, one more step.
What's your name, kid?
Shu Ah Ai.
No, "shu" means lose.
So.
Wa.
Wai.
So Wa Wai.
Show your grandpa your walk.
You're amazing.
Dad, Wa Wai is doing great.
Darling, I went to see the doctor.
He said that
Wa Wai's condition isn't hereditary.
He said our next child will be fine.
It's very tiring to raise another child.
Get one more job.
When we're old,
someone has to take care of Wa Wai.
Stop playing around. Hurry up.
Wa Wai!
Kin Wai.
Where were you, little guy?
Both of you, hurry up.
I have tons of clothes to sew.
I must bring them to the factory too.
For your homework tonight--
Mom! I need to go to the toilet.
You're so fussy. Be quick.
Kin Wai.
What's your grade in memorization today?
I think you got a zero again.
Okay, tell me. What's this word?
I don't know.
What about this?
"Sports Association
for the Physically Disabled."
"Sports Association."
"Athletics team"?
God of Fortune is here!
May you prosper, Mrs. Chan!
God of Fortune!
You're so smart. You can write now?
Nice writing!
Here are ten dollars for you.
Thank you, Mrs. Chan. Thank you!
Good boy!
Wa Wai! Mom wants you
to come back for dinner.
What are you doing?
Selling God of Fortune!
Kin Wai, we can get extra food tonight!
Great!
Hey, who allowed you
to sell God of Fortune here?
You can stay if we keep half of the cut.
What are you doing?
Don't move or I'll beat you up.
Mom, they're bullying Wa Wai.
What?
Wa Wai!
Hey! Stop running, you punk!
-Don't let me catch you!
-Wa Wai!
Come on! Run faster!
Hurry up! Catch him!
Go upstairs.
Hurry, outflank him!
On the left.
Wa Wai! Run faster!
Outflank him! Don't follow me!
Go! Up ahead!
Where are you going?
Damn! That retard is so fast!
Hurry! Don't let them catch you!
Wa Wai! Run faster!
-Run faster!
-Stay there!
Stop, you retard!
You bunch of brats!
Scram!
Let's go! Don't just stand there.
Wa Wai, did you get hurt?
Do you feel unwell?
We can get extra food tonight.
I came to register.
Wa Wai.
How old are you?
Thirteen years old.
He's too young then.
ALL PARTICIPANTS MUST BE
14 YEARS OLD AND ABOVE.
ALL PARTICIPANTS MUST BE…
He's already 14. Based on his nominal age.
Nominal age?
All right, ma'am. He's 13 now.
If I let him join,
he'll compete with 18 and 19-year-olds.
It's unfair for him too.
Look how long his limbs are.
He's probably taller
than those 18 and 19-year-olds.
He's still in puberty,
and he's already taller than you.
Come on, give him a chance.
Come back next year, ma'am.
Wa Wai!
Where are you going?
Do your best to run to the finish line.
Look over there and keep running, go!
Wa Wai,
those 18 and 19-year-olds
aren't as tall as you.
Okay! Get into position.
Let's go, Wa Wai.
Wa Wai! You finished the race!
Wa Wai!
Wa Wai! You finished the race.
-Come back! Wa Wai!
-Ma'am.
-Come back!
-Wa Wai!
He's your son?
Yes.
I'm Fong, coach of
Hong Kong Para-Athletics Team.
I would like to invite your son
to join our training.
What?
Bring him here at 7 p.m. on Monday.
Wa Wai.
You're going to start training soon.
Listen to Coach Fong.
Don't be too shy to ask questions.
Don't give up easily, okay?
Did you hear me?
Can you do it?
Of course,
it's just running.
How hard can it be?
Seven more laps to go.
Keep running!
Get lost if you can't run.
Don't slow others down!
Coach Fong, are you sure about this kid?
-Let's get someone else.
-How are you feeling?
Are you tired? Have some water.
What's going on?
Go home if you want to rest.
Keep running.
Run.
Mrs. So,
if you're going to let me train your son,
please don't interfere.
Don't come here again.
Also, you're not an athlete.
Keep off the track.
Here, have some water.
Drink it slowly.
Let me tell you.
You don't take Coach Fong too seriously.
If he says ten laps,
just answer, "Sure!"
Then run two laps.
And walk for the rest.
By the way,
are you part
of the Physically Disabled Team too?
Coach Fong is my elder brother.
By the way,
why is he running
with a plastic bag on his head?
He's crazy.
He said it's as good
as high-altitude training.
He can train his cardiovascular function.
Rumor has it
that he used to have
100 m races with trains.
He really ran faster than a train.
That's why we call him Train Tung.
Don't be silly, it's not going to work.
What's he saying?
Who knows? Only Gai can understand him.
So we always need Gai
to translate for him.
All right! Okay, do whatever you want,
even if it kills you.
Whatever, suit yourself.
What does he want this time?
He said he came up with a quicker way
to pass the baton. What a joke.
-Hurry up.
-All right, I'm coming.
Okay, I'm here.
Come on, be quick.
Train Tung, train by yourself.
Gai and Keung. Run five laps first.
Then another lap
after a three-minute break.
Full speed for the last 200 m.
Repeat 3 times.
Train baton passing with me afterward.
Okay.
Wa Wai, run ten more laps tonight.
That's 20 in total.
I mean nonstop.
Do you know what nonstop means?
Sure.
Go on, then.
Hey!
I told you to run, not walk.
All right, that's a wrap!
The lights are off, but you're not.
You have eight more laps.
Don't go home until you finish them.
Run.
You know why I chose you?
That day, you showed very steady
and frequent strides.
I've never seen such a strong first-timer.
But I've only seen that once.
I've never seen that again on you.
Wa Wai, Coach Fong is tough on you
because he wants you to be good enough
to take his place.
In the last Paralympics,
he took Train Tung, Keung, and I
to run the 4x100 m relay.
Even with our usual practice time,
we could have pocketed a medal.
But Keung and I thought we crossed
the changeover box during baton passing
and lost some time.
We came fourth in the end with no medals.
It hit Coach Fong the hardest
as it was his last Paralympics.
Why did he stop running?
He hurt his back, and he's old.
But the three of us are over 30 years old.
This could be our last one too.
So,
we're counting on you this time.
Does it mean
we can win a gold medal if I run?
Who knows?
You're so slow, maybe a silver.
No way, I have to get a gold medal!
Yes, I have to get a gold medal!
His 100 m record is still over 15 seconds.
That's not a big problem,
we can help him make up for some time.
My biggest worry now is his balance. Look.
It means he can't run
the first and third bends.
So he must be second?
He's bad at baton passing,
so that's even riskier.
Hurry!
No, we'll be in trouble.
Why?
I have always run the anchor leg!
That's my decision and it's final.
Why should we always accommodate him?
We're a team.
It doesn't matter
who crosses the finish line.
It matters to me!
I quit!
-Let go of me!
-Are you done?
We're doomed if he runs the third leg.
But we still stand a chance
if he runs the anchor leg.
You want him to run fourth?
I'm quitting unless he runs
in under 15 seconds!
Carry on.
Yes.
Do it slowly.
Find your balance first.
Squat lower.
Do it slowly, find your balance first.
Can you do it or not?
Wa Wai?
What's with the bag over your head?
Why are you crying?
Have you been bullied?
Tell me.
I want…
I want to run faster.
I'm already working so hard.
Instead of crying hard, run hard.
Let's make it
less than 15 seconds together!
Faster!
A nice and juicy hamburger.
Wa Wai, you must eat more beef.
Build more muscles,
then you'll be able
to carry two Gills in the future.
Kin Wai, this is yours.
Yours has a slice of cheese.
Wa Wai's has none.
Hey, Wa Wai. Wait for me.
Dad, have some eggs.
Mom, have some eggs.
Wa Wai, have some eggs.
Hand!
Hey!
Young man.
Excuse me, please.
This place is mine.
How did it go?
Train Tung really never showed up.
It's up to him to run with us or run away.
But there are only three of us,
will you run again?
Call him and talk to him.
Are you insane?
He doesn't have a problem with Keung.
You call him.
Forget it, leave him be.
I'm not allowed inside.
You are allowed to, but you just won't.
It's full of mosquitoes here.
It's so annoying.
Do you know that you have a fan?
That silly boy Wa Wai
is putting a plastic bag over his head
just like you.
Are plastic bags used for that?
I thought a bag
is for carrying stuff only.
Do you want some?
It's good.
Shall we share it?
That silly boy was crying as he said,
"I wish I could run just as fast as him."
It must be cool
to be someone's idol.
Run!
I said run, laggard!
Extend your hand!
Grab it!
Run!
Faster!
Look ahead! Run!
Run faster! Run!
Run!
14.57 seconds!
You did it!
Do your best, son.
I told all our relatives to watch
the live broadcast on television
and cheer for you.
There's no live broadcast
of the Paralympics in Hong Kong.
Really?
But when Lee Lai Shan
got her Olympic gold medal last month,
I watched her on television.
How can the Paralympics
compare to the Olympics?
We only get a few dozen thousand
if we win a medal in the Paralympics.
The government gave Lee Lai Shan
one million for her gold medal.
Why is the difference so big?
In this world, equal pay
for equal work doesn't exist.
I'll check in.
Stay right here and wait for me.
Wa Wai?
Mom, can you hear me?
Yes, I hear you.
I can only talk for five minutes.
What?
I'll speak faster then.
You flew over ten hours, are you tired?
Did you get some sleep?
Eat more beef, US beef is good.
Yes, there is a lot of beef here.
There's steak and hamburgers.
Everything is free.
Stuff yourself up then.
You need fuel for running.
But I don't want to run anymore.
You guys are not here.
I'm all alone.
How are you alone?
I'm watching you.
How?
Are you going to fly over here?
When you start running,
imagine me watching you
at the finish line.
It's just like what they always say.
Eyes on your mom, set, go!
What?
It's "on your mark,"
not "eyes on your mom."
By the way, where are Dad and Kin Wai?
Those two are sleeping like pigs.
Let me hear it.
Wait a moment.
Wait.
How is it now?
No, there's still no signal.
-How about this position?
-No.
Move it a bit, Hong.
There's still no signal!
And now?
Still no signal.
It's working! Don't move!
It's Wa Wai.
I want to pee.
Endure it for a bit.
The race will start soon.
Keung!
Don't be scared!
You have a chance, it's no time to fear!
Fearing is losing!
Run while you still can!
Keung! This is our last race.
Win a medal for me, okay?
Can you? Keung!
Yes!
I can do it!
-Yes!
Faster!
Go!
Hand!
Run!
Run to the finish line!
Get up!
We won first place!
We won!
Get up!
Look!
First place!
-Here they come.
-It's So Wa Wai!
-They're back.
-Over here.
-Get off from here.
-Stop here.
Wa Wai!
Smile!
-Mom!
-Say a few words.
-Mom! I miss you so much!
-Wa Wai!
I miss you!
You were incredible.
Gosh, it's so heavy!
-How are you? Are you tired?
-So Wa Wai.
What it's like to win the first
Paralympics gold medal for Hong Kong?
What about Mrs. So?
So Wa Wai represented Hong Kong
at such a tender age.
With such good results,
how do you feel?
It's wonderful.
So, "Wonder Mom,"
what's your secret
to raising this "Wonder Boy"?
Just eat more beef.
As a mom of a Paralympic athlete,
what do you think the government
needs to improve on?
Equal pay for equal work.
What?
It's true.
I mean they're all Olympic gold medalists.
Why do Paralympians get
so much less than normal Olympians?
I think there should be
equal pay for equal work.
-Yes!
Well said!
Mom.
This is for you.
When I was little,
Grandpa always said
that when you married Dad,
you didn't have any gold jewelry.
So
I'm going to get lots and lots
of gold medals for you.
SO WA WAI'S MOM SUPPORTS HER SON
SHOULD HE BECOME
A PROFESSIONAL ATHLETE
Did he win?
Wa Wai!
-At the 2004 Paralympics in Athens,
-Don't move.
So Wa Wai, our Wonder Boy,
won a gold medal in the 200 m men's
T36 classification for Hong Kong again,
breaking his own world record
at the same time.
Congratulations to the winners
from various fields
for receiving the 35th Hong Kong
Ten Outstanding Individuals Award.
Please come to the stage
for a group photo.
Thank you, our media partners.
Congratulations again to our winners.
Hello, Mrs. So.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Did I startle you?
-No.
This is my business card.
Mr. Lau?
Just call me Victor.
My company specializes
in representing athletes.
We negotiate sponsorships for athletes.
Sometimes, we arrange
advertisement deals too.
Increasing one's popularity is secondary.
What's important is earning extra cash.
You know how hard life is
for Hong Kong athletes.
Mrs. So, the press is waiting.
Do the interview with Wa Wai.
All right.
I'll leave you to it.
Mr. Lau, how much can you make
from an advertisement?
It's hard to give an exact number.
But it's safe to say that it'll be more
than winning a gold medal.
Mrs. So?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Thank you in advance then.
Let's work together then.
Bye.
-Bye.
The next Olympics will be held in Beijing.
To us Hong Kong athletes…
It's…
It's extremely meaningful.
Well…
I hope that I can run faster
when the time comes.
I hope that I can break my own record.
-Happy Mid-Autumn Festival, everyone!
-Coach Fong, what do you want to eat?
-Thank you, I'll help myself.
This beef is good.
Okay, thank you.
Gill, these are your favorite fish balls.
Eat more.
Thank you.
Thank you, you should eat too.
Coach Fong, for the next Paralympics,
I want to join the 100 m, 200 m,
and 400 m events.
Sure.
You agreed so easily, Coach Fong.
If Gai and Keung
weren't over the age limit,
I would let him
join the 4x100 m relay too.
Wa Wai, look at how much faith
your coach has in you.
No, I'm just spreading my bets evenly,
just like horse racing.
-Happy Mid-Autumn Festival.
Hey.
Here.
You always wear flip-flops.
Your toes!
You don't cut your nails?
-That's not true.
-I'll cut your toenails! So Wa Wai!
So Wa Wai!
Want some mandarin oranges?
Wa Wai.
Let me ask you a brain teaser.
Why does Ming run faster than a train?
Because Ming runs really fast.
Wrong!
Because it's a toy train!
Why do you and Gill have the same answer?
Why can't you believe that Ming
can really run faster than a train?
You keep talking about Gill all the time.
Ask her out if you like her.
Don't say ridiculous things.
Don't you ever, ever
say this in front of her!
You can't fool me, kiddo.
The wind is high, and the sun is out.
It's perfect for asking a girl out.
Wa Wai, you're already a grown-up.
Go and ask.
I can't hear you.
Hey!
I can't hear you!
Wa Wai!
Faster!
You did it.
My son ran faster than a train! Wa Wai!
I have no idea how he got into a fight.
I…
Hi, Miss.
Where is the Orthopedics Department?
-Take the lift to the seventh floor.
-Thank you.
I have to go.
We'll sue him!
Darling, take me to a private hospital.
Get me a specialist to check my head.
Let that bastard pay for it.
You tripped yourself down the stairs.
Who are you suing?
Are lawyers free?
Are private doctors free?
Mr. So, how much have you got
in your pocket?
The doctor wants you to lie in bed
for two months.
If you twist your neck again,
you'll become paralyzed.
Mom, I just asked Keung.
He can recommend me
to the courier company he works for.
No way! You're training all day long.
And courier? Your legs won't last.
-Even better, I can treat it as training.
-No way.
I'll take another part-time job.
Kin Wai, stop playing basketball
after school for the next two months.
Take care of your dad.
Help him with going to the toilet.
I'm on the soccer team.
Hello, is this Victor?
Speaking. Who is calling?
I'm Mrs. So.
Can you find
some advertisements for Wa Wai?
Gosh, it's difficult to get those lately.
The Olympics are years away.
No one will get an athlete
for advertisements.
With your capabilities,
I'm sure you can find something.
You're too kind.
I'll try to ask around tomorrow.
Thank you.
I'll call again in a couple of days.
Sure, I'll let you know
if I have any news.
Get some rest, Mrs. So. Bye.
Here.
Take it.
Get the medals back with the money.
Is it not enough?
Here.
I still have over 3,000 dollars
in the bank.
That's everything I have.
Take it!
Do you know that your brother
won every medal with blood and sweat?
How can you sell them?
Aren't you embarrassed?
Yes, I'm a disgrace!
I'm a loser, unlike my elder brother!
Have you ever taken care of me?
Do you know what my favorite food is?
When we go out for Christmas dinner,
my steak is always missing
from my mixed grill.
My burgers are buns without patty!
I'm your son too.
My purpose is just to care for Wa Wai.
So I'm making money to care for him now!
Also,
I'm not on the basketball team.
I'm on the soccer team,
Mom.
Keung's company is willing to hire me.
I told you not to worry about us.
No, Mom.
I don't want to run anymore.
I want to go and earn money.
I've already been to the Paralympics
and won gold medals.
I have no regrets.
I don't want to see you working four jobs
and Kin Wai making money,
just so that I can continue running.
I don't want you all to suffer.
I'll suffer even more if you quit, Wa Wai.
People look up to you because you run.
But I'm the one looking down
on myself now.
All right, it'll be fine.
Don't worry, okay?
Breakfast is on the table.
Okay.
What the heck!
I waited for you for so long.
Stop eating and move!
It's already 3:30 p.m.
No, because I was--
Stop jabbering!
The Paralympic Committee called me.
They want you to be the torchbearer.
No, Coach Fong.
I'm not an athlete anymore.
I'm a courier now.
You're really not running anymore?
You'll be over 30 at the next Paralympics.
This might be your last chance.
Coach Fong.
My dad still can't go back to work.
I can earn around 7,000 dollars a month
with my job now.
After probation,
I'll get the 13th month's pay.
If I go back to running,
I only get 3,000 dollars
of government subsidy a month.
Earlier, the Olympic flame touched down
in Hong Kong from Ho Chi Minh City.
The torch relay in Hong Kong begins.
The first time Hong Kong took part
in the Olympic torch relay was in 1964
in the run-up
to the Olympic Games in Tokyo.
This is the city's
second Olympic torch relay.
At 8 a.m. this morning,
the Olympic torch relay began
at the piazza
of the Hong Kong Cultural Center.
Celebrities and athletes
will join hands for the relay.
The relay will last for eight hours,
passing throughout the city.
Crowds holding the national
and HKSAR flags have lined their route
while the torchbearers wave
at the crowd as they run.
What a spectacle.
Everyone wants to personally witness
the momentous Olympic torch relay.
COUNTING DOWN TOWARDS
2008 BEIJING OLYMPICS
HONG KONG TEAM STRIVES
FOR ANOTHER GROUNDBREAKING VICTORY
Hello, Victor. I'm Mrs. So.
Mrs. So? What's the matter?
Didn't you say
that you couldn't get an advertisement
because the Olympics is still far away?
The Beijing Olympics is coming.
Can you get him something?
Of course, but I heard
that Wa Wai has quit running.
In that case, it would be difficult,
unless he runs in Beijing.
He will! He never said he would quit.
Wa Wai! Run faster, slowpoke!
Wa Wai,
I got you some advertisement deals.
With the money, you can keep running.
What? Advertisements?
-Okay, our crew is ready.
-It's so cute.
You look really cute, it's very nice.
Can't you stop laughing?
You really look like him.
No, Mom.
I really can't do this sort of thing.
-You look good!
-I know, right?
Yes, you look like Wonder Boy
in the flesh.
The client will love it.
Really, the client will love it.
Hey, he's ready.
All right, Wa Wai. Let's have a rehearsal.
Mrs. So.
I've negotiated some sponsorships.
Shirts, trousers,
shoes, socks, and health drinks.
Sign here.
They'll send them to your house.
-Okay. Look this way, Wa Wai.
-They're free?
-That's what sponsorship means.
-It's all right.
Really? So generous?
It's not that they're generous.
It's because I'm competent.
You're really running today.
You're not being Wonder Boy.
How can you say that?
How was it?
How long did it take?
You're back to your time in Atlanta.
It's normal, you stopped training
for one and a half years.
You only have eight months
before the games in Beijing.
I know.
You need the adverts to keep running.
Hang in there.
Let's make up for the lost time.
You have a slow start,
so you can only catch up
with others after 50 m.
That's why 200 m
is the best distance for you.
Because you'll have time to catch up.
But there's another problem, your balance.
There are bends in the 200 m track.
You must begin practicing starting
on the outer track.
Run towards this line
and it'll turn into a straight track.
Even if it takes longer,
it lessens the curve of the bend.
-Our beverages have four new flavors.
-Take one and try it.
One, two.
Again.
Your slow start is your biggest weakness.
Since you wear a hearing aid,
you have a slow reaction.
You're the last to hear the shot.
One, two.
One, two, three, smile.
To get a better result,
we must focus on training how you start.
Are you So Wa Wai?
-I am.
-Gosh! You're so handsome!
You're so cute!
My fingers are too weak.
Train until you can.
You weren't a celebrity
before this either.
We must try new ways for you to catch up.
I will train your fingers too.
It's fine even if you can just be
0.1 seconds faster.
Again.
Higher, over here by my hand.
Can you see it?
Lower, take strides.
Can you do it higher? Over here.
Hurry up.
-Lower.
-Higher, over here.
Lower. Get up!
-Faster!
-Higher!
-Again!
-Faster!
Lower!
Higher!
Here.
Get up. Carry on.
I can't, I have to run.
Just shut up and do it.
Can we train now?
Do you want to fail the qualifiers?
Fine.
He's coming.
Go and train first.
Mrs. So.
Victor, I said no more advertisements.
Wa Wai's time is even worse
than when he was in Atlanta.
He has to train hard now.
I negotiated these contracts
for you this week.
Take a look at this first.
We won't do them.
Look at the price first.
What are you still thinking about?
It's the most profitable time
for Wa Wai now.
Has he ever thought about
what he would do after retiring?
In Hong Kong,
after a normal athlete retires,
it would be hard to support himself,
let alone someone like Wa Wai.
Make him more money.
That's how you can really help as his mom.
There's a saying
that really suits athletes.
"Fame is fickle food."
It never lasts.
How can a champion
stink like a tramp?
Cut!
Very good. For this part…
It's going smoothly, isn't it?
I'm so sorry.
He got held up a little from training.
Five hours is a little?
Will you pay for our overtime?
Is he late for his races too?
I know,
but I need a rest too.
What's the matter? What's wrong?
The director…
He said…
He said that I spoke too well,
it doesn't sound like me.
He told me to stutter on purpose,
to sound like a spastic person.
I want to know what's the rationale.
Just listen to the director.
Do as the director says.
Try to stutter.
-Don't speak too well and act stupid.
-He…
Speaking smoothly
isn't what you do, right?
Go and finish the shoot.
Come back.
Try again.
Use more force in your fingers.
Come back.
One more.
Hey!
What are you doing?
I want to run, not practice this thing!
Fine, forget it!
Forget it!
I'm trying to help!
But you just want it your way!
Are you going to keep wasting time?
I only know that my way
is to look forward,
not stare at this thing!
Yes, I know that I start slow.
But that's why I kept catching up
and charging forward.
It's just like my life.
I must catch up from behind!
Wa Wai.
The television interview Victor arranged
has been changed to tomorrow.
I have to train tomorrow.
Okay. I'll apply for leave
at the Sports Institute.
Apply for leave?
I don't have time anymore!
Okay.
I'll ask Victor to reschedule then.
You said I only need to do it once.
Why are there more and more?
You'll be done after these few.
Hang in there.
Mom, I just want to run.
Wa Wai.
You can't run all your life.
After filming these ads,
you'll get a few hundred thousand.
Just run a bit less.
Run a bit less?
If I ran one lap less when I was little,
you would say that it won't do!
Now, everything is fine with you.
The key is with me.
Let's watch the replay.
Okay, watch the replay.
-Sir, can I borrow an outlet
-We're done here.
to charge my phone?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
This shot is okay. Prepare the next scene.
-All right.
-This shot is okay, switch scenes.
What happened? Did you find Wa Wai?
My phone is out of battery.
The next scene is his.
Yes, okay.
-Mrs. So.
-Yes?
Talk to him.
If he doesn't come today,
they'll sue me.
You'll need to pay them too.
-Done.
-Okay.
Perhaps the traffic is bad.
When my phone gets charged,
I can find him.
You must find him.
Hurry. Help me out.
Fifty-eight times.
What 58 times?
Your mom called you 58 times.
Mrs. So is worried about you
and wants you to earn more money.
Or you can tell Victor
that I can stand in for you.
That's right.
There was once when he wanted me
to make a starting pose.
Then he told me to turn my head up.
Hang on, how could I turn?
-Also--
-Wa Wai!
Did I buy a phone for you
to listen to songs?
-Go, come on.
-Why didn't you pick up?
Don't run away!
We waited eight hours for you!
-Mrs. So--
-We have to compensate them back!
-Mrs. So, have some water first.
-Help me talk to him!
If he's not listening to you,
why would he listen to me?
He'll listen to his girlfriend.
Hey! Mind what you say!
You've liked her for so many years,
but you don't dare to tell her.
I'll tell her if you won't.
He has always treated you
as his girlfriend.
You've never had a boyfriend
in over a decade.
He's a good man,
why don't you consider him?
Mrs. So.
Wa Wai isn't the man of my dreams.
There are things
that I want to bury in my heart
and keep to myself.
Why must you dig it out?
I wanted to help you.
You don't want to help me.
You want to control me.
I want to help you find someone
to cut your toenails.
I don't need anyone to cut my toenails.
I'll cut them myself!
You'll do it yourself? Fine, do it.
Cut them now. Show me!
You won so many gold medals
in the past ten years.
I told myself that my son is a genius.
My son is an extraordinary person.
But after this Paralympics,
can you still race?
Soon, nobody will remember
who So Wa Wai is.
After your dad and I are gone,
who will take care of you?
You'll end up getting subsidies
from the government.
I can go back to being a courier.
Your friend helped you out with that one.
Otherwise, who would hire you?
If I were him,
I would prefer a normal person.
You never treated me like a normal person.
Since I was little, you've treated me
like a handicapped person.
You had my brother
because I'm handicapped.
You let me run when I was little
You also accepted so many advertisements
because I'm handicapped.
Wa Wai, I know
that it's hard to be handicapped.
But being the mom
of a handicapped person is hard too.
Since the day you were born,
everyone blamed me.
When I sent you for training,
your dad asked me why I'm forcing you
to run in the Paralympics.
When you were little and couldn't walk,
I forced you to walk.
Everyone pointed their fingers at me
and scolded me,
"Your son is crying,
and you're still forcing him.
Don't you have a heart?"
Wa Wai,
no one blames you for being handicapped.
Everyone would only blame me.
Wa Wai couldn't even walk
when he was little.
Who would've thought
that he would be a world champion?
If you're willing to believe,
everything is possible.
A slow starter can be a winner too.
-I believe.
Seon Bon Insurance.
I bought some wine.
Coach Fong.
Bring it to Beijing and enjoy it slowly.
You can just give it to me
at the airport tomorrow.
I'm not going there tomorrow.
What's the matter?
Please take care of him for me.
Wa Wai is all grown up.
He doesn't need me to take care of him.
Running on a track is simple.
Forward is the only way to go,
so you're never lost.
But it's different in life.
I think you're the one Wa Wai
needs the most now.
Coach Fong.
Do you believe that Wa Wai isn't ordinary?
I believe in him.
If he says he can,
he can.
Front-runner So Wa Wai
from Hong Kong had a disappointing race,
coming in third with 12.38 seconds.
The men's 400 m in T36 classification
is about to begin.
All athletes have arrived
at the starting line.
The crowd favorite, So Wa Wai,
had a lackluster performance
in the 100 m race,
only coming in third.
Let's see if he can perform better today.
The race begins,
everyone started very well.
At lane four is
the assertive Zheng Hai Feng from China.
He already overtook Ukraine's Viktor Buka
at the first 100 m bend.
Russia is close behind him,
while Hong Kong's So Wa Wai has been
lagging behind in the first 200 m.
I wonder if he can catch up in the end.
In the last 100 m,
Zheng Hai Feng is winning by a mile.
His time is 54.14 seconds.
Ukraine takes the silver,
and Russia gets the bronze.
So Wa Wai finished in sixth place.
I believe that he's surprised
with his abysmal performance himself.
As I told you,
the plastic bag doesn't work.
Instead of crying hard, run hard.
Don't worry,
it will be fine when I'm done.
Don't be scared.
You'll lose half the battle
if you're scared.
I didn't just lose half the battle.
I already lost two races.
Exactly.
What's left to fear then?
-Mom.
-Yes?
Do you know
why Ming runs faster than a train?
It's because…
He has a Wonder Mom.
Save it.
It's the Wonder Boy
who made her the Wonder Mom.
Wa Wai.
You walk slower than others,
but you run faster than them.
Eyes on your mom.
-Eyes on your mom.
-Eyes on your mom!
It's time, Wonder Boy.
Time to shine.
Wa Wai.
Do you know when you look the coolest?
When?
-Wa Wai!
SO WA WAI, LANE 7
When you start running,
imagine me watching you
at the finish line.
Walk!
Wa Wai.
You walk slower than others,
but you run faster than them.
I want to run faster.
I'll run with you from now on.
Eyes on your mom.
Faster!
I know I can do it.
Believe me, you'll like it.
I'm going to get lots and lots
of gold medals for you.
He's amazing!
Wa Wai won, Grandpa. Cheers!
Wa Wai!
You won! Wa Wai, you're incredible!
AT THE 2008 BEIJING PARALYMPICS
200 M T36 FINALS,
SO WA WAI BROKE HIS OWN
WORLD RECORD AT 24.65 SECONDS.
HE'S STILL THE CURRENT PARALYMPIC
RECORD HOLDER IN THIS CATEGORY.