Q, are you awake?
MY SECRET LOVE
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Nothing, brother.
Why don't you take them off?
Do I need to?
Yeah.
Quickly!
Wait, wait!
What are you doing?
You said I need to take them off?
Not that.
I mean, the shoes!
You'd take the shoes off
when you come into other people's house!
Do it. Quickly!
So cute.
Stop watching BL series.
And eat quick!
Otherwise, you'd go to school late.
Brother Kim, I can't not watching it.
It's #1 on-trend BL series daily.
I can't miss the trend!
Aren't you afraid of missing your school bus?
It's the first day of this semester.
Don't act like you know the way to school like a pro.
Spare some time.
Before we moved here, I have planned all my routes.
Everything will be perfect. I won't be in school late.
Don't let me find out later that you're late!
Otherwise, I'm gonna phone mum overseas!
The one who'd be late now is you!
Look at the time. What time is it now?
You said you're gonna go early.
Why don't you go already?
How do I look?
Good. Just go.
If you don't want to clean the dishes, just put them there.
I'll clean them later.
Sure.
Also, don't forget to lock the door.
Noted.
Just hurry.
Alright.
Just don't come home too early.
[WHEN EARTH SHAKES AND BRINGS THEM TOGETHER]
Hello. My name is Kimhan Thirathana.
I'm a sophomore at Faculty of Liberal Arts.
But people knew me as Kim the student club president.
It is the position I'm mostly proud of.
This is one of the goals that I've planned for.
Someone like me cannot live my life without a plan.
What's up?
What are you doing?
For someone like him,
he's working for the club, of course.
This is just first day and you already work so hard?
I work hard everyday, don't I?
Whoa!
Be serious you guys.
We have Say No SOTUS project to present today.
Are you two ready?
I already did the presentation for you.
I ensure you the chancellor must be very pleased.
Great job, Lee!
Bomb.
Bomb!
What?
Are you ready?
You watch Thunderous Sky again?
It's fun.
Don't tell me you also watch it?
No.
Is it weather forecast channel?
Kim! How come you didn't know Thunderous Sky channel?
Come here. I'll bring you to hailstone fandom.
Thunderous Sky that I'm about to tell you..
is a channel with good content.
They'd hide camera and prank people creatively.
It's led by Mek, no.1 founder of the channel.
His charm is at the top that
people don't mind being pranked by him.
Next is Park.
An editor whose personality is gentle and quiet.
But his editing skill is the best.
The last one is..
Bare. My bias.
He's playful and friendly.
He always keeps cool but a bit clumsy and very cute.
So, now you can choose your bias?
Nah. I'll pass.
Me too.
Pranking people is good content?
What's your good content then?
Like..
I gotta go.
Who is that?
They scream so loud I thought
they're running away from zombie.
Don't you guys know Brother Tim?
No.
If I have to compare..
The Thunderous Sky channel that Bomb likes
is hell!
And Absolute Tim channel by Brother Tim which..
gather all the men's grooming content
is heaven.
He's so handsome and so cool.
He's also rich and neat.
Why is he so perfect?
You know a lot about him.
So you like someone handsome and cool like him?
Better than your Thunderous Sky channel!
Enough you two.
Pack your things and let's go.
We might be late for the presentation.
Bomb, take this.
This is yours?
Yeah.
It is so interesting.
I think this job fits perfectly with Tim.
Please send the details to me via e-mail.
And I'll be in touch. Thank you.
We have new job, Tim.
We have a lot of clients lately?
We have some but don't worry.
I can handle it for you.
Wow, you're good, Mr. manager.
You dare saying that.
You're the one who forces me to do it.
No one knows me well like you.
Perhaps. Who'd have known you're so clumsy.
Right?
This year, our student club has a project to propose.
That is..
Say No SOTUS project.
We must say no to cruel activities for first-year students.
And let people know negative impact of those activities.
Here are the ideas from me and my team.
Actually, SOTUS is an activity to break the ice..
Brilliant! Very brilliant!
I never thought that your idea and my idea will connect.
A round of applause for Kimhan!
This project is in line with this year's policy.
Let's say this together.
Elevate ideas, conquer young gens, be conscious about technologies!
Say it louder this time.
Bravo!
Kimhan.
I think if you continue to do great like this,
your recommendation letter'd be brilliant!
You take that to any big company, you'll receive a warm welcome!
Another round of applause for Kimhan.
Bravo!!
I knew the chancellor'd like it.
You're worried too much.
You knew he didn't want to fail.
You can say anything now.
I'm in a very good mood.
Alright.
We have class, right? Let's go. We'll be late.
You go first. I have things to do at registration room.
You're a lot of work.
Just hurry.
Later. Later.
Let's go.
Hello, friends and hailstone fandom.
You're now with Thunderous Sky.
I'm sure you're gonna love me like a bang!
We're now in a common classroom to make some great content!
Let's see how it goes!
Park, can you wait here and watch out for us?
Okay.
What's that smell?
So stink!
Everybody! Please calm down!
Who's the one who farted?
This guy! This guy!
Who did it!?
So stink!
So cool! The smell was so bad!
I'm still feeling goosebumps.
I think our audiences would love it.
We should gather thousands of views!
I was outside and still smell it.
Should we add more sound effect?
Or should we cut some not-so-good scenes out?
Was it too much?
I think I lost my wallet.
Wallet?
You forgot it in the classroom?
Yeah.
Are you searching for this?
Do I still smell bad?
The smell hits me once you walk in.
I met some guys pranking me like young kids.
If you do BL content, I might watch it.
Are you searching for this?
Yes!
Thank you so much, brother!
Are you trying to piss me off!?
Do you have any problem?
You can tell me.
I should ask you what's your problem?
Do you think it's funny pranking people?
Ouch! I was wondering where did bad smell come from?
It's coming from you!
Did you realize you're going to be famous?
When I edit, I'll make it as funny as I can.
I'll tell professor.
Why are you saying this? You have evidence?
Evidence? When you post your clip, we'll see.
Wait, you know my channel?
Actually, you are member of the hailstone fandom!
Hailstone my ass!
It's the name of their fandom.
Being my fan club, you don't have to be shy.
Shy my ass!
Your channel name is awful.
And the content you produce is rubbish!
Hey, what did you say, you pale face?
what did you just say!? You..
Come! Come!
Come and I'll tell professor that you invade my privacy.
And also being violent.
Enough!
Just calm down.
If you want this to end, just apologize to me.
And erase the clip too.
I think we haven't done anything that wrong.
Instead of an apology, can we do a selfie?
I can give a selfie for you only.
Which phone should we use?
Your phone or my phone?
You can use mine.
Okay, sure. Let's do it.
Perfect!
Come, come! Let's stand close.
Get off me!
Kim, let's go.
Brother, I apologize.
Mek, Bare, enough already!
Good chance like this comes only once, brother!
Mek, Bare! You two please calm down.
Please beware that small thing like this can go big.
But he said our channel is awful!?
You're okay with that?
Yeah, Park. Why did you tolerate it?
This guy can really tell professor.
I think it's best not to post this clip.
What about our fans? What are they going to watch?
What if he really tells professor?
Can you handle that?
Just erase it.
Okay, okay.
I won't post it.
What?
I take it as a farsighted thing to do.
You two shouldn't forget that..
We are in our senior year.
If you can compromise on things, just do it.
Otherwise, we're all screwed.
You complain like an old dude.
Alright, let's go.
You acted like a child.
I hate all those Thunderous Sky guys!
Why did it have to be me who's been pranked?
What did your friends do to my friend?
Are you gonna tell me!?
Ouch, ouch!
I'm sooo sorry.
If I knew he's your friend, I'd stop them.
Usually, he has a lot on his mind.
But you still annoy him.
You know that Mek and Bare
always carelessly prank people.
You pranked Kim, you should beware.
If anything bad happens, I'll say you deserve it!
I'm already tired with work at the club
now I have to be annoyed with you guys.
You're tired?
If you're tired, just sit still.
Be relaxed. Be chilled.
I'll drive as smooth as the bed in our room.
Enough!
Stop pampering me!
Just go back to our place, I'm hungry.
Yes, sir.
Alright, darling.
Stop! Have you fallen into the toilet?
Do I still smell bad?
The smell hit me once you came in.
What did you do to smell this bad?
there was some guy pranking me.
he pranked people like kids that didn't want to grow up.
And he called me pale face too!
Pale face? haha.
Now I want to know who was that person?
If this happens in BL series,
You will meet him again.
After that, you fall for each other.
Next step is..
Okay, stop!
Don't be so imaginative.
I'll pray to god not to meet him again!
Okay, okay, okay, it's up to you.
But now, just go take a bath and change clothes.
I can't stand it anymore.
Just hurry!
You think our neighbor is okay?
They screamed so loud.
Since they moved here, this is the first time I heard them.
Hey, why don't you watch my channel?
Please help increase more viewership.
No. I don't like it.
Why!? I want to know.
It's non-sense. Lots of cliche and boring stuff.
You only do the same joke.
One more thing. There's not many thing to watch.
If not for you, brother, who did it, I'd..
Stop!
Thank you for telling me.
But this is your own brother.
Ever been interested in doing sort of BL content?
It's very popular.
Lots of people are fan clubs.
Perhaps it might be even better than
those rubbish things you're doing.
I won't do it!
No matter what happens, I won't do it!
Bare, Park and I are so committed to this channel.
It becomes part of our lives.
I won't do it just to gain more fame.
Who knows.
At first, you liked gardening.
You even wanted to study landscape.
But now, you study communication arts
being content creator.
Anything can happen.
You're so genius!
Especially with other people's business.
Just eat quickly and I'll take garbage out.
What if Kimhan disappoint chancellor?
If something like that happens..
Do you think what I think, B2?
If you want to be part of our faculty, just sit up 100 times. Do it!
Please join Say No SOTUS project with us!
Please join together.
Bomb, do you still have a lot?
I don't have much left.
People seemed excited and interested in our project.
Our student club this year is the best.
Certainly, my friend.
Where's Lee?
He told me he had things to do.
And I didn't ask him what was it.
After we're done here,
I think I'm gonna go checking on each faculty.
You think it's okay?
I think it's good idea. So, we'll know..
if our project works or not.
Okay, I'll do it fast.
Then, I can go eat.
This morning, I woke up so early.
But the traffic was so bad.
Why don't you spare some time?
You already know traffic is bad.
What did you do with your time?
I watched..Thunderous Sky channel.
Bomb!
Just take this and please take care of it.
I'll just go.
See you later.
Okay, okay.
See you in the evening.
I'll find someone else to help.
Sister, could you help?
Thank you.
Please join Say No SOTUS project with us!
Please join Say No SOTUS project.
Here. Please join our Say No SOTUS project.
Please join our Say No SOTUS project.
What is this?
It's a project we campaign against cruel activities with first-year students.
The project is called Say No SOTUS.
This project is cool.
Who came up with it?
It's Kimhan's idea. He's this year's student club president.
That one!
That guy is student club president?
Yes. He's the chancellor's favorite too.
Well..
What if Kimhan disappoints chancellor?
No way! Kimhan is always cautious.
But if something like that happens..
I just don't want to say it.
Chancellor's reputation is at stake too.
I'll just go. Don't forget to have a look on Say No SOTUS project.
Do you think what I think, B2?
I think the same, B1!
What are you guys thinking?
It's gonna hurt, you fart bag.
Hahaha.
Faculty of Engineering, no.
Faculty of Education, no.
Faculty of Arts, okay.
There's Comm Arts left?
Okay, let's go.
Thunderous Sky invites all hailstones to watch live!
And let's make fun content exclusively.
Meet at Comm Arts building at 2pm. See you!
Student club work can be done later.
Thunderous Sky first!
Hello, everybody!
I invite you all today to join and create content together.
It's a great moment we will have.
And now, we will have hidden camera.
Every word coming out of my mouth, you need to follow.
Understood?
Yes!
Understood!?
Yes! Yes!
If you're ready, and..action!
Get up. Stand up! Quick!
Stand in line! In line!
In line!
You want to be a part of the faculty?
Yes, we want!
If you want it, just squat up 100 times. Do it!
Do it fast!
Squat and up!
One, two, three.
Can you go on!?
Do it fast!
Fifty one. Fifty two. Fifty three. Fifty four.
Fifty five. Fifty six. Fifty seven. Fifty eight.
Are you still okay?
Oh crap!
My life as a fan is complete!
I'm able to make video with Brother Bare.
Even squat up 1,000 times, I can do it!
Let's do it together, brother!
A friend is fainted! Just go help him!
Stop!
This is....
a fake first-year activity from Thunderous Sky!
Thank you everyone for joining the fun.
Brother, can I take a selfie with you? / Sure!
You want this angle?
Thank you so much!
Me too! / Sure.
See you later, everybody.
No matter how cruel, I obey and let you prank me!
Bye, bye.
Brother, wake up!
Everyone goes out already.
Wow, the hailstones are so strong!
Brother, just wake up now.
Brother!
My viewership'd increase because you act so good like this!
Brother, wake up.
You expect to be nominated for an Oscar?
You two hired someone to be fainted here?
Is this too real?
I didn't hire anybody!
Bare, did you?
A joke like this is yours, right?
No, I didn't do it.
You said you're going to manage.
Brother. Brother. Brother.
Brother. Brother.
This is bad, you guys!
He's fainted for real!
Crap!
Brother. Brother. Wake up!
Brother. Brother.
Let's check up on him.
Here. Let's drink first.
You're feeling better now, right?
You want me to call your friend?
Why do you know his friend?
Yeah.
I just wanted to help. That's all.
You couldn't do it. Why didn't you tell us?
You didn't have to do it for us like that.
Yeah. I know your love for us is huge!
But you have to take care of yourself too.
Alright?
I don't have anything to give unless..
This! An inhalant.
Just take it and inhale into your lung!
Freshen yourself up.
This is not the time.
He's not in good condition.
I'm totally fine.
I'm okay now.
I haven't had breakfast this morning.
That's why I was fainted.
We're sorry.
Next time I'll invite you to do a video with us again.
Yes.
How about we go eat something together?
I'll pay!
Yes, I'd love to!
Just a moment.
Bomb, what happened?
Why don't you go to work?
A senior at work can't contact you.
Brother, I can't go with you.
Let's do it next time.
I have to go.
Hey, wait!
He looked familiar though.
My name is Dao.
I live next door.
Why did this incident happen, Kimhan?
How could you make Say No SOTUS project work?
At first, I thought it's going to die.
Suddenly, it's in full bloom.
And it looks young and new.
Hi! My name is Dao. I live next door.
My name is Q.
Nice to meet you, Q.
So glad to have people same age live next to each other.
I'd be a little less lonely.
If there's anything I can help, please tell me.
Yes. Thank you.
Okay. I gotta go. Bye.
Hey, wait!
I have a question.
Hey, guys. You wait here long?
Where did you go yesterday?
I didn't go anywhere.
I was checking the work in several faculties.
Then, I was off to work.
Also, my phone's battery was empty,
so I could't contact anyone.
What happened?
Bomb went off to other faculties and just gone.
And a senior at work called me.
You don't have to be serious with him.
He's just lazy!
What do you guys think I am?
A lazy ass, of course!
It's okay. You must be tired.
You can be lazy but don't waste your time
watching Thunderous Sky channel.
Water?
Are you okay now?
I'm okay.
How's the project?
We did great.
It's surely better than the chancellor has expected!
Chancellor just texted me.
Be prepared for her compliment.
I think this year, our student club..
will be remembered as the best student club in many years.
Let's see.
Are you brother Bare?
I'm actually your fan club. Can I have your autograph?
You guys! Do they really want my autograph?
Unbelievable!
Sign your autograph for them first.
So cute.
Guys!
The viewership for this clip..
already reaches hundreds of thousands.
No surprise we gather a lot of hailstone members.
But I was wondering..
If the student club would react to this.
This means the university becomes more famous because of us?
Yes, of course!
The chancellor doesn't need the student club
to gain good reputation for the university.
Announcement: Mr. Meka, Mr. Komkrit and Mr. Atikorn.
Senior students from Faculty of Communication Arts.
Please urgently join a meeting with the chancellor
at the student club's meeting room.
I think..they want to give us compliment!
Or..
Are we going to become university presenters?
I'm gonna ask my mom money for botox.
Where should I inject?
Let me see. Here and there and there.
I'll go with you, my friend.
You're trouble again!
Hello. I'm Sao Kanchiang. And this is Fame Hunger!
This program will recap all drama stories
of fame hungers out there.
If you want fame, I can give it to you!
And what we will talk about today is..
The story happening in a famed university.
Owner of Thunderous Sky channel just wanted more fame.
They decided to conduct a fake first-year activity.
But it caused real drama. There's a student being fainted for real.
What do you guys think?
Let's see some comments from social media.
It's 2022 now and you still did something like this?
Are you nuts!?
Since you're handsome, I don't mind being pranked!
The university should take some action.
You shouldn't let this happen.
We must wait and see if the university'd take any action
on such terrifying incident like this.
But if the university takes no action,
I can tell you right now that the university'd be damned!
We're damned! Damned! Damned!
Why did this incident happen, Kimhan?
And how could you make Say No SOTUS project work?
I have a bad feeling about this.
You too! You're nearly done with your senior year.
Why are you still pranking people like kids?
Don't you see..
how people on social media talk about us?
But they said we're very funny.
They also said we're handsome.
Yes, yes!
I know..that you are handsome.
But what you did..
Not only harmful to his heart.
It can possibly threaten his life!
Have you any idea about that?
If he's not just fainted.
If there's something more, who would be responsible for it?
Can you all handle that?
It's already 2022.
Why are you still using violence!?
Why!?
They deserve a punishment, right?
Suspended
or expelled.
Your bad mouth should be slapped!
Thunderous Sky go!
Stop!
Seeing this, I feel extremely hurtful.
So is it going to work, your Say No SOTUS project?
Since you all continue to fight like this.
I have consulted with the committee.
You three will be suspended!
But don't worry.
I also find you a solution.
In a way that modern chancellor would do!
Since you are content creator,
You must do a music video for Say No SOTUS
to publish on university channel.
We don't get suspended now!
It's so easy! You don't have to worry.
We're experts in what we do.
But this project is Kimhan's.
Kimhan and friends,
you must help Thunderous Sky team create this MV.
What!?
Why not?
It's for the sake of unity between you all.
This is the only way out
if you want to graduate.
And if you still want to be student club president.
I know this might not be a good time to say this but..
I want to say it anyway.
Because it sounds so grand!
Allez Cuisine!!
Let's get started!
Urghhhhhh!
What's wrong!? You gave me a fright!
What's wrong? What happened to you?
You looked so upset the past two days.
It's about the university project.
It seemed great at first.
And then there's this annoying guy messing it up.
Just calm down, brother.
I'm sure everything will turn out great in the end.
But now, you need to be back in the good mood, okay?
How about..you cook some food?
Perhaps it calms you down.
I'm actually hungry too.
Hungry
What do you want to eat?
Truly, whatever you cook, I can eat.
Because it's all delicious!
Have you done something wrong?
Nothing at all! Just cook.
You have something suspicious.
I just wanted you to be in a good mood.
Hurry!
Just talk slowly. Chewing first.
Brother Kim, you're the best.
Now I feel better.
Oh, the plant that looks like dying in front of the house.
Now it's in full bloom.
From what I remember, it really looks like it's about to die?
Yeah. And I was surprised too.
So I asked and found out that a guy next door
has been taking care of it until it blooms.
What fertilizer did he use?
I don't know but it's interesting to know.
I'll ask again.
Perhaps I'll bring some food
to say thank you to him.
Since he's taking care of our plants.
It's done now!
Dao Salon guaranteed!
Can I trust this?
How long should I do this?
Two days perhaps. Since your face is too thick.
Why does everyone being sharp-tongued today?
Who taught you to say such a thing?
Someone nearby obviously.
Why aren't you born first and be my big sister then!?
I heard that!
Mek, can you open the door?
Who'd come at this hour?
Brother, thank you for taking care of my plants.
I want to share my food with you.
You fart bag!
What the heck!?
I'll go first. / I came here first!
Are we going to survive all this?
One, two and three!
You don't have to be in the center.
If you perform well, you'll have a lot of air time.
I actually don't want to help that much.
But I'm afraid you might not get better
on time for the MV production.
And I'd be screwed too!
Just rehearse well.
Because as you stand still, it already look funny!
When this is all done, I hope not to see you again!
I also don't want to work with someone like you!
Do you realize what you have done?